<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-5000</phone><name>Charles Hotel </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>744847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;***** You may call the Charles Hotel at (617) 661-5000 to confirm if the jazz is cancelled&lt;br /&gt;Read the last paragraph on this page to find out Plan B *****&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel and the Berklee College of Music have come together this summer to create a special Monday night series that is free and open to the public. Berklee students and teachers will perform from 5 until 7 in the Upper Courtyard area at the Charles Hotel. During the concerts, Henrietta’s Table will sell $10 burgers (beef or salmon) and $5 beer and wine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regattabarjazz.com/courtyard_series/" target="_blank"&gt;Courtyard Summer Series Schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Annette Philip Group is tonight's artist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTIST BIO: &lt;br /&gt;Annette Philip is an Indian vocalist, composer/arranger, recording artist, and choir conductor who thrives on experimenting with the human voice. In 2003, she cofounded Artistes Unlimited (AU) in New Delhi, a performing arts ensemble promoting collaboration among musicians in the city. With a vast, genre-spanning repertoire, AU is now India's largest and most diverse youth platform for musicians, with a rotating lineup of over 250 artists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Philip was the 2009 Berklee recipient of the Sylvia Zunz Memorial Scholarship, awarded for her commitment to learning and performing music from the Great American Songbook tradition. She is currently recording and performing with her own jazz fusion ensemble, the Annette Philip Quintet, as well as the Boston-based vocal group Women of the World and the Makanda Project big band. A recent Berklee graduate, Philip is also an established recording artist, lending her voice to albums, jingles, and voiceovers in nine languages. is tonight's artist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Less than five (5) minute walk from Harvard subway station on the Red Line and the last stop of the #1 and #66 buses on Mass Ave in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the jazz is cancelled the drinking, meeting and chatting will be held in Noir, the Charles Hotel's bar located in the lobby. You'll find me playing the card game solitaire.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the doorman at the hotel entrance to direct you to the Courtyard...find me seated nearest the stage area, playing solitaire.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282038978000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281441825000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks With Music at Charles Hotel Monday August 16th</name><id>14376729</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281992400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/14376729/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/7/global_16790871.jpeg</photo_url></item>