<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In Russian, a “dacha” is a small house outside of the city where family and friends can get together after the long winter months and enjoy the summer time while cooking together.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, our Dacha for this event is a private home near the Burlington Mall and just a few minutes from Rte. 3 North. The address and directions will be sent to RSVPs shortly before the event. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Olga will be preparing authentic Russian zakuska (appetizers) as well as a cold borscht and “Shuba” Salad –  a herring salad made with beets and potato. Iris will bring a main course dish, possibly a Georgian meat stew or pirozhki (meat pies). We will also enjoy some Russian dessert wine (yes, there's more to Russian drinks than vodka!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have your favorite Russian recipe that you want to try and share with everybody – great! Please let one of us know what it is to avoid duplication. We look forward to tasting your creations!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;(If you are NOT going to be bringing food, please bring a bottle of wine or be prepared to pay an additional $10 when you arrive.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SPECIAL NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Since this event is taking place at a private home, we'd prefer attendees who have previously come to another meetup with this group.  But we don't want to be turning people away, either. So, if you have not attended an event with the group yet, please email Iris or Olga before you RSVP and we will work it out.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be sent to "Yes" RSVPs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283393518000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279677602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at the Dacha -- join us for home-cooked Russian food!</name><id>14164714</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281218400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/14164714/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/f/1/global_16596753.jpeg</photo_url></item>