<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Braintree, MA</address_2><address_1>128 Town Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.203080</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>n/a</phone><name>Braintree High School</name><city>Braintree</city><id>172533</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.021370</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You need to be able to do some rallying to attend this event, as well as know the rules of tennis. Join players of most levels as we get together for some rallies and Tennis Games.  The game plan is to warm-up with some rallies and then break out into some games or singles, doubles and round robin play!  We are here to have fun, get to know each other and play Tennis!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School offers plenty of opportunity to play tennis on its 6 tennis courts and two practice backboards.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity to just show-up and play!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Day, Date &amp;amp; Time: Wednesdays @ 6:00pm till dusk&lt;br /&gt;*Location: Braintree High School&lt;br /&gt;*Meeting Place: At the Tennis Courts between the practice boards and door to the courts on the side of fields (not the street/parking side).  &lt;br /&gt;*Alternate Meeting Place: Look for us on one of the courts.  Courts are first-come-first-serve and we try to get courts next to each other.  We try to play on the courts by the backboards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Event Organizer(s): None.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Fees: Annual Members &amp;amp; Org Team - Free, Members and Guests - 2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Min/Max: 12.  We need at least 4 Yes RSVPs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Guests: 1 per member &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Case of Inclement Weather:&lt;br /&gt;If it is raining the event will be cancelled.  Heavy rains will cancel.  All Yes RSVPs will be emailed shortly after the RSVP Deadline with more info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Directions: Posted on the &amp;quot;Directions to Frequently Used Venues&amp;quot; Discussion Thread on the Message Board (Pinned, so they're on the first page.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting by the entrance to the Tennis Courts next to the two green practice boards near the basketball court and softball field.  If the courts are crowded look for us on one of the courts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chandra</member_name><member_id>4844140</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285196920000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281312224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weeknight Tennis!</name><id>dbtxnynmbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285192800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/14360469/</event_url></item>