<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color : #140202"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;A Vision for Progress: M2D2 Companies Move In&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt; When: September 22nd, 2011, 10:00 a.m. - 12:00 noon Where: Wannalancit Office and Technology Center, 600 Suffolk Street, Lowell, MA 01854 Website: 
&lt;a href="http://www.uml.edu/M2D2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.uml.edu/M2D2&lt;/a&gt; In May, the Massachusetts Medical Device Development Center (M2D2) opened their new medical device business incubator/accelerator. The new facility is open for business and features state of the art wet labs, private offices, and flexible cubicle space. Start-up companies and entrepreneurs can license from M2D2 the space needed to grow their medical device from idea to fruition. M2D2 is a joint initiative of the Lowell and Worcester UMass campuses aimed at helping new medical device entrepreneurs bridge the gap from invention to production! M2D2 can help your new medical device venture be a success! 
&lt;strong&gt;10 a.m. Ribbon Cutting Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt; Help dedicate UMass Lowell's new $4 million M2D2 (Massachusetts Medical Device Development Center) incubator, with UMass President Robert Caret, Chancellor Marty Meehan and other officials, 2nd Floor of Wannalancit 
&lt;strong&gt;11:30 a.m. M2D2 Inventor and&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Researcher Poster Session&lt;/strong&gt; See the new products medical device entrepreneurs are developing and the companies they are creating, 1st and 2nd Floors of Wannalancit</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316704554000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315359432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Vision for Progress: M2D2 Companies Move In</name><id>32536182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316700000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/32536182/</event_url></item>