<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We gathered for the Interfaith Book Club on February 24 with some new friends joining us in a lively discussion around the first three chapters of Jonathan Sack?s, The Dignity of Difference. We gathered as Reformed Jews, United Church of Christ and Catholics that evening, each in their unique faith journeys. If I could sense a common thread that interlaced our sharing around such issues as the moral outrage in an era of globalization, increased disparities and and sense of powerlessness in front of the enormous wrongs that plague our world, was where new possibilities begins in small things and new habits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In our common thirst for God, the redemptive Hand from the heavens that molds and moves us, we talked of a recognition that we are changing. The religion of our pasts is no longer enough. Our faith required more of us and some of us felt this quite acutely. Social justice was a way of talking of what is required of us all in helping to create a new world of hope and peace in the name of the God we love so dearly. Jew and Christian said this. Our dissatisfaction with what is bespoke of a restlessness that many of us felt, both within ourselves and our churches and synagogues. Some were more articulate about it than others, but underlying assumption in the sharing was that the power of our faith and religions still have the last say.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sacks says that the overriding belief that plagues our world up to the present is the notion that those who do not share my faith, race, or ideology, do not share my humanity. Much of what we discussed and shared was an attempt to debunk this belief.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a special blog dedicated to contemporary interfaith visual arts and poetry called &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/912/pages/www.sacredartpoet.wordpress.com"&gt;Sacred Bearings&lt;/a&gt;. For those who may be interested, feel free to comment on the postings. If you wish to post art and/or poetry, send them me. I will post them for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy and Fr. Joe Matteucig&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205870636000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203890708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club March Meeting</name><id>7399919</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205697600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/7399919/</event_url></item>