<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Franky G will be our illustrious guest speaker for February! For those of you not in the know, Franky G is a classically trained chef from the New England Culinary Institute and a certified holistic health coach from the Institute for Integrative Nutrition. His marriage of culinary artistry, flavourful ingredients, and medicinal herbs and spices are sure to take your taste buds and health to a whole new level! Check out his website at &lt;a href="http://www.frankgiglio.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.frankgigli...&lt;/a&gt;. (There are also a number of cool videos on his website where you can see him in action!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Franky G will be demonstrating his new lines of spice blends, Frank's Finest, and will preparing foods for us to sample!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a raw vegan dish to share and come in comfy clothes. Additional guests are welcome! Fresh local spring water, iced and hot herbal tea, dishes, cutlery, etc. will be provided. If you need directions, call or email me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! xoxo&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266963311000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawmaine</urlname><id>1161576</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Raw Maine: The Way Food Should Be!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266202783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Maine February Potluck: Spicin' It Up with Franky G!</name><id>12606051</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266789600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawmaine/events/12606051/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/d/global_7695373.jpeg</photo_url></item>