<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass, Framingham, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Framingham 15 AMC Theater</name><city>Framingham</city><id>597341</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390236</lon></venue><fee><label>donations welcome</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Iron Man it is! At 7:30 on Wednesday.&lt;/b&gt; It got 4 votes, so it's the winner. Prince Caspian got 2, so we'll be sure to hit that after it opens! (I'm thinking a weekend show for this, seeing as how several people have told me that weekend shows are better for them.) Please RSVP if you haven't already. If you want to buy tickets online ahead of time so we can be sure to get in (although Wednesday evening probably won't be a problem), &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/showtimes/showtimes.html?z=01702&amp;amp;r=sim#T1" target="_blank"&gt;go right ahead&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, anyone interested can head over with me to TGI Friday's to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you're coming, please RSVP with a yes.&lt;/b&gt; I'd like to know how many people will be there (and who). I'll also let the people who are going how I can be identified on Wednesday and where to find me at the theater. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Please take the poll so we can decide what we're going to see. If I don't get a majority on any movie, I'll just pick one and then all the members of the group can decide whether they'd like to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As far as buying tickets goes, I think we should probably each buy our own online when we decide what we're going to see and when. I was going to buy the bunch, but if someone RSVPs and then can't come, I'm kind of stuck with the extra ticket. If you aren't able to buy online (I think you have to be an AMC member -- but membership's free) and are sure you're going to show up, I can buy it for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring a friend if you'd like. Just note that in your RSVP, so I know how many total people to expect. My husband and a stepkid or two may show up at some of the outings. But this first one, I think I'll be flying solo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to take the poll!! (Iron Man's in the lead so far.) And fill out your profile questions if you haven't already so that we can get to know you better.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions at all. (dana@framesbydana.com)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, everyone! And see you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Well, I look a lot like my profile picture... :-) I'll update this field and send out an email to the ppl who RSVP when I can think of something that would identify me!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210639570000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>I'll bring name tags so we can get to know each other a bit. I'm thinking we'll head to TGI Fridays after the movie for some refreshments and discussion.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209782286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our first outing!</name><id>7862233</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210201200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/7862233/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>