<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon and Park St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357746</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MA Statehouse</name><city>Boston </city><id>1529618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063171</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;At noon this Friday, June 8, two Religious Right groups -- Pro-Life Action League and Citizens for a Pro-Life Society -- will host rallies in a number of cities nationwide (for other MA locations, visit &lt;a href="http://standupforreligiousfreedom.com/locations"&gt;http://standupforreligiousfreedom.com/locations&lt;/a&gt;). The events are misleadingly named "Stand Up For Religious Freedom" and are designed to push back against the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services decision on birth control coverage in the 2010 Affordable Care Act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Atheists will be on hand during the rally, to distribute flyers expressing our support for a strong wall of separation between church and state in America, and to show solidarity with any theists who agree that this principle is an essential part of our civic well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew, Mary and I will be the points of contact, and will meet any members -- or SOCAS supporters from any other local group -- across from the Statehouse at 11:30. They'll have fliers to hand out (see text below), as well as signs and sign-making materials. We'll be meeting there with members of the Massachusetts chapter of Americans United for the Separation of Church and State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it is perhaps unlikely that our presence will dissuade rally-participants from their belief that the HHS regulations are a threat to their religious liberty, we want nonetheless to make a strong showing. Especially since we do not want any media present to take away the idea that Bostonians are unconcerned with the separation of church and state. So: if you don't have work, or can take a long lunch, please make an effort to meet with our group on the Common, so you can be seen, and be heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have trouble finding the group, call Zachary Bos at 617-935-4951, and he'll connect you by phone to Andrew or Mary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* * * * *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FLYER TEXT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STAND UP FOR RELIGIOUS FREEDOM &lt;br /&gt;

 Protect The Rights Of Americans To Choose For Themselves&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Members of the Boston Atheists are participating in today's "Stand Up for Religious Freedom" rally on Boston Common, in order to show our support for the separation of church and state in America. This rally is to support the First Amendment and the restrictions placed on our government from using religious dogma as a basis for any U.S. law, including religious exemptions to the 2010 Affordable Care Act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The First Amendment is currently under attack by the hierarchy of the Catholic Church and other conservative religious groups that are seeking to redefine the concept of religious liberty to guarantee them religious privilege and freedom from accountability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Religious freedom does not include the right to interfere with the rights of others. Religious institutions have the right to participate in our society on the same basis as all other institutions. They do not have the right to dictate the rules in which they get to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To reinterpret the First Amendment to grant privileges and exemptions to large religious institutions would mean the depriving of the exercise of personal religious conscience by individuals who do not share the religious dogmas of those institutions but who nonetheless are employed by or use the services provided by those institutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this particular issue, granting religiously affiliated organizations a sweeping right to opt out of the contraceptive coverage rules would have two adverse social effects:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) The exemption would provide religious organizations with a competitive advantage over other non-religious service providers who would still be expected to cover the cost of contraceptive coverage to their employees; and &lt;br /&gt;

 2) All Americans who work for any of the religious institutions would be denied the ability to exercise their own religious and human right to make their own reproductive choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neither outcome is morally justifiable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over 98% of sexually active U.S. women, including those from the religious groups standing loudest against this requirement, use birth control at some point in their lives. The leaders of those churches are hypocritical in demanding that government enforce the doctrines that they themselves are unable to persuade their own parishioners to follow and unethical in demanding that they be allowed to impose their doctrines on others who do not agree with those doctrines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The contraceptive coverage required by the 2010 Affordable Care Act supports the right of all Americans to make their own reproductive decisions. It is reasonable to expect that taxpayer-funded institutions that serve the public follow the law in supporting the exercise of reproductive choice by their employees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We demand and expect that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Government enact policies ensuring that the contraceptive coverage required by the 2010 Affordable Care Act supports the religious and human rights of all Americans to make their own reproductive decisions; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Religious communities and leaders not be permitted to use taxpayer funds or government policy to further their dogma; &lt;br /&gt;

 - Religious privilege be kept out of our government and our laws.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call Zak at 617-935-4951 to be connected by phone to Andy or Mary</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Hall</member_name><member_id>14022569</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary Stanton</member_name><member_id>14527063</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339181752000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339010609000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Demonstration for Separation of Church and State</name><id>68034982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339169400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/68034982/</event_url></item>