<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, May 13th, 7 pm to 8:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Psychic and Psychological Perspectives on Faith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost is free with suggested $10 donation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Join Isabeau Esby and Dr. Joel Glenn Wixson, clinical psychologist, as they speak on the concepts and challenges of faith.&amp;nbsp; What is faith?&amp;nbsp; How delicate is the balance between science and faith?&amp;nbsp; And, why is it difficult sometimes to hold on to faith?&amp;nbsp; While Isabeau brings to the table an understanding that stems from spiritual experience and direct experience with higher dimensional spirits, Joel brings to the table a viewpoint of faith that was developed through the witnessing of countless, amazing life stories.&amp;nbsp; A question and answer session will follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Isabeau Esby, a internationally known psychic medium, resides in Portsmouth, New Hampshire.&amp;nbsp; She studied Mathematics from the University of Minnesota with minors in Biology and Teaching.&amp;nbsp; In addition to psychic readings, she works as a spiritual collector and volunteers her time working with patients who are being cared for by their families in their last days of life as well as helping people to understand their own psychic abilities.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Joel Glenn Wixson holds a doctorate in clinical psychology, a masters in substance abuse counseling and is a certified addiction specialist.&amp;nbsp; He is the co-founder of The Living Way, center for organic learning, has a private practice in Portsmouth, New Hampshire and is on the faculty of Leslie University&amp;rsquo;s Division of Counseling and Psychology.&amp;nbsp; He has presented and published numerous papers on various topics including substance dependance and narrative therapy.&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From the I-95, take exit 3 (95 northbound) or exit 3B (southbound) to Route 33 W.  The Center will be 2.6 miles on the right, at the corner of 33 and Bayside, in the Gowen's Corner Plaza.  The entrance is just to the left of Bayside Custon Frame &amp; Mi</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305417696000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>An intriguing blend of information from both the spiritual and the psychological perspectives.</why><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298171352000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic and Psychological Perspectives on Faith</name><id>16629999</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305327600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/16629999/</event_url></item>