<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.212359</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 749-7160</phone><name>Wompatuck State Park</name><city>Hingham</city><id>726971</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.859782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us to volunteer and help find a cure for pediatric brain tumors.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To volunteer RSVP yes on here and then go to &lt;a href="http://www.gearedupforkids.org" target="_blank"&gt;GEARED UP FOR KIDS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CHILDREN'S BRAIN TUMOR FACTS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, nine families across America will learn that their child has a brain or spinal cord tumor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brain tumors are the leading cause of solid tumor cancer death in children under the age of 20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because brain tumors are often located in the control center for thought, memory, sensation, emotion, vision and movement, their effects can be particularly devastating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brain tumors have no socio-economic boundaries and do not discriminate among gender or ethnicity. Brain tumors can strike anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, a survivor on the brink of adulthood will wonder if he or she will ever date, marry, be able to have children, hold a steady job, due to the long term effects of both the brain tumor and the treatments that were administered in order to help truncate the tumor's growth. &lt;br /&gt;THIS IS SIMPLY UNACCEPTABLE. WE MUST FIND A WAY TO CHANGE THIS OUTCOME FOR OUR CHILDREN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RESEARCH STATISTICS ON CHILDREN'S BRAIN TUMORS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently brain tumor research is under-funded and the public remains unaware of the magnitude of this disease.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Less than 3% of NIH/NCI's budget is targeted at childhood cancer research with a miniscule fraction of these funds being utilized for targeted children's brain tumor research.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only 2 new treatments for brain tumors have been approved in the past 25 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are over 126 different types of primary brain tumors, which complicates the development of effective treatments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cure rate for brain tumors is significantly lower than that for other types of childhood cancer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>6525575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247272452000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242963133000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer at "Geared Up For Kids"</name><id>10468532</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243774800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/10468532/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/d/global_5005469.jpeg</photo_url></item>