<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A looping hike of roughly 6 miles and roughly 4.5 hrs. at Hubbard Park in Meriden, CT. We'll stop at Merrimere Resevoir and follow the road to the back, ascend South Mountain to the cliffs, return to the back end of the reservoir, and back to the start. There will be many beautiful views of and on the various cliffs with water views aplenty. Some of the hike will be on a portion of the Metacomet Trail.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at the large parking lot on the east side of Mirror Lake (see map below) and we'll hike from there. Due to the distance and some up/down I would rate this hike high easy to moderate. You must bring a quart of water and trail appropriate shoes. A small backpack would be advised to carry water and maybe a snack so hands are free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate location/directions (Notch Rd., Meriden, CT): &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=95+Notch+Rd"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=95+Notch+Rd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Lat.=41.5499, Long.=-72.8321]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail map (1st page) &amp;amp; general information: &lt;a href="http://www.meridenlandtrust.com/Hubbard_quad.pdf"&gt;http://www.meridenlandtrust.com/Hubbard_quad.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about Hubbard Park: &lt;a href="http://www.cityofmeriden.org/CMS/default.asp?CMS_PageID=426"&gt;http://www.cityofmeriden.org/CMS/default.asp?CMS_PageID=426&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306800786000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306532577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Hubbard Park (via South Mtn.) in Meriden CT</name><id>19996541</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306677600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/19996541/</event_url></item>