<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Why use an Integrated Development Environment (IDE)?  How will an IDE improve your productivity?  What are some common features of popular IDE's?  Which IDE's are Cross-Platform compatible?  Which IDE's are Open Source?  Please join BostonPHP and Jesse Burns when he discusses his reasons to move from a simple text editor to a PHP/Web development IDE, and the process he went through to make that decision.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will focus on Cross-Platform Open Source IDE's covering some common features that most IDE's include such as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Text Highlighting&lt;br /&gt;    * Code Completion&lt;br /&gt;    * Code Folding&lt;br /&gt;    * Code Templates and&lt;br /&gt;    * Integrated Version Control Clients to name a few.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also discuss how IDE's can improve programmer and team development. Here is a list of some of the IDE's we will talk about:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Eclipse with the PDT package PHPEclipse&lt;br /&gt;    * Aptana&lt;br /&gt;    * Netbeans&lt;br /&gt;    * jEdit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Whether you are a hobbyist PHP developer, an independent contractor or you are member of a team of developers, there is a fit for you. There are many IDE's to choose from, but which fits your development cycle the best? After this presentation, you should have enough information to decide which IDE is the best fit for you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236813875000</updated><rating><average>2.1400001049</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228362473000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February User Group :: PHP IDE Bake-Off </name><id>9277617</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234395000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/9277617/</event_url></item>