<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Free Workshops for Jobseekers&lt;br /&gt;Are you looking for $$ Part time or Full time Work&lt;br /&gt;Come to the Alternative Jobs Fair, Saturday, July 17, 2010, 10 am – 1pm&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford Senior Center, 15 Starkel Rd. off Albany Ave., West Hartford&lt;br /&gt;Donation of a can of food requested for the West Hartford and Jewish Family Service food pantries&lt;br /&gt;10:30am   I’m on Online, Now What?! with Steve Porcaro&lt;br /&gt;Define your networking goals, Build your online profile, Add connections, Join and Create groups&lt;br /&gt;Give and receive recommendations, Get warm introductions, Create and list your own events  and more!&lt;br /&gt;11am  What is Network Marketing? with Kristie Oren&lt;br /&gt;What's important to you? Why now is a good time, What to look for when starting a business, Why Network Marketing is a viable solution, What is Network Marketing? Key factors for choosing a company&lt;br /&gt;11:30am   USING YOUR RESUME AS A BRANDING TOOL with Miriam Hyman&lt;br /&gt;Tips for developing a resume that creates a picture of who you are and what you can do for the employer.&lt;br /&gt;Noon Noon Your Appearance Can Affect Your Interview!  with Rosemarie LaBossiere&lt;br /&gt;12:30 pm New ways to earn $$ in today’s market? &lt;br /&gt;West Hartford Senior Center, (Bishops Corner). 15 Starkel Road, West Hartford, CT Off Albany St., next to Bishops Corner Library, Please call Nancy Frede 8605295579, nfrede@aol.com, &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy</member_name><member_id>4345102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279380444000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277859980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Workshops for Jobseekers - open to the public -- FREE</name><id>13954955</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279375200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/13954955/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>