<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 East Broadway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03038</zip><lat>42.882759</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Derry Public Library</name><city>Derry</city><id>1162219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.322777</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Your Bridge to Wealth is an educational series focusing on building wealth and creating multiple streams of income&lt;br /&gt;Our mission is to educate people about finances, multiple streams of income and weathering the current economic storm that we are currently facing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first meeting features Bernadette Trafton, Co-Founder and Owner of the Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association, MSI Radio (Multiple Streams of Income), WIRE (Women In Real Estate) Steps for Success Mentorship Program, BT Real Estate and SMJ Enterprises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bernadette Trafton is an entrepreneur.  &lt;b&gt;Now!&lt;/b&gt;  It wasn’t always that way.  Life chose that path for her.   She had a career in marketing, but, when her little boy was born, she wanted to be a stay at home mom.  She knew she had to help with the bills, so she made jam and baked goods and sold it at farmer’s markets.  She was doing ok, adding a couple thousand dollars to the budget every month. Wow, that’s a lot of jam.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, life happened, as it does to so many of us, and she became a single, stay at home mom, not receiving child support.  You can be sure, jam wasn’t cuttin’ it.   Every month she had to ask, &amp;quot;Pay the credit cards or feed the kids?&amp;quot;  This is no way for anyone to live and certainly no way for children to have to grow up.  Bernadette realized very quickly that the only way to weather this and any economic storm was to have income coming in from various different places.  It's now her mission to bring that message to as many people as possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the 20th, Bernadette will cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• The 3 biggest reasons why you need to create multiple streams of income&lt;br /&gt;• The cash flow quadrant&lt;br /&gt;• The different ways there are to make money&lt;br /&gt;• 7 Tips to a positive mindset&lt;br /&gt;• 5 Tips to help you Market yourself for Success&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is strictly educational and is &lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt; to the public to attend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264212807000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Health/Wealth Builders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>yourbridgetowealth</urlname><id>403924</id><group_lat>42.7999992371</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3000030518</group_lon><name>Your Bridge to health and wealth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263508033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your Bridge To Wealth</name><id>12322060</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264030200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/yourbridgetowealth/events/12322060/</event_url></item>