<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are interested in participating in this workshop you need to act fast - some of the classes are nearly full!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For the second straight year we have had a great turnout for the annual Winter Hiking &amp;amp; Backpacking Workshop offered by the AMC's Boston Chapter. This year's program filled quickly and some of you who were left out in the cold (sorry, couldn't resist) have been contacting me looking for an alternative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The AMC's NH Chapter runs a weekend-long program at Cardigan Lodge that covers hiking, snowshoeing, backpacking, backcountry skiing, and leadership. While I help instruct at the Boston Chapter's programs I have not done anything with the New Hampshire Chapter so I spoke&amp;nbsp;with Rick Silverberg, Director of the AMC New Hampshire Chapter's&amp;nbsp;annual Winter Workshop. After talking with him for quite a while I think he and his group have put together an excellent program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The same workshop is offered at two different times - January 20-22 or February 24-26. Each workshop has different classes - you pick the one you want and then spend a weekend filled with&amp;nbsp;instruction, field exercises, lectures, and discussions. They are also bringing a chef to prepare the meals (you will be put to work helping out though).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While you can use our event page to communicate with others from our group you will need to register directly with the NH Chapter. Before you register be sure to read about the workshop offerings described below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The workshops will begin promptly at 7:30 P.M. Friday evening and end Sunday afternoon at approximately 4:00 P.M. Cost is $135.00 (AMC members) or $155.00 (nonmembers) and includes lodging, excellent meals, materials, and instruction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Here is the registration information from their site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please apply via their on-line application to ensure the accuracy and priority of your application. You can access the on-line detailed information and application by clicking &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://amc_registration.ccntr.org/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. If this is the first time using their on-line registration form you will need to create an account first.&amp;nbsp;After you have completed your registration form you will need to send your payment to Rich Dasmaris at 17 Longwood Avenue in Londonderry, NH 03053.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Learn how to go out and explore the NH wilds this winter safely and with confidence. Once again this winter, the NH Chapter will sponsor two training workshops. They&amp;rsquo;re designed to teach you what you what you need to know for safe travel in the winter mountains; what to wear, what to take, how to use it, how to get there, how to get back, and how to plan for the unplanned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Both workshops will offer the same curriculum, except as noted below. All sections include extensive time outdoors. The first one, the NH Chapter Annual Winter Workshop # 1, will be held on January 20-22.&amp;nbsp; The second workshop, Workshop # 2, will be held on February 24-26. Both weekends of learning and fun run from Friday night until Sunday afternoon and are conducted at the Cardigan Lodge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Choose from one following classes.&amp;nbsp; If you are not sure which class is right for you, just give us a call and ask one of our Workshop Directors. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve found a class, just fill out an application and send it to us with your payment. Please indicate which workshop, #1 or #2, and which class, you want to attend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YOU NEED TO BRING YOUR OWN CLOTHING, GEAR, EQUIPMENT, AND SUPPLIES TO PARTICIPATE!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The classes offered at the workshops are as follows - pick one:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A. Introduction to Winter Wilderness Travel:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in general mountain safety, clothing, &amp;amp; equipment, nutrition, risk management &amp;amp; trip planning. Instruction includes an introduction to snowshoeing as well as map &amp;amp; compass. This workshop section is intended for individuals with limited experience in the New England outdoors who would like to start winter activities safely. Anticipate hiking as much as three miles at a slow pace with occasional uphill grades.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B.&amp;nbsp; Intermediate Snow Shoeing:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in snowshoeing, route finding (map &amp;amp; compass) as well as general mountain safety, clothing &amp;amp; equipment, nutrition, risk management &amp;amp; trip planning. This workshop section is intended for individuals with extensive 3-season experience in the New England outdoors, but limited winter experience, who would like to get into more winter activities safely. Anticipate hiking/snowshoeing up to five miles at a moderate / slow pace with sustained uphill grades.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C: Advanced Winter Wilderness Travel:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction is offered in winter travel on steep terrain &amp;amp; above tree line. Subjects covered include snowshoeing on mountain terrain, use of crampons, dressing for extreme weather conditions, off-trail navigation &amp;amp; risk management. This workshop section is intended for individuals with winter experience in the New England outdoors who are interested in climbing NE mountains safely. Anticipate hiking six or more miles at a moderate/fast pace with sustained steep uphill climbs &amp;amp; significant exposure to wind.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;This class does not include training in ice axe use.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D: Introduction To Backcountry Skiing:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in basic backcountry skiing techniques, including use of equipment, trail travel (safety and some map &amp;amp; compass), gliding, stopping &amp;amp; turning. Participants will spend about 3 to 4 hours at a time outside on skis. Trips will be on ungroomed backcountry trails, &amp;amp; vary in length from 2 to 4 miles. There won't be any great elevation gains, but rather frequent small ups &amp;amp; downs. Participants will be expected to ski with their day packs containing necessary items. This class will only be offered for Workshop # 1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E: Intermediate Backcountry Skiing:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in skiing technique, map &amp;amp; compass, general backcountry safety, clothing &amp;amp; equipment. Participants should be able to herringbone (to climb) &amp;amp; wedge to a stop, ready to learn wedge turns &amp;amp; possibly telemark turns. Trips will be 3 to 4 miles on fairly narrow, ungroomed backcountry trails with 500 feet elevation gain &amp;amp; loss. We will be outdoors 3 to 4 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;F: Advanced Backcountry Skiing:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in free-heel skiing techniques, with an emphasis on telemark turns, and necessary snow skills. Participants should be able to do wedge, step or basic tele turns. The majority of time will be spent outdoors with instruction on telemark turns, followed by 2 to 3 mile tours on backcountry trails. We will search for powder skiing in open trees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;G: Down Mountain Skiing:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Instruction in general backcountry safety, clothing and equipment, navigation, and trip planning. Review of ski techniques for radical backcountry terrain. Participants should be able to do wedge &amp;amp; parallel, or tele turns. We will tour 5 to 6 miles with an elevation gain of 2000 feet. Conditions encountered will include narrow trails, open tree skiing, bushwhacking, and some above-timberline windslab. This class will only be offered for Workshop # 2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;H: Leadership and Mountain Skills:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This section is for those who have mastered the basics of winter hiking. Exercises in planning, organizing, and expediting a trip with emphasis on leadership techniques and group dynamics. A review of the basics, accident scene management, medical considerations and off trail navigation. This section is also for people with potential and desire to become trip leaders for the NH Chapter Excursions Committee. NOTE: proficiency on snowshoes is a prerequisite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I: Introduction to Winter Backpacking:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;For those that have mastered the basics of 3-season backpacking skills. Instruction (will cover as many of these topics as possible) in general winter mountain safety, snowshoeing, equipment, proper camp site selection, how to erect a tent in winter, how &amp;amp; what to cook, trail finding, map &amp;amp; compass, off trail navigation, weather, trip planning, nutrition, emergency situations. Warning: All participants must have proper winter clothing, a winter sleeping bag that has a rating of 20&amp;deg; below zero or lower, a winter foam pad and a winter backpacking tent. Tents will be provided if needed. This group will participate in indoor lectures and evening programs, sleeping outside Fri. &amp;amp; Sat. night, prepare 1 meal outdoors. This class will only be offered for Workshop # 1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;J: Intermediate Winter Backpacking:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Same as Introduction to Winter Backpacking except this group will be spending more time outdoors. They will not participate in most lectures or evening program, will sleep outside both Fri. &amp;amp; Sat. night, prepare 2 meals outdoors. This class will only be offered for Workshop # 2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327281021000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322501436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC NH Chapter's Annual Winter Workshop (January 20-22)</name><id>drjzgcyqcbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327276800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/42625912/</event_url></item>