<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's always Springtime at The Butterfly Place! When you are ready for Spring and warm weather, and long to see colorful flowers with butterflies fluttering about, it's time for a visit to The Butterfly Place!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Place is an indoor living environment which has been carefully designed for the propagation and development of some of nature's most colorful living creations. This wonderful man-made habitat is contained within a 3,100 sq. ft. glass atrium building towering to a height of over 27 ft. at its peak. Within this atrium?s living butterfly environment can be found a variety of colorful plants and shrubs, each of which has been selected as a source of nectar for the butterflies. ( taken from their website)   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entry fee is $9.00.  Welcome Spring!   &lt;br /&gt;I believe there are coupon savings available through The Entertainment Book?   &lt;br /&gt;but am not sure of the amount  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: This is  truly a serene, peaceful and beautiful environment. Do you draw? Bring your sketchbook...Into photography? Excellent for photos! I have also posted  &lt;br /&gt;           this on other meetup group sites. After, we can head out for an early afternoon  &lt;br /&gt;           lunch or snack at an area restaurant. We can either decide that afternoon? Or,  &lt;br /&gt;           decide on it in advance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meetup @ the entrance</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207066056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Let's all welcome Spring!</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199636434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Springtime @ The Butterfly Place </name><id>7044664</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206892800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7044664/</event_url></item>