<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a hike that our single members might enjoy. Charlie's Active Singles hikes are for active single people in their 30's through 50's and average up to 200 people per event! These events have been found to be fun and well planned!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet-up is at 9:00 AM at location of the hike. Hikers are usually split up into 3 different hiking skill levels (something like advanced, novice, and social) and the difficulty of the hike corresponds. The hike starts at 9:30 AM and usually lasts about 2 hours. Afterwards, dinner facilities are arranged for refueling and socializing. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (a bit sketchy but best I have): &lt;br /&gt;* Take I84 West &amp;amp; get off Exit 10&lt;br /&gt;* End of ramp take right onto Church Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Church Hill Rd up hill to Intersection of Rt 25 ( Flagpole )&lt;br /&gt;* Turn left onto 25 (South) &amp;amp; continue on 25 till it turn into Highway&lt;br /&gt;* Get off Exit 9&lt;br /&gt;* Parking lot is across street at end of Ramp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* I84 East, take Exit 10&lt;br /&gt;* End of ramp take left onto Church Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow directions above&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Route 25 North&lt;br /&gt;* Take exit 9&lt;br /&gt;* End of ramp turn left onto Daniels Farm Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Cross over Highway &amp;amp; take 1st right onto Park St.&lt;br /&gt;* Parking lot on left&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Merrit Parkway take Exit 49N onto Rt 25&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Route 25 North&lt;br /&gt;* Follow directions above&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles is a 10 year old, non-profit Connecticut organization that brings together singles who enjoy participating in a variety of outdoor activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Charlie (organizer of Active Singles) 860-489-9611&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO Children or Dogs, Singles only (this doesn't mean you can't have a boyfriend or girlfriend). Wear Hiking Boots. Bring water. Optional Brunch follows each hike. Non hikers can join us at the restaurant. Call Charlie early to reserve a spot for Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540105000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1140449175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Active Singles Hike to Daniels Farm Rd in Monroe CT</name><id>4858560</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1142776800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4858560/</event_url></item>