<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A lovely looping Vereran's Day Fall hike on the Mattabesett Trail and Lone Pine Trail. This hike will have two options with a shorter 4.25 mile loop first for those who wish to have a shorter hike and the full 9.5 mile loop complete with clifftop views of Myerhuber Pond below. This portion of the Mattabesett is the most southerly section of the &amp;quot;U&amp;quot; shaped trail system with the Lone Pine Trail cutting accross to form the large loop. The eastern section of the greater loop is the smaller loop using Rte. 77 to return the shorter option hikers to their cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Weather forecast update 11/10/08: At hike start -sunny, 39 F. Around Noon to end of hike -sunny, 46 F high. Percipitation chance only 10% for the day (very unlikely).***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 9 AM at the Rte. 77 parking area for the Mattabesett Trail (on rte. 77, 4.6 miles south of Durham or 4.3 miles north of Rte. 80 in Guilford - see location below). This will be both our starting location and our ending location. We will be heading in a counter-clockwise dirction in the loop. We will hike 2.4 miles east to north-east on the Mattabesett Trail marked with blue blazes up onto the Boomstick Ledges. We will then turn west onto the Lone Pine Trail blazed with blue and a red dot for 1.1 miles until we intersect with Rte. 77. Those opting for the short hike will hike .75 mile south to the cars and their endpoint. The rest of the group will continue on the Lone Pine Trail for 3 miles west to north-west and up onto Totoket Mountain. This is a traprock mountain of altitude 720 ft. We rejoin the Mattabesett and hike 3 miles to the south-east, past Bluff Head and its associated cliffs overlooking Myerhuber Pond and the three preserves in the valley. We reach the endpoint back at the cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is anticipated that we start hiking at 9:15 AM (please arrive by 9 AM) and we reach the Rte. 77 turning point for the short loop hikers at about Noon. It should take the short option hikers only about another 20 min. to reach their cars hiking on the road .75 mile. The rest of the group will complete the hike no later than 4 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we should come in earlier than I estimated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Daypack -for gear, layers, and water/food&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - avoid cotton as it stays wet.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket -just in case&lt;br /&gt;* 1 qt water (short hike), 2 quarts water (long hike)&lt;br /&gt;* A lunch meal for on the trail. High energy meal should be planned. No cooking.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit (for blisters &amp;amp; such)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate/directions (fixed) location of the meetup location, Rte. 77 (Durham Rd.) in Guilford, CT via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Guilford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=4600+Durham+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions, use Google Maps (works for lat/long,  approx. GPS lat=41.409, long=-72.6959):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=41.409+-72.6959+(Hike+meetup%2Fparking+location)&amp;amp;sll=37.771274,-122.411749&amp;amp;sspn=0.008175,0.012295&amp;amp;g=41.409+-72.6959&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.409454,-72.695889&amp;amp;spn=0.007371,0.012295&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=addr" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the Rte. 77 parking area with my dark blue Grandcaravan Sport.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226773563000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226182514000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the Mattabesett Trail in Guilford and Madison, CT</name><id>9122447</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226412000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/9122447/</event_url></item>