<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;I'm a loner, Dottie... I'm a rebel...&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It should a lot of fun, with random people chosen to compete on stage who is the biggest fan of the movie. Who can answer the trivia questions? Who can do the best Big Shoe dance? It's fun watching people try to compete. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When&lt;/b&gt;: Friday, April 9th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;: Pee Wee's Big Adventure, presented by The Action Pack in SMELL-a-VIS-- no, no, wait, it's just a quote-along&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time&lt;/b&gt;: 11:59 am (Let's get in line at 11:20 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;: $10.00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Release Date: 8/9/1985. Damn, I feel old.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Coolidge Corner site:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/node/2620" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;PEEEEE WEEEEEEEEE!!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There is only one truth in this life: Pee-Wee's Big Adventure is the FUNNIEST MOVIE EVER MADE. If anyone tells you different, they're just trying to start trouble.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Watch the most entertaining man who has ever roamed the earth embark on a cross-country quest to reclaim his kidnapped best friend: a bicycle. Along the way, ol' P.W. will encounter tough-as-nails bikers, giant dinosaurs, wild animals, ninjas, chubby billionaires, escaped convicts, buckin' broncos, tone-deaf hobos, unwanted romance, fibbing gypsies, clumsy Godzillas, basement-less Alamos, vengeful boyfriends and even an undead trucker! Fun didn't exist until Pee-Wee invented it, and now the most funrocious, funtacular, fungorious funsplosion in the history of FUN will finally get its due as the most funeriffic Quote-Along ever! And you know we won't be able to start this show until we've done our very own Tequila dance competition...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costumes! Competitions! Prizes! Subtitles! It's the amazing Action Pack! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get together by 11:20 pm to get in line and hang out before the show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sharpen up your quoting skills:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0089791/quotes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/t...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Pee Wee's Big Adventure, according to Amazon.con:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Pee-Wees-Big-Adventure-Susan-Barnes/dp/B001CK1D44/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=dvd&amp;amp;qid=1269376584&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Former animator Tim Burton (Beetlejuice, Edward Scissorhands, Ed Wood, Batman, Mars Attacks!) made his feature directorial debut with this delightful comedy, coscripted by the late Phil Hartman (who also appears briefly as a reporter). Wisely, they keep the story simple so as to concentrate on the characters: Pee-wee's most prized possession, his shiny new bicycle, is stolen, and he sets off on an obsessive cross-country journey, determined to recover it. Pee-wee's awkward and childish attempts to be cool and mature (&amp;quot;I meant to do that!!&amp;quot;) are hysterical, as when he tells his girlfriend (Elizabeth Daly): &amp;quot;There's things about me you don't know, Dottie. Things you wouldn't understand. Things you couldn't understand. Things you shouldn't understand.... I'm a loner, Dottie. A rebel.&amp;quot; Look for Saturday Night Live vet Jan Hooks in a hilarious bit as a tour guide at the Alamo. And beware of Large Marge!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;According to Wikipedia:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pee-wee%27s_Big_Adventure" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Pee-wee's Big Adventure opened on August 9, 1985 in the United States in 829 theaters, accumulating $4,545,847 over its opening weekend. The film went on to gross $40,940,662 domestically, recouping five times of its $7 million budget, making it a financial success. At the time of release in 1985, the film received mostly positive reviews. Gene Siskel gave it a rare zero-star rating, and called it one of the worst films of 1985, but Pee-wee's Big Adventure developed into a cult film. Based on 34 reviews collected by Rotten Tomatoes, Pee-wee's Big Adventure received a 91% overall approval rating. By comparison Metacritic calculated an average score of 47 from 13 reviews collected. The film was nominated with a Young Artist Award for Best Family Motion Picture (Comedy or Musical).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Christopher Null gave positive feedback, calling it 'Burton's strangest film.' Variety compared Paul Reubens to Charlie Chaplin and Buster Keaton, while Empire called the film 'a one-comic masterpiece' and 'a dazzling debut' for Burton. Stephanie Zacharek of Salon explained 'Everything about Pee-wee's Big Adventure, from its toy-box colors to its superb, hyper-animated Danny Elfman score to the butch-waxed hairdo and wooden-puppet walk of its star and mastermind is pure pleasure.' Burton had no interest in directing Big Top Pee-wee,[20] and the financial success of the film prompted Warner Bros. to hire him to direct Batman.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271093808000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269376923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Action Pack: Pee Wee's Big Adventure Quote-Along @ Coolidge Corner</name><id>12971417</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270870200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12971417/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/9/global_13866921.jpeg</photo_url></item>