<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is Module #3, which follows from #1 and #2 already held.  This series will repeat starting in June.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested in learning about permaculture design but not sure if you can invest in a full-blown design course?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then the &lt;b&gt;Permaculture Design Seminar Series&lt;/b&gt; might be a good fit for you.  In a &lt;b&gt;small group&lt;/b&gt; setting (no more than 10-12 people) and at an &lt;b&gt;affordable price&lt;/b&gt;, work with local permaculture designer and organizer Lisa Fernandes on a real design project close to Portland.  We will meet for 3-hour sessions and you can enroll in one or more modules.  It is expected that the whole series will be about 3-4 modules long (depending on the property) stretching over several weeks.  Design and some implementation strategies will be covered.  &lt;i&gt;The series will repeat with a different project if there is enough interest. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The series is suited to those who are new to permaculture or are ready to apply some of their permaculture knowledge to a &amp;quot;live&amp;quot; project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Module #3:  Pattern Literacy, Water Strategies and Hands-on Project&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this module we will build on our work so far with our South Portland &amp;quot;client&amp;quot; as well as gain some additional insight into a primary inspiration for permaculture design:  patterns in nature.  Since we are helping to create an edible perennial ecosystem (aka &amp;quot;a garden&amp;quot;) then we will also examine a variety of ways to incorporate and work with water on this property.  We will either have hands-on experience with installing one aspect of the draft design we're creating OR we will turn our attention to Zone 0 (the house), depending on clients' readiness to proceed, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Module #4: May 28 &amp;quot;Bring it All Home&amp;quot; by developing an implementation plan for/with the clients and by understanding the elements of a comprehensive permaculture design report.  Hands-on project very likely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet from 5:30 to 8:30 with a short 15 min break part-way through.  We can either bring potluck food to share or chip in on something to share.  Beverages provided.  Bring your potluck kit either way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Payment Note:  I have turned on the Amazon payments tool that the meetup site offers because it is the only way to require payment as a condition of making a 'yes' RSVP.  This isn't my preferred method BUT in order to keep admin costs down and avoid having to manage checks/deposits/chasing non-payments &amp;amp; no-shows....well, you know.  If you are REALLY serious about attending this but cannot use plastic, please email me and we can make arrangements.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243164678000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241450381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Design Module #3: Pattern Literacy, Water Strategies + Hands-on Project</name><id>10333458</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242941400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10333458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/f/global_7822847.jpeg</photo_url></item>