<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2-day hike on the Appalachian Trail starting north of Dalton, MA and heading northbound over Mt. Greylock to North Adams, MA for a total of about 21.4 miles. We'll be spending the night at a Lean-to on the trail (there is a chance it could be full so plan accordingly). This hike is for experienced hikers who have done 10 mile hikes before as well as lightly equiped backpacking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet 6:45 AM at the small AT parking lot just north of Dalton, MA on Gulf Rd. (see below). The hike will start promptly at 7 AM. The first day's hike will cover 12.7 miles with first a 1,000 ft. altitude gain to get over North Mtn. and then a loss of 1,200 ft. into Cheshire, MA. we'll get into town at about 2 PM. We'll then hike up the flank of Saddle Ball Mtn. for an altitude gain of 1,800 ft. and overnight at the Mark Neopel Lean-to. We should be getting to the Lean-to before 8 PM to set up for the night. The Lean-to sleeps up to 10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the second day, we'll continue starting 7 AM at the latest on to the peak of Mt. Greylock (the tallest mountain in MA) with an altitude gain of 740 ft., for an elevation of 3,491 ft. We'll then hike down hitting Mt. Fitch and Mt. Williams with a total elevation loss of 2,590 ft. Overall we'll cover 8.7 miles this day and end at the parking area for the AT on Pattison Rd. (see below). We should end hiking by about 4 PM at the latest. After the hike, we'll hit any one of various places to eat in N. Adams. After that, we'll head back to the starting point to pick up vehicles via shuttle by my van.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we should come in earlier than I estimated. In Chesire, MA a determination will be made on timing to reach the Lean-to for the night or if any party members need to drop out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Full pack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks -3 pair&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold mornings &amp;amp; hot afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet. Heve a second day's clothing packed.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/rain jacket&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag -3 season advisable&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp -To see at night. LED versions best&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches&lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag &amp;amp; 15' minimum light weight rope&lt;br /&gt;* 2 quarts of water&lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (5 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too.&lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -If needed&lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils -If needed&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent&lt;br /&gt;* Backpack lantern&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* AT trail map -Massachusetts &amp;amp; Connecticut: Massachusetts Section 1, 2, &amp;amp; 3 (Map One) (VT line to Dalton, MA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT meetup starting point, north of Dalton, MA via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b2%2d28%5d%20Gulf%20Rd&amp;amp;city=Dalton&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01226&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=ZwuDGaRIb%2bhNQTDePwIoBvOffdJrnMiDogFD%2fYlROL7wHxsAqAERgxuhNyGakPBO4XrUT6SFTtiHdOBjyvXF821%2fuF%2fF5PDs52J8YwVMm5R16LM72HR6FQ%3d%3d&amp;amp;ambiguity=1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT ending point, on Pattison Rd. south of N. Adams, MA via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;addtohistory=&amp;amp;address=%5b358%2d377%5d%20Pattison%20Rd&amp;amp;city=North%20Adams&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;zipcode=01247&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;location=Sxi%2fKHL5zzE%2f%2fRyIsL8jsV%2fxDW4oKRel0g8IF0h%2fmssRpcBO7k4e5gT7o6TCZrtc5GDLAEk1%2frr1Qp2HnONk2UPySyQ2Lo%2f9BnLR8vBEiopmpbRx3z0f6hWvmecK1Xc9op4blqvwqaIg1lHLxIKbHZqxQPPXLRq4&amp;amp;ambiguity=1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180521801000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179857676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT North of Dalton MA to N. Adams MA</name><id>5806142</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180263600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5806142/</event_url></item>