<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>TONIGHT- NOT STARBUCKS!  Merry Christmas/Kwanzaa/Chanukkah/Yule/Mithras feast/Holidays&lt;br /&gt;7p onwards, casual supper at my place, in the South End.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by phone for directions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(In JAnuary, back to Starbucks)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Reece&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;MEET at STARBUCKS Coffee shop!!!  Bring a sign! You can print it from the FILES column on the left &lt;br /&gt;(sign printing directions below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group will meet across the street from the Boston Public Library, at STARBUCKS coffee shop, 755 Boylston St between Exeter St and Fairfield St. 617-450-0310&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have tables inside and outside, we will choose a table when we get there. The group sometimes sits at the large table on the left and sometimes pulls several small tables together on the right. Look for smiling faces! If you're first to arrive, please pick a table and look out for people looking for the group. Please be aware that people often arrive at very different times, so sometimes there are only one or two present at first. You may not see a large group right away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND EACH OTHER! Print a sign (or write one yourself &amp;quot;Meetup&amp;quot; and place it on the table in front of you where people can see it when they come in)&lt;br /&gt;To Print a red and white MEETUP sign, go to the left side of this page, do you see the blue boxes above my (old) photo? &lt;br /&gt;Click on the box marked FILES&lt;br /&gt;Click on ESOL Tabletop Sign&lt;br /&gt;Print the sign and bring it to put on the table in front of you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I agree it's a bit awkward having to ask people if they are there for the English Meetup group, but we have to find each other somehow! If you want to ask, it's good practice, if not, put a sign on your table and try to look friendly  :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a coffee shop, so refreshments are available to buy yourself if you want to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-If there is something you'd like to practice, please bring it, or suggest an activity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-If you arrive before 6:30 and don't see anyone else, please choose a table and welcome everyone as we arrive. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS&lt;br /&gt;We need more Organizers to help the group meet more often! &lt;br /&gt;Please email the organizer if you'd like to help or suggest a meeting. Thanks to those who have replied so far! Email me with dates and location you would like to meet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>call my cell if you need directions 781-820-4114</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>reece</member_name><member_id>1920240</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232154092000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>English Students &amp; Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>esl-76</urlname><id>55264</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston English as a Second Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227875397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tonight- Boston English as a Second Language December Meetup</name><id>9242018</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230249600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/esl-76/events/9242018/</event_url></item>