<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Whitney Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.173733</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-241-3300</phone><name>Elks Lodge #902</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>383630</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.650604</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Empire One Running Club (EORC) holds a fun run at the Ashley Reservoir in Holyoke every Thursday from October thru March. The run starts at 6 PM sharp, be there earlier if you want to stretch or warm up. Between 20-40 people usually show up. There is no charge. Usually everyone goes into the Elks afterwards to socialize. Once a month EORC buys pizza for everyone that shows. The course is flat, no cars, no dogs. Holyoke plows the path in the winter, but you can benefit from YakTraks when it is icy. There is plenty of parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting 10/24 a headlamp is recommended as it will be dark when we finish, after 11/4/12 it will be dark when we start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be no run on 11/22 (Thanksgiving).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great way to meet other runners. Not so many that you become anonymous, not so few that you feel like an outsider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter "250 Whitney Ave, Holyoke, Ma.", or the coordinates, "42.175,-72.6515" into the search box at maps.google.com to see a map of the area.There is a building (the Elks Club) with parking lots on either side. When you get there you will see a fire gate blocking the road just past the second lot, that is the entrance to the reservoir.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a crowd at the fire gate.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gene R</member_name><member_id>11009036</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359683687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Running-Hot</urlname><id>1551891</id><group_lat>42.2599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5199966431</group_lon><name>Running Hot</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345842078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun Run at Ashley, Every Thursday, October - March, 5:45PM, Headlamp Recommended</name><id>dzfphdyrcbpc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359672300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Running-Hot/events/97001222/</event_url></item>