<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;"First, there were twelve - a curious assortment of strangers summoned as weekend guests to a private location on the edge of Danvers. Their host, an eccentric game-player known to all of them, works frantically behind the scenes. All that the guests have in common is a wicked desire to play games - and a passion to outsmart the rest. For each has been marked as a detective, and in groups of four they must compete to solve the case first. As the only people at this event, unable to leave until the games are finished, they know that the only thing to do is jump right in and enjoy. And only the dead inside won't have fun."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;-Adapted from Agatha Christie's 
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;And Then There Were None&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mystery lovers and fans of crime and punishment, rather than steal the mystery dinner idea that Devon and others suggested, this event will be a "lite" version featuring traditional games with that theme. &amp;nbsp;For this evening, I would like to setup tables to play 3 different 4-player games and have people rotate between them (at least in the beginning so that everyone can try the games). &amp;nbsp;Of course, I can't just tell you what the games are, so instead here are clues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game #1 - a board game involving a most infamous murder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game #2 - a card game involving the brains of Scotland Yard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game #3 - a video game involving the grisly and unfathomable question of who ate father's figgy pudding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can you figure them out? &amp;nbsp;:-D &amp;nbsp;If you love exercising your wits, this event's for you. &amp;nbsp;Hope to see you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;. Anyone can sign up, but I would please ask that you&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;allow new or previously inactive members get a slot if they are on the waiting list since there is limited seating. &amp;nbsp;Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;See this&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food theme:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme for this event will be "dark". Please bring a food item to share with the group that is "dark". &amp;nbsp;Interpret that however you want, some examples could be dark chocolate, blackberries or blood oranges. &amp;nbsp;I will try to have also generic, healthy snacks on hand for all diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted at a private residence,&amp;nbsp;conveniently&amp;nbsp;located at the intersections of Route 1 and Route 95. &amp;nbsp;If you need directions, just ask. &amp;nbsp;This is a housing complex, so please do NOT park in any numbered spaces. &amp;nbsp;There are no animals on the premises. &amp;nbsp;Look for Unit 901 since Meetup doesn't display addresses correctly! :-(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unit 901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1312243987000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310001209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Mystery Night Lite</name><id>24835881</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312059600000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/24835881/</event_url></item>