<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Kingston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353490</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-2622 </phone><name>Good Life</name><city>Boston</city><id>669027</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Last week at least 35 of us made it to Whiskey's during the coldest day of the week.&lt;br /&gt;How many will show for what has been forecast as the warmest day of this week?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week Rebecca asked me when happy hours were outlawed in Massachusetts. I thought it was about 4 years ago but it was actually inacted in December 1984. Does that mean I can't buy a drink for the first person who finds me? Since there are more bar promotions with food specials, I wonder if bar patrons are heavier than pre 1983 imbibers. Inquiring minds want to know or is it just me.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But I digress.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again, Leo has a great suggestion, Good Life, which if you haven't been in a while, has changed....I think for the better, especially the food and the decor.....the people are still nice. It has a cool laid back vibe.&lt;br /&gt;Around 6:30 I'm heading downstairs to the Afterlife Lounge to dance the night away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goodlifebar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Good Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line: Downtown Crossing Station at Washington and Summer Streets or Summer and Chauncey Streets walk down Summer Street away from Macy's and toward South Station to Kingston Street which will be on your right (Bank of America is on the corner) Good Life will be on the left side of Kingston # 28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Meters:Good luck. If you're lucky enough to find an available meter, you will want to read hours of operation...some need to fed until 8&lt;br /&gt;Garages and Lots: Are a plenty...check out this link for options &lt;a href="http://www.parkingcarma.com/default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Parking Carma (in beta mode but still helpful)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hang as long as you want but I will check out around 8, for real this time....unless???? &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Encourage you to pay as you order or maintain your own tab&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be at the upstairs bar wearing a Happy New Year silver tiara...which was so trendy last week.
Around 6:30 plan to move to the bar downstairs in the Afterlife Lounge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>20</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><why>Meet Friends, Make Friends, Have Fun</why><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199672274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Have a Good Time at Good Life</name><id>7049176</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199831400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/7049176/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/0/global_2926240.jpeg</photo_url></item>