<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>97 Boston St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.520100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Training center</name><city>Salem</city><id>1278483</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.911697</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>All too often we hear stories of people taking two and three day classes on how to read cards, they spend a small fortune and still come away with nothing but months of studying ahead of them. If they are lucky they will be able to read cards for their friends or families, but most often they are left more confused than when they went in. The trend of selling people long stretched out courses which teach people to use their own intuitive gifts is not one that is followed or ascribed to at MMHC. We believe that nothing is a secret, we can all do it and the information should be provided as succinctly as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This class is only a 3 hour time commitment and by the time you are done, you will be able to give readings! You need only an open mind and heart to be able to read for yourself and others. I have taught beginners and professional readers alike and all have walked away with the ability to not only read the cards but to create their own spreads and individualize them for any kind of question! All ages are welcome in this class and some of the students who have attended this course started working as psychics almost immediately. I have had a resounding success rate with child psychics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will need a notebook and a pen. You may bring your own deck or use one of mine. I essentially teach out of the Sonia Choquette deck. However, there will be various decks for you to look at and practice with. My suggestion is to not buy a deck in advance. Do the course and then decide which one you would like go with. Come and see how simple it can be! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refund Policy: There will be no refund, but if you need to cancel and give at least 24 hour notification, you may take another class or healing in its place.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Readings By JD</member_name><member_id>9397498</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281943900000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gifted</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Friends-in-Spirit</urlname><id>1373252</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Friends in Spirit</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281677663000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to read Tarot and Oracle cards with out the schlep of studying! </name><id>14410156</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281888000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Friends-in-Spirit/events/14410156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/4/global_7183796.jpeg</photo_url></item>