<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>130 Daniel Webster Highway </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.812099</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BAE Systems’ Worrell/Weeks Aircrew Protection Center </name><city>North Merrimack</city><id>8424382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.485207</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;PLEASE CONSIDER SHOWING UP AND ASKING A TOUGH QUESTION ABOUT FISCAL WASTE AND THE D.O.D. BUDGET!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT SHOULD BE NOTED THAT MCCAIN WAS ONE OF THE ONES WHO VOTED FOR THE DEBT CEILING RAISE WHICH RESULTED IN THE FORMATION OF THE "SUPER COMMITTEE" WHOSE FAILURE RESULTED IN THE SUBJECT BUDGET CUTS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SENATORS McCAIN, GRAHAM AND AYOTTE LAUNCH “PRESERVING AMERICA’S STRENGTH” TOWN HALLS HIGHLIGHTING IMPACT OF LOOMING DEFENSE CUTS &lt;br /&gt;

Senators to host Town Hall-Style Meetings in Florida, North Carolina, Virginia and New Hampshire &lt;br /&gt;

July 25, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

Washington, D.C. – U.S. Senators John McCain (R-AZ), Lindsey Graham (R-SC) and Kelly Ayotte (R-NH) today announced the launch of their “Preserving America’s Strength” series of town hall-style meetings in Florida, North Carolina, Virginia and New Hampshire highlighting the devastating impacts of the looming defense cuts now scheduled to take place under budget sequestration next year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The three senators, all members of the U.S. Senate Armed Services Committee, will discuss how the cuts will weaken American national security, put one million jobs at risk, and break faith with the men and women of our Armed Forces and their families. The Department of Defense has already agreed to reduce defense spending by nearly $500 billion over ten years. The additional military spending cuts called for under sequestration would add another $500 billion on top of that figure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“President Obama’s own Secretary of Defense called the looming defense cuts under budget sequestration ‘devastating,’ likening them to ‘shooting ourselves in the head,’ and yet to date, Congress and the Obama Administration have done nothing to stop them from going into effect,” said Senators McCain, Graham and Ayotte. “We look forward to visiting communities in Florida, North Carolina, Virginia and New Hampshire to sound the alarm about the profound negative consequences of these cuts to our national security and economy. These communities – which provide our troops the equipment and support they need to defend our country – will bear the brunt of the defense sequestration cuts. Their voices must be heard in Washington.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mccain.senate.gov/public/index.cfm?FuseAction=PressOffice.PressReleases&amp;amp;ContentRecord_id=bf600654-946f-2ee5-e94b-6c535654212b"&gt;http://www.mccain.senate.gov/public/index.cfm?FuseAction=PressOffice.PressReleases&amp;amp;ContentRecord_id=bf600654-946f-2ee5-e94b-6c535654212b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343753223000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343420591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Prevent Military Spending Cuts" Town Hall with Senator's McCain &amp; Ayotte</name><id>75190042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343741400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/75190042/</event_url></item>