<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are joining up with another singles organization for a nice relaxing alternative to the last-minute Christmas Shopping mania....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that would like to stretch their legs in the fresh air, we will be walking around Jamaica Pond from 11am thru 12 noon or so, after which we will stroll to a local restaurant for Brunch @ 12.30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last we heard The NE Patriots are playing The Dolphins on 12/23, at 1pm, so Brunch will merge into &amp;quot;Football Fest&amp;quot; for the rest of the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you over-sleep and / or don't feel like walking around the Pond, you can head directly to the restaurant anytime from 12.30pm. Ditto any hard-core NFL fans who would like to watch the game on a big screen &amp;amp; enjoy some wonderful grub &amp;amp; draft beer at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: **** RSVP is ESSENTIAL for this event ****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our fellow singles organization (The Post Club) requires pre-registration / RSVP for this event, so you need to RSVP a Yes or Maybe if you will / might attend this event. &lt;br /&gt;In your RSVP, please indicate whether you will attend the Brunch or not, so that we can have an accurate headcount for our reservation at the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will e-mail specifics re: where to meet up at Jamaica Pond, and the name and location of the restaurant, to all those who RSVP a Yes or Maybe to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, please e-mail us at meetup@hubtall.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198697342000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196459748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singles Walk &amp; Brunch &amp; NFL in Jamaica Plain</name><id>6832454</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198423800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/6832454/</event_url></item>