<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Halloween (also known as The Festival of the Dead in many cultures) is a time when the boundary that separates the living from the dead is dissolved and the dead walk among the living. It was traditionally believed that the the dead would cause sickness, crop failures, and other hardship for the living. To prevent this, living people would dress up as the dead in order to pacify the evil spirits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In honor of Halloween, we will be sharing our scary dreams. We will also explore what can be done to cope with scary dreams and nightmares. You are encouraged to bring any of your nightmares, scary dreams, or dreams of monsters, demons, or dead people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dressing up as a scary spirit is one way to diffuse the power of the spirit over you. You are welcome to come dressed up as a scary character from your dream if you want. If you don't want to wear your costume on your way to the Meetup, there is a small bathroom in which to change. Playing the part of a character from your dream may also give you new insights as to the meaning of the dream character. You will have the opportunity to act out a scene from your dream as your chosen dream character.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deerheart has been keeping various types of dream journals off and on for twenty-five years. Deerheart is an artist, a spiritual advisor, and dream guide. An experienced explorer of the dream realms, he has had many teachers of art, creativity, yoga, meditation, dreamwork, shamanism, psychology, empowerment, and healing. He has an online dream journal (a dream blog) called Deerheart Dreams ( &lt;a href="http://deerheartdreams.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://deerheartdreams.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://deerheartdream...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ). In addition to starting Boston Dreamers Meetup Group, he also started the Facebook group called Dream Blog Network ( &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=36258693723" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=36258693723" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, October 13, 2009&lt;br /&gt;7 pm - 9:00 pm (Two hours)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is $10. Anyone who cannot afford to pay should contact the group organizer, Deerheart, to arrange alternatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you. Blessings, Deerheart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by car: Very limited parking at chapel, otherwise nearby streets such as Broadway and Mass Ave. There is a free small parking lot on Kirkland Street side of chapel, up to 8 cars. Coming from either direction on Massachusetts Ave into Harvard Square, turn onto Cambridge Street, then onto Quincy Street and around the corner onto the parking lot on Kirkland Street. The chapel is right on the corner of Quincy Street and Kirkland Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by T: The Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel is a lovely Gothic-revival stone chapel located at 50 Quincy Street in Cambridge, Mass. Please note that the official and historical name as may be found on maps and church directories is The Cambridge Society of the Church of the New Jerusalem (Swedenborgian). We are located at the corner of Quincy and Kirkland Streets, across from Harvard's monumental Memorial Hall/Sander's Theatre, which is behind Harvard Yard in Harvard Square. Access is an easy 5 minute walk from the Harvard Station MBTA stop on the Red Line and buses - just walk through Harvard Yard and ask anyone for Memorial Hall if you don't readily see the large fancy tower, then walk around the Hall to the chapel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions for the Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, check out their website ( &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256684747000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252959095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nightmares, Monsters, Demons, and Dead People</name><id>11370721</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255474800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/11370721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/global_10716220.jpeg</photo_url></item>