<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's start gathering at 6:45 the film time is 7:30.   We are going to want to go in for seats by 7PM.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Normally, I would not pay much attention to a remake of the Karate Kid.  But I love Jackie Chan and Jaden Smith is on his way to being as much of a heart breaker as his famous Dad.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge.   If the movie is upstairs, I will try to grab a table near the windows at the top of the escalator.  If it is downstairs, I wil be near the ropes by the concession stand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, meet us after.  We gather in the hallway for a bit to discuss the movie and do a head count of those who want to go out for drinks and munchies after the show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: June 11, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Columbia Pictures (Sony) &lt;br /&gt;Director: Harald Zwart &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Chris Murphy, Steven Conrad &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Jackie Chan, Jaden Smith, Taraji P. Henson &lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG (for bullying, martial arts action violence and some mild language) &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.karatekid-themovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.karatekid-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: In Columbia Pictures' &amp;quot;The Karate Kid,&amp;quot; 12-year-old Dre Parker (Jaden Smith) could've been the most popular kid in Detroit, but his mother's (Taraji P. Henson) latest career move has landed him in China. Dre immediately falls for his classmate Mei Ying—and the feeling is mutual—but cultural differences make such a friendship impossible. Even worse, Dre's feelings make an enemy of the class bully, Cheng. In the land of kung fu, Dre knows only a little karate, and Cheng puts &amp;quot;the karate kid&amp;quot; on the floor with ease. With no friends in a strange land, Dre has nowhere to turn but maintenance man Mr. Han (Jackie Chan), who is secretly a master of kung fu. As Han teaches Dre that kung fu is not about punches and parries, but maturity and calm, Dre realizes that facing down the bullies will be the fight of his life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Badge.  If movie is upstairs meet at the tables at the top of the escalators. Iff movie is downstairs meet near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825591000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271945178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Karate Kid</name><id>13257971</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276296300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/13257971/</event_url></item>