<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sweet Trail to Great Bay Estuary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four miles long from Longmarsh Road in Durham to the Great Bay Estuary in  Newmarket, the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sweet Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; leads hikers by a remarkable array of  upland forests, freshwater wetlands and tidal salt marsh.&amp;nbsp; The landscape and terrain of this area is on par with the White Mountain National Forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1973, shipping and oil magnate Aristotle Onassis planned to build the  world&amp;rsquo;s largest oil refinery on these lands here on Durham Point, with a  pipeline stretching all the way out to the Isles of Shoals. Had those plans  materialized, they would have forever changed the nature of Great Bay and New  Hampshire&amp;rsquo;s coast. In 1974, however, the plans were defeated by well-organized  local residents who understood these lands&amp;rsquo; value for nature, recreation, and  beauty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Conservation Partnership  &lt;br /&gt;Widely recognized as an estuarine ecosystem of  local, regional, and national significance, New Hampshire&amp;rsquo;s Great Bay has been a  focus of planning and management since the 1940s. Formed by the outflow of five  rivers, the Great Bay Estuary and its watershed encompass 9 percent of the  state&amp;rsquo;s land area. Sitting at the confluence of approximately 930 square miles  of major watersheds in Maine and New Hampshire, it brings a tidal flush of salt  water from the Atlantic Ocean, located nearly five miles east. The inland  location of Great Bay makes it unique in ecosystem and wildlife, providing rich  aquatic habitat that supports more than 150 rare plant and animal species, and  55 exemplary natural communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The total mileage for this hike will be 8 miles roundtrip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAIL GUIDE PDF&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;this is a big file, it may take awhile to download&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://durham.nh.us/generalpdfs/Sweet_Trail.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://durham.nh.us/generalpdfs/Sweet_Trail.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Photos from a previous Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/photos/890135/14437158/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/photos/890135/14437158/&lt;/a&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you  acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks  that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to  participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity;  you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities,  clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and  will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the  leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and  indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims  for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those  caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetig place TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303644876000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303397049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sweet Trail to Great Bay Estuary, Durham &amp; Newmarket, NH</name><id>17384792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303567200000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17384792/</event_url></item>