<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>438 Daniel Webster Hwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.861398</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.424.0995</phone><name>Buckley's Great Steaks</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>793985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.493902</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The membership has voted!  The November restaurant of the month will be at Buckley's Great Steaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About The Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chef and owner Michael Buckley first entered the restaurant scene in 1995 when he and his wife Sarah opened Michael Timothy’s Urban Bistro, Wine &amp;amp; Jazz Bar on Main Street in Nashua, NH. Critically acclaimed for its upscale atmosphere and cuisine, Michael Timothy’s quickly became one of the region’s premier dining destinations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to opening Michael Timothy’s, Chef Buckley cooked at some of the most prestigious restaurants in New Hampshire, and also spent time in Europe working under a master chef. He uses only fresh, quality ingredients in every recipe, and relies on local organic farmers and independent purveyors who share the same high standards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building on their success with Michael Timothy’s, the Buckleys opened a second restaurant – Surf – in 2002 just across the street from their urban bistro. Devoted entirely to creatively prepared and seriously fresh seafood, Surf continues the tradition of excellence set by Chef Buckley. Surf was recently voted Best Seafood Restaurant in the state by New Hampshire Magazine’s Readers Poll.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Buckleys’ passion for serving finely prepared foods led them to open their third restaurant, Buckley's Great Steaks, in December of 2005. Almost immediately, it was voted the best steakhouse in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a look at the menu.  Some of the steaks are a bit pricy, but there are also some reasonable priced dishes, like the meatloaf for $15 and the Buttermilk chicken for $19.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.buckleysgreatsteaks.com/specialties.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.buckleysgr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Tavern:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located inside Buckley's Great Steaks, Riddle's Tavern is fast-becoming one of the &amp;quot;must try&amp;quot; spots in Southern New Hampshire. The combination of live music, premium cocktails, impeccable service and incredible food attracts locals and travelers from all over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rich earth-tones, soft lighting and a comfortable atmosphere make Riddle's Tavern the ideal location to meet friends after work or for a special evening out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spend your time at Riddle's mingling with friends at the rose-marble bar or settle into an oversized leather sofa in front of our fireplace. Order one of our incredible martinis, a specialty cocktail or let us recommend something from our wine cellar. Either way, the relaxed surroundings will draw you in and soon you'll feel right at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.buckleysgreatsteaks.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.buckleysgr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227406780000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224557352000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Southern New Hampshire Restaurant of the Month Club November Meetup </name><id>9000507</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226798100000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9000507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/5/global_5966677.jpeg</photo_url></item>