<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Development Circles are a committed group of people who sit together regularly in order to build and work with the Energy that is Infinite Spirit. The focus of our Development Circles is always Serving Spirit and the Spiritualist Community by developing one's sensitivity to bridge the gap between our physical world and the Higher Side. As Spiritualists, our focus is on the Healing that is brought to souls on both sides of the veil through Spirit Communication. Classes run from September through May, with a hiatus for the holidays in late November &amp;amp; December. Committment to a Development Circle is vital. Participants are asked only to miss a class when it is unavoidable. This means taking responsibility for one's life and keeping the physical body healthy so that you can do the work of Spirit. Priority for Development Circles is given to active Church Members and then the Community-at-large based on availability of space. Names will be taken for a waiting list, should space become available during the course of the year. Sign Ups for Classes will be taken from SEPTEMBER 3, 2011 Beginner / Intermediate Development Circle Beginner / Intermediate Development Circle meet the First and Third Wednesday of each month. Classes will be taught by Nancy Smith and Bill Bean. The class size will be kept to 16 people. This class will look at the foundations of Spiritualism, the power of thought, healing, as well as psychic development exercises and Mental Mediumship. This class looks at the importance of developing &amp;quot;trust&amp;quot; in oneself and Spirit in order to establish the framework for Spirit Communication. It is open to those with a desire to develop their Spiritual skills, as well of those that wish to polish existing skills. To sign up call Nancy Smith 978-835-0005 or e-mail at nancy@angelscapes.net Please note in your message the class for which you wish to sign up. Advanced / Working Mediums Development Circle The Advanced / Working Mediums Development Circle will meet the Second Wednesday of each month. Classes to be taught by Nancy Smith and Bill Bean. Class size wil be limited to 10 people, chosen based on experience. Priority is given to those Mediums who sincerely wish to serve our Church and the other Spiritualist Churches in the local area. Emphasis of this class will be on Platform work, how to &amp;quot;hold the energy&amp;quot; throughout a demonstration, and working with the Communicator to provide the best evidence possible to prove the &amp;quot;Continuity of Life&amp;quot;. The Circle will further the knowledge of the Philosophies of Spiritualism, Hands on Healing, Mediumship, inspiritational speaking and lecture development, and some types of experimental spirit communication. Advanced students will be asked to develop and teach a portion of a Beginner&amp;#146;s class. After the first of the year some of the classes will be opened to Church Memebers and Beginer/Indermediate Development students to observe and act as sitters for Spirit Communication. To sign up, call Nancy Smith 978-835-0005 or e-mail at nancy@angelscapes.net Please note in your message the class for which you wish to sign up. Trance Development Circle Trance Development Class will meet the second and fourth Tuesday of each month, with a hiatus for the holidays in late November &amp;amp; December. Class will be taught by Rev. Marie Gaines. This Development Circle is for those with a foundation of Mental Mediumship who wish to explore light and deep trance, ectoplasm, and the influence of Spirit Guides. To sign up, speak to Rev. Marie Gaines after Service or leave a message on the church answering machine: 617-770-2246.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Lynch</member_name><member_id>10020850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315062883000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-First-Spiritualist-Church-of-Quincy</urlname><id>1493078</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>The First Spiritualist Church of Quincy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314722974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sign up for Development Circles</name><id>31561762</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315058400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-First-Spiritualist-Church-of-Quincy/events/31561762/</event_url></item>