<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Power Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.548980</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Outlook at Nashoba Valley</name><city>Westford</city><id>488945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.437350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A room with a view! Take in all of the game and slopeside action! Join us for the Superbowl, we will watch the action on six 50&amp;quot; HD Plasma TVs! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner reservations will guarantee a seat. The tv coverage is scheduled to begin at 6 and I will make dinner reservations for 5:30 PM. Others joining in after dinner may be relegated to standing room and seats left at the bar depending on the crowd. All reservations will be made on Wed, Jan 30th. Please RSVP as soon as possible so I have an idea of how many to expect. Since this is for dinner there will NOT be any &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; responses, please reply YES or NO &lt;b&gt;and&lt;/b&gt; &amp;quot;I will be coming for dinner&amp;quot; OR &amp;quot;I will join you later.&amp;quot; Costs are based on what you order, please anticipate drinks, taxes and gratuity when paying your share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nashoba has a bar, fireplace and televisions in the restaurant along with beautiful views of the slopes and skiing... they are also offering a free halftime buffet!!!&lt;br /&gt;Come for the food, laughs and cheering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dineoutlook.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dineoutloo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservations will be made for those coming to dinner. I will request to be seated near the fireplace. Those joining in later can just look for us there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202655463000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201112153000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SuperBowl Sunday Event...</name><id>7179589</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202077800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7179589/</event_url></item>