<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Park Ave and Elm Streets</address_2><address_1>250 Park Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.264890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774-239-0214</phone><name>stART on the Street</name><city>Worcester</city><id>341550</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.819016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The original festival that stARTed it all! 2008 hosted over 25,000 attendees, 250+ artists and crafters, 20+ performers, youth activities, food court and more at this one-day, FREE event that is literally &amp;quot;on the street&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday September 20, 2009, 11am - 5pm         (rain date Sept 27)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Ave, between Highland and Pleasant Streets - Worcester MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also at the Festival you can find....&lt;br /&gt;Worcester, Massachusetts - The Worcester Cultural Coalition will mark 10 years of creative city-making with a celebration known as WOOphoria on Sunday, September 20, 2009. To be held in conjunction with the 7th Annual stART on the Street Festival, WOOphoria will offer dynamic, hands-on, interactive, multi-generational experiences 11 a.m. - 5 p.m.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located within the stART footprint at the corner of Elm Street and Park Avenue, WOOphoria will feature nearly two dozen of the Cultural Coalition's members  including:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;walking tours of Elm Park with Preservation Worcester and the Worcester Cultural Commission, featuring tales of the colorful history of the first publicly purchased park in America and the ongoing Art in the Park Exhibit&lt;br /&gt;create a huge rubber band art installation with the Worcester Art Museum&lt;br /&gt;record your Worcester memories with WCUW Radio via a 1940's radio console&lt;br /&gt;create commUNITY quilt squares with the Henry Lee Willis Community Center, and learn the cultural significance of quilting relative to African American history&lt;br /&gt;help write a giant Community Poem along with the Worcester County Poetry Association&lt;br /&gt;try your hand at Gaelic calligraphy and Irish drumming along with the Worcester Hibernian Cultural Center&lt;br /&gt;have your pictures taken with a series of giant Worcester postcards created by the Worcester Public Schools&lt;br /&gt;Meet &amp;amp; greet with a Knight and Princess from Higgins Armory Museum&lt;br /&gt;and so much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WOOphoria will unveil an interactive public art project that will quite literally &amp;quot;put Worcester on the couch.&amp;quot; The Couch, created by local artist Gary Orlinsky, will make its first appearance at WOOphoria and then will be displayed at Clark University and various events and locations (indoors and out) around Worcester County in the months to come. Visitors to The Couch will be invited to write out their complaints, concerns, hopes and dreams on slips of paper and to deposit them in a box provided as part of The Couch display.  These slips will subsequently be given to other artists and performers to create original music, poetry and creative city expressions that will help us let go of our negativity and look to a forward thinking creative identity.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Cultural Coalition will use WOOphoria to introduce its new public WOO Card. Modeled after a loyalty card program developed for college students two years ago, the WOO Card program will now offer the general public discounts and special offers for cool concerts, dynamic theater, unique museums, magical music, street festivals, outdoor adventures and more - throughout Worcester County, throughout the year! The cards will be available for purchase for the first time for $20.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The WOOphoria celebration will continue with the Cultural Coalition's 10th Anniversary Bash to be held on Tuesday, September 29th at 5:30 p.m. at the Hadley Building, home to GArtH - Gallery of Art at the Hadley, 657 Main Street, Worcester.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253632472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253031932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>stART on the Street Art's Festival Click and Shoot</name><id>11378395</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253458800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11378395/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/e/global_10729598.jpeg</photo_url></item>