<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join others from Boston Small Business Success Network to learn about email marketing&lt;/strong&gt; at an event sponsored by Cereus Women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Space is limited.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;See below for registration details. T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;his workshop is promoted elsewhere, so don't delay. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About This Event&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the recent spotlight on social media, by most measures email is still the most effective sales-driving tool for your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But getting started with email marketing may feel overwhelming. How do you get people to sign up for your list? What will you say in your emails? Which email marketing tool should you use? How can you be sure your emails get through spam filters to your prospects and customers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erin Howard will teach you how to put an effective email marketing plan in place for your business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Format&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cost: $15 in advance/$20 at the door&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One 45 minute presentation followed by ~15 minutes of Q&amp;amp;A, plus time for networking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring plenty of business cards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coffee and muffins will be provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Our agenda for the meeting will be as follows: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 9:00 – Sign in and networking, (registration for those not prepaid) &lt;br /&gt;

 9:10 – Meetup News and go around the room introducing yourself and sharing business cards &lt;br /&gt;

 9:20 – &lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;Presentation with Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 10:20 – Closing remarks, Upcoming events &lt;br /&gt;

 10:30 – Meeting ends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Presenter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/2/event_218703042.jpeg" width="101" height="109" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erin Howard has over 15 years of digital marketing experience at companies ranging from Staples and EMC to small high tech start-ups. A few years ago she broke free of her cubicle and started Streamline Marketing as a way to help authors, speakers, and consultants use the power of internet marketing to build their brands and businesses online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erin frequently speaks to local business groups about social media and marketing and teaches social media classes at Assabet After Dark and Brookline Adult and Community &lt;br /&gt;

 Education. She has an MBA from Boston College and lives in Shrewsbury with her husband and 2 daughters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Host&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/6/event_172360662.jpeg" width="100" height="119" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Kim Reddington’s entrepreneurial career started in 1995 after she decidedthat dropping her year old son off at day care every day was just too heart-wrenching. She realized the only way to have the flexibility she needed was to create it herself. That’s when she just quit and took off on her own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim’s journey has led her to helping other women entrepreneurs think big with their online marketing to get all the clients they need and is known as a Client-Generating Website Guru. She helps her clients to build a system around their website that will convert their prospective clients into paying clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving using GPS?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are using a GPS or Navigation System, 1900 West Park Drive often does not appear. Use 1 Research Drive (University of Phoenix) and from there enter Westborough Office Park on West Park Drive, go 1/2 mile, 1900 is on your right. Suite 280 is on the second floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost and How to Register &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$15 in advance/$20 at the door.  Capacity is limited and the event is promoted elsewhere, so you need get a ticket in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register &lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;amp;hosted_button_id=THV682WG9Q9ZJ"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or click the Paypal button to reserve your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;amp;hosted_button_id=THV682WG9Q9ZJ"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/3/e/event_207172542.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't have a Paypal account, you can still pay through this link.  First click the Paypal button above, then follow the link labelled "Don't Have a Paypal Account?" to pay with your credit card without logging in to Paypal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure to mark your calendar now&lt;/strong&gt; so you don't forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Got Questions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can post your questions below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Reddington</member_name><member_id>3156875</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366986630000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364831516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5 Simple Steps to Successful Email Marketing</name><id>112076982</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366981200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/112076982/</event_url></item>