<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Irving St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.263210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Academy of Music</name><city>Worcester</city><id>6904132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.806068</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark your Calenders Everyone! This is an amazing show...Not to be missed! And we are looking for folks to pass the info along to friends, family, and others... Please join us! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Worcester Academy of Music and Worcester Alliance of Photographers &lt;br /&gt;

 Present &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Photographic Harmony&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Worcester Alliance of Photographers in partnership with the Worcester Academy of Music  is &lt;br /&gt;

 pleased to announce their new "Photographic Harmony" exhibit taking place at the Worcester Academy of Music. This juried exhibit of photographs compliments the already wonderful melodic atmosphere at the Music Academy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The almost 50 pieces of creative and unique photography have been provided by our local &lt;br /&gt;

 Alliance of Photographers. The show portrays music  and art  in and around Worcester. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please join us at the Worcester Academy of Music, located at 11 Irving Street in Worcester, MA, on &lt;strong&gt;May 19th, 2012 from 5:00 - 7:00 pm for the reception&lt;/strong&gt; celebrating the opening of this special exhibit. The photography will allow you see and enjoy a new perspective about music and how it can be visually shared through this medium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Scott Erb and Donna DuFault, Proprietors of Erb Photography and founders of the Worcester &lt;br /&gt;

 Alliance of Photographers, together with Sarah Kelly, Executive Director of the Music Academy, are responsible for creating this idea and for generating enthusiasm among both organization participating in this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah Kelly says "This is a wonderful collaboration and a great opportunity to see a beautiful &lt;br /&gt;

 marriage between music and photography."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stop in and say hello to Sarah and the photographers. They welcome your thoughts and &lt;br /&gt;

 questions about the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We invite you to visit Photographic Harmony taking place at the  &lt;br /&gt;

 Worcester Academy of Music this May, and runs through this November. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be looking at the photos on ech floor!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Morse</member_name><member_id>3632743</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Lane</member_name><member_id>5229126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roy Johnson</member_name><member_id>11489085</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis Ditto</member_name><member_id>13146412</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337714430000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335475657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photographic Harmony Exhibit Opens at the Worcester Academy of Music</name><id>62289242</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337461200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/62289242/</event_url></item>