<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Taken from the Museum of Fine Arts website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Unforeseen by Laura Dunn, with executive producers Terrence Malick and Robert Redford (2007, 93 min., video). Laura Dunn's beautifully crafted documentary follows the career of Gary Bradley, an ambitious West Texas farm boy who moved to Austin and became one of the state's most powerful real estate developers, capitalizing on Austin's boomtown growth beginning in the 1970s. At the peak of his powers, Bradley transformed 4,000 acres of pristine Hill Country into fastest-selling subdivisions. When the development threatened local treasure Barton Springs-a natural spring-fed swimming hole-the community fought back and the subdivision became a lightning rod for environmental activism. A powerful meditation on the destruction of the natural world and the American Dream as it falls victim to the cannibalizing forces of unchecked development, The Unforeseen is an intricate tale of personal hopes, victories and failures, and debates over land, economics, property rights, and the public good.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Per group custom, I will be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater during the credits.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>The film's topic (over-development of the US) should provide for good conversation after the film. This event is part of the Human Rights International Film Festival.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198706092000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Unforeseen</name><id>6972375</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200762000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6972375/</event_url></item>