<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Newport Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02861</zip><lat>41.878472</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 728-0500 x252</phone><name>Daggett Farm/ Slater Memorial Park</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>784324</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354237</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event is sponsored by the Pawtucket Arts Festival.  This is the last concert of the Philharmonic’s series featuring resident conductor Francisco Noya. The opening band is Ronnie &amp;amp; The Satellites. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would suggest that we get there early and stake out an area.  I will email my phone number to attendees prior to the concert so that we can be sure to meet in one location with a minimum of hassle.  I also thought that people might like to bring a picnic to enjoy during the concert.  Just in case - the rain date - is the following night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are fireworks at the conclusion of the performance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information please check out the Arts Festival website: &lt;a href="http://www.pawtucketartsfestival.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pawtucketa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And please note:  This year the Pawtucket Arts Festival is partnering with the Pawtucket Soup Kitchen to assist with a food donation drive at festival events. Look for the blue donation barrels and drop-off your non-perishable food donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email my phone number to attendees prior to the event so that we can meet each other.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284243740000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282441074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society - RI Philharmonic in the Park and Fireworks!</name><id>14498104</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284238800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/14498104/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/0/global_13237216.jpeg</photo_url></item>