<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Photo Plus</address_2><address_1>655 West 34th Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10001</zip><lat>40.750000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774-239-0214</phone><name>Jacob K. Javits Convention Center</name><city>New York</city><id>199356</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.989998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>AutumnColor Open House&lt;br /&gt;Saturday December 2, 2006 - 10:00 am to 3:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;AutumnColor Digital Imaging, 70 Webster Street, Worcester, MA 01603&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Join Us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This open house gives AutumnColor an opportunity to invite the Worcester area art &amp;amp; photography community - as well as our own clients, neighbors, friends &amp;amp; their families - to explore our gallery &amp;amp; see samples of a wide variety of projects taking place at AutumnColor. We hope you will come &amp;amp; learn more about AutumnColor &amp;amp; our unique niche business. We will be offering a tour of the facilities, light refreshments, a mounting demo, &amp;amp; door prizes. You will have the chance to obtain information packets &amp;amp; samples as well as learn about our workshops. We hope you will join us for this event. All members of the community are welcome &amp;amp; encouraged to attend. We urge you ask questions &amp;amp; enjoy our hospitality, Please join us on December 2!&lt;br /&gt;What you?ll see...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just this past year alone, AutumnColor has helped many of our clients complete a wide variety of unique projects. We handled everything from scanning Eric Meola?s original 1973 negatives from the Bruce Springsteen cover shot of the Born to Run album to creating over 45 large photographs by Chris Barnes of a deteriorated Ellis Island for a traveling exhibition. Each day we have amazing images with incredible stories pass through our digital printing lab. This is the day we open the doors to the public to come and view this work and our process. AutumnColor has been in business for over 8 years in Worcester. Our process and digital talents have attracted many local artists and folks from all over the world. Come see those results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP ~ By Nov 30, 2006  ~  email: light@autumncolor.com  t. 800-533-5050  &lt;br /&gt;t. 508-798-6612       f. 508-757-2216&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1165244585000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1164053871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AutumnColor Open House! Please come by and Check it out!</name><id>5281032</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165071600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5281032/</event_url></item>