<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Harvard Bookstore site: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/event/anton_zeilinger/"&gt;http://www.harvard.com/event/anton_zeilinger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome professor of quantum physics ANTON ZEILINGER as he explores the theory of quantum entanglement and his new book,&lt;em&gt; Dance of the Photons: From Einstein to Quantum Teleportation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Einstein&amp;rsquo;s steadfast refusal to accept certain aspects of quantum theory was rooted in his insistence that physics has to be about reality. Accordingly, he once derided as 'spooky action at a distance' the notion that two elementary particles far removed from each other could nonetheless influence each other&amp;rsquo;s properties&amp;mdash;a hypothetical phenomenon his fellow theorist Erwin Schr&amp;ouml;dinger termed 'quantum entanglement.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In a series of ingenious experiments conducted in various locations&amp;mdash;from a dank sewage tunnel under the Danube River to the balmy air between a pair of mountain peaks in the Canary Islands&amp;mdash;Dr. Zeilinger and his colleagues have demonstrated the reality of such entanglement using photons, or light quanta, created by laser beams. In principle the lessons learned may be applicable in other areas, including the eventual development of quantum computers".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. Maher will be grabbing a bite to eat in The Garage &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-garage-cambridge"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-garage-cambridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;at 36 JFK Street starting at 5:45 pm. Care to join him? The Food Court is on the lower level. We should prolly take off at&amp;nbsp;6:25 pm&amp;nbsp;to start walking to the Harvard Book Store. Let's grab seats&amp;nbsp;by 6:30 pm. It's a small&amp;nbsp;venue with only thirty or&amp;nbsp;forty seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. A few MEETUP signs will be used as table tents at The Garage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More from the Harvard Book Store:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;""More than a century after its birth,&amp;nbsp;[quantum] theory is as perplexing as ever, and recent lab results have only underscored just how strange it is. No one is better qualified to describe the weirdness than University of Vienna physicist Anton Zeilinger, director of the Austrian lab where many of these experiments were done....&amp;nbsp;Zeilinger is at his best when detailing the experiments behind these remarkable results. He also examines the philosophical issues they raise: questions, one suspects,&amp;nbsp;that could well take another century to answer."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Anton Zeilinger (according to Wikipedia):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anton_Zeilinger"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anton_Zeilinger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Anton Zeilinger (born on 20 May 1945 in Ried im Innkreis, Austria) is an Austrian quantum physicist. He is currently professor of physics at the University of Vienna, previously University of Innsbruck. He is also the director of the Vienna branch of the Institute for Quantum Optics and Quantum Information IQOQI at the Austrian Academy of Sciences. Zeilinger has been called a pioneer in the new field of quantum information and is renowned for his realization of quantum teleportation with photons [...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"[Anton Zeilinger] has held positions at the University of Innsbruck, the Technical University of Munich, the Technical University of Vienna and at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) and distinguished visiting positions at Humboldt University in Berlin, Merton College of Oxford University and the Coll&amp;egrave;ge de France in Paris. Zeilinger received many awards for his scientific work, among the most recent being the King Faisal Prize (2005), and the first Newton Prize of the IOP (2007). He is a member of six Scientific Academies. Anton Zeilinger is currently Professor of Physics at the University of Vienna and Scientific Director of the Institute of Quantum Optics and Quantum Information of the Austrian Academy of Sciences. Since 2006, Zeilinger is the vice chairman of the board of trustees of the Institute of Science and Technology Austria, an ambitious project initiated by Zeilinger's proposal. He is a fan of the Hitchhiker's Guide To The Galaxy by Douglas Adams, going so far as to name his sailboat 42.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"2005 Anton Zeilinger was among the "10 people who could change the world", elect by the British newspaper New Statesmen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In 2010 he received the Wolf Prize in Physics". [ &lt;strong&gt;MORE about his work&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anton_Zeilinger"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anton_Zeilinger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About his book, according to The Varsity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://thevarsity.ca/articles/40796"&gt;http://thevarsity.ca/articles/40796&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"[...] Throughout the book, Zeilinger intersperses his descriptions of quantum physics with a story of two fictional experimentalists, Alice and Bob, and how they arrive at several different conclusions that contradict or support each other. His way of conveying the trials and tribulations of generations of experimental physicists gives the reader an almost personal connection in understanding how certain theories remain widely accepted by the scientific community, while others have been disproven over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"On the other hand, one perplexing issue in Zeilinger&amp;rsquo;s narrative style is the careful explanation of hypotheses, when some are immediately shot down as a contradiction to other experimental results or established theory. Separating fact from fiction, so to speak, was difficult in this sense. Or perhaps this was Zeilinger&amp;rsquo;s intention &amp;mdash; to motivate the reader to dive into the questioning mindset of an experimentalist?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"What might set this book apart from, for example, a standard quantum mechanics textbook, is the focus on conceptual understanding over mathematical reasoning. Zeilinger makes it his mission to portray physics in an informative, yet interesting and occasionally humorous, manner. The material is based on up-and-coming research &amp;mdash; after all, the technique of quantum teleportation was only experimentally confirmed in 1997 &amp;mdash; and the clear explanations, complete with real-life analogies, make this book a worthwhile introduction to the phenomena described in quantum mechanics."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Dance-Photons-Einstein-Quantum-Teleportation/dp/0374239665"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Harvard Book Store&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/about/hbs_in_brief/"&gt;http://www.harvard.com/about/hbs_in_brief/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Harvard Book Store is an independently run bookstore serving the greater Cambridge area. The bookstore is located in Harvard Square and has been family-owned since 1932. We are known for our extraordinary selection of new, used, and bargain books and for a history of innovation. In 2009, we introduced same-day environmentally-friendly bike delivery and a book-making robot capable of printing and binding any of millions of titles in minutes."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video: &lt;/strong&gt;Interview with Anton Zeilinger: Part 1: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o5dNg6pmgPg"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o5dNg6pmgPg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to Harvard Book Store:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/about/hours_directions/"&gt;http://www.harvard.com/about/hours_directions/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To get to the store from the Harvard Square T station: As you exit the station, reverse your direction and walk east along Mass. Ave. in front of the Cambridge Savings Bank. Cross Dunster Street and proceed along Mass. Ave. for three more blocks. You will pass Au Bon Pain, J.P. Licks, and Leavitt &amp;amp; Peirce Tobacco.&amp;nbsp; Harvard Book Store is located at the corner of Mass. Ave. and Plympton St [...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Harvard Book Store customers receive a discount at the Charles Hotel Parking Garage [...] a $2 discount".&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We all should be grabbing seats inside the Harvard Bookstore by 6:30 pm. It gets mighty crowded by 6:40 pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299604839000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299085449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Anton Zeilinger, "Dance of the Photons: From Einstein to Quantum Teleportation"</name><id>16768051</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299542400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/16768051/</event_url></item>