<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.303934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Scenic Theater</name><city>Rochester</city><id>709969</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.976582</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been to a Murder Mystery Party? It's a blast! This will be our fifth party. Ask anyone who may have attended one before and they will tell you they had a great time! We will be having the the Murder Mystery party at the Scenic theater, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This murder mystery game is not a board game; everyone will be participating at the same time; you must not be afraid of the dark, and you must dress all in &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;black clothing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! This is not a show. We will be in a big old scary theater with two or three large rooms; plenty of space to wander around in and hide victims! &lt;br /&gt;

At 6 pm we'll have dinner, I will explain the game and give a brief tour of the theater. At 7pm the murder mystery will start. This is not a child event so please do not bring your children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will buy food, appetizers, drinks, condiments, cutlery and plates. Hotdogs, BBQ chicken, wraps, salads, mixed fruit, chips, dip, watermelon and deserts too. I'll keep the costs low at $15 per person. (To be paid in person at this event) I’ll bring a cooler with ice, too. If others want to bring some ice and coolers that would be great, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not doing a potluck because we all know that a few members usually don't show up and don't bring the food they've signed up for. Potlucks usually end up with alot of desserts and less varieties of food. As I have planned this event, there will be a greater diversity and balance of food, with less pressure on members having to figure out what to bring. I will need help setting up, cooking and cleaning up afterwards so please let me know if you'd like to volunteer: I'll need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 setup volunteers to show up at 5 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 clean-up volunteers to clear away dinner. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please attend only if you are willing to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;actively&lt;/span&gt; participate. This is not a spectator event, be aware this event is played in nearly dark rooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is plenty of free parking in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Scenic Theater is on main street across from Citizens Bank. &lt;br /&gt;

More details will follow as we get closer to the event. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you have any questions call me (Peter) at 603-312-6735. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

See you there for a memorable night! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Peter&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347757656000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345888519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Murder Mystery Party/ Dinner</name><id>79292622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347746400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/79292622/</event_url></item>