<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>kayak rental doughnation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per kayak rented</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I invite you to a trip which i have done with the group many times before in the past.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple trip down a close river and lunch party afterward.&lt;br /&gt;It is good for beginners and the tide is at its highest on the river around noon to provide an easier entrance at Dunkin Donuts river entry point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Hartford starting with October 7, 2007. &lt;br /&gt;Day High Tide Height Sunrise Moon Time % Moon &lt;br /&gt;/Low Time Feet Sunset Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Su 7 High 12:35 AM 2.1 6:54 AM Rise 3:15 AM 16 &lt;br /&gt;7 Low 8:18 AM 0.3 6:23 PM Set 4:53 PM &lt;br /&gt;7 High 12:52 PM 2.1 &lt;br /&gt;7 Low 8:43 PM 0.3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; the water is pretty low..hasnt rained for a whle..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We still have to move the cars to the boat ramp and that takes time anyway..someone has to stand guard with the yaks and equipment..but usually only takes 15 or so minutes via rte 9 to harbor park weslean boat launch. or another suitable take out..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now there is a slight addition to the trip..we can watch the rigotta form the water, yep parkin at harbor park may be made more difficult by the event and we amy just take out a bit more south or even north....&lt;br /&gt; see the info below..&lt;br /&gt;weslean rigotta.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hctr.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hctr.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE, from hartford, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;get onto Rte 9 south, (to and in Cromwell/Middletown) go to exit 19 &lt;br /&gt;Turn (right) off the exit, =west toward Kmart and Stop and Shop &lt;br /&gt;At the first light you see (intersection of rte 372 and rte 3) take the left (south toward stop n shop) onto rte 3= shunpike rd &lt;br /&gt;There is a KFC, MackDonalds, and a Drunkin Doonuts while heading to the next traffic light. Use Drunkin Donuts (driveway) there is an empty lot right next to the dunkin donuts lot, just pull in there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a water trail sign showing the most dangerous animals and what not to feed the animals...including the banjo boys... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have a few spare kayaks with me but only those that have been reserved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip usually takes 2-3 hours or so but if we do some exploring ..then its over when its over provided you have not been eaten by wild creatures.... &lt;br /&gt;iF YOU SURVIVED..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE....the new take out is a bit north of the outlet CT/Mettabassette and picknic, there or at a nice spot on the same road nerby the take out..&lt;br /&gt;Take out RIVER ROAD Cromwell&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;I drive the dark blue toyota avalon with the kayak trailer.&lt;br /&gt;if necessary i put out an orange cone to find me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok i cant rent to maybees..nor can i hold up everyone with them..&lt;br /&gt;you can say maybe in the NO area and still join us on the trip or just meet us for lunch at the end point, trips like this i found are made difficult by maybe persons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191942171000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191519084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Trip Down The Metabassett and Coganchug River Cormwell CT and Dinner After</name><id>6487718</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191769200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6487718/</event_url></item>