<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;CEMI (&lt;a href="http://cemi.org"&gt;http://cemi.org&lt;/a&gt;) is hosting a laid-back audio-hacking, learning and performance event, where members and friends engage in an evening of audio show-and-tell and/or open-mic performance, sharing their new music, sound art and audio hackery. It's a glorious mashup of sound at the Artisan's Asylum in Somerville. You are welcome to attend and can participate (bring your music!) or not. There are music-people to meet, music-toys to play with, and music-talking to be enjoyed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To set your expectations, the total headcount last time was...hmm...five?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is about a relaxed as it gets. Come visit and meetup with some folks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: There is a $5 fee for attendance which goes to CEMI. They're a non-profit technology incubator/gear-share. They could use the dough. It *does not* go to this group. We're free, we just want to share their space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ideas of things you want to do, or have music you want to perform or share (we'll even let you connect your ipod and playback from your sound cloud account if you want,) please let us know in the planning thread in the discussion forum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/musical/messages/boards/thread/30768732/#92621412"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/musical/messages/boards/thread/30768732&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Luke is organizing the night at CEMI. He's big and bald and bearded and most likely has a STAR WARS t-shirt on.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luke Stark</member_name><member_id>3565678</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361738899000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Music Makers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>musical</urlname><id>413373</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Music Makers With Relaxed Expectations</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359076684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Musical Meetup in Somerville, MA - CEMI Lab Series: Audio Hack N' Jam</name><id>101263482</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361664000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/musical/events/101263482/</event_url></item>