<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.958260</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pilgrim Memorial State Park</name><city>Plymouth </city><id>2073491</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.662415</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Steampunk is awesome, i'll say it again and again. If you're looking to expand your portfolio a little bit and have a great time then this is the place you want to be. Here's the info for the picnic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello! Join us for the Third Annual New England Steampunk Picnic in beautiful Plymouth Massachusetts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sited on the waterfront, it is immediately next to Plymouth Rock and the  Mayflower II. Ample shade and a number of nearby vendors/restaurants  for foodstuffs make the site very comfortable, and with the majority of  the tourists gone, there should be ample parking along the Park and on  Water Street. &lt;br /&gt; A VERY short walk across the street is beautiful Brewster Gardens, the  location of many weddings; a path from the Gardens leads upstream to one  of the oldest existing grist mills in the country, with a working water  wheel (and ice cream parlor, BTW!). &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; We hope you will bring a potluck item to share, and will have a largish  table set up for food items. We will have a stove and kettle provided  for hot beverages such as tea. In fact, feel free to bring your tea  cups! &lt;br /&gt; We recommend you bring your own seating to ensure your comfort. &lt;br /&gt; Weather Permitting, we will bring out the Victrola to 'crank out' some  tunes! If you have some 78s, feel free to bring them with and I'll  supply the needles! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; NOTE however that alcoholic beverages are NOT permitted in the Park at any time.... &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; And being historic Plymouth, there are many places to see such as the  massive (and surprisingly, little visited) Founders Monument; the  Pilgrim's Gravesites at Burial Hill, Pilgrim Hall Museum, and I believe  there is a Cemetery Tour conducted from the Park for a small fee. &lt;br /&gt; I will direct interested parties to the sights as they request. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; For those that the Lady Raven and I are acquainted with, we will be  retiring after the picnic to our home nearby for a casual evening with a  fire pit and sheltered by my 20 foot Geodesic Dome. Be aware we have  two small dogs, Shiba Inus, and they are little attention hogs. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The Commuter Rail trains from Boston stop at Plymouth Station a couple  miles up the road from the Park....we will provide some shuttle service  for those arriving. Plan on the Saturday schedule being in effect....and  keep our phone number handy. We will update at a later time with a cell  number for day-of-the-event contact. &lt;br /&gt; Please, be courteous and phone us a few days in advance if you will need a ride from the Train and back again...... &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; RAIN DATE: Saturday Sept. 17th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call us when you arrive. 1-800-210-9531.    We'll be the guys with the cameras.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315741893000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307507962000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England 3rd Annual Steampunk Picnic</name><id>21420901</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315670400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/21420901/</event_url></item>