<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bldg 4, Room 163</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.378963</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9844022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119621</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bhopal Second Disaster is the fruit of the FotoEvidence Book Award. The annual Book Award is given each year to a photographer whose work demonstrates courage and commitment in documenting social injustice and violations of human rights. It is a photo documentary of the ongoing second disaster in Bhopal, India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex Masi will present this Photo Documentary and share his experiences from Bhopal, India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://alexmasi.photoshelter.com/"&gt;http://alexmasi.photoshelter.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/alexmasiphotography?ref=ts&amp;amp;fref=ts"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/alexmasiphotography?ref=ts&amp;amp;fref=ts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex Masi is an award-winning documentary photographer and multimedia journalist based in London, UK. &lt;br /&gt;

 Born and raised in northern Italy, Alex left him hometown near Milan for the United Kingdom in January 2001. After having completed a degree in ‘Photojournalism’ at the ‘London College of Communication’ in 2006, Alex has begun to investigate and document critical socio-environmental issues in countries such as India, Afghanistan and most recently Iraq. He has devoted his attention on exposing peculiar stories of human-made injustice, focusing mainly on children, their living conditions, their health and their human rights. Alex strongly believes documentary photography ought to be an active catalyst in promoting awareness, political and juridical change, and in fostering action by individuals, NGOs and governmental bodies. He strives to portray his subjects with intimacy and meaning. Alex has won various awards and has been recognized worldwide for excellence in photojournalism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is brought to you by International Campaign for Justice in Bhopal (ICJB). ICJB is a coalition of disaster survivors and environmental, social justice, progressive Indian, and human rights groups that have joined forces to hold the Indian Government and Dow Chemical Corporation accountable for the ongoing chemical disaster in Bhopal, India. It was set up to address the grave injustices suffered by the half million Bhopal Gas Disaster survivors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://studentsforbhopal.org/"&gt;http://studentsforbhopal.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it is a FREE EVENT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/109684562523708/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/109684562523708/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex's work in CNN : &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/109684562523708/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/109684562523708/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>swapna</member_name><member_id>8664561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351648911000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350433797000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Bhopal: Second Disaster" - A Photo Exhibition by Alex Masi</name><id>87297472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351638000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/87297472/</event_url></item>