<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Cambridge</address_2><address_1>738 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-2685</phone><name>Cantab Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>274611</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105023</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>let's meetup at the cantab lounge in central square, cambridge, at 9:00 pm on thursday night, 2 july, to listen and dance to the music of the chicken slacks, a great soul, funk, and r&amp;amp;b band.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i know you're all off on friday, 3 july, so why not kick off the holiday weekend by dancing our asses off all night?  (i consider it a preemptive strike against all the eating i'll do over the weekend.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you haven't seen them before, you should know that the chicken slacks will get you moving, not only with their rousing covers of songs we all know, but also with great songs you never knew as well as their own original material.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;wherever they play, it's &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; a great show, but the chicken slacks at the cantab?  that's special.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;in last week's Weekly Dig, justin, the slacks drummer and founder, summed up the slacks at the cantab perfectly:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'&amp;quot;You check any bullshit and attitude at the door, and enter the timeless world of the local juke joint,&amp;quot; says Slacks member Justin Berthiaume. &amp;quot;Our Thursday night scene is an unpretentious, sweaty crowd of youngs, olds, blacks, whites, guys, gals, newcomers, regulars,&amp;quot; he says, taking a breath. &amp;quot;Anybody and everybody that wants to smile and get their groove thing on.&amp;quot;'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so come on out and get your groove thing on.  it'll be a sweaty good time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;the band, the music&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for more on the band, check out the &lt;a href="http://www.chickenslacks.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Chicken Slacks web site&lt;/a&gt; and definitely read the &lt;a href="http://www.weeklydig.com/%5Bcatpath%5D/200906/funky-stuff" target="_blank"&gt;Weekly Dig's take&lt;/a&gt; on the band.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;also check out &lt;a href="http://www.thenoise-boston.com/content/view/217/17/" target="_blank"&gt;this review of their latest cd&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;details&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the cover charge for this show is $5.  also note that the cantab is &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;cash only&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; but there is an ATM inside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you come to the show, please text or call me to find me, preferably text. i do wander around and look for folks (so it really helps if you posted a good picture of yourself), but texting me is the way to find me.  as noted above, i'll send out an email with my cell number to all 'Yes' and 'Maybe' RSVPers late thursday afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the cantab can get really crowded, so please be understanding if we can't all be in the exact same area.  i will get there early to try to grab the limited table space, but if anyone else can get there early, please join me in lying across the tables to reserve them....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you're driving to the show, note that there are street parking spots in the area (metered spots are free after 6 pm) and there are also a couple of small parking lots behind the cantab.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;there's also a &lt;a href="http://www.cambridgema.gov/traffic/OffStreetParking.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;city of cambridge municipal garage&lt;/a&gt;, located at the corner of pearl and green streets, less than a five minute walk from the cantab. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you're taking the T, the Central Square Red Line stop is just a block away from the cantab.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>i'll email a cell # to everyone who RSVPs 'Yes' or 'Maybe' by 2 July, 5 p.m.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247179893000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244482410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Chicken Slacks @ The Cantab Lounge</name><id>10604392</id><headcount>34</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246582800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/10604392/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/7/5/global_6848933.jpeg</photo_url></item>