<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lang Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.898380</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>237586</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.701836</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We hike at Northwest Park a lot, so for those who are able, let's lend them a hand with some spring cleaning. Volunteers will help with litter cleanup, trail repair, butterfly and organic garden work, and planting shrubs as part of Earth Day Action Week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Northwest Park provides all of the tools and supplies. Volunteers are asked to bring their own work gloves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start time is 9:00, so we're asking our group to meet at 8:45 at our usual place in the parking lot and then we can report as a group to the nature center at 9:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be doing some pond clean-up, but they have assured me that we will not get our feet wet, and also planting trees.  It is estimated that our project will take 2 to 2 1/2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No special equipment needed, but dress for the weather and you may want work gloves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The park will provide snacks and beverages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants are invited to an Earth Day concert at 2:00 and free passes will be handed out to those who volunteer.  If you want to stay for the concert, you can feel free to pack a lunch or go home for lunch and clean-up and then come back to the concert.  If we have the group we expect and are done before noon, I'd be open to a little picnic and a short hike before the concert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

I'll need to register us for this event, so I'm cutting off registration a couple of days before and please, if you sign up, show up, as we'll be counting on you to help.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot at 8:45 so we can report as a group at 9:00</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366499942000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363471778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Work Day at Northwest Park</name><id>109591502</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366461900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/109591502/</event_url></item>