<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail:&lt;/strong&gt; Pumpelly Trail &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Hike starts:&lt;/strong&gt; 10am &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate (The trail is 4.5 miles, for 9 miles round-trip, but we will do less without hitting the peak due to snow cover. Maybe 5 hours or less at a group pace?) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Trail information:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html"&gt;http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/trav-rec/mt_monad/mmpumpelly.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's try yet again! There's snow on the peak, but we can go most of the way, and a long part of this trail is above the treeline, anyway! It will be &lt;strong&gt;great weather&lt;/strong&gt;...not even any nighttime freeze starting Sunday, then in the 60s all week! (So at least 50s up there!) That should clear the trail a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear boots or hightops to keep your feet from getting wet and muddy from all the melted snow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pumpelly Trail is a &lt;strong&gt;longer, easier trail&lt;/strong&gt; that traverses the eastern ridge. It spends half its length above the treeline, with fantastic views! It's not steep, like the White Dot/Cross trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boots or hightops are strongly recommended.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress in layers, for cool weather with light wind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring lunch and enough to drink.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For safety, on mountains, always bring a flashlight or headlamp in case of ome emergency that slows you down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be aware I may not see morning emails/RSVPs; I'll be gone before 7:30am. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Google Maps, enter, "&lt;em&gt;E Lake Rd, Dublin, NH&lt;/em&gt;" (&lt;strong&gt;without&lt;/strong&gt; "&lt;em&gt;Pumpelly Trail&lt;/em&gt;"). Alternatively, enter, "&lt;em&gt;Barney Rd, Dublin, NH&lt;/em&gt;" (because the trailhead is &lt;strong&gt;just east&lt;/strong&gt; of this private road).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I imagine most members would take Route 2 East or West to get to 202. (If so, it is Exit 19.) Take Route 202 North into New Hampshire. At the center of Jaffrey, go straight onto Route 137 North. This will take you past the park entrance for the White Dot/White Cross trails. At Route 101 (maybe 10-15 minutes?), turn left to head west.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The center of Dublin is not far on 101. It's rather obvious...instead of a light, there is a &lt;strong&gt;rotary&lt;/strong&gt; at the center of this tiny town. Then, ignore the first brown "Monadnock State Park" sign. Across from the &lt;strong&gt;second&lt;/strong&gt; brown sign, both Snow Hill Rd and E Lake Rd are on your left. The "&lt;em&gt;E Lake Rd&lt;/em&gt;" sign is covered by foliage. Just look for the 2nd brown Monadnock sign, and &lt;strong&gt;don't take a sharp left...go diagonally left&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E Lake Rd becomes &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lake Rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; somewhere before the trailhead. #59, a private residence, is shortly before the trailhead. &lt;strong&gt;The trailhead is on the left,&lt;/strong&gt; then there is a stone pillar with #97 marking a private residence. (&lt;em&gt;Google Maps does &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; recognize these addresses!&lt;/em&gt;) There is also a cabin/cottage on the right slightly after the trailhead. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barney Rd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is on the left after that, so if you pass it, you've gone too far. Parking is on the side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;F.Y.I., the drive from Worcester is about 2 hours, 1.5 hours from Fitchburg/Leominster area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be driving up 290 and 190 and passing through the Fitchburg/Leominster area. So if anyone wants to make a carpool, please comment below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a white Dodge Stratus, and I'm short with dark brown, curly hair.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320883752000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320379164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pumpelly Trail @ Mt Monadnock (Rescheduled from Oct 28)</name><id>39904262</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320850800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/39904262/</event_url></item>