<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1033 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.351951</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.787.4242 </phone><name>Brown Sugar</name><city>Boston</city><id>906361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121927</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I, Mark Shar, will be presenting "The Neuroscience of Trauma as an Argument for the Elimination of Government and for the 'Instituting' of a 100% Voluntary Society"...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will argue that given what we know about trauma and the way it can incapacitate us physically, emotionally, and psychologically -- that it can incapacitate our ability to think, let alone rationally -- is reason enough for the elimination of all violence from any and all interpersonal relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that government, by its very nature, must go. It means that all the best interpersonal or societal structures to be considered "best" must be 100% voluntary. Even Rand's conceptualization of government doesn't meet the 100% voluntary requirement. Only a true free market, in everything, does.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By defining trauma, showing how it operates to hinder the best in us, our ability to think and reason, ... by showing how it can twist and contort perception, how it can deaden us to the harm we may be doing our fellow human beings ... I hope to show that government, or any organization that is not 100% voluntary is creating an atmosphere that fosters traumatic responses, thereby hindering us in our ability to think and reason -- and live lives proper to that of human beings qua human beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at Noon on Jan. 29, 2012 at the Brown Sugar Cafe on Commonwealth Ave in Boston for as brief a presentation as I can make -- followed by a lively discussion and great camaraderie. All non-violent, free-of-the-initiation-of-force criticisms, questions, witticisms, confusions, exasperations, metaphors, epanalepses, cheers, jeers, hyperboles, etc. are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the intellectually and spiritually adventurous -- with just a bit of time available :-) -- I recommend reading Scaer's &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Body Bears the Burden&lt;/span&gt; and Perry and Szalavitz's &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Boy Who Was Raised as a Dog&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Born for Love: Why Empathy is Essential and Endangered&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our familiar faces... perhaps this time we'll have a sign "Meetup Group" or ask a waiter/waitress</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Shar</member_name><member_id>9291676</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327947073000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326257219000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Neuroscience of Trauma as an Argument for the Elimination of Government and</name><id>47613392</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327856400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/47613392/</event_url></item>