<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correct map:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=Administration+Road%2C+Ware%2C+MA"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?q=Administration+Road%2C+Ware%2C+MA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; (The tower is uphill from the rotary...more west of where the map shows the marker. There's no real address I can enter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather alert:&lt;/strong&gt; It is supposed to rain; however, I don't know how hard it will be raining in the morning. I &lt;strong&gt;really need this&lt;/strong&gt; after the Mt. Monadnock hike, so I will go if it is a light rain. &lt;em&gt;Please check this event before leaving your house...I will make a decision by 8am.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Intermediate...&lt;em&gt;I want to keep a good pace on this walk...I need a good stretch!&lt;/em&gt; (4.25 miles, paved road, with one long, steep hill.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Quabbin Park, off Route 9 at the south end of Quabbin Reservoir, has &lt;strong&gt;spectacular&lt;/strong&gt; views! From the tower, you can see much of the 18-mile reservoir, Connecticut, New Hampshire (including Mt. Monadnock), Vermont, and New York. Bring quarters if you want to use the binoculars. The tower is uphill from a rotary on "Administration Road" per Quabbin maps ("Quabbin Hill Rd" and "Old Ware-Enfield Road" on Google Maps). There is plenty of parking at the tower, plus bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the tower, we will drive a short distance to Enfield overlook, one of the most beautiful spots in Quabbin Park. It overlooks the former location of the town of Enfield, as well as Prescott Penninsula. From there, we'll hike up through the rotary, then down a long, steep hill (with a couple of lookouts, one with spots to sit) to the DCR boat cove. (I often see bald eagles near the boat cove or dams.) Then we will continue past the spillway and over Winsor Dam, which terminates at the Visitor's Center. We can rest, eat lunch, use the restrooms, and (if anyone wants) flip through binders of photos and newspaper clippings. We will then retrace our steps to Enfield overlook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I break for bald eagles!&lt;/strong&gt; It is rare to see them for more than a couple minutes, but in the case any hang around, I will turn into an incurable shutterbug! (And yes, interrupt my stretch.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking information:&lt;/strong&gt; Quabbin Reservoir is a public water supply. No pets, swimming, or wading are allowed. Trash is "carry in, carry out" although there are receptacles in restrooms at the Visitor's Center and lookout tower. (There is also an outhouse at Enfield Overlook.) Wear comfortable shoes, a raincoat, and bug repellant, and bring a lunch and water. I highly recommend a camera!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;From the East&lt;/em&gt;, follow Route 9 through Ware, MA. After downtown there will be a couple of steep hills. At the bottom of one hill, on the right, is a pulloff with a wooden barrier, where fishermen often park. Slow down...take the East Entrance on the right after a curve. Drive a few miles to the rotary, turn uphill 2/3 of the way around, and park. (If you miss it the entrance, take the Middle Entrance 1.5 miles further on your right to the rotary, then take the first right uphill to the tower.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the West&lt;/em&gt;, go through Belchertown. Pass the West Entrance with the blue State Police sign. The Middle Entrance is 1.5 miles further on the left. From the Middle Entrance, follow the road to the rotary and take your first right to go uphill to the tower. (If you miss it, continue to the East Entrance 1.5 miles further on your left. Turn uphill 2/3 of the way around the rotary.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From North or South&lt;/em&gt;, take Route 202 to Route 9 East; &lt;em&gt;or, from the North&lt;/em&gt;, take Route 32A South to Route 9 West. Continue as above.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The lookout tower is uphill from  the Rotary on Administration Road. Take the East or Middle entrance for Quabbin Reservoir off Route 9  to get there.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317160457000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316649838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last-minute Friday Hiike: Quabbin Park, the lookout tower at Quabbin Hill</name><id>34491032</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316786400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/34491032/</event_url></item>