<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mysticism refers to &amp;quot;the pursuit of achieving communion with, identity with, or conscious awareness of the ultimate reality , the divine, or God through direct experience.&amp;quot;  A mystic is one who seeks to move far beyond dogma or belief and into a loving relationship with God at the center of their being.  All of the major world religions have always had their mystics and their mystical, on inner, paths.  Buddhism has Zen, Islam has Sufism, Hinduism has contemplative Yoga, Judiasm has Kabbalah, and Christianity has Christian mysticism.  Some well known mystics are St. John of the Cross, St. Teresa of Avila, Rumi and Paramahansa Yogananda.  Mysticism is the territory where the seeming differences in all of the religions fall away and only the truths, which are shared, remain.  It is the realm of experience, peace and love.  If you have always felt drawn to move past dogma and into the essential truth of things, if you are looking to deepen your experience of Gods love and of peace and balance, than you will love this seminar.  Welcome to a powerful look at mysticism and the mystical life. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183384966000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181659199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Mysticism and the Mystical Life</name><id>5882614</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183212000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/5882614/</event_url></item>