<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Higby is a wonderful staple hike in this area.  It provides views of the countryside and the surrounding mountains to the west.  The hike from the trailhead to the first vista on the ridgeline takes perhaps 20 minutes to a half an hour.  From that point, the trail continues to the north, following the edge of the trap-rock ridge much of the way, and it's nearly all &amp;quot;view&amp;quot;, until it descends into a minor depression, and then back up again.  This part of the trail is much less traveled than the more accessible parts, and is consequently the hand of man is less evident here.  The trail continues until the final rock-encrusted vista, which is near the rest stop on I-91 just north of Meriden.  The hike is approximately 4 miles in length, and should take a little over 2 hours in full.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trailhead to Mount Higby lies on Rt 66 on the  Meriden and Middlefield border.  The most strait forward route lies in getting off of I-91 in Meriden at East Main St.  As you follow this east, you'll see the traprock ridges ahead, and route 66 running in between them.  E. Main will merge into Rt 66 here.  You'll notice as you come to the top of the incline that there's a parking lot for the trailhead on your left, but it's blocked from this side by the median.  Continue until you come to the stop light ahead (near Guida's Ice Cream and a taxidermist), and make a U-turn here.  We'll meet up at the trailhead at 11 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Skinner (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/4429379/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) is leading on this one so please direct questions to him. Thanks Adam for leading!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187622391000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187152761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Mt. Higby in Middlefield CT</name><id>6183090</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187449200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6183090/</event_url></item>