<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>382 Walnut St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.327189</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish UU Church Brookline</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1293940</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.130638</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>149.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi All,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I wanted to tell you about a workshop I’ll be leading on Saturday, July 10 (the last one that I'll be leading before leaving for Oregon) that I think you'll enjoy and benefit from.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of you have told me that you wanted a better understanding of Neuro-Linguistic Programming (and how to use it) without enrolling in a 6-month certification program.  Well, your wish has come true!&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What:   Powerful Tools for Personal Change: An Intensive Introduction to NLP (Neuro-Linguistic Programming)&lt;br /&gt;Date:    Saturday, July 10, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time:    9:30am - 5:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Place:   First Parish UU Church in Brookline, 382 Walnut St, Brookline 02445&lt;br /&gt;Tuition: $149 ($99 if paid by July 2)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this one-day interactive and stimulating workshop, you will learn and practice the following key concepts:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rapport building: simple and effective ways to create and maintain connection with others&lt;br /&gt;- Setting outcomes: powerful techniques for goal setting&lt;br /&gt;- Behavioral flexibility / Anchoring: processes for enhancing your internal state, wherever/whenever you need it&lt;br /&gt;- Sub-modalities: the underlying structure of our experience, and powerful tools to change those experiences&lt;br /&gt;- NLP operating model: how NLP morphs from just a collection of techniques into a process for personal change&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to advanced NLP topics: get a sense of what else is possible with NLP&lt;br /&gt;- Integration: putting it all together&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the end of the day, you will have both a useful framework for how to apply NLP, and tools to help yourself and others create personal change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Attendance is limited to 30, so if you are interested please register soon,&lt;br /&gt;- Tuition is $149, but I'm offering a steep early bird discount ($99!) if you register by July 2.&lt;br /&gt;- There are a limited number of scholarships and work-study positions available - please inquire if interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Please forward this to anyone who might want to learn more about NLP. **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to email (adam@NewLightNLP.com) or call (617-329-1657) if you have questions about how this workshop would be useful for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the Best,&lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx&lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner&lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP&lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;www.NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;(617) 329-1657&lt;br /&gt;317 N. Main St, Natick MA 01760&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;- Becoming your best self in times of transition:&lt;br /&gt;Counseling, Coaching, and Training&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter in the lower street entrance (not the front of the church).  The Dana room will be the first room on your left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278772928000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276059713000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One-Day Intensive Introduction to NLP</name><id>13745584</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278768600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/13745584/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/0/global_11885328.jpeg</photo_url></item>