<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the wonders of late 20th century world cinema was the sudden wave of extremely talented directors who emerged in Taiwan during the 1980s, an incredible efflorescence that essentially reinvented a national cinema where only its pale shadow had previously existed. Yet, despite the international acclaim given to the leading directors of the so-called New Taiwan Cinema, , their films rarely screened outside of festivals. HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of these films never screened in the U.S. The Harvard Film Archive will be presenting 10  films by directors Edward Yang and Wu Nien-jen in September. Edward Yang's last film , &lt;b&gt;Yi Yi&lt;/b&gt;, was awarded Best Director at Cannes in 2000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Taipei Story&lt;/b&gt; (Qingmei Zhuma)&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Edward Yang. &lt;br /&gt;Taiwan 1985, 35mm, color 110 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edward Yang's brilliant &lt;b&gt;Taipei Story&lt;/b&gt; starts with an empty, open space, an apartment that a couple is considering. It's an everyday, commonplace scene, yet Yang somehow imbues it with a palpable yet subtle sense of discomfort, of things being incomplete and in a state of change -- but whether the change is for the better or the worse is hard to pinpoint, and the audience senses the incompleteness that the characters themselves are feeling. Yang is a master at creating tension from such settings, and at using visuals to get at the inner lives of his characters; indeed, in Taipei, Qin's sunglasses at times become a character in their own right (or rather an expression of part of Qin's character). Taipei's people are rootless and unsatisfied, seeking a self-definition that seems forever beyond their reach, and there's a sadness and an anger that lurks beneath their surfaces. They sometimes mask their emotions with remoteness or placidity, but the confusion and discontent remain nonetheless. All of this may sound like heavy going, but Yang's touch, while deliberate, is not overpowering, and he infuses the film with humor (especially of the ironic sort). If things are not tied together neatly, they still fit together in a way that feels inevitable and right. Taipei is a challenging and at times difficult film, but it is richly rewarding.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the film’s English-language title (assigned by Yang himself) deliberately echoes Ozu, its restrained exploration of urban malaise is better compared to Antonioni. What&lt;b&gt; Taipei Story&lt;/b&gt; has in common with both Ozu and Antonioni is a concern for the moral and intellectual lassitude and pervasive disillusionment that gradually takes hold in the wake of an economic boom.  HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note&lt;/b&gt; After &lt;b&gt;Taipei Story&lt;/b&gt; The HFA will also be screening exerpts from his uncompleted last film, &lt;b&gt;The Wind&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will be going to a local eatery for our group discussion. If you can not make it to  this one, here's the link to the HFA's schedule: &lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/films/2008septoct/yang.html#taipei" target="_blank"&gt;http://hcl.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be holding a Meetup Sign near the front row</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221527732000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219277652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edward Yang's Taipei Story </name><id>8587797</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221346800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8587797/</event_url></item>