<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 8:00 tomorrow, so &lt;b&gt;let's meet right inside the doors BY 7:30&lt;/b&gt;. Then we can buy tickets and snacks and head into the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets, as always, are $8.50 for FMM members and their guests. This includes the $1 fee per person for the Meetup. Seeing as how tickets now are $10.25, your deal is even better than it was! I also have small popcorn and small soda vouchers for $3 each.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW, we're getting a few people lately who have RSVPed yes and then not showed up. So that we don't all wait for you needlessly, if you know you're not coming, please call me at 508-308-4897. We won't have hurt feelings; we know things come up. I just really need an accurate head count so that we don't wait around an extra 20 minutes for someone who's not showing. I know you understand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you're a Maybe and know you're going to make it, give me a call, too. 508-308-4897. We don't usually wait too too long for the Maybes if the Yeses have shown up, but we are perfectly willing to wait for someone I &lt;b&gt;know&lt;/b&gt; is coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Same goes for if you're going to be late or got lost. I'm good with directions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, if your yes/no/maybe changes, please log  it on the site. If you can't (I cut off RSVPs 2 hours before the meetup), just call me. If you're running late, please call me. 508-308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at Slumdog Millionaire tomorrow! Everyone says it's a GREAT movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Hi, there, Movie Lovers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Holidays!!! (Happy Hanukkah, Merry Christmas, Happy New Year and happy whatever other winter holiday you celebrate!) Also happy 18&amp;quot; of snow. White Christmas, indeed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our site has gotten a colorful facelift. Let's say I brought it to the Chanel counter in Neiman-Marcus and got it a makeover. &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/polls/163225/"&gt;Tell me what you think about it in this poll.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, I've slightly changed the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/polls/155334/"&gt;poll about the craft day&lt;/a&gt; here. If you've answered yes or maybe to that poll before, please let me know who you are!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay, now down to business. &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809956055/info"&gt;Slumdog Millionaire&lt;/a&gt; has won lots of awards, and started out as a small-release type of artsy-fartsy movie, but now has gotten such traction it's in wide release. So how about we find our inner Indian (hi, Manish!) and go find that love that got away! Here's the summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;The story of Jamal Malik, an 18 year-old orphan from the slums of Mumbai, who is about to experience the biggest day of his life. With the whole nation watching, he is just one question away from winning a staggering 20 million rupees on India's &amp;quot;Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?&amp;quot; But when the show breaks for the night, police arrest him on suspicion of cheating; how could a street kid know so much? Desperate to prove his innocence, Jamal tells the story of his life in the slum where he and his brother grew up, of their adventures together on the road, of vicious encounters with local gangs, and of Latika, the girl he loved and lost. Each chapter of his story reveals the key to the answer to one of the game show's questions. Intrigued by Jamal's story, the jaded Police Inspector begins to wonder what a young man with no apparent desire for riches is really doing on this game show? When the new day dawns and Jamal returns to answer the final question, the Inspector and sixty million viewers are about to find out...&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll go to the 7ish show, but details about times will be updated a few days before the meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have discount tickets, which are especially valuable bc ticket prices at AMC Framingham just went up to $10.25 while I wasn't looking. Our tickets are $8.50/person (including any guests/friends you may want to bring) and that includes the $1/person/meetup fee. As always, I have $3 small popcorn and $3 small soda vouchers for anyone who's interested. Exact change makes me like you more. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you next Tuesday! And don't forget to vote in those 2 polls!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we get a nice big group, there could be some fun games at Friday's after the movie... Stay tuned!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231126179000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230052000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slumdog Millionaire</name><id>9380429</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230683400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9380429/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>