<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Philosophy Meetup 4/10/05: Plato's Apology (of Socrates)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(A) What is philosophy?  &lt;br /&gt;(B) And who or what is the philosopher?  These will be our two main guiding questions as we consider what Plato is trying to tell us in this, one of his most famous and important dialogues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a brief synopsis of the dialogue and its main points, we'll try to raise and consider a number of questions to complement your own &lt;br /&gt;(re-)reading of the dialogue:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) How and for what reasons did Socrates come to stand trial?&lt;br /&gt;2) If you were his attorney, how would you advise your client?&lt;br /&gt;3) How does Socrates defend himself against the charges?&lt;br /&gt;4) How does Socrates respond to the verdict and why?&lt;br /&gt;5) Towards the end of the dialogue, Socrates suggests that those who voted against him have harmed themselves a great deal more than they've harmed him.  What does he mean by that, and to what extent do you agree or disagree?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The format is informal and conversational.  That is, where we go and how we get there is completely dependent on the audience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reading the dialogue beforehand is helpful, but not essential.  If you haven't read the dialogue yet, there are a number of decent translations available online as well as in most bookstores.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy and see you Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erick&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have the time (and luck), the one I recommend the most is the one found in Thomas and Grace West's &amp;quot;Four Texts on Socrates: Plato's Euthyphro, Apology, and Crito and Aristophanes' Clouds.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to an ok (but not great) translation of the Apology:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://pd.sparknotes.com/philosophy/apology" target="_blank"&gt;http://pd.sparknotes....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And to help orient you around the dialogue, here are a couple of links that I've found useful:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ablemedia.com/ctcweb/netshots/apology.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://ablemedia.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sparknotes.com/philosophy/apology/summary.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sparknotes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1111356517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Apology!</name><id>4455550</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1113166800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/4455550/</event_url></item>