<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>103 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06442</zip><lat>41.348319</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 436 9449</phone><name>Ivoryton Playhouse</name><city>Ivoryton</city><id>991948</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.442000</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ONLINE SPECIAL</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Join the CT Theatre Group on Thursday August 13  for Neil Simon's Classic The Odd Couple at The Historic Ivoryton Playhouse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet before and after the show for wine or coffee, meet the CT Theatre Group guests, and to talk Arts and Theatre at the Tuskan Restaurant at the Ivoryton Inn, which is down the street from the Ivoryton Playhouse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The food is excellent and inexpensive, and they will give members of The CT Theatre Group a free glass of wine with each dinner. We will meet there from 6:00 to 7:15, the show starts at 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Neil Simon’s The Odd Couple on Thursday August 13 at The Beautiful Historic Ivoryton Playhouse – get you tickets today while they last! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Odd Couple&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Lawrence Thelen&lt;br /&gt;By Neil Simon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the play, compulsive neatnik Felix Unger is thrown out of his house by his divorce-bound wife. and gravitates to the apartment of his best friend, incorrigibly sloppy sportswriter Oscar Madison. Worried that Felix will try something desperate, Oscar, himself in the process of being divorced by his wife, invites Felix to move in with him. Within a few days, this mismatched pair is on the verge of mutual murder: Felix cannot abide Oscar's slovenliness, while Oscar is driven insane by Felix's obsession with cleanliness&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To listen to the Ivoryton Playhouse interview on Spotlight on Connecticut&lt;br /&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.SpotlightonCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Spotlighto...&lt;/a&gt; ), &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit: &lt;a href="http://www.spotlightonct.com/Jacqueline-Hubbard-Ivoryton-Playhouse-Past-and-Present.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spotlighto...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in Ivoryton, CT just 15 minutes from Middletown &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ivoryton Playhouse &lt;br /&gt;103 Main Street &lt;br /&gt;Ivoryton, CT 06442 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $35 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Special: Get Your Ticket for $30 Online!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888 for tickets or info &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The voices come to low hush and then nothing but silence fills the Theatre as the lights begin to dim. The curtain lifts and all eyes are on stage. The audience is taken on an adventure, a tale brought to life. &lt;br /&gt;Be part of the audience...be part of the Connecticut Theatre Group, where people who enjoy the Theatre can meet others with the same love for the Arts and Theatre! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a member of the CT Theater Group, you will receive an email when an event is coming up – there’s no fee, no obligation…but you will want to respond and get your ticket quickly, before things sell out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We always combine being an audience with some social fun, so feel welcome to join us after each show to chat about what we have seen and to get to know one another… &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet before the show, and then again after the show for wine, coffee, and conversation. Location and time will be emailed to all CT Theatre Group ticket holders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit us &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888 and enjoy a great night of Theatre with new friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE YOU AT THE SHOW&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet before and after the show - we will email you the meetup location</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Connecticut Theatre Group Events</member_name><member_id>8868299</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250377545000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245953249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Join the CT Theatre Group on Thursday August 13 2009 for The Odd Couple</name><id>10734777</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250204400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/10734777/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/f/global_9339071.jpeg</photo_url></item>