<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Revolve Nation's Green &amp;amp; Sustainable Business Group -- Boston Chapter&lt;br /&gt;Attend this meeting with Green Business Leaders to discuss the issues facing emerging businesses with sustainable models, services, and products. At this meeting you will have the opportunity to meet, collaborate and network with other &amp;quot;Green&amp;quot; and sustainable businesses to discover opportunities to work together, partner, and support the development of an emerging industry!! Bring your ideas and challenges to the table and share them with other entrepreneurs in an engaging discussion on the issues facing Green businesses today! Be sure to bring your business cards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then! Space is limited, so RSVP today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;6pm-6:30pm Open Networking over Wine &amp;amp; Cheese &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30-7:45 Discussion Group on selected topics offered by members and relevant to sustainable business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:45-8pm Networking &lt;br /&gt;Send me your questions and I will select several to be discussed with the group during the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPONSORS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.revolvethis.com" target="_blank"&gt;Revolve, Inc  (www.revolvethis.com) &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.exemplarlaw.com" target="_blank"&gt;Exemplar Law Group, LLC (www.exemplarlaw.com) &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the stiff in the suit</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238016639000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>smallbiz-1186</urlname><id>1252936</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation: Boston's Green and Sustainable Business Grp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233768045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston's Green and Sustainable Business Grp (Revolve Nation) January Meetup</name><id>9672156</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235516400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/smallbiz-1186/events/9672156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/5/global_5114293.jpeg</photo_url></item>