<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Moody Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371522</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BU center for digital arts</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1463688</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236862</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;**UPDATE **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Big Shots Photography Series – with Clint Clemens &lt;br /&gt;When: - Tuesday – January 18, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time: - 6:30 p.m. – 8:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where: BU CDIA – Waltham Campus – Studio C&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Free!&lt;br /&gt;RSVP: events@cdiabu.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The CDIA Big Shots Photography Series would like to welcome Clint Clemens, who’s work in advertising photography has consistently won numerous awards, including Andies and Clios.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the course of his work, he travels many thousands of miles each year, shooting and interpreting the world as he sees it. He has a passion for cars and sports, and literally anything that moves. Join Clint on January 18 as he talks about his work, and discusses the reasons behind the current state of assignment photography in the digital age and where we can grow and benefit from the new era of imaging and distribution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clint’s photographs have been featured in many magazines including Communication Arts (cover), Lurzer’s Archive Magazine, Graphis, Photographis and Applied Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His account list over the last several years includes: Coke, Toyota, Prada, Porsche, Jaguar, Mercedes, BMW, Volvo, Volkswagen, Specialized Bikes, Conde Nast Women’s Sports and Fitness, The North Face, Asics, New Balance, Bell Helmets, Harley-Davidson, Chris Craft, Jeep Chrysler, NetJets, Nokia, Men’s Journal, Wrangler Jeans, Buell Motorcycles, Asics and Indian Motorcycles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clemens has developed a deep understanding of the HDR automotive process. Several years ago, he traveled the country giving presentations to major agencies with the &amp;#64257;rst advertising ready automotive CGI images. He has been one of the featured speakers at CGI conferences hosted by Spheron and Stern Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is sponsored by Canon Cameras through their exclusive Explorer’s of Light program.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295398075000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294366628000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The CDIA Big Shots Photography Series -- Clint Clemens</name><id>15952789</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295393400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/15952789/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/global_14013533.jpeg</photo_url></item>