<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 Church Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01247</zip><lat>42.696575</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Houghton Mansion</name><city>North Adams</city><id>2661231</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.107292</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>87.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has investigated the Houghton Mansion in North Adams, MA, knows that it is one of the premier haunted locations in the state, with good reason. It has a fascinating history and is very active.It has been featured on Ghost Hunters and Ghost Adventures. I've investigated there numerous times and have had memorable experienes. It was the first place where I saw a full-body apparition, and it was the place where I was first touched by a spirit. Several of the meetup members who went on last year's investigation also saw an apparition, in addition to a host of other first-hand experiences. It's a great place for capturing visual as well as auditory phenomena. Take a look at some of the photos members took last year, including an impressive light anomaly that we couldn't debunk. (See the photo album "Houghton Mansion Investigation, 2012" on the meetup Photos page.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have booked the mansion for the entire night of Saturday, April 27th.The investigation is from 7pm to 7am, and you'll want to stay the entire time, there's so much to experience.  You can bring a sleeping bag and sleep there, if you choose. You can read about the mansion and its history at its website: &lt;a href="http://houghton-mansion.tripod.com/"&gt;http://houghton-mansion.tripod.com/&lt;/a&gt; . Also, you can take a look at what the Ghost Adventures guys experienced at the mansion: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7xvNBiUrvs8"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7xvNBiUrvs8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a pretty steep expense for this event, but if you can affort it, you'll have a great time.Registration is $87.50 (includes the Paypal processing fee) for this because we don't yet know how many people will go. If we get more than 10 people (and I'm pretty sure we will), you'll get a $10 refund. The price includes dinner, coffee and other drinks, and snacks. If for any reason the event is canceled, you will receive a repayment via Paypal for the full amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're setting a cap of 20 members, plus the organizers, so you'll have a chance to investigate in small groups..  If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367319825000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361219057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Houghton Mansion Investigation, North Adams, MA</name><id>105210952</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367103600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/105210952/</event_url></item>