<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>564 Hammond Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02467</zip><lat>42.325344</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Longwood Cricket Club</name><city>Chestnut Hill</city><id>11126412</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.165184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Bruce Marshall Group live show treats their fans to a soaring ride as they rip through a catalog of original material that truly sets this band apart. They love to mix it up, whether it’s pulling off exciting jams that build with dynamics and layering, or playing the concise arrangements of their songs with discipline and taste. The sound defies categorization, slipping seamlessly around touches of Blues, R&amp;amp;B, Rock and Southern Boogie. The interplay between Bruce and longtime guitarist Dave Cournoyer is the heart and soul of their performances and they always deliver. The songs are mostly upbeat, but even those dealing with love lost and missed opportunities, carry an underlying sense of hope and optimism. The band continues to work tirelessly and must be experienced live to be fully appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bruce Marshall Group played for us in Feb. of 2011. We had over 180 people, many of which danced through the last song. Our members and guests loved this band!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't miss this terrific dance. $30 Guests, payable at the door. Jackets and Ties , Cocktail Attire. Coffee/Tea and Dessert included.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 See &lt;a href="http://www.longwoodcricket.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.longwoodcricket.com/&lt;/a&gt; for directions, including access to the parking lot. Do not park in the Chestnut Hill Mall parking lot. Free parking on the street or in the nearby T  Chestnut Hill Station D Riverside Line lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Visit &lt;a href="http://www.brucemarshall.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brucemarshall.com&lt;/a&gt; or click &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LrYsJKt1cX0" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LrYsJKt1cX0&lt;/a&gt; to hear them play Muddy Waters' I'm Ready and &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s6DN8hh1tpI" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s6DN8hh1tpI&lt;/a&gt; to hear Bruce Marshall's Slave to My Senses. Dance the night away!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben S.</member_name><member_id>5230699</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362017527000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358043585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Winter Blues Dance</name><id>99315702</id><headcount>180</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361667600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/99315702/</event_url></item>