<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come out to Temporada Latina for an amazing night of workshops and dancing! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;100% of the evening's profits will be donated to Chilean Relief efforts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**How to find us**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Angel:&lt;/b&gt;  Look for the Grey Fedora Hat.  If later than 8pm, then look for him at the reserved meetup tables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ellen:&lt;/b&gt;  Look for a scarf around her neck.  She'll be your friendly greeter at the front door of Temporada Latina!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ana:&lt;/b&gt;  I'll be arriving after 11 due to classes.  Look for the black lace gloves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************************&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April Genovese, salsa dancer, choreographer, and teacher extraordinaire, will be teaching 2 workshops at Temporada Latina. April rarely gets back to Boston so don't miss this incredible opportunity to experience her unique style, charisma and skill. April has worked in Boston, New York, Connecticut, San Francisco, and internationally. She has performed and danced with some of New York's finest Mambo dance companies, including Yamulee Dance Company, Eddie Torres, Descarga Latina, RAZZ M'TAZZ, Santo Rico Dance Company, and Stacey Lopez. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raul Nieves has been teaching at Temporada Latina since 1996 and has been co-owner of Dance Caliente for nearly 12 years. Raul possesses a contagious energy and a unique ability to invent new and unique strategies to help students understand dance and movement. Raul's goal is to impart the joy of partner dancing to all his students and he welcomes dancers of all abilities and levels. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here's the lineup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshop 1: Ladies Styling with April from 8-9 pm&lt;br /&gt;Graceful Body Movement, Elegant Arms, Effortless Head Whips, Creative Expression of your Femininity. Learn how to incorporate the above skills into your partner work. Men are welcome, and will be given male styling options on all material covered in class. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Workshop 2: Advanced Beginner/Intermediate Shines &amp;amp; Partnerwork w/ April from 9-10 pm&lt;br /&gt;Classic NY Style footwork and turn patterns. Leading and following technique, spin technique, and styling included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lesson: Beginners Salsa with Raul from 8:45-10&lt;br /&gt;Basic Salsa footwork, right and left turns, introduction to partnering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dancing w/ DJ Rob Suave from 10-1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COSTS (includes dancing from 10-1)&lt;br /&gt;One workshop with April: $15&lt;br /&gt;Two workshops with April: $25&lt;br /&gt;One lesson with Raul &amp;amp; Suzanne: $12&lt;br /&gt;Dancing only: $8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angel Santiago</member_name><member_id>5161614</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269130035000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266325147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lessons &amp; Dancing with Temporada Latina at Ryles</name><id>12616704</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268956800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/12616704/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/global_522835.jpeg</photo_url></item>