<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Simplify Your Life &lt;br /&gt;a workshop with Father Peter Bowes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If life is supposed to be simple, free and easy, why does it feel so complicated and overwhelming? Wouldn't it be nice to return to the carefree and loving nature of our youth? Life is simple when we forget about our problems, fears, worries, and doubts. Slowing the mind down and learning to breathe and relax is the most simple thing we can do to accomplish the most challenging of tasks. Learn to simplify your life by letting go of the complications that clutter the heart and mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Refreshments will be provided **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has devoted his life in service to God; for over 20 years, he has served as a Priest and Master Teacher. Currently, &lt;br /&gt;he serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding thirteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father &lt;br /&gt;Peter's music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Center of Light is located in Jamaica Plain just around the corner from the Stony Brook T stop on the Orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210462676000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206764429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Simplify Your Life</name><id>7625608</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210289400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/7625608/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/8/global_1017208.jpeg</photo_url></item>