<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>178 Kneeland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349682</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-350-0028</phone><name>South Street Diner</name><city>Boston</city><id>866420</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057804</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well we need some diversions in late Jan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets meet up for breakfast before at the South Street Diner at 10 am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Street Diner &lt;a href="http://www.southstreetdiner.com/menu.php" target="_blank"&gt;(Menu)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Street Diner &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;q=178+Kneeland+St+Boston,+MA+02111-2715&amp;amp;safe=active&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=178+Kneeland+St,+Boston,+Suffolk,+Massachusetts+02111&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;sqi=2&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;(Google Map)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Motorcycle Expo &lt;a href="http://www.kevmarv.com/expo.asp?type=show_boston" target="_blank"&gt;(Event Website)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a day pack for your coat, and some bottled water &amp;amp; snacks as you will pay an arm and a leg for them at the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the South Street Diner:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South Street Diner (formerly the Blue Diner) was built in 1947 by the WorcesterDining Company to serve local factory workers. Over the years, the Diner hasbecome a local landmark, a constant in Boston’s after-hours scene and a finalevening destination for local residents, students and visitors. When the clubsclose, the Diner is the place to grab something to eat, to hang out with friends,to celebrity watch, and to keep the party going. No visit to Boston is completewithout a stop to the South Street Diner.Over the years, the Diner has been named a “Best of Boston” by Boston Magazineand quoted as, “The PLACE for college students to start their Spring Break Tour” byRolling Stone Magazine. The Diner has also been featured in numerous feature films, including: Hiding Out with John Cryer; Second Sight with JohnLaroquette; House Guest with Steve Martin; and The Blue Diner for PBS.South Street Diner is currently owned and operated by local restraunteur, SolSidell. Sol grew up in the restaurant business and always dreamed of owning aplace where people could have fun, get great food at reasonable prices, and feellike a regular the first time they walk through the door. He brings his passionfor creating great dishes and making people happy to everything he does atSouth Street Diner. Today, South Street Diner is Boston’s only all-night dining destination openseven nights a week. While the neighborhood around South Street Diner hasevolved from factories producing shoes and hand bags, to an artist community,student mecca, and part of the city-wide Big Dig construction site, one thinghas remained unchanged – South Street Diner is Boston’s true diner, and theheart of Boston’s late night scene.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296344457000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294074326000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northeast Motorcycle Expo</name><id>15897954</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296313200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/15897954/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/0/global_20596688.jpeg</photo_url></item>