<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Organizer: Monica Trust (978)877-1119&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update 3/6/12 ***New meeting time and place**** I have decided to forgo hiking the Wildcats and making this hike a more moderate hike. I haven't figured out exact mile but it will be about 12-13 miles. I will update weather conditions and mileage in a couple of days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to&amp;nbsp;read the entire event description&amp;nbsp;before you RSVP and&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;answer all of the questions&amp;nbsp;that are part of the RSVP process&lt;/span&gt;. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - in that case update your RSVP from a computer to generate them again so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared to respond to an emergency situation or being able to send a night in the woods if you have to. Bring your own stuff (described below) and know how to use it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The plan is to hike 3 New Hampshire 4000 footers: &amp;nbsp;Middle Carter(#15 4610'), South Carter(#20 4420'), Carter Dome(#9 4832'). The Carter Range is located east of the Presidential Range, running northeast from Pinkham Notch into Maine. It is one of the highest and most massive of the White Mountain ranges, ranking behind only the Presidential, Franconia, and Twin ranges in elevation and interest to hikers. You will need to be prepared for&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;steep&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;snow-covered&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;icy&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We will we meet at the Nineteen Mile Brook Trailhead. This hike is considered a moderate hike and you should only consider it if you have been hiking similar trips regularly. Although our goal is to summit all three peaks, we will reassess if conditions and situations dictate we abort our plan.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&amp;nbsp;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are discouraged&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on this hike due to the nature of the hike and the sledding at the ending. If you have a dog with experience hiking in the winter and would like to bring him/her, please email me directly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&amp;nbsp;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for current weather conditions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. Mountaineering snowshoes with aggressive teeth for traction while climbing. Mountaineering crampons with 10-12 teeth that strap on are required for this trip - Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable as back-up only. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it. I will update as we get closer to the date if full crampons will be necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly draws heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket. Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants. Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens.&amp;nbsp;Goggles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead of a hydration bladder since the mouthpiece/tube can freeze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket which packs small and weighs just ounces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. &lt;strong&gt;Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries - lithium work best in colder temperatures.&lt;/strong&gt; Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our meeting spot will be Nineteen Mile Brook Trailhead to begin our hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.301968,-71.220903(Nineteen-Mile+Brook+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.301968,-71.220903&amp;amp;sspn=0.007571,0.01929&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFZD-owIdWUHB-w&amp;amp;oq=bos&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for directions to the Nineteen-Mile Brook trailhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; You agree not to hold the Organizer, Assistant Organizers, or any other members responsible for any injuries, mishaps, or any other situation that may happen at a planned event. You are responsible to research the event, know the area, and bring the proper gear and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in white or green Toyota Highlander - both have MA license plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330125990000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325734938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carters (moderate hike)</name><id>46735782</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328961600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/46735782/</event_url></item>