<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/8/e/event_192860622.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT Building 51, Room 335 &lt;span&gt;map -&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=E51"&gt;http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=E51&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;70 Memorial Drive, Cambridge, MA (Entrance at 2 Amherst Street)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Parking behind the building, or one block West off Amherst Street on Hayward)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Top 10 Predictions for 2013 -- Will Investment Opportunities Improve in a Risky World?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Presentation by Nariman Behravesh, Chief Economist for IHS Global Insight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nariman Behravesh will give his outlook on current economic trends and market risks.&lt;/span&gt;   In 2012, worldwide growth slowed to about 2.5%, and the Eurozone and Japan went back into recession.&lt;span&gt;  &lt;/span&gt; Several key economies have created massive monetary stimulus.&lt;span&gt;  &lt;/span&gt; We face extreme uncertainty due to the U. S. debt and deficits, the Eurozone debt crisis, slower growth in China, and instability in the Middle East and Africa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Yet, Dr. Behravesh is cautiously optimistic that world growth will stabilize in 2013, and growth will accelerate in the latter part of the year and during 2014.&lt;/span&gt;  Join the Boston Investors Group to hear a noted economist give his top 10 predictions for 2013, which explain his cautious optimism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bio of Nariman Behravesh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Nariman Behravesh is Chief Economist of IHS and author of &lt;em&gt;Spin-Free Economics: A No-Nonsense, Nonpartisan Guide to Today's Global Economic Debates&lt;/em&gt; (McGraw-Hill). Directing the entire economic forecasting process at IHS, he is responsible for developing the economic outlook and risk analysis for the United States, Europe, Japan, China and other emerging markets. He oversees the work of over 400 professionals, located in North America, Europe, Asia, Latin America, the Middle East and Africa who cover economic, financial, and political developments in over 200 countries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Behravesh is a "Bloomberg Best" and ranked as one of Bloomberg's Top Forecasters for 2009, 2010 and 2011.&lt;/span&gt;  He and his team have been rated among the top economic forcasters by MarketWatch, &lt;em&gt;USA Today&lt;/em&gt;, Reuters, and &lt;em&gt;The Wall Street&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Journal.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As the chief economics spokesperson at IHS, Behravesh is quoted extensively in the media on such topics as the outlook for the U.S. and global economies, exchange rates, the budget deficit, the trade deficit, globalization, country risk, and sovereign debt crises. He is cited frequently in leading business publications such as the &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;Financial Times&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;USA&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Today&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Investor's Business Daily&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Business Week&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Newsweek&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Fortune&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Forbes&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;U.S. News&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;and World Report&lt;/em&gt;. He also regularly appears on national radio and television programs including BBC World Business Report, NBC Nightly News, CNN Headline News, The News Hour with Jim Lehrer (PBS), Fox News, CNBC, Bloomberg TV and Radio, and All Things Considered and Market Place on National Public Radio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Behravesh holds Ph.D. and M.A. degrees in economics from the University of Pennsylvania, and a B.Sc. from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. He has lived in Europe and the Middle East, and is fluent in several languages. He travels extensively to Europe, Asia, Africa, and Latin America.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT Building 51, Room 315&lt;span&gt;  map -&amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=E51"&gt;http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=E51&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;70 Memorial Drive, Cambridge, MA (Entrance at 2 Amherst Street)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Parking behind the building, or one block West off Amherst Street)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you! Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room. We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358996719000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>123</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357318065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Speakers Meeting: IHS Global Chief Economist Nariman Behravesh</name><id>97885122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358294400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/97885122/</event_url></item>