<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>335 Bloomfield Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.801112</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-236-1927</phone><name>Mandell JCC </name><city>West Hartford</city><id>792616</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.724865</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for an evening of 3 films as part of the Hartford Jewish Film Festival!  Tickets are available by calling the JCC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartford Jewish Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;The Hartford Jewish Film Festival showcases films highlighting the international Jewish experience and is acclaimed as one of the foremost Jewish film festivals in North America because of the fine caliber of films offered and the unprecedented participation we receive from the greater Hartford area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tickets and Information&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Individual Tickets:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; $10 General admission; $9 Discount admissions for seniors 65+, students, Trinity College faculty, Mandell JCC members, Let’s Go card-holders and Wadsworth Atheneum film subscribers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$8 A Hero In Heaven 3/16 &amp;amp; Autism: The Musical 3/22&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5 Tribute: Observations on Survival and Spirit - &lt;br /&gt;Lessons of the Holocaust 3/23&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Special Programs:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; $50 Opening night film and reception&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Patron Passes:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; $350 Producer’s Circle Pass (includes admission to all films and events and includes a $152 charitable deduction)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$250 Director’s Circle Pass (includes admission to all films and events and includes a $52 charitable deduction)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$175 Senior (65+) Pass (includes admission to all films and events)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All JCC Grand Patrons receive free tickets. Patrons must order tickets and RSVP to all events.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;General Information:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Seating: Seating is not assigned. Seats are limited, so advance sales are recommended. Pass holders must arrive 15 minutes before screening on opening night to assure seating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refunds: Available only for cancelled or rescheduled programs. Due to circumstances beyond our control, all films are subject to change.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Purchasing Tickets:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; By phone with credit card: Call Festival Box Office (860-231-6316). MasterCard, Visa, Discover and American Express accepted&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By fax with credit card: Download Ticket Order Form and fax to JCC (860-233-0802).By mail: Mail order form with credit card # or check made payable to Mandell JCC, include stamped, self-addressed envelope and mail to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mandell JCC - Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;Zachs Campus&lt;br /&gt;335 Bloomfield Avenue&lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06117&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In person: At the Mandell JCC reception desk (860-236-4571). Visit www.mandelljcc.org for hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For films other than opening night, tickets will be available at each theater if not sold out. Tickets ordered at least 7 days prior to screening will be mailed. Tickets ordered less than seven days prior must be picked up at theater.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Click Here To Download Ticket Order Form&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Tuesday, March 17, 7:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Mandell JCC, West Hartford&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CORNER DELANCEY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;USA, 2006, 8 minutes, English&lt;br /&gt;Director: Neil Needleman&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In this bittersweet animated tale, an illustrator sketches key events in his family life to illuminate his relationship with his son.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; STEAL A PENCIL FOR ME&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;USA, 2007, 1 hour 34 minutes, English&lt;br /&gt;Director: Michèle Ohayon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Immediately following film &lt;br /&gt;Corner Delancey&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Click for film trailer&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jack and Ina Polak’s unlikely love affair begins illicitly in 1943 pre-war Netherlands, and continues through two concentration camps, liberation and new life in America. Married more than 60 years, their true story is a heartwarming and joyous affirmation of love’s power even in the worst of times. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yad Vashem Award, Jerusalem Film Festival&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; CIRCUMSIZE ME: The Comedy of Yisrael Campbell&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Israel, 2007, 48 minutes, English&lt;br /&gt;Directors: David Blumenthal &amp;amp; Matthew Kalman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Immediately following film &lt;br /&gt;Steal A Pencil For Me&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Click for film trailer&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“Is it hot in here, or am I the only one dressed for Poland in the 17th Century?” Yisrael Campbell, Israel’s funniest Hasidic comedian, started out as Chris Campbell, son of an ex-nun and a Catholic teacher in Philadelphia. Three conversions (Reform, Conservative and Orthodox) later, he discovered his Jewish soul in stand-up comedy.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's All Meet in the Art Gallery,  15-20 Min.. Prior to the 7  PM Start Time</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stuart</member_name><member_id>4565209</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256246743000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-2183</urlname><id>1179521</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Connecticut Jewish Singles:  35+ Social Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236741349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hartford Jewish Film Festival:  Three Films  Including "Circumsize Me"</name><id>9928921</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237330800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-2183/events/9928921/</event_url></item>