<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street/Moody Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.368141</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508)523-5238</phone><name>Waltham common</name><city>Waltham</city><id>398092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237442</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Every Tuesday this Fall we will meet for drinks (does not have to be beer or alcohol) and some food at a bar or restaurant in Waltham Center.  These meetups are a great way to find out about our ski club and meet skiers/ riders before the season gets going.  We are all about having fun and sharing good times so this is a perfect introduction to our Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have new people attending every week and we are always friendly to first timers.  The group will be small, usually between 8 to 12 people and we may grab a table or corner of a bar.  Some will also attend our Ski Fitness Training that takes places at Waltham Common at 6:30.  Yes, we may be a bit ripe from the workout but it is all about getting ready for the season - it was also make us easy to find, just look for the group in work-out clothes.  You do not have to attend the Ski Fitness Training to attend the Beer night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The actual bar will be chosen a week in advance and posted to this page.  All will be in the Waltham Center, Moody Street area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ps - does anyone have a suggestion for a better name?  &amp;quot;Waltham Tuesday Beer Night&amp;quot; just does not convey the true spirit of the gathering.   I hope to see you!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>actual Bar will be chosen about 1 week in advance, we will come from our Ski Fitness Training so just look for the groups they looks like they completed an intense workout</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288797989000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282016419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltham Tuesday Beer Night</name><id>rnrgpynpbdb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288742400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/15078217/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/5/global_10444549.jpeg</photo_url></item>