<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per dog</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi pug folks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group member, Betsy, and I have been trying to schedule an indoor meeting with the folks at The Good Dog Spot in Chicopee. It has been frustrating, but we've finally made contact and gotten the information about holding a meetup at their new location. Here's the scoop:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because they now have a bigger and better facility (and one in which clean-up is more difficult than it was last year due to their rubber floors), the fee for utilizing their venue is higher. We are a bit of a bigger group this year, so hopefully we'll be able to cover it. Unfortunately, though, we were not able to find a date in December that was feasible, so we will have to wait until after the New Year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next meetup will be Saturday, January 9, 2010 from 11am-1pm. The cost will be $5 per dog. We need AT LEAST 15 dogs at that rate to cover the $75 fee. This fee is, of course, in addition to the meetup fee. Please RSVP by January 3rd. If we don't have enough dogs to cover the fee, I will have to cancel our January meetup. If you RSVP &amp;quot;yes,&amp;quot; please do make every effort to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Good Dog Spot is now at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Good Dog Spot, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;35 C North Chicopee Street&lt;br /&gt;Chicopee MA 01020&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(413) 534-1333&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;info@gooddogspot.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you have questions. Best wishes for happy holidays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt;Marianna&lt;br /&gt;(organizer)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263321837000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Pug Owners and Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>westernMApugs</urlname><id>1207399</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western MA Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258661351000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Meetup!</name><id>11913665</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263052800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/westernMApugs/events/11913665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/c/global_4651788.jpeg</photo_url></item>