<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>113 Goodnow Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.455643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass Audubon's Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Princeton</city><id>3918582</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.905052</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Join Single Outdoor Adventurers of New England (Ages 30 - 50)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Wachusett Meadow is a beautiful place with a wide variety of habitats. Beaver ponds, vast meadows, woodlands, and wetlands. Wildlife is abundant in all seasons. We will hike around for a couple of hours and explore this beautiful place. This will be the last weekend event till late June.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  After the hike is over we will visit a local resturant/bar. MA Audubon charges a $4.00 admission for non members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Directions: &lt;br /&gt;

From Rt 2: Take exit 28 (Rt 31, Fitchburg/Princeton). Follow Rt 31 south for 3.9 miles to a blinking red light. Turn left at the light and follow Rt 31 and Rt 140 south for 1.8 miles to a blinking yellow light. Turn right and follow Rt 31 south for 2.8 miles to a steep hill and a blinking yellow light (center of Princeton). At the light, follow signs for Rt 62 west by crossing the intersection and bearing right (follow the road as it curves right on the far side of the common after the light). Follow Rt 62 west for 0.6 miles, and you will see the sanctuary sign on the right at Goodnow Road. Turn right on Goodnow Road, and the parking lot is 1 mile ahead on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  From Rt I-190:Take exit 5 (Rt 140, Sterling/W. Boylston). Follow Rt 140 north for 2.4 miles to the intersection of Rt 62 (blinking yellow light). Take a left onto Rt 62 west and follow it for 4.2 miles to a stop sign. Turn left on Rt 31 and go up the hill to a flashing yellow light (center of Princeton). Follow directions above from the "center of Princeton."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>13113337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368987377000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368748642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nature Hike at Wachusett Meadows Princeton MA</name><id>119787132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368975600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/119787132/</event_url></item>