<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Lexington Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06052</zip><lat>41.664328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.229.0257</phone><name>New Britain Museum Of American Art</name><city>New Britain</city><id>853476</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.792121</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ashford, Connecticut-based filmmakers Michael Maglaras and Terri Templeton of 217 Films will debut their new documentary &amp;quot;John Marin: Let the Paint be Paint!&amp;quot; at the New Britain Museum of American Art on Thurs., May 27, 5:30-8 p.m. At the Museum's red carpet event guests will indulge in extravagent sweets and savories and then preview the Marin documentary, the first full-length documentary about the father of American Modernism. Cocktails begin at 5:30 p.m., opening remarks at 6:15 p.m., film begins at 6:30 p.m.; reservations required, limited seating, tickets are $20 per person, contact Heather Whitehouse at (860) 229-0257, ext. 203 or at whitehouseh @ nbmaa. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;John Marin: Let the Paint be Paint!&amp;quot; tells the story of one of the most important artistic figures of the first half of the 20th century and the undisputed father of American Modernism. Utilizing more than 70 of Marin’s paintings, drawings, and etchings, including, those in the private collection of Norma Marin seldom seen anywhere, filmmaker Michael Maglaras tells the story of Marin's life, from his beginnings in New Jersey and his early experiments in watercolor, to his days at Cape Split in Down East Maine, where, with his late oils, he established himself as one of the preeminent masters of American art. Written, narrated, and directed by Michael Maglaras of 217 Films. 2009. Not rated. (95 min.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I may not be there. Will update later.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275010976000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272716770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Marin: Let The Paint Be Paint</name><id>13348018</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274995800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13348018/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>