<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>131 State St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358955</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 725-0100</phone><name>Kitty O'Sheas</name><city>Boston</city><id>709575</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a joint event with the Social Fun Meetup Group, the Happy Hour Meetup Group and the Boston Nightlife Meetup Group, and the Inquisitive Minds Meetup Group.  I'm probably not going to be able to make it, but members had so much fun at the last mix and mingle that I wanted to post the event again.  So, we won't be meeting as a group at the event, but I still encourage you all to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a Singles Party. Meaning anyone can come, including couples. All are welcome to Party and Socialize.  Kitty O'Sheas has 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathroom upstairs so this will be like a private party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will medium levels in main room upstairs. Music will be tuned very low in the back room so members can have a separate area to chat! &lt;br /&gt;At about 9PM the dancing and music starts, &lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 Bartender upstairs: 2 at the upfront Bar and 1 in the back . &lt;br /&gt;Some appetizers will be provided (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The entry fee is $5 to cover the cost to rent the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders +the DJ.  Please find Biagio at the party and please give Biagio the $5. (No one dollar bills please) If you don't know Biaggio, go to the Social Fun Meetup and his picture is listed as the organizer.  Or ask when you're there.  Some one will point you in the right direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you get inside there is a Security at the stairs please tell them you are with Social Fun to get in (Even if you are with a different group).  There were some issues last time and if you say you are with any other group they will not let you in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some things to keep in mind:&lt;br /&gt;1. Everyone, but the Social Fun Organizers and Invited groups Organizers pays $5. &lt;br /&gt;2. If you arrive after 9PM, you will have to pay another $10 as a cover charge for the Bar Entrance fee to get in so that $15 total. $10 to bar and $5 to cover the cost to rent the 2nd floor. &lt;br /&gt;3. If you get in before 9PM you only have to pay $5 to Biagio to cost to rent. Make sure you get there early! &lt;br /&gt;4. It will be packed. &lt;br /&gt;5. If you come after 7:30PM you might not even get in right away and will have to wait in line downstairs to go upstairs. So come at 7PM to get in. &lt;br /&gt;6. Tell Security you are with Social Fun to get in -Even if you are with a different group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: Because this is a joint event, we only have 40 spots.  So, if you RSVP with another group, don't RSVP for this group too.  Also if you RSVP and then later know you can't make it, please change your RSVP to a no so that other members can come.  Maybe RSVPs will be moved to NO RSVPs 1 week before the event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Biaggio</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272236679000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271157183000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix and Mingle (Joint Event)</name><id>13168039</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272063600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/13168039/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/3/global_7135059.jpeg</photo_url></item>