<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;What is a Content Management System and how can it simplify the creation and management of websites?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A content management system (CMS) is a way to automate updating of websites, quickly alternate between several website looks and add more complex functionality. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are a number of free CMS's (Drupal, Joomla, WordPress and others) out there and each one might be more useful depending on the purpose and complexity of the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; All content management systems are linked to a database where the website content is stored and allows the look, content, and functionality to be separate.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is &lt;i&gt;CMS Made Simple&lt;/i&gt; and how is it different than other CMS's?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cmsmadesimple.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;CMS Made Simple&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/a&gt;has the unique capability of automating the conversion of static html pages to the CMS.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Web Developer  will demonstrate how to set this up and has also found a hosting company that is affordable, has lots of space and allows the creation of new databases within minutes (&lt;i&gt;1 and 1&lt;/i&gt;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the group is small and people bring their lap tops he will help people install this either on a local or remote server. If you are installing on a remote server please create a database ahead of time with your database name, and password recorded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6:30- 7:00 snacking and mingling&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Refreshments&lt;/b&gt;: Snack provided, drinks and sandwiches can be purchased from Woodstar Café next door&lt;br /&gt;Suggested donation at the door: $5-10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; please RSVP to help us plan accordingly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Parking: on street after 6pm or paid lot across street&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:00-8:30 Presentation will include&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;brief discussion of: I will explain why I think Drupal and Joomla are more useful for a specific type of site, and why CMSMS handles smaller sites better in some ways than some of the other CMS. Problems that may come up with some of the other small open source content management systems.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Five aspects of converting a static website to the CMSMS that will be covered are: installation, conversion of website, editing of content, defining and using modules and templates. will also cover support for CMSMS (&lt;i&gt;CMS Made Simple&lt;/i&gt;) and how to choose hosting.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326922538000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263524315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tools to simplify the Creation and Managment of Small Websites</name><id>12324804</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267745400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/12324804/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/b/global_11475755.jpeg</photo_url></item>