<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1071 5th Avenue</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10128</zip><lat>40.782978</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum</name><city>New York</city><id>6512152</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.958870</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>99.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I know this group doesn't like to travel too far, but think of New York City as a mere half hour away for this trip. I welcome you to ride in style with me to New York City via the Currier Museum's Big Apple Express, a luxury coach with bathrooms and WiFi onboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Will We Get There and Back?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

In style, baby, in style. We'll park at the Catholic Diocese in Manchester (right by the Currier Museum), and board at 6:30AM. Be sure to get there on time or download that app on all the lovely places to visit while in Manchester for the day. We'll arrive at the Guggenheim on 5th Avenue around 11:30AM, and have the day to spend in NYC until re-boarding for the return trip at 7PM, arriving back in Manchester at 11:30PM and snug in your bed around midnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be riding a luxury coach with all the amenities on board, so the five hour trip will fly by. You may bring whatever you like, including food, drink, quiet entertainment, and can leave what you like securely on board while traipsing around the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Will We Do in New York?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

You are, of course, free to do whatever you like. Hit the Guggenheim and then Museum Mile; find the many waterfalls in Central Park; take a carriage ride; get the Naked Cowboy to sign your forehead in Times Square; take in a show; hit the top of the Empire State or the Top of the Rock; take in the views and hobnob with the Hoi Polloi at 230 5th's rooftop garden; find Grant's Tomb; buy a diamond necklace at Van Cleef &amp;amp; Arpels; enjoy a Circle Line or yacht charter around Manhattan; hit Ellis Island and the Statue of Liberty; meander through and figure out what SoHo, DUMBO, and TriBeCa stand for; or whatever you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, sorry, you cannot visit the photo meccas of B&amp;amp;H Photo or Adorama, they are closed Saturdays for the Sabbath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, you can tag along with me on one of my favorite NYC photo walks through the very southern tip of&amp;nbsp;Manhattan, mostly along the water, where there's something interesting around every corner. I also plan on hitting some of the &lt;a href="http://www.hellskitchenfleamarket.com/home/?page_id=77"&gt;Hell's Kitchen area outdoor bazaars&lt;/a&gt; for photo props and other goodies, with a side trip to the newly expanded raised &lt;a href="http://www.thehighline.org/"&gt;High Line Park&lt;/a&gt;. We'll group up on Metro Cards (four per card) to minimize the cost of speedy travel down and back. In case of inclement weather, I plan on hitting indoor facilities such as the Museum of Natural History and New York Public Library, some of which charge an entrance fee. Please note,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone else is welcome to put together another itinerary for others to follow - use the comment section or message board to work it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Many Arms and Legs will this Cost Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Very few, actually. The bus round trip is $95 ($75 for Currier members). Subway fare is $2.50 per trip. Food is actually cheaper in NYC than in Portsmouth, NH because of all the competition. The price on this meetup is padded a bit to cover PayPal costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a Currier member, email me after signup with your name and address as the Currier has it on record to get the discount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll batch-purchase tickets in groups of ten. If the trip is canceled, or there's no room for you (over 30 seats are available now), or you have a valid Currier membership, the entire or discount portion of your fee will be fully refunded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can save a couple bucks by purchasing your tickets directly through the Currier, but you will be ineligible for refunds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we don't have a minimum of six participants a week before the trip between our group and the CAPE group, we will likely cancel this event and refund your money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;What Should I bring?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Bring light layers of clothing, including a windproof and/or waterproof outer layer, especially if the weather is iffy or you're planning a trip on the water. It's about 10 degrees warmer in NYC than this area typically, and you can leave excess clothing in the bus if you bring too much - err on the side of caution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear very comfortable walking shoes - you'll be amazed at the miles you will walk without noticing it. For reference, 20 blocks equals about a mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring cash for purchases, noshing, entrance fees, and&amp;nbsp;souvenirs, though there are&amp;nbsp;plenty&amp;nbsp;of cash machines throughout the city. If you're planning on hitting a museum, visit your local library to see if they have free or&amp;nbsp;discounted&amp;nbsp;passes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your camera (duh!), plenty of battery power and memory cards, and the lightest kit you can muster. A good 18-200mm or fast 50mm lens is an excellent walk-around lens, and a sharp wide angle zoom will be your Big Apple friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to have your phone, as I'll ask for all numbers on the trip down so we have a way of communicating. If you have a smart phone, you may wish to grab one of the excellent subway or tourist apps available through your app store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why, Why, Tell Me Why!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This is a rare chance to visit New York as a group for a very low cost. Seriously, this is cheaper than taking the extended family to the movies. New York City is so full of photographic opportunities that you could do this trip every day of the year and never hit the same photogenic place twice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New York is not what is was when I grew up there as a kid - it's safe, friendly, clean, and full of free stuff to cover every&amp;nbsp;photographer's&amp;nbsp;desire. It would be very difficult to be disappointed as a photographer with a trip to New York.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a question about what to see or do, where to eat, who has the best&amp;nbsp;cappuccino&amp;nbsp;or Hungarian&amp;nbsp;Goulash, or whether it's a good idea to travel to Coney Island and see all of Central Park in one trip, ask me or one of the other jerks originally from New York, we'll gladly tell you how it is ;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Board the Luxury Big Apple Express at the Manchester Diocese by 6:30AM (hint: get there earlier)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336186406000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333475373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Day Trip to the Big Apple</name><id>59085082</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335609000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/59085082/</event_url></item>