<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1001 Watertown St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02465</zip><lat>42.349892</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gymnasium  in the Rear, we share the huge parking lot with CVS) </name><city>Newton</city><id>11935752</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226006</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Performance vs. Longevity: You Don’t Have To Choose (Free event) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Where: Gymnasium &lt;br /&gt;

1001 Watertown St., Rear (We share the huge parking lot with CVS) &lt;br /&gt;

West Newton, MA 02465 &lt;br /&gt;

When: March 9, 2013, 1:00-5:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP: By March 2 please, to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://us.mc1252.mail.yahoo.com/mc/compose?to=josh.conway@inspiredperspiration.com" target="_blank"&gt;josh.conway@inspiredperspiration.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can chose 1 or many of these Sessions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Sessions: &lt;br /&gt;

(1) 1:00-1:50pm *Active Isolated Stretching: Stretch For Mobility, Resilience, Recovery and Performance* LED BY Peter Benjamin LMT, CPT, AIST &lt;br /&gt;

Maintaining a healthy range of motion is essential to prevent injuries that come with modern lifestyles and age. But stretching wrong can actually make matters worse. The Active Isolated Stretching (AIS) Technique will teach you how to stretch, to improve your range of motion and resilience, and minimize risk of injury. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

(2) 2:00-2:50pm *Twice The Results In Half The Time: Build Power, Strength AND Resilience With Kettlebells* LED BY Josh Conway, CPT, WKC Coach, &amp;amp; Founder, Inspired Perspiration &lt;br /&gt;

So you’re not a hard-core “athlete” but you’re active, and you want to stay that way for the long term. How can you ensure you’re working with your body, and not against it, to keep doing what you love? ...Learn how working with kettlebells will help you build functional strength and resilience that will get you healthy and fit, and keep you that way! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

(3) 3:00-3:50pm *Chiropractic And Sports Medicine: Are Your Fitness And Health Aligned?* LED BY Dr. Karson Mui, DC. Learn how chiropractic techniques can reduce your risk of injury, improve your range of motion and posture, and keep you healthy for the long-run. Dr. Mui covers techniques including Graston, FAKTR, vibration plate therapy, flexion distraction and kinesio taping. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

(4) 4:00-5:15pm  *How Your Fitness Is Hurting You And What To Do About It* LED BY Josh Conway, CPT, WKC Coach, &amp;amp; Founder, Inspired Perspiration . Your fitness habits might not be making you healthier.It’s no surprise that many programs produce as much injury as they do fitness and health. Even holistic approaches such as yoga can result in overuse and hyperextension injuries. The solution is simple: We need to exercise in ways that mimic and enhance the body’s natural movements and functions. Whether you’re a fitness instructor, regular gym-goer or casual walker, these 10 essential movements and strength patterns will get you to peak health and keep you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find Taylor Jacobson</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Taylor Jacobson</member_name><member_id>25978182</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362869091000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361837720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Performance vs. Longevity: You Don’t Have To Choose (Free event)</name><id>106404802</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>17100000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362851100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/106404802/</event_url></item>