<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Sicily</address_1><lat>37.612598</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sicily</name><city>Sicily</city><id>9046692</id><country>it</country><lon>14.938886</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;NEW YEAR'S TOUR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;OF SICILY &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; December 26/January 4   &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;- 6 nights in Catania&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- 2 nights in Taormina&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Daily Breakfast&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Excursions: Palermo/Monreale, Agrigento, Taormina, Mt.Etna&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Sicilian Barocco &amp;amp; Nero D'Avola Wine Tour with visit of Modica &amp;amp; Noto&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Licensed Local Tour Guides&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Welcome dinner&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- New Year's Eve Dinner&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Cooking Class - Eggplant Parmigiana - by my Mom Gina &amp;amp; my Dad Loris&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Sicilian Wine &amp;amp; Cheese Tasting&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Arranged Private Transportation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Professional Bilingual, native of Italy Tour Manager, myself, Elsa  &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;br /&gt;

$ 1,950 + airfare; &lt;strong&gt;$ 100 OFF&lt;/strong&gt; IF YOU SIGN UP BY END OF SEPTEMBER!!! &lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;br /&gt;

For more info contact: &lt;br /&gt;

Elsa Gramola - A Taste of Italy in Austin &lt;br /&gt;

Italy Tours | Italian Language | Cooking Classes &lt;br /&gt;

Elsa@ATasteOfItalyInAustin.com &lt;br /&gt;

www.ATasteOfItalyInAustin.com &lt;br /&gt;

   &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;ITALY&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;TOURS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;New Year's in Sicily - Dec 26/Jan 4 [$1,950]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;- Sicily: Taormina, Agrigento, Siracusa, Mt. Etna, Palermo - Jun 5/15 [$1,950]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;- Venice, Florence, Rome, Amalfi Coast, Pompeii - Jun 14/25 [$2,950]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHY BOOK A TOUR WITH A TASTE OF ITALY IN AUSTIN?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Join us to visit one of the most romantic places of the world: ITALY! &lt;br /&gt;

All year around, you can visit different parts of Italy from North to South, to the island of Sicily! &lt;br /&gt;

My tours are personally designed &amp;amp; escorted  by, myself, Elsa Gramola, as your Tour Manager-Escort. &lt;br /&gt;

They are very small &amp;amp; intimate groups, with a max number of 10/15 people. &lt;br /&gt;

I will immerse you in the everyday Italian lifestyle and culture, while making you feel at home. &lt;br /&gt;

I offer you an experience like no other, because you are touring ITALY with a real ITALIAN! &lt;br /&gt;

Since this is the land of my childhood, I will take you in places you'll never find on a crowded commercial tour. I will show you an Italy that tourists never get to see! I also organize private, wedding and genealogy tours!!! &lt;br /&gt;

I have run more than 20 successful tours with more than 30% repeat customers to almost every city in Italy. &lt;br /&gt;

Prices do not include airfare. &lt;br /&gt;

Let's go! What are you waiting for?  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;TOUR TESTIMONIAL:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JUST IN!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The tour my daughter and I took in Italy with Elsa this summer (2012) was our third time to go and the first time with a tour.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; We spent a few days in Rome on our own and then hooked up with Elsa’s group to Florence and continued on to Venice. It was my first time to Florence and the first time for both of us to Venice.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; While we had been to Tuscany before, it was really nice to have knowledgeable local tour guides and the 2 winery tours, the olive oil tour and visit to the pottery studio are things we would have had trouble scheduling on our own.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; When we were in Tuscany before, my husband was driving a rent car and we were stopping at small towns on the major roads.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; With the tour guides we went off the beaten path and saw things we would not have on our own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Elsa was familiar the areas we visited and was able to help out with the language anywhere we needed.&lt;/span&gt;  The pre-scheduled tours to the museums in Florence, day trips to small towns in Tuscany and visit to the Murano glass blowing in Venice were all great.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; My daughter had missed the Uffizi before because she had not been able to purchase a ticket in advance. We went to a couple of great restaurants we would not have known about, let alone found.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; The travel agent she recommended here in Austin helped us with flights and the hotel in Rome we stayed in before our tour started. &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We had a lot of fun and would definitely recommend Elsa’s tours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Jill &amp;amp; Sara&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We were so excited and looking forward to our trip to Italy. We had been wanting to go ever since we got married. Our expectations were set so high that I worried we were building it up so much that we would be let down. The trip completely exceeded our expectations. What I enjoyed about the tour was that the days were filled with the "must sees" in terms of museums and historical monuments, however, the evenings were truly up to you. You were free to really experience Italy on your own and be part of it, rather than just see it. It was the best of both worlds - the comfort of knowing all the details were taken care of, and the ability to go on your own adventure if you wished. The beauty, the food, the customer service - everything was top quality. Elsa is knowledgeable, helpful, and is very funny. We are grateful for the friends we have made on this trip. Thank you, Elsa.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Oscar &amp;amp; April&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hello Elsa, &lt;br /&gt;

We thoroughly enjoyed our trip.  Thanks for taking us!  I want to share all 500 plus pics with all of you.  I am trying to download them into a flash drive and am seeking help with process.  I hope to have this done before our tour reunion. &lt;br /&gt;

Oscar &amp;amp; Rosie Duran&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elsa Gramola</member_name><member_id>11973325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356545623000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334517864000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW YEAR'S IN SICILY</name><id>60685452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356534000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/60685452/</event_url></item>