<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May 15 , 2008- Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;Strategies for Selling Quickly in a Down Market! 4 speaker panel &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Strategies for Selling Quickly in a Down Market! &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;So you found the deal, rehabbed it, and it's ready to go. But everyone says there are no buyers. Or that there are so many choices for the buyers who are looking, that you have to drop your price. And the longer it stays on the market, the more it costs. So .... &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;How do you make your house stand out from the crowd so it sells quickly?&lt;br /&gt;? Make it sparkle! Strategies for staging your house so it pops! &lt;br /&gt;o Joanne Rodriguez &lt;br /&gt;? Open up your pool of buyers who buy at full price ! &lt;br /&gt;o James Gage &lt;br /&gt;? Sell your house in 5 days with Auction strategies you can do yourself!! &lt;br /&gt;o Bert Cox &lt;br /&gt;? Financing that works for your buyer!! Yes, there are financing strategies that work in TODAY's MARKET! You can actually structure the deal so that you get full price, and your buyer can get financed. &lt;br /&gt;o Michael Ciavarini, Certified Mortage Planner &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;Free to Boston AREIA members (please see website for details - &lt;a href="http://www.BostonAREIA.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonAREI...&lt;/a&gt;, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211060200000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208471860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association May Meeting</name><id>7759756</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210887000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/7759756/</event_url></item>