<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:00 - 07:30 Fast networking, exchange business cards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:30 - 08:00 Getting Your Brand Online (3): Email Marketing - what you don't know can hurt you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:00 - 08:30 Bring your own challenges - discussion, networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Email Marketing - what you don't know can hurt you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What works, what doesn't, and why.  Do you know what your emails look like when they arrive at the Inbox?  You might be surprised by what some email clients do to your HTML emails.  Go beyond the basics and learn what can prevent your emails from getting to their intended Inboxes and discuss techniques that can measure and improve open and click-through rates.  We'll cover a range of topics from the basics to advanced concepts including: Best practices for including images in email and ideas for incorporating video into email campaigns.  What is the &amp;quot;fold&amp;quot; and how does it affect design?  Comparing CSS techniques and tables, and combining them for consistent rendering.  How to use email campaign reporting data to measure performance.  What are &amp;quot;bounces&amp;quot; and how should you use that data?  How can you list segmentation be utilized to improve results?  What are SPF Records, DomainKeys and SenderIDs? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenter Profile:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric Salerno founded Red Ember Marketing and EmberMail.com in November of 2008 to help organizations increase their marketing efficiency and turn cold leads into hot prospects through the use of marketing software and technology.  EmberMail.com is an email service aimed at small and medium sized businesses that want more control over their email communications' design, delivery and reporting.  He advises clients on Marketing Automation techniques and prospect profile development.  He has more than 8 years of Sales and Marketing experience, primarily within the technology industry.  Prior to Red Ember, he was Product Marketing Manager for Liquid Machines where he was responsible for online marketing initiatives including email, marketing automation, the corporate website and multimedia content.  He also led North American business development for a Finnish CAD company, Vertex Systems and has an MBA from Babson College and a mechanical engineering degree from Lehigh University. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website Info:&lt;br /&gt;www.EmberMail.com&lt;br /&gt;www.RedEmberMarketing.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About &amp;quot;Getting Your Brand Online&amp;quot; Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a series of topics about tools and methods of marketing and creating a brand online.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the backroom.  There are two metered parking lots near by.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victor</member_name><member_id>3780423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>20</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256249266000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising</urlname><id>984032</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Internet Marketing and Advertising  Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228266775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting your brand online(3): Email Marketing - what you don't know can hurt you</name><id>9268877</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235520000000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising/events/9268877/</event_url></item>