<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>900 East Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.527122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Inn</name><city>Meriden</city><id>1046895</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.772480</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Comedian Dave Reilly is a POWERFUL national touring HIGH ENERGY stand up comedian that WILL make you laugh with PASSION!! Dave performs his comedy nationwide. He is primarily a stand up comedian but this show is more like a One-Man Broadway Comedy Production and he can perform non-stop hysteria for longer than any other comedian on tour today! Dave Reilly's Stand Up Comedy Adventure is not a show for the weak of heart! Your face will hurt from laughing and you will be talking about Dave's show for weeks after. Dave Reilly is a Gold Medalist when it comes to Extreme Comedy! The biggest complaint after the show is &amp;quot;My face hurts from laughing!!&amp;quot; So don't say we didn't warn ya.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So...save the date of Wednesday November 24th (Thanksgiving Eve)is the 10th anniversary of the annual Thanksgiving Eve Comedy show! This year Dave will be headlining the show with a TON of new material and new stories AND Rob Hamm will be performing live music at the opening of the show so get there early! Plus we will be drinking like fish...lol! This year Dave will be at the Comfort Inn banquet hall in Meriden which is right off the highway and only 15 minutes from Waterbury and Hartford. Tickets are on sale today so start getting a table together. Only $15 a person for VIP tables up close if purchased before Nov 1st with promo-code of &amp;quot;special&amp;quot; (VIP section is normally $30 a ticket so this will sell out in the next 2 weeks)! Tickets at www.funnyguyproductions.com/calendar.asp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know in the comments field as you purchase your ticket so I can manage to get us all seated together. The more the merrier!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you use the promo-code &amp;quot;special&amp;quot;, the discount will be shown on the next screen of the purchase site A confirmation number will appear at the end of the transaction which you will use at the door the nite how nite.Just show an ID with your credit card that you purchased with. NO PRINTED TICKETS ARE REQUIRED. Seating is general admission and we seat from front to back as people arrive. Please be sure to double check your email address as you enter in on the following form because that is where we will send you information about your tickets. If there is any problem, you can always call our offices 24 hours a day at 800-523-7280. Tickets are non-refundable&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for  Terri or the Meetup Sign...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290686425000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286831686000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>10th Annual Thanksgiving Eve Comedy night with Dave Reilly!</name><id>15075836</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290645000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/15075836/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/7/c/global_18673404.jpeg</photo_url></item>