<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Deals Exchange Network&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: 1st Tuesday of Every Month 6:30 PM - Enjoy Networking, Deals, Prizes and Fun!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Doubletree Suites, 400 Soldiers Field Road, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT: James Goddard will discuss Using Social Media to Skyrocket your Real Estate Business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLUS - Networking, Deals Exchange, and Deal or No Deal &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BE THE EXPERT at Boston AREIA's Deals Exchange Network!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sit on our volunteer panel and walk through the process of analyzing deals presented from our audience. Learn techniques and questions that experts ask to make a first glance decision in less than 15 minutes. Contact us at info@bostonareia.com to volunteer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Already an expert? Want to sit on the panel of experts? Contact us today at info@bostonareia.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a deal that you would love for someone to help you analyze? Contact us today at info@bostonareia.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;James Goddard -- Using Social Media to Skyrocket your Real Estate Business&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Which social medias you need to be a part of &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The low/no cost way to increase your sales &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ways to take control of your market with so little time and investment &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The next generation of real estate investors will make more money and work less &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use the system you have used and integrate it with social media &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;To have the internet do your work for you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to market yourself while you do the things you enjoy in life &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James purchased his first business at age 25, by 29 he got into Real Estate and was in on 10% of all sales that occurred in the County by his third year. In 1996 he became part owner of a Real Estate Company which he helped grow by over 400% and sold to Coldwell Banker Residential Brokerage in 2006. Since 1995 he has been the top agent in the State for his franchise many times, including 2008 where his income actually rose 15%, while the average agents income declined 30%. In March of this year he retired from Real Estate to put his focus on helping others to achieve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is good for 1/2 hour Purchasing and 1 hour Marketing credit for our PHP progam. &lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/php.php" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for more information on PHP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***SAVE THE DATE - BRING YOUR DEALS - BRING LOTS OF BUSINESS CARDS AND COME PREPARED TO NETWORK!***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;D.E.N. Meeting&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Doubletree Guest Suites, 400 Soldier's Field Road, Boston &lt;br /&gt;Free to members, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257464312000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255646599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association November Meetup</name><id>hxwlfympbfb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257291000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/11636962/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>