<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Murder at the Wellness Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look At Me Now, A Wellness Center will be the host site for a Murder Mystery Gala in coordination with Catch a Healthy Habit Cafe. &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a fun and social evening of spontaneity and improvisation. &lt;br /&gt;Guests will enjoy live music and h'orderves when suddenly a murder occurs and the participants determine the motive and solve the crime.&lt;br /&gt;Prizes and awards will be presented based on best actor, best costume, &lt;br /&gt;most outrageous accent and best super sleuth. &lt;br /&gt;The first event begins on Saturday, October 11, 2008 6:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Pre-registration is required and there is a $20.00 admission fee per person. &lt;br /&gt;Please contact Lori either by phone or in the Unknown Zone Members Section&lt;br /&gt;Regarding Pre-registration &amp;amp; Payment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional information call Lori Larsen at (203)-933-2200.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lookatmenow22.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lookatmeno...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.lookatmenow22.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=ddbbbd8ff0&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=inline&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=11c1658bcd30d3ea" target="_blank"&gt;http://mail.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=ddbbbd8ff0&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=inline&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=11c1658bcd30d3ea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being from West Haven, I am aware of the parking &lt;br /&gt;Problems on Campbell Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;I am also aware of parking areas&lt;br /&gt;That others might not be aware of or use.&lt;br /&gt;Most of the time, I use the large parking area that is behind&lt;br /&gt;Lori's store.   I was using that parking area over a decade ago &lt;br /&gt;Long before Lori even moved into that store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, turn into the side street&lt;br /&gt;Of Curtis Place next to&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony's Pizza Italian Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;(Restaurant has had a few different names over the years &lt;br /&gt;But this is its latest name.).&lt;br /&gt;There is a large parking area behind there.&lt;br /&gt;Going to Campbell Avenue, you can walk over towards&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony's.&lt;br /&gt;Then turn right on Campbell Avenue to Lori's store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I walk over toward the right from the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;There is an alley between the buildings.  &lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, I turn left. &lt;br /&gt;Lori's store is a few stores in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a fun Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9/28 This is a reminder memo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lori Larsen is POC for this Mystery Event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224352186000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219183222000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UZ Helps To Solve Murder Mystery at the Wellness Center on 10/11</name><id>8579164</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223764200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/8579164/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/f/global_2489375.jpeg</photo_url></item>