<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA SINGLES EVENT PRESENTS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                             A DAY AT THE WORLD’S BEST ZOO AND COOLEST PLACE IN                                            AMERICA!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                      Sunday, October 4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Beautiful Bus Ride to the Bronx Zoo. Our gorgeous bus accommodates 52 Fun- Loving Folks.  Relax and enjoy the fun ride on comfy seats, with WIFI, DVD, and almost a bathroom, highlighted with Gold and Marble inlay flooring and faucets. (OK, maybe you have to use your imagination). Think no pit stops at crowded rest areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our trip will begin rain or shine at one of three convenient pick up places. Exact times, pick up/drop off locations will be announced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hartford/Chowder Pot Area- 9:30&lt;br /&gt;New Haven Area- 10:15&lt;br /&gt;Stamford Area- 11:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bronx Zoo arrival in the 12:15ish Range. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch: Brown Bag, or eat at the Zoo Cafeteria Areas. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be at the Zoo until about 4:30, and then leaving for Greenwich Village- How cool is this? Enjoy Fine or Funky Dining, Shopping, People Watching. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenwich Village arrival around 5:30—Play time till about 9 p.m., for a great ride back home.  Exact Departure times to be announced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Zoo is most wonderful. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open All Year:&lt;br /&gt;Congo Gorilla Forest &lt;br /&gt;Congo Gorilla Forest is a 6.5 acre African rainforest habitat for 400 animals of 55 species, including one of the largest breeding populations of western lowland gorillas in North America&lt;br /&gt;Bug Carousel &lt;br /&gt;Come and see our first-of-its-kind insect carousel! You can ride on of ten enormous representations of the insect world, including a long-legged praying mantis, a brightly colored grasshopper, a rounded ladybug, a formidable bombardier beetle, or an endearing firefly. The 76-seat fully accessible carousel is a year-round blast!&lt;br /&gt;Butterfly Garden &lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Garden allows visitors experience the wonder of butterflies flying freely as well as an assortment of many other “backyard bugs’ in a fantastical setting of winding planted paths, a greenhouse and a “secret garden” filled with interpretive sculptures, artwork and plants.&lt;br /&gt;Zoo Shuttle One-way ground transportation on a train that takes you from one side of the park to the other. Pay once, ride all day. Seniors (65 and over) ride free.&lt;br /&gt;Open May – October: &lt;br /&gt;Wild Asia Monorail Experience our 20 minute tour abroad the monorail where you will see rare Asian wildlife such as tigers, rhinos and elephants – plus little known creatures such as sambars, barasinghas and barbirusas.&lt;br /&gt;                                                             Greenwich Village&lt;br /&gt;Pease see:  &lt;a href="http://www.nycgv.com/about.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nycgv.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Big Print Details:&lt;br /&gt;COST:  One low Price of $45 includes Upscale Bus, Bronx Zoo Total Experience Admission Ticket Package,  Light Snacks on the bus, and “Entertainment” provided by The Ira.   Regular Total Bronx Zoo Total Experience Admission alone is $27 – this  trip is a great deal!&lt;br /&gt;Limited to a total of 52 fun-loving folks.  Please share with friends so we can fill the bus for a fabulous, adventure-filled fall day trip. A second bus will be added if we get an additional 52 people.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP no later than September 13.  I need to have your check for a confirmed yes by this date as well. &lt;br /&gt;If we do not meet the 52, all checks will be returned. &lt;br /&gt;RSVP to: Mistrchrming@aol.com  Questions- 860-604-5792. Checks to be sent to:&lt;br /&gt;Ira Wettenstein, 44 Dibble Hollow Lane, Windsor Locks CT. 06096&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Large Bus. Exact Pickup Location TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255365598000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251648616000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THE IRA - Bronx Zoo and Greenwich Village Trip </name><id>11238005</id><headcount>41</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254663000000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/11238005/</event_url></item>