<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Boylston Street at 180 Lamartine Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.317017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Southwest Corridor Park</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>317277</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104340</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>UPDATE: IF IT'S RAINING WE'LL MOVE THE FUN INDOORS TO BELLA LUNA'S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT? YOU CAN'T PLAY FRISBEE WITH YOUR PIZZA? &lt;br /&gt;YEAH, BUT THEY TASTE BETTER.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bella Luna's (aka Milky Way) is around the corner from Stony Brook T stop at the Brewery complex: &lt;a href="http://www.milkywayjp.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.milkywayjp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recess for Justice is going down at the Stony Brook court right off Lamartine Street in JP. (Exit Stony Brook T station on the Orange line, walk directly across the street to the park - we'll be on the field and in the courts right in front of you.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can't wait for sunny days of summer! Like this:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://lh4.google.com/send2robbie/Ru4Eo_3q5JI/AAAAAAAAACQ/3BobgVu34fY/Birthday07%20003.jpg?imgmax=512" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your favorite outdoor game or check out the assortment of fun we'll have on hand: Frisbees, kickball &amp;amp; chalk (for 4-square!), jump rope, basketball, softball (bring a glove) and whatever other randomness we can think of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's hot we can run through the fountain sprinkler to cool off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around 4pm we'll start to figure out what to do next.  We'll likely get out of the heat by going to Ula Cafe for iced coffee and smoothies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the photos from previous Recess for Justice events in &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/?photoAlbumId=226090&amp;amp;photoId=2233731"&gt;2007&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/photos/382694/"&gt;2008&lt;/a&gt;,  and &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/photos/685627/"&gt;last year&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/a/3/event_2233731.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while perfecting your Frisbee forehand, you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1300 members and 3 1/2+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275921472000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272313418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recess for Justice</name><id>13297701</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275760800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/13297701/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/d/global_14659789.jpeg</photo_url></item>