<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 2</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03593</zip><lat>44.366652</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Appalachia Parking Lot</name><city>Randolph</city><id>3558392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.315083</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Northern Presis - Water Feature Tour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a moderate hike for those of you that aren't ready to tackle the typical Northern Presi elevation - or want a little break from the extreme and some time to play.  I've been trying to hit some of the other, non-AMC points of interest and explore some side trails in the Northern Presis for a while. &lt;strong&gt;This will not be a peakbagging climb.&lt;/strong&gt; Instead, we will create a loop that leaves and returns to Appalachia and stays below 3,500 feet, stopping at various falls, water features and viewpoints.  Total mileage is about 10 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cool and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. These are wet trails - come prepared to stay dry - or dry off after!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This IS NOT a traverse, so we will NOT need to carpool to another location.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will meet in the Appalachia parking lot on Route 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunset will be at  about &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;6:05&lt;/span&gt; pm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike will be not be very exposed.  Come prepared for rain and cold conditions just in case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water sources appear to be plentiful on this "water feature tour". Bring enough potable water for 10 miles of hiking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamps are not required.  As a reminder, you should  always be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.   &lt;strong&gt;I require participants to wait at trail junctions, major water crossings and summits so that the group can exchange information and reset their pace.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am NOT a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.  I'm doing about book time these days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The distance and pace means that is NOT a beginner hike.  I expect people to do about book time (1.5 mph). This should not be too hard since there is limited elevation gain.  I do expect to stop at these features and take pictures, etc, but I expect to keep moving in between.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.  I would like you to be around for another day too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog &amp;amp; bring appropriate amounts of food and water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors.  If the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule, possibly to the next weekend if it looks clearer.  Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP Questions are NOT optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Plagerized" Trail Descriptions  from the AMC Guide will follow shortly  &lt;br /&gt;

 ----------------------------------------------------------   &lt;br /&gt;

 Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Link to Cliffway (2 miles)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cliffway to Sanders Bridge via White Cliff, Bog Ledge &amp;amp; King Cliff (2.1 miles)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Randolph Path to Inlook Trail (1 mile)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inlook Trail to Kelton Trail (.7 miles)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kelton Trail passing Dome Rock &amp;amp; Kelton Crag (1 mile)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;If there is interest, we can do a little more elevation gain and go UP the Kelton Trail first, to Salamancis Falls and maybe Duck falls. This adds 2 miles round trip but not much elevation. We would descend via the Kelton trail to Sylvan Way)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sylvan Way to Appalachia Parking Lot passing Gordon Falls (1 mile)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Addition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brookbank/Fallsway Loop (+1.4) (out and back to the falls) basically from the parking lot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Totals   &lt;br /&gt;

 --------   &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;10-12 miles   &lt;br /&gt;

 10 hours (MAX) - I expect to do this in less.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). WHILE I HAVE CLIMBED THIS PEAK BEFORE, I HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic, bumper sticker in the back window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351561812000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346097303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northern Presi Playground:  Moderate, Low Elevation Exploration Hike</name><id>79609792</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351429200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/79609792/</event_url></item>