<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi Folks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us as we explore some myths and facts about social fundraising with Jeremy Sher, president of Grassroots Giving Group, Inc.  &lt;br /&gt;Social fundraising works by letting nonprofits harness the strength of people's connections with each other.  People give more, and they give more often, when they're asked to give by someone they know and trust.  Technology makes this easier -- but social fundraising is about people and relationships, not about gizmos and I/T.  &lt;br /&gt;Learn about the history of social fundraising, including its formative years in walk-a-thons and (separately) in politics, and how the field continues to evolve.  We'll distinguish myths from facts, with a keen eye toward demystifying the field, and including a brief discussion on how to recognize a good consultant.  Emerge with a clear sense of what social fundraising is useful for, how it fits within your existing fundraising program, and how to get started.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  We will be meeting at a new space thanks to City Year!  So make a special note of the location.&lt;br /&gt;TAlso, tere is a $5 admission to defray the costs of the room and admin fees I accrue as organizer.  Anything beyond that we will donate to a charity - tbd!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REQUEST:  For a volunteer or 2 to take on the role of photographer.  We can take photos and post them on our site...Let me know if you're interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on the 16th!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monique Morimoto Flaherty</member_name><member_id>8025083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268953456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267559307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Demystifying Social Fundraising</name><id>12759417</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268780400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/12759417/</event_url></item>