<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2056 Mohawk Trail</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01370</zip><lat>42.622330</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crab Apple White Water</name><city>Charlemont</city><id>1592007</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.788666</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/d/9/event_34526841.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Crab Apple always runs great events.&amp;nbsp; We have had&amp;nbsp;many trips with them&amp;nbsp;and all have been spectacular.&amp;nbsp; AL is running this same post for his kayaking group so I thought we could all join in together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to give this a try:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call Crab Apple 1-800-553-7238 and tell then you want Monroe Bridge Sunday&amp;nbsp;June 24, 2012.&amp;nbsp; You would like to&amp;nbsp;be in&amp;nbsp;Timo's (another hiking group member)&amp;nbsp;boat and you are from Hartford Area Hiking Meetup Group.&amp;nbsp; The cost is going to be $95 per person.&amp;nbsp; You will need to pay for this over the phone when you make the reservation. This is a special for that day.&amp;nbsp; If you do not request Timo and the hiking group you will be put with other folks in a random boat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you decide to go and respond, I will be happy to answer any other questions you may have.&amp;nbsp; Monroe Bridge is not a beginners trip.&amp;nbsp; You need to be in good physical health.&amp;nbsp; Its got some class III and IV to handle, but it is super fun.&amp;nbsp; If there is an interest in the slower paced trip, I will be more than happy to post a trip on that stretch called Fife Brook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Summer!&amp;nbsp; The photo is from the June 12, 2011&amp;nbsp;trip and I&amp;nbsp;the one in the back right&amp;nbsp;screaming like a crazy person.......&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to the Crab Apple site for this trip.&amp;nbsp; Many questions can be answered here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.crabapplewhitewater.com/massachusetts/deerfield-monroe_bridge.shtml"&gt;http://www.crabapplewhitewater.com/massachusetts/deerfield-monroe_bridge.shtml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;

By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340555162000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327980794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crab Apple White Water, Mohawk Trail Mass.</name><id>50340172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340542800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/50340172/</event_url></item>