<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Higher Than the Niagara Falls!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet outside the ticket booth for the cable car at 10:30. We will take in the sites here and then go for lunch nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must stop by the parc de la Chute-Montmorency during your next visit in the beautiful Québec region. This enchanting site has many surprises in store for you. During your visit, walk along the hiking paths where viewpoints offer impressive views of the falls. The view from the suspended bridge over the falls opens on the falls below, the St. Lawrence River and the île d?Orléans. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You do not think your heart or your legs can carry you up the hundreds of step of the panoramic staircase? Climb aboard the cable car to see the falls under all its angles. Walk along the walkway between Manoir Montmorency and he falls. The Manoir offers delicious meals, whatever the occasion.&lt;br /&gt;There are staircases that allow visitors to view the falls from several different perspectives. A suspension bridge over the crest of falls provides access to both sides of the park as well as a spectacular view. There is also an aerial tram (cable car) that carries passengers between the base and the top of the falls. In the summer the park hosts an international fireworks competition with the falls as a backdrop.&lt;br /&gt;There are a variety of platforms from which the falls can be viewed, including a footbridge that spans the river just where it flows over the cliff, stairs that descend one side from the top to near the bottom, and a cable car (not for the vertiginous) that runs from the parking lot to a terminal near a manor house that contains an interpretation center, a cafe-bar, and a restaurant. Manoir Montmorency, above the falls, was opened in 1994, replacing an earlier structure that burned down. Lunches and dinners of notably improved quality are served there daily, all year, except Monday and Tuesday January through March, when only lunches are served (tel. 418/663-3330 for meal reservations, which are suggested). The dining room and porch have a side view of the falls.&lt;br /&gt;Round-trip fares on the cable car cost C$8 (US$6.40) for adults, C$4.75 (US$3.80) for ages 6 to 16. The cable car operates all day, every day from late April to late August, and on a more limited schedule the rest of the year.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211898755000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208304910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Montmorency Falls in Quebec</name><id>7747203</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211725800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7747203/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/f/global_3811839.jpeg</photo_url></item>