<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;UPDATED INFO:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Al,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Please contact the rafting folks and let them know there is a car pool for Saturday.  &lt;br /&gt;AL_R: OK i call friday morning and let em know..and get the last details if necessary..&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Walmart in East Windsor (it is the exit for rt 140 Ellington off of 91).  Right at the end of the ramp, at the top of the hill take a right onto rt 5 south.  YOu will pass a Friendlies (bathroom).  Walmart will be on the right.  Kevin has the dark blue mini van and my Jeep will be there.  Meet time is 6:00 A.M. If anyone is lost or late call Janice at 860-543-4591.  The van will hold 6 comfortabley.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;Janice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AL-r Comment,&lt;br /&gt;I too will meet there, its a good lsafe location: i personally park out on the very edge of the lot farthest from the store..easier to see out there..and put a cone on the roof till its time to go..&lt;br /&gt;I have the portable GPS if needed..&lt;br /&gt;Please offer a donation to Kevin or if things need another person driving..&lt;br /&gt; there is a bit of time coushion..we can eat something if we get there earlie..or whatever..&lt;br /&gt;the distance is not that far..but timing can be difficult if there is a later arrival...&lt;br /&gt;so..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the meeting is still: &lt;br /&gt;Mount Snow...the directions on youer E-Ticket are good..for gps/mapquest, you can use &lt;br /&gt;Mount Snow Road, or South Acess road in WEST DOVER Varmount to get you close enough..&lt;br /&gt;transportation to the start site is provided by Crabbyappilton...&lt;br /&gt;We have 8 of us....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok this is the last trip of the year..&lt;br /&gt;if you dilly dallied to get you place on the last trip..this is your last chance to go this year...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEPT 22&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok some of us had a great time last year, and just a fantastick time on SUNDAY...&lt;br /&gt;There is an other chance to do a trip again this year...&lt;br /&gt;especially if you were not able to go earlier..or you just want a bit more of summer..OK here are the deatils:&lt;br /&gt;West River  VERMONT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We raft the West River on scheduled dam releases during Fall foliage in September. The West offers a unique trip combining eight miles of continuous Class III intermediate action with some bigger whitewater in rapids such as &amp;quot;Landslide&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Dumplings&amp;quot;. We meet our trip at Mount Snow Ski Resort and end the trip there with a delicious cookout and slide show of the day's raft trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We begin our trip by walking to the top of Ball Mountain Dam. Views from atop the dam are breathtaking as we look down at the first rapid and back across the reservoir at Stratton Mountain Ski Area. The first half of the trip runs through beautiful Jamaica State Park and includes a half-mile rapid called &amp;quot;Landslide&amp;quot; and the feature rapid of the day, &amp;quot;The Dumplings&amp;quot;. &amp;quot;The Dumplings&amp;quot; is a tight S-turn where strong team paddling is necessary to avoid giant boulders and hit the biggest waves. After a quick snack, the second half of the trip has several more rapids like &amp;quot;The Ledges&amp;quot; and works back toward our base camp at Mount Snow. The West has an unbeatable combination of action and scenery which is universally loved by both veteran and new rafters. Check out the Photo Gallery &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip Overview:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miles: 8 &lt;br /&gt;Trip time: Full day &lt;br /&gt;Minimum Age: 12 &lt;br /&gt;Food: Cookout at base after trip &lt;br /&gt;No. of people per boat: 6 - 7 &lt;br /&gt;Rapid Classification: Class II-9 blood curdeling arm breaking blood and guts rapids..&lt;br /&gt;Digital Slide Presentation from &amp;quot;Landslide&amp;quot; rapid &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;West River Prices and Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;Rafting Price:  &lt;br /&gt;September  Adults $100pp Children 12-15 $83pp &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Schedule:  September 22 ONLY&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Includes: Pre-trip safety instruction, guide, equipment, transportation to and from river, chicken, fish or vegetarian option cookout, photo presentation of your adventure&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think by now there is nothing left but a last minute cancellation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok here is their website..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crabappleinc.com/vermont/west_river.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.crabapplei...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;How do I make reservations?&lt;br /&gt;Speak with our friendly reservation staff at 1-800-553-RAFT(7238). The office is coordinated by Sharyn and Carrie, so this part of the process has family members involved also. We feel that this opportunity to ask questions and get information from our staff is important for you and your group. The reservation office is open 8am to 8pm, seven days a week. You can also make a tentative reservation by sending an email with your trip details (name of river trip, number of people, dates, etc.) and we will confirm the trip by email or phone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Janice just talked to Crab Apple sept 18 and this is the list of who is going to experience the most turbulant, pointy sharp rock filled white water in america.  also hear that toothless guys wearning suspender Jeans try to shoot shotguns at the rafters to see the rafts deflate on the treturous section.&lt;br /&gt;lets hope they all live to tell about it&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;Janice&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;Kevin&lt;br /&gt;Bill&lt;br /&gt;Elaine&lt;br /&gt;Charleen&lt;br /&gt;Pam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok 2 will be in a different boat, Frank i guess chooses..it really dosent matter, its the trip thats fun then the time together after.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190638927000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188267186000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATEBreakaneck River WHITEWATER RAFTING TRIP&gt;&gt;&gt; VERMONT sept 22 CLASS 9 RAPIDS</name><id>6254364</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190466000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6254364/</event_url></item>