<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822075</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>For tickets visit MERI site</phone><name>Trinity Repertory Company</name><city>Providence</city><id>825670</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416074</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For this Meet-up we will head to the Trinity Repertory Theater in Providence for an historical fiction interpretation of the events leading up to the Salem Witch Trials.&amp;nbsp; You may be familiar with the Hollywood movie version starring a young Winona Ryder. Here is the description of the play on their website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fear stalks the people of  Salem, Massachusetts. Is it the work of the devil? Or has hysteria,  malice, and one young woman&amp;rsquo;s lust started a chain of events that will  undo a whole community? Trinity boldly re-imagines this American  classic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $51 plus a $2.00 handling fee. Seating is reserved and tickets are selling fast.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, I will close RSVPs effective February 22nd and purchase all tickets at that time.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt; Please note that I will moniter ticket availability online.&amp;nbsp; If tickets appear to be selling out fast, we may be forced to close RSVPs earlier.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the way Meetup.com handles online payments, we will try something different with this play.&amp;nbsp; When you RSVP, you will be asked to provide your e-mail address.&amp;nbsp; I will send you a Paypal Invoice for the ticket price.&amp;nbsp; If you are not comfortable paying via Paypal, you may contact me and arrange other methods of payment.&amp;nbsp; Please note, though, that Paypal does provide a secure means for paying by credit card without saving that information online and without having a Paypal account.&amp;nbsp; It is as secure as using your card at your local supermarket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be in the lobby at 7:00 and will be holding a small MEET-UP sign.&amp;nbsp; When you RSVP, I will provide my cell phone number in case you're running late or get lost.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby of the theater holding a small MEETUP sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299978776000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297539792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Crucible</name><id>16541772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299974400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/16541772/</event_url></item>