<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The title says it all, Its midweek, and sunny  weather is forecasted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is limited parking at the trailhead so we will meet at the information center and carpool from there. The plan is to hike the Algonquin Trail over Black Mtn to Sandwich Dome which is just shy of a 4000 footer but has better views than many 4K mountains.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trail provides many extensive views from open ledges on the southwest shoulder, sometimes called Black Mountain. The trail is steep and rough in parts, with one fairly difficult rock scramble. The hike is 9.1 miles with 3109' of elevation gain. That is a book time of 6 hours 10 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the return we will decide to either return the way we came or add some extra mileage by either taking a spur to Black Mtn Pond and Mary Cary Falls or do a loop by the pond and falls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we &lt;br /&gt;have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the &lt;br /&gt;hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Red SUV</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215177085000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214880126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sandwich Dome and Black by Algonquin Trail</name><id>8250762</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215003600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8250762/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/e/global_4645182.jpeg</photo_url></item>