<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Church St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Haven Green</name><city>New Haven</city><id>168450</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924644</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hang on to your fedoras, film fans! In celebration of the release of Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull, the summer?s most anticipated blockbuster, the Elm City is planning a party of epic proportions! In case you missed it, Indy and his gang of adventurers spent two weeks filming a number of sequences in New Haven last summer. The movie officially opens on May 22, but who can wait that long?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday,May 17th Downtown goes back to the future in honor of Indy with a classic car show, folks dressed as characters from the movie and live music from the Cobalt Rhythm Kings and the Big Fat Combo. Bring the family and enjoy the bounce house, rock climbing walls and performances by Helium Aerial Dance. Oh yeah,did we mention that there will also be ticket giveaways, so you can be the cool kid on the block who got to see the new Indiana Jones movie on opening day for free? Sweet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festivities will take place on Chapel Street (between College and York Streets) and York Street (between Elm and Wall Streets) from 12pm to 4pm. Can?t make it to the party? Come back Downtown on opening night for dinner (we hear there will be lots of restaurant specials) and the big show at Criterion Cinemas (86 Temple Street).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to be a part of the action from the inside out? Volunteers are needed for various shifts from 9:30 a.m. until 4:30 p.m. Call (203) 946-5761 to sign up or download a volunteer application here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by the City of New Haven Office of Cultural Affairs, Market New Haven, University Properties, and the Greater New Haven Convention and Visitors Bureau. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Haven: Come for the adventure! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call 946-2896 for more information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cheryl</member_name><member_id>3822665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211204007000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210030420000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indiana Jones!</name><id>7879539</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211031000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7879539/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/3/4/global_4037428.jpeg</photo_url></item>