<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person (cash @ event)</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>** Only the first 10 &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; RSVP's can go on this event due to space limitations!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come enjoy beautiful Litchfield County on horseback-during the best riding time of the year!!  &lt;br /&gt;We will be led on horseback through Topsmead State Park by an experienced guide and enjoy a relaxing hour of equine beauty!  &lt;br /&gt;   The hour long ride will be at a walk and ALL riding levels are welcome! Children must be at least 10 yrs. of age to join us. Helmets are required and will be provided for those needing to borrow them. &lt;br /&gt;     Lee's Riding Stable is located at 57 East Litchfield Rd. directly off of rt. 118 going up through Litchfield. If you miss the turn, you can't miss the field of horses on your right!!! &lt;br /&gt;    Lets meet up at 10:45 in the parking lot! Rides are hourly so PLEASE be on time!  &lt;br /&gt;The cost of an hour ride is $30 per person and is payable to me ($$ only please) the morning of the ride! &lt;br /&gt;  Lunch is optional afterwards and I know a wonderful Chinese Buffet close by! :) &lt;br /&gt;  *** After speaking to Lees&amp;quot;s Stables again, I have had to limit the amount of riders to 10! lee's likes to keep the groups small to ensure the safety and enjoyment of all riders!*** So..PLEASE rsvp yes or no by 10/28. The first 10 yes rsvp's will be accepted. If there are still interested members, I will schedule another ride in the near future. Reservations must be made so please let me know your plans asap! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1162927019000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1161207144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Horse Back Riding!!</name><id>5207435</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1162655100000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5207435/</event_url></item>