<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Time to take it up a notch!  I am ready (I think!) to attempt a hike that will be a little bit more strenuous.  If the weather is nice, there should be a glorious view!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance: About 5 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: About 1500 feet (cumulative)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;With its open summit and expansive views of west-central New Hampshire, Mt. Cardigan is an extremely popular destination for hikers. This scenic loop hike will bring the visitor through many of the mountain’s noteworthy ecological features.  To the east one can see all the way to Lake Winnipesaukee and the Ossippee and Belknapp Mountains, and on a particularly clear day, you might even catch a glimpse of Mount Chocorua. To the west, you can look into Vermont’s rolling hills. To the north you can just begin to see the White Mountains, when the skies are clear.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a MAP of the loop we are taking go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhparks.state.nh.us/explore/state-parks/cardigan-state-park.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhparks.st...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Click on the link at the bottom that says &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Cardigan Subalpine Summit and Rocky Ridge&lt;/b&gt;.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;You will get a nice pamphlet with a very clear map of our loop hike and a little description of what we might see!  &lt;br /&gt;There is also a  map of how to get to Cardigan Lodge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!  The top of Cardigan is completely bare and exposed, so it may be chilly and windy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at Cardigan Lodge. From Bristol, take Rte. 3A north for 2.1 miles to the blinking light. Turn left on West Shore Rd and go 1.9 miles to where West Shore Rd turns right. Stay straight on Cardigan Mtn. Rd. Go 1 mile and turn left onto North Rd. Go 1 mile and turn right on Washburn Rd in Alexandria. Go 200 yds. and bear right on Mt. Cardigan Rd. Go 3.6 miles and stay left at the intersection with Brook Rd. Take Shem Valley Rd 1.5 miles up to Cardigan Lodge. The trailhead is at the far end of the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Rain cancels!  I will keep an eye on the weather!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is cross-posted with &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/New_England_Over_40_Hiking_Group"&gt;New England Over 40 Hiking Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there by 9:15.  I have a bright orange backpack, a blue-green Corolla and a big smile.  774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286188623000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284865686000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (More) Into It - Loop Hike to Cardigan and Firescrew</name><id>14818581</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286112600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14818581/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/3/global_18048515.jpeg</photo_url></item>