<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup fees</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a fun and casual February meetup at which we will be reconnecting with each other and/or meeting new members.  We will have our usual [excellent!] potluck followed by a brief discussion of the year ahead for our group.  We're meeting slightly earlier in order to do some of this....it will be worth it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After that we will have a cheese tasting and presentation from Margaret Hathaway and Karl Schatz, goat aficionados extraordinaire! (more below).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A great night for some winter comraderie as the days lengthen an many of us are already dreaming of our gardens....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6pm Potluck + Group Discussion starts&lt;br /&gt;7:15 ish Presentation + Cheese Tasting&lt;br /&gt;8:30 ish Wrap Up and Questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck Breakdown&lt;br /&gt;Last Name A-G bring a veg or salad dish&lt;br /&gt;Last Name H-M bring bread or dessert&lt;br /&gt;Last Name N-S bring beverage or &amp;quot;appetizer&amp;quot; item&lt;br /&gt;Last Name T-Z wild card ... bring whatever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;In the spring of 2003, feeling like something was missing from their city lives, writer Margaret Hathaway and photographer Karl Schatz began to dream of an existence that was closer to the land. They became captivated by the idea of themselves as... goat farmers and cheese makers. Realizing that they knew little about goats, and even less about farming, they gave themselves a year to explore the world of goats and decide if that was where they belonged. On a life-changing journey that covered forty-three states and 40,000 miles, the couple learned not only about goats and cheese, but a new back-to-the-land movement that included sustainable agriculture, Slow Food, heirloom vegetables and heritage livestock. Now the couple lives on a homestead of their own, Ten Apple Farm, in Gray, Maine, with 2 small daughters and a growing menagerie of animals. The story of their transformation from city folk to small farmers is chronicled in Hathaway’s book, The Year of the Goat: 40,000 Miles and the Quest for the Perfect Cheese. In a presentation that includes a reading from the book, a slideshow of their adventures, and a tasting of the cheeses they’re beginning to make, Hathaway and Schatz will talk about their goat travels and how they are applying many of the principles they learned on their journey to their life today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1236728554000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233783847000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Meetup: Social Gathering + The Year of the Goat</name><id>9674302</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234306800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/9674302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/0/f/global_7168367.jpeg</photo_url></item>