<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389534</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Center for the Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>6657372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106071</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The First and Last Word Poetry Series, hosted by Harris Gardner and Gloria Mindock, presents Richard Fein, George Kalogeris, and Marcia Karp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Fein was Fulbright Professor of American Literature at the University of Madras from 1971-72. He has published eight books of poetry, one of which, Kafka's Ear, won the Maurice English Award. His latest collection, B'KLYN appeared in 2011. He has also published two books of his translations of Yiddish poetry, Selected Poems of Yankev Glatshteyn and With Everything We've Got, as well as a memoir of Yiddish, The Dance of Leah, and a critical study, Robert Lowell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;George Kalogeris teaches Literature and Classics in Translation at Suffolk University. He is the author of a book of poems based on the notebooks of Albert Camus, Camus: Carnets. His book of paired poems in translation, DIALOGOS, is due out in May.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marcia Karp has poems and translations in Partisan Review, Republic of Letters, Catullus in English (Penguin), Literary Imagination, The Guardian, Seneca Review, Petrarch in English (Penguin), Agenda, Harvard Review, Ploughshares, Warwick Review, TLS, and Oxford Magazine. She is included in Joining Music with Reason: 34 Poets, British and American, Oxford 2004-2009 chosen by Christopher Ricks (Waywiser), and The Word Exchange: Anglo-Saxon Poems in Translation (Norton). &lt;br /&gt;

 Admission: $4. An open mic will follow the featured readers, with optional accompaniment by bass guitarist Ethan Mackler. &lt;br /&gt;

 The Center for the Arts is located between Davis Square and Union Square. Parking is located behind the armory at the rear of the building. Arts at the Armory is approximately a 15 minute walk from Davis Square which is on the MTBA Red Line. You can also find us by using either the MBTA RT 88 and RT 90 bus that can be caught either at Lechmere (Green Line) or Davis Square (Red Line). Get off at the Highland Avenue and Lowell Street stop. You can also get to us from Sullivan Square (Orange Line) by using the MBTA RT 90 bus. Get off at the Highland Avenue and Benton Road stop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334708428000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334237586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry at the Cafe: Fein, Kalogeris and Karp</name><id>60271982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334703600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/60271982/</event_url></item>