<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Western Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.630001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stage Fort Park/Gloucester</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>272762</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.690002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Combine walking around Gloucester with a great exhibit, music and food. We can meet up hill at the visitor center at noon, walk around Stage Fort Park then head down to the waterfront exhibits. Later we can choose a local spot to eat and enjoy the good company. If you are concerned about parking, please consider carpooling into the center together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A collection of over 175 juried artists and craftsmen from throughout the U.S. will display their unique creations, live music, plus delicious ethnic foods. A pancake breakfast on Saturday morning and traditional New England Lobster Bake on Sunday afternoon complement this picture perfect seaport event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exhibits include: fine jewelry, watercolors, pottery, custom signs, bird houses, quilts, silk and dried flower arrangements, wildlife art, dolls, pressed flowers, painted antiques, photography, metal sculpture, western wear, sandstone, carved birds, maps, fiber arts, stained glass, music boxes, scroll work, masks, candles, copper, wood burning, slate, tapestry bags, nautical crafts, shaker style furniture, oils, primitive and folk art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and sample an array of gourmet delights such as herbal dips, trail mixes, jams and jellies, maple products, dried fruits and nuts, salsa, mustards, vinegars, and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free live &amp;quot;family style&amp;quot; entertainment includes Celtic, ragtime bands, and juggling stilt walkers. Over 30 antique autos will be on display on Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the Cape Ann Chamber of Commerce&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187712377000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181608944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gloucester Waterfront Festival</name><id>5880701</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187539200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5880701/</event_url></item>