<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Stroszek&lt;/b&gt; directed by Werner Herzog   West Germany 1977  108 minutes   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MFA is presenting a mini-retrospective of Werner Herzog's films during March and this one looks intriguing to say the least.&lt;b&gt;Stroszek&lt;/b&gt; will screen at 7:30 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this is a work-night event I think it would be best to &amp;quot;meet-up&amp;quot; before the film. Boston Shawarma is a small Lebanese cafe with great food within walking distance to the MFA. If you are riding the Green-Line, take the E-train and get off at the Northeastern stop and walk about 2 blocks &lt;b&gt;away&lt;/b&gt; from the Museum towards Symphony Hall. Boston Shawarma is on the same side of Huntington Ave where all the small shops and restaurants are located. If you don't make it to the restaurant I'll  also be holding a Meetup Sign in the MFA theater before the film starts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Stroszek&lt;/b&gt;  may qualify as one of the weirdest features ever made. The premise - about a mentally-impaired German ex-con, a prostitute and a diminutive, wizened octogenarian scientist who collectively move from Berlin to rural Wisconsin and take up in a hideous prefabricated trailer - is unquestionably bizarre, but &lt;b&gt;Stroszek&lt;/b&gt; is also, in its own idiosyncratic way, a brilliant, illuminating and heartfelt movie.&lt;br /&gt;All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who else but Werner Herzog would shoot the film in the hometown of Ed Gein, the murderer who inspired &amp;quot;Psycho?&amp;quot; Who else  would cast all the local roles with locals? Who else would end the movie with a policeman radioing, &amp;quot;We've got a truck on fire, can't find the switch to turn the ski lift off, and can't stop the dancing chicken. Send an electrician.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Roger Ebert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stroszek&lt;/b&gt;  is described by Mr. Herzog as a ballad, which is probably as good a way as any to categorize it initially. It's a &amp;quot;road&amp;quot; picture. In some distant way it reminds me of &amp;quot;Easy Rider,&amp;quot; but it's an &amp;quot;Easy Rider&amp;quot; without sentimentality or political paranoia. It's terrifically, spontaneously funny and, just as spontaneously, full of unexpected pathos. NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those keeping score at home &lt;b&gt;Stroszek&lt;/b&gt; garnished a 100% rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there and like I said I'll update where we will meet depending on the number of people who plan to attend-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup sign at the restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235697752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Werner Herzog's Stroszek </name><id>9833936</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236982500000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9833936/</event_url></item>