<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1563 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.379210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Law School Langdell South</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>377656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this film is NOT at the Harvard Film Archive where the group has seen a number of films but at the Harvard Law School.  More directions and a map will be provided below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The separation wall was first started by the Israeli government in April 2002, and consists of a series of walls, trenches and barbed wire fences in the Palestinian West Bank.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best description of the barrier, its routing and impact is shown in the film The Iron Wall.&amp;quot; ? President Jimmy Carter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I think the wall is a problem...it is very difficult to develop confidence between the Palestinians and Israel with a wall snaking through the West Bank.&amp;quot; President Bush, July 25, 2003  (Geesh, I never thought I'd be quoting Bush)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE IRON WALL by Mohammed Alatar &lt;br /&gt;Palestine, 2006, 57 min &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 1967 and the occupation of the West Bank and Gaza, the aim of Israel?s settlement movement became clear:  create facts on the ground that make the creation of a Palestinian state impossible.  Israel?s almost surgical placement of The Wall renders this long-held Zionist intention inescapably?and quite literally?concrete.  Festival Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As can be imagined, its difficult to find reviews on Palestinian documentaries- here is a link to one: &lt;a href="http://theantidote.wordpress.com/2007/02/07/movie-review-the-iron-wall/" target="_blank"&gt;http://theantidote.wo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screening along with this documentary: &lt;br /&gt;CONFRONTING THE WALL: ART AND RESISTANCE IN PALESTINE by Alan Greig &lt;br /&gt;USA/Palestine, 2007, 29 min &lt;br /&gt;Director will be present. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refusing to leave their home, a Palestinian family must face the dramatic?and absurd?development of Israel?s building its Apartheid Wall around them, creating a virtual cage in which they must live. The family resists peacefully by creating a mural that covers the Wall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These films will be at Harvard Law School&lt;br /&gt;Langdell South, 1563 Massachusetts Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge , MA 02138&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Landgell South is the name of the building  and here is the map: &lt;a href="http://map.harvard.edu/level2.cfm?mapname=camb_allston&amp;amp;tile=F6" target="_blank"&gt;http://map.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, if we use the Harvard Sq. T (subway) stop as a point of reference, you would walk north along Mass Ave ( in the opposite direction of Central Sq ) and the Landgell building will be a bit further north then the Science Building. I'll be getting there a bit early and  asking students where the heck the Langdell Building is and you might want to do the same. If any members know how better to describe the location of the Langdell Building- please let us know! And if you have questions, drop me an email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh and by the way this is a free screening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And as is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the films and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191623548000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190250112000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Palestinian Films at Harvard: The Iron Wall</name><id>6392373</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191450600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6392373/</event_url></item>