<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>990 Great Plain Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02492</zip><lat>42.280225</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-449-4050</phone><name>Masala Art</name><city>Needham</city><id>1157180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236439</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For January - moving book group to Masala Art in Needham - better venue for this larger group.&amp;nbsp; Cost:&amp;nbsp; approx $15F&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE check your RSVP for this event, and change to "No" if you will not be joining us.&amp;nbsp; Please also make an effort to arrive on time.&amp;nbsp; I am expanding the group to accommodate the waiting list people... we may be seated at two large tables, rather than one very large table. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book Review from Amazon:&amp;nbsp; "On the outskirts of a small town in Bengal, a family lives in solitude in their vast new house. Here, lives intertwine and unravel. A widower struggles with his love for an unmarried cousin. Bakul, a motherless daughter, runs wild with Mukunda, an orphan of unknown caste adopted by the family. Confined in a room at the top of the house, a matriarch goes slowly mad; her husband searches for its cause as he shapes and reshapes his garden.&amp;nbsp; As Mukunda and Bakul grow, their intense closeness matures into something else, and Mukunda is banished to Calcutta. He prospers in the turbulent years after Partition, but his thoughts stay with his home, with Bakul, with all that he has lost&amp;mdash;and he knows that he must return."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Books on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328671074000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319816815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January 2012 - An Atlas of Impossible Longing, by Anuradha Roy</name><id>39059412</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326560400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/39059412/</event_url></item>