<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When&lt;br /&gt;    Tuesday, May 13, 2008 at 5:30 PM 20080513T213000Z &lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;    AL-r&amp;quot;s&lt;br /&gt;    321 Silas Deane Highway Pull into the back or next door lot&lt;br /&gt;    Wethersfield , CT 06109&lt;br /&gt;    860 257 9132 &lt;br /&gt;Organized by&lt;br /&gt;    AL-r &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since most of us have been out paddling a few times this year already,&lt;br /&gt;we all seem to have found worthwhile modifications that are needed to our boats..&lt;br /&gt;some simple some more complex..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This night is for the simple ones, and to determine what else we need for the more complex repairs, modifications or just new comfort ideas..safety things too..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a hardware store just down the road, or Home Depot a few miles further..I really like the selection of the stainless steel screws, bolts and nuts that depot has..but i dont remember seeing any &amp;quot;boat&amp;quot; hardware just things that will work just as good..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ie small eyelets, and common bungies for those extra tiedowns and stuff for the inside of your boats..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cabella's is near by also, again i dont know what &amp;quot;Boat&amp;quot; hardware they have for our intended updates and modifications...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think right now all we want to do is lube up the rudders, check the foot pegs for usability, fix any cords that are weather beaten, improve sealing.. setup for the best FIT..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;wash em...and wax em up too..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do this stuff before it gets real nice out..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 67. Breezy, with a north wind between 16 and 20 mph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday Night: Clear, with a low around 44. North wind between 7 and 10 mph becoming calm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a nice night to go paddling..but a good night for fixing... get the idea....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh ..its backyard Pot Luck Barbie-Q also...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOW WEDNESDAY...THAT MIGHT BE A GOOD NIGHT FOR A LOCAL PADDLE TO TEST OUT YOUR BOAT OR MEET US FOR A FIRST TIME....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LET ME SEE HOW THINGS LOOK FOR THE WEATHER PREDICTIONS AND A SUITABLE PLACE FOR US TO MEET.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK GETTING TO AL'S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;321 Silas Deane Highway in Wethersfield..(the map link above is accurate enough) be careful of using Mapquest directions...read what i wrote first and compare...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a business section but i have one of the last 12 or so residential houses on the street..(the 5th or 6th one down on the right or west side) ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From hartford area take 84 east to 91 south...take exit #28 (same exit number for either 91 north or 91 south)..its the rte 5/15 exit to Wethersfield..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from there take the next exit #85 on to (rte 99 south= Silas Deane Hwy) , take right off exit..you cant turn left anyway here..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;go strait (south)on Silas Deane hwy ..Landmarks=pass Mercury Oil Gas Station on right, Price Right store on left and ...further a police station (dont stop there) and DRUNKEN donuts...2 streets on right Cumberland st then Oxford st....now..on the left is a bunch of businesses..the medium bright medium-blue house on the left is a hair dresser shop..im directly across from it in a small off white little ranch... about quarter mile south of the doonut shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the mail box next to the house there is #321 is in orange/red...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will JAM 2 traffic cones on the end of the driveway on the posts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pull way into the back yard SLOWLY... its still a bit wet back there..but its OK...&lt;br /&gt;You can park next door too at my sisters..if you plan on leaving earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see ya..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210887563000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210603881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Fixup Night at AL's</name><id>7922105</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210714200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/7922105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>