<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(First large parking lot on right)</address_2><address_1>93 Ricciuti Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.243389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quincy Quarries</name><city>Quincy</city><id>816334</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.034096</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe Spring is here?  It seems this March, the lion ate the lamb :).  But if the forecast holds, it's predicted to hit the 50s this weekend; great for a season warm-up on real rock!  Quincy Quarries is one of the best early season rock climbing destinations, since with open sun-exposed cliffs, it often feels 10 degrees warmer than the actual temperature.  Come get your climb on, and let's do some rope-sharing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who:&lt;/strong&gt;  All levels welcome, beginner to advanced.  Event intended for climbers who are, at a minimum, solid on their top-rope belay skills, and it's recommended to confirm the competency of your belayer before getting on the wall.  We'll also be double-checking each others' anchors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt;  Quincy Quarries.  Let's shoot to meet up at J and K walls.  (We'll move on from there if already taken, but I'll try to get there a little early to grab some prime real estate, and feel free to join me).  Just look and ask around for the Meetup group folk.  I may be at the top of the cliff setting up anchors when you arrive, so maybe give a shout up there.  Directions are in the Boston Rocks climbing guide, &lt;a href="http://www.bostonrocksonline.com/about.html"&gt;http://www.bostonrocksonline.com/about.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What To Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Personal climbing gear: harness, climbing shoes, belay device, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Appropriate outdoor clothing and layers to handle temps in the 40-60 degree range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Snacks, Water, etc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Sunscreen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Boots/shoes to handle possible muddy ground conditions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Rope and Top-Rope anchor setup gear (if you have it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tarp or Carpet Scrap, etc, for changing shoes at cliff base (if you have it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Boston Rocks Guidebook (if you have it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVPs and Cancellations&lt;/strong&gt;:  Please RSVP if you're committed to coming, and update your RSVP status if you need to cancel.  Except in case of emergency, no-shows are NOT cool.  Inclement weather or lack of interest will cancel the event (when in doubt, leave a comment, or shoot the event host a message).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get Ready to Rock Out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb</member_name><member_id>9443907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364684718000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364490623000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Outdoor Rock Climbing @ Quincy Quarries</name><id>111508282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364650200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/111508282/</event_url></item>