<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1339 Whirlwind Hill</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.436666</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-265-5526</phone><name>Gouveia Vineyards</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>1189908</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.765769</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am looking forward to the warm, sunny Saturdays of summer. So.....at the wonderful suggestion of a fellow group members, I'm planning a day at the Gouveia Vineyard in mid-June. Certainly, we will be EATING, DRINKING, and being MERRY this day :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please find a link to the vineyard (&lt;a href="http://www.gouveiavineyards.com/about_our_wines.php)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gouveiavin...&lt;/a&gt;, so you can see all of the cool things we can do here. The great thing about this meetup is that you can spend as much or as little as you want. We can plan on all meeting at my house at 11:30am and carpooling, so we don't have to worry as much about parking. Or, you can meet us there, probably around 12:15/12:30pm. More details to follow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are a few reviews I found of the vineyard...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Gouveia is my favorite vineyard/winery on the CT wine trail! The views were breathtaking, the tasting room gorgeous with beautiful vaulted ceilings and exposed beams. The building is spacious with plenty of room to accommodate large groups. The bottle of white wine was hands down the best CT wine I have had thus far. &lt;br /&gt;I am looking forward to going back with a packed lunch and taking in the view with the newly laid snowfall.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hopefully this review will encapsulate how excited I feel about this place. We visited this place a few months ago during a trip around the CT wine trail. This was by far the most excellent stop out of all of them. The wine, the atmosphere, the architecture, the landscape, the tasting, were all 100% enjoyable and perfect.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277735794000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269720251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gouveia Vineyards</name><id>13009413</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277577000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/13009413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/7/global_9949255.jpeg</photo_url></item>