<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meetup's topic is 'An Overview of MySQL Cluster' by Oracle/MySQL sales engineer Bill Papp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, more than ever, databases have to scale linearly to handle high spikes in usage, deliver 24 x 7 continuous availability and low latency. At the same time, many workloads need to maintain the data consistency delivered by transactional integrity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MySQL Cluster is the industry's leading real-time, write-scalable transactional database, combining 99.999% availability with the low TCO of open source. With a distributed shared-nothing architecture and no single point of failure, MySQL Cluster can scale linearly to meet the unprecedented demands of next generation web, e-commerce, and telecommunications / network services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Typical use cases in web services include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * User profile management for service authentication and authorization&lt;br /&gt;    * eCommerce (customer and order data, payment processing, product inventory tracking, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;    * Web Session Management&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Networks (user profiles, authentication, real-time status updat! es, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;    * On-Line Content Delivery (i.e. user data, content catalogs, subscription processing &amp;amp; management)&lt;br /&gt;    * Near Real-Time Data Analysis (using Geographic Replication to update MyISAM, InnoDB, etc. tables with real-time transactional updates from MySQL Cluster) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you can join us on December 13 to better understand how MySQL Cluster can help meet your particular needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;Logistics&lt;br /&gt;-------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the building (E51) highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=E51&amp;amp;Buildings=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's map with the Kendall square T stop highlighted:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(the stop is in red on that map, and you can see E51 in the bottom right)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT's maps with parking lot information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P4&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5&amp;amp;Parking=go" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that MIT lots are free to park in after 3 pm or so, even if it says &amp;quot;reserved for faculty&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free pizza and soda will be served, so please RSVP accurately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP anonymously, please login to the Meetup site with the e-mail address &amp;quot;admin at sheeri dot com&amp;quot; and the password &amp;quot;guest&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/calendar/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the third floor, make a right, and walk until you find room 372.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheeri Kritzer Cabral</member_name><member_id>2380684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294708355000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Boston-Metro MySQL Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mysqlbos</urlname><id>212864</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278935593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>lqzznynqbrb</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292284800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/events/15368971/</event_url></item>