<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is our second monthly video screening in Nashua. We'll have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesday-Plymouth. If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, maybe we'll have a Truth Party somewhere!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month in Nashua we will see &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://lc911finalcut.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Loose Change: Final Cut&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; This video by Dylan Avery, Corey Rowe and Jason Bermas is the final version of their runaway internet sensation. This version, though, contains all new material and is not just an edit of their &amp;quot;2nd Edition.&amp;quot; Each of the Loose Change videos stands on its own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like previous versions, this third installment in the evolution of the Loose Change series continues to ask the tough questions about the 9/11 attacks and related events. It presents over 2 hours of new, undeniable evidence challenging the official story that will leave you speechless.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change Final Cut is substantially different from Loose Change and Loose Change 2nd Edition Recut in the way it presents the information surrounding 9/11. However, it remains true to the spirit that has made Loose Change what it is today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the intention of presenting the most balanced documentary possible, dozens of professionals who both agree and disagree with the official version of events of that day were interviewed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The information in this film will hopefully be a catalyst for a new independent investigation, in which the family members receive answers to their questions, and the TRUE PERPETRATORS of this horrendous crime are PROSECUTED and PUNISHED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loose Change Final Cut will leave no doubt that the actual events of 9/11 were far different from what the public has been told. Come learn what the government and corporate media want kept secret. This is the knowledge that will provide a foundation for understanding our wider political reality we face today. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;We'll also go over how each attender can become more involved and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have free DVD's and DVD's and books for sale. Everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We've developed a collection of books for sale at these various meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------ &lt;br /&gt;Please arrive at 7:00 PM, since this meeting is on a tight schedule. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin promptly at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is in the lot in front of the building. Please enter the right entry doorway and suite 135 will be directly ahead of you. After entering the office, turn left to go to the video viewing room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------ &lt;br /&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online at &lt;a href="http://mv911t.eRideShare.com" target="_blank"&gt;eRideShare.com&lt;/a&gt;. Carpooling arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above to go to the online ridesharing group. It may take a little getting used to, but now that gas has gone over $3.90, it gets more interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you will have to do is set up an individual username &amp;amp; password on eRideShare.com. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, donations for the ride-sharing are appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the left in the picture</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218150366000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217773504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua monthly video - Loose Change: Final Cut</name><id>8466894</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217977200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/8466894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/0/global_4598208.jpeg</photo_url></item>