<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADVANCE NOTICE - NO EXCUSES ABOUT NOT HAVING ENOUGH TIME TO PUT TOGETHER YOUR OWN TEAM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Random Greatness team will be competing in three different team relays in 2011 and would love to have others from the different local meetup hiking groups form their own teams to compete in these events with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Great Race and Josh Billings are your basic, three-segment team triathlon relay race - they have a peddle (road bike), paddle (lake kayak), and plod (road run) while the Greenway Challenge strings together 6 - 10 segments that could also include a river paddle or a mountain bike peddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Great Race XXXIV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;on August 14, 2011 in Auburn, NY. This will be our first year competing in this race. We will be competing in the traditional kayak race that consists of a 6.2 mile run, a 19.5 mile road bike, and a 4.0 mile lake paddle. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.great-race.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about the great race.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 35th Josh Billings RunAground&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;on September 18, 2011 in Lenox, MA. This will be our fourth year competing in this race - in 2010 we finished 3rd out of 17 teams in the Mixed Over 40 category and 140th out of 435 teams overall. We will be competing in the kayak race that consists of a 27.0 mile road bike, a 5.0 mile lake paddle, and a 6.2 mile run. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.joshbillings.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about the josh billings.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 11th Blackstone River Valley Greenway Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;on September 24, 2011 in Worcester, MA. This will be our fifth year competing in this race - in 2010 we finished 5th out of 38 teams in the all-ages category and 15th out of 68 teams overall. While the course won't be announced until next year (it changes every year), the 2010 course covered about 55 miles and had seven segments: 4.3 mile run, 20.8 mile road bike, 4.8 miles river paddle, 5.0 mile mountain bike, 17.0 mile road bike, 5.8 mile run, and a 1.6 mile lake paddle. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenwaychallenge.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about the greenway challenge.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me know if I can answer any questions or help out in any way if you want to put a team together (or if you are an iron person and are looking to go solo). If you would like to be part of a team indicate in your RSVP what part of the race you would like to do and maybe we can piece together a team or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Blair&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;(978) 808-1932&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313548553000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288413165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Great Race XXXIV Team Triathlon Relay Race</name><id>15276566</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313326800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15276566/</event_url></item>