<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Come out on Saturday night for our first event at the newly-opened W Hotel Lounge!  This venue has won rave reviews and has quickly become a Boston hotspot - with all the style and sophistication one would expect from the W Hotel brand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  This is also the first time I am hosting an event since stepping away from day-to-day organizer duties, and I am looking forward to a special and fun evening for all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;The W Lounge is the perfect venue to lounge out, meet new friends, and enjoy an upscale atmosphere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  We will meet at the lounge starting at 8pm.  This lounge does get VERY busy as the night progresses, so &lt;b&gt;I encourage you to come EARLY&lt;/b&gt;.  We will gather there until 10pm or so, and head out to one of the local clubs to get our groove on!  New and current group members are welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;W Lounge web site:  &lt;a href="http://www.starwoodhotels.com/whotels/property/dining/attraction_detail.html?propertyID=1787&amp;amp;attractionId=1004569644" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.starwoodho...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: &lt;b&gt;We will meet at 8pm at the W Lounge&lt;/b&gt; (inside the W Hotel at 100 Stuart St, between Tremont St &amp;amp; Warrenton St, in the Theatre District) and head over to a club venue (to be determined) between 10pm-11pm to beat the lines.  These venues do get busy as the night rolls on, &lt;b&gt;so if you can't find the group, please give me a ring (646.541.0708)&lt;/b&gt;. Please meet us at the W Lounge if you can, and get there early as to have time to meet folks. Cover: None for W Lounge, but expect a cover for the club, around $10-$20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, call my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Please dress appropriately as these are upscale venues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; If traveling by T, Boylston Station is the closest for W Lounge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277512285000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266383139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One More Time!  Nightlife Style and Class at the W Hotel Lounge, Sat. Night!</name><id>12625823</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266714000000</time><rsvp_limit>66</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/12625823/</event_url></item>