<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;CHANGE OF PLANS......&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note the change of trails/starting location. After further review, the lack of parking at the Visitors Center prompted a change to an area with better parking. We will now be parking at the Stage Coach Trail trail head on Westminster Rd. Because this will add distance to our hike and the need to be at the summit for the 7:30 moonrise, we can shave time by hiking the Administration Road until it intersects with the Harrington Trail. We will then take the Harrington trail to the summit. Our return will be by the same route!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those unfamiliar with this trail head, Westminster Road is roughly a mile and a half, or so, south of the Visitors Center on Mountain Road. The turn is a rather sharp right if you are traveling south. Follow Westminster Road about 3/4 of a mile and the trailhead is on your left. There is more room to park here, but parking is still tight so PLEASE squeeze in where you can and do not park ON the roadway.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also, 6pm is the time I would like to head up the mountain so please plan on arriving prior to that!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Many folks have mentioned bringing a picnic supper to enjoy on the summit as well. If you're so inclined, feel free to do so. (No alcoholic beverages please...)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And last, but not least, you'll notice the large turnout for this hike. Luckily for us, other Organizers are joining us in order to help herd you folks to the top of the mountain in some semblance of order. While we are hiking as a group, those of you with longer legs and quicker pace may want to plan on being at the front of the pack (with appropriate waiting points if the rest of us lag behind). Those of you who are shorter or enjoy a more casual pace should take up the middle and back of the pack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank you, and goodnight!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;___________________________________________________&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;What you should bring:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Water or equivalent&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Camera&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Comfortable shoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Insect repellant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Headlamp, flashlight, or both(we will hike down after sunset)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Appropriate dress(might get cooler after sunset)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;And as always, check this site a couple days prior to the meetup in case of inclement weather...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;___________________________________________________&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This summer there will be a "nearly" simultaneous sunset and full moonrise on Wednesday August 1st. There will be another on August 31st as well. &lt;br /&gt;

On August 1st, the official time of sunset will be 8:03pm while the full moon will officially rise at 7:30pm. Another meetup group is doing this in the Pioneer Valley, but since most of us are North Central MA and Southern NH folks, I though about doing a similar thing for this group. My current thoughts are to use Mt Wachusett as the hike is fairly quick and not difficult at all. I considered Mt Monadnock, but the hike is twice as long and much more strenuous (in my opinion). We have plenty of time to work out the details...&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343915988000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337722013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Sunset/Moonrise hike on Mt. Wachusett</name><id>65896552</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343858400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/65896552/</event_url></item>