<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/5/4/event_213636692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Our book club selection for April is &lt;strong&gt;The Heart and the Fist: The Education of a Humanitarian, the Making of a Navy Seal&lt;/strong&gt; by Eric Greitens.  Here is a brief summary from the publisher:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE HEART AND THE FIST shares one man’s story of extraordinary leadership and service as both a humanitarian and a warrior. In a life lived at the raw edges of the human experience, Greitens has seen what can be accomplished when compassion and courage come together in meaningful service.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Rhodes Scholar and Navy SEAL, Greitens worked alongside volunteers who taught art to street children in Bolivia and led US Marines who hunted terrorists in Iraq. He’s learned from nuns who fed the destitute in one of Mother Teresa’s homes for the dying in India, from aid workers who healed orphaned children in Rwanda, and from Navy SEALs who fought in Afghanistan. He excelled at the hardest military training in the world, and today he works with severely wounded and disabled veterans who are rebuilding their lives as community leaders at home.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greitens offers each of us a new way of thinking about living a meaningful life. We learn that to win any war, even those we wage against ourselves; to create and obtain lasting peace; to save a life; and even, simply to live with purpose requires us—every one of us—to be both good and strong.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And from Publisher's Weekly:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;This book, by Greitens, a senior fellow at the University of Missouri and founder of the Mission Continues charity, confronts the same dilemma as the American military, which strives to be a strong deterrent against the evils of the world while protecting the sick and powerless. The concept of a mighty warrior with a good heart is not an original one, but the humanitarian soldier epiphany comes to an idealistic Greitens after stints in Bosnia, Rwanda, and Gaza, and Calcutta where he sees unspeakable carnage and suffering without end. He takes the words of philosopher John Stuart Mill as his credo: "The person who has nothing for which he is willing to fight, nothing which is more important than his own personal safety, is a miserable creature." The rigors of his Navy SEAL training are intensely depicted, as are his deployments in Kenya, Afghanistan, and Iraq, with Greitens slowly evolving into a balanced man with equal parts of compassion and warrior spirit. A glorious tale of humanity, resolve, and strength, Greitens's book reminds us of how many things we take for granted in our well-ordered lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a great group on Sacre Bleu this evening!  I think many of us found a new favorite author.  Here is my review:  &lt;a href="http://blogs.seacoastonline.com/seacoast-nh-books/2013/03/08/sacre-bleu-by-christopher-moore-book-review/"&gt;Sacre Blue Book Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other books in contention for this month's pick were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Ready-Player-One-Ernest-Cline/dp/0307887448/"&gt;Ready Player One&lt;/a&gt; by Ernest Cline&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Lady-Horses-Judith-Tarr/dp/031287572X/"&gt;Lady of the Horses&lt;/a&gt; by Judith Tarr&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Bad-Pharma-Companies-Mislead-Patients/dp/0865478007/"&gt;Bad Pharma&lt;/a&gt; by Ben Goldacre&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365609206000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328671493000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club April - The Heart and the Fist</name><id>dpskncyrgbmb</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365548400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/108986992/</event_url></item>