<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Farnsworth St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.351366</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>888.210.8895</phone><name>Flour Bakery &amp; Cafe</name><city>Boston</city><id>743495</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.048807</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I must have been hibernating somewhere in order to have not heard of this event until today! I'm sure most members of this group wouldn't want to miss it, so why don't a bunch of us try to get together and enjoy it en masse (or should that be en Mass :-) !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The whole Fort Point Channel area, right around the Children's Museum, is being taken over by this celebration of locally produced food and drink. We'll be able to taste freshly made homemade cheese. . . baked goods of all varieties. . . sample local craft brews, wines and even mead!. . . watch a chef's duel featuring local ingredients. . . see demos of crepe making, sausage making, cheese making, and learn how to butcher a goat (I'll skip that one myself.) Follow this link to learn more about what's happening:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonlocalfoodfestival.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.bostonlocalfoodfestival.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Realistically, it isn't practical to expect a large group to hang around together at a festival of this size. But if we meet somewhere just before it starts, we can sort ourselves out according to who is most interested in what, and arrange to get together later in the afternoon to compare notes and share our experiences. (And if we have any room left for dinner, we could try that too.) Sound like a plan?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event officially starts at 11 a.m. and runs till 5. I thought of meeting at Flour Bakery and Cafe at 10:30 a.m. and planning our joint and individual explorations there. Open to other ideas for this, though!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you want to participate in the beer/wine/mead tasting, you must purchase a ticket in advance.&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the site where you can do this: &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/126349" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/126349" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brownpaper...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The festival organizers ask that as many people as possible bring their own fork/spoon/plate/drinking utensils/recyclable shopping bags. Please try to remember to do this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Getting there by public transportation is also recommended. However, if anyone would like to car pool, let me know where you are coming from and I will try to connect you with someone else from the same area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us with a Meetup sign at the cafe. . . we will sort ourselves out into smaller groups depending on interest and head on to the festival when it starts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob</member_name><member_id>4061181</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286034114000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285545033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mass Foodie Field Trip to the Boston Local Food Festival</name><id>14904302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286029800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/14904302/</event_url></item>