<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Rowes Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.355973</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts Bay Lines</name><city>Boston</city><id>958833</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.049677</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>With summer soon coming to an end, it is time to kick-off the weekend and take in the beautiful weather aboard an amazing cruise with new friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the night with an exquisite summer cruise filled with entertainment, cocktails, views of the Boston skylight by moonlight, and many young professionals from throughout the greater Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the group aboard one of Boston’s most famous ships - the Harbor Belle. This two level authentic replica steamship is the perfect place to unwind and take in the fresh air as we bask on the background of the Boston skyline and waterfront. Don’t miss the USS Constitution fire her cannon at sunset, a truly spectacular sight. This boat contains an indoor level for climate-controlled comfort and an exciting outdoor open-air deck for optimal enjoyment of the weather and the best views of the city. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our travels will take us on a three hour cruise around Boston Harbor viewing the illuminated Boston skyline and beautiful harbor islands. All this while enjoying multiple fully stocked cash bars and our spacious decks to socialize with other young professionals. Includes one of Boston's best DJs and dancing to the hottest Retro and Modern hits. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some friends and make some friends, you're not going to want to miss this exclusive, private night on the harbor.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>7970205</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222383590000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220473394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor Twilight Cruise and Party</name><id>8681297</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221262200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/8681297/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/9/global_5390201.jpeg</photo_url></item>