<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>695 Hillside St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.213120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Hills Reservation</name><city>Milton</city><id>8038552</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094185</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am intending to hike the entire Skyline Trail (9 miles) at the Blue Hills Reservation in Quincy and Milton this Sunday with some friends, and have decided to turn it into a meetup event, or 2 for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire trail can be seen as the blue dashed line trail on the map at this address: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blue.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/blue.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second part of this trail will be a 2+ mile loop trail starting and ending at the Blue Hills Reservation Headquarters at 695 Hillside Street in Milton, and will be what is covered in this part of the meetup. As the name of the trail suggests, there will be many good views from the various hill peaks we will be passing through, especially at Great Blue Hill. the path we will be taking here is highlighted in pink below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/c/2/event_135641922.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We estimate that it should take much less than 4 hours to complete this part of the hike, and afterward we can either relax by Houghton's Pond near the start of the trail or head somewhere for dinner, depending on what time we finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With respect to arrivals and transportation to the start area, we will only be waiting for latecomers till 2:15 pm before we set off. Please notify us if you need transportation from the Milton T-station, and arrangements will be made if possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do note, this is meant to be a relaxing hike, so we will try to match the pace of the slowest. Please wear boots or sneakers, and other proper hiking attire. As the weather is expected to be very hot, please bring lots of water, and snacks as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When RSVPing, please include a comment as to whether you will be doing part I of the hike as well, which will start at 10am in Quincy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wen</member_name><member_id>28888902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341782124000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Asian Professionals</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Asian-Professionals</urlname><id>431528</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Asian Professionals Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341380362000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Skyline Trail at the Blue Hills Part II</name><id>71901122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341770400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Asian-Professionals/events/71901122/</event_url></item>