<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Fleet Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.364681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Twilight LLC</name><city>Boston</city><id>1568161</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053177</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A  Party at the North End boutique Twilight &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join the Hello Stiletto Shoe Club for a night of  mingling, shopping, complimentary wine &amp;amp; cheese, games and the pink  carpet walk-off! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Twilight will offer a 15% discount for non-sale  items. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; About Twilight: Owner, Alison Barnard opened Twilight in  2007 following the success of her sister store, in-jean-ius.  Inspired  by the beautiful and the feminine, Twilight stocks styles that will take  you from day to night for any type of occasion.  Best known for our  selection of party dresses, we also feature fabulous tops &amp;amp; knits,  skirts, pants and jackets; not to mention a great selection of jewelry,  stylish handbags, colorful pashminas/scarves, and every essential  undergarment known to women.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Twilight offers top name  designers, as well as new up and coming talent, which gives customers an  opportunity to find pieces that are new and distinct.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the store.  If you have trouble finding us, please call 774 232 0000.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301096672000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Join the ladies of the Hello Stiletto Shoe Club for a fun night of shopping, mingling and complimentary wine and cheese!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300466675000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies Night Party at Twilight, North End boutique</name><id>16967792</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301092200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/16967792/</event_url></item>