<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1157 Chapel Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308735</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Study at Yale Hotel</name><city>New Haven</city><id>5104742</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.932770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Everyone is in charge of doing their own separate $15 Event Registration&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?oeidk=a07e6t5klb7cfd51339&amp;amp;llr=be57c9cab&amp;amp;utm_source=Daily+Nutmeg+New+Haven&amp;amp;utm_campaign=4b6ec305c7-Daily_Nutmeg&amp;amp;utm_medium=email"&gt;at this Web address&lt;/a&gt;. (&amp;lt;- It's Linked, you can click on it!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I Plan to do Flights of Fancy this Thursday, and you're welcome to try and joint me for part or all of it.  I go to try the wine though, only so much shopping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will go to the start (The Study) right after work and will wait there for people to group up until 5:05pm.  (Or however long it takes to get through the start line.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're welcome to group with me, and we can &lt;em&gt;browse a little&lt;/em&gt; where people want, but I doubt I'll be spending more than &lt;em&gt;15 minutes&lt;/em&gt; outside of waiting in line at any one place.  Come and go from the group as you please if you want to spend more time somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description for those not familiar:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Flights of Fancy is a 2-3 times yearly Wine Tasting and Shopping event in Downtown New Haven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;On the day, go to "The Study" any time from 4-7 to sign in, pay your event fee if you're doing Cash, and get a wine glass which is yours to keep.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #6e1b29 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You also should get a MAP, which is very helpful.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;From there you walk around downtown going from shop to shop on the provided map of participating stores until 8pm. (Note: I cannot stress enough, PICK UP A MAP!  Ask if they're not obvious.) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;Each participating store will pour a wine, and there usually is a discount on purchases made at that store.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;At the end of the night there will be Coffee, Dessert, and a Raffle at 8:15 at The Study, where you signed in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking at the York Street Garage&lt;/strong&gt; is validated if you bring your ticket to the Study at sign in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AJ's initial plan:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Get to The Study by 5:00. Depart for the first stop at 5:05 or however long it takes to get through the sign-in line.  I'll wait near the Doors/Lobby of the Study until 5:05, &lt;em&gt;maybe&lt;/em&gt; a grace period if you've met up with me and are in registration line at that point. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Route: I hit the first couple in the immediate area, (i.e. the Art shops, Willoughby's) then go to the North-East most shop in the Upper Broadway district first and proceed Southerly, then once finished in the Broadway area travel to the South-West most shop on Chapel or Crown (probably Wine Thief) and work our way back N.E. towards The Study. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;(We will only stop at the shops that are not pouring wine by special request).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;Some where along the way I plan to grab a fast bite, we'll see how people feel and how many shops put out food themselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're going to be late or get lost anywhere then you can try and catch up with us along that path.  &lt;em&gt;My Cell number is 315-345-9348, text me to find out where we are at.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, former NHCer Neil and I did the above and managed to get wine at every store that had not run out.  Though if there's more shopping this time it might not happen again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;If anyone would like to lead alternative groups for different PACE, start times or paths you're welcome to pitch in and we can add the alternatives to the posting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you can't make the 5:00 meeting you'll have to try to catch up on the trail and or text my Cell (315-345-9348).  Intended path is listed in the Event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359686330000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359384732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Flights of Fancy" - Optional Grouping</name><id>101765952</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359669600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/101765952/</event_url></item>