<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Be sure  to forward  this announcement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; around to others you think may be interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This month in Nashua:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Obama Deception&lt;/b&gt;, a film by Alex Jones&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tyrrany gets a facelift!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Obama Deception is a hard-hitting film that completely destroys the myth that Barack Obama is working for the best interests of the American people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Obama phenomenon is a hoax carefully crafted by the captains of the New World Order. He is being pushed as savior in an attempt to con the American people into accepting global slavery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have reached a critical juncture in the New World Order's plans. It's not about Left or Right: it's about a One World Government. The international banks plan to loot the people of the United States and turn them into slaves on a Global Plantation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Covered in this film: who Obama works for, what lies he has told, and his real agenda. If you want to know the facts and cut through all the hype, this is the film for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch the Obama Deception and learn how:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Obama is continuing the process of transforming America into something that resembles Nazi Germany, with forced National Service, domestic civilian spies, warrantless wiretaps, the destruction of the Second Amendment, FEMA camps and Martial Law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Obama's handlers are openly announcing the creation of a new Bank of the World that will dominate every nation on earth through carbon taxes and military force.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- International bankers purposefully engineered the worldwide financial meltdown to bankrupt the nations of the planet and bring in World Government.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Obama plans to loot the middle class, destroy pensions and federalize the states so that the population is completely dependent on the Central Government.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The Elite are using Obama to pacify the public so they can usher in the North American Union by stealth, launch a new Cold War and continue the occupation of Iraq and Afghanistan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The information contained in this film is vital to the future of the Republic and to freedom worldwide. President Barack Obama is only the tool of a larger agenda. Until all are made aware, humanity will remain captive to the masters of the New World Order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your blank DVDs to the meeting and be sure to get a copy of this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Short subjects&lt;/b&gt; - bring what you think others should see - we'll see what shorts we have time to view. We also have the capability to show You Tube and Google videos, so bring your links.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesdays are now OPEN.  If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, we'll have a special organizing meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive by 7:00 PM&lt;/b&gt;, since this meeting is on a tight schedule. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin promptly at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please bring healthy snacks and/or drinks&lt;/b&gt; for sharing, since some may have come to our meeting directly from work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contributing a box of your favorite tea is always a good idea to build an inventory of available beverages at Balanced Health!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; is in the lot in right in front of the building and Balanced Health is the last office bay on the right. You'll see the Sunset Restaurant at the far left end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://RockCreekFreePress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C. and see &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Newspapers_and_Journals/"&gt;our meetup page for others&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online&lt;/b&gt; at eRideShare.com. Ride-sharing arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above (&lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com"&gt;http://mv911t.eridesh...&lt;/a&gt;) to go to the online ridesharing group. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride. ( Donations to the driver for gas are always appreciated.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;/b&gt; - Forward our email announcements to others you think will be interested in this important topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Write to us at MerrimackValley911Truth@gmail.com with your suggestions for the next month. Here's &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Our_video_collection/"&gt;our present inventory of videos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be making tea and munching snacks</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252446963000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250720390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua September video - The Obama Deception</name><id>11151683</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251846000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/11151683/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/global_10482009.jpeg</photo_url></item>