<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>129 SOUTH STREET</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351189</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.542.5108 </phone><name>LES ZYGOMATES</name><city>Boston</city><id>835348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057343</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join me at Les Zygomates for an evening of wine tasting.  The wines will be New Zealand Pinot Noir.  The cost is $30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm also the assistant organizer for the Boston Wine Meetup, so this event is on their calendar as well; therefore, not everyone at this tasting will be divorced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know most of you probably live and work in the 'burbs, but this restaurant is within walking distance from South Station, so maybe you could hop on a train for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I plan to get there between 6:30pm to 6:45pm, so feel free to call me before the wine tasting starts.  I may need to turn off my phone once it starts because they often have a speaker there discussing the wine, so I don't want to be rude by distracting the speaker and the people around me if my phone rings.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Les Zygomates' website to reserve your spot and to get more info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.winebar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.winebar.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consider taking public transportation and here's the link for that:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, Les Zygomates often has a jazz band playing, so I may stay after the tasting to listen to the band.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call the restaurant first to reserve your spot, then reply yes on the calendar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell phone # is 617-999-9094.  It should be pretty easy to find me.  I look like my picture ... Well, okay, maybe I'm 20lbs heavier and my hair is a bit lighter, so picture that and you'll find me.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207868802000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>To taste wine.</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203693872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine Tasting</name><id>7386036</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207695600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/7386036/</event_url></item>