<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the last &amp;quot;On the water event i plan to list this year&amp;quot; so its for the last remaining of us that enjoys a cool weather paddle event  , after this i will  list more walking and hiking events on my other site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There should be about 1 - 2 or so inches total of rain to make sure we don't bottom out in any spots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather, Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 51. North wind around 7 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;actual Wind ?? &lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple Farmington River Paddle on a  flat water section, yet great for the visuals along the way and  social times along the way with an ending in Curtis Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put In and meeting Location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sickomoore Tree Put In&lt;br /&gt;# 20 Hartford Road &lt;br /&gt;Use the short north side of the road  driveway before Bridge (Where the Large Tree is)&lt;br /&gt;Simsbury , CT 06070&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These locations allow for an easy in and out loading, along with a fast car transport between locations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have to do the car moving thing here...some have to stay and guard the equipment, most go to the end and drop off cars. ...then some have to take us back..then some take those who drove us to the beginning get a ride back to their cars, Identical as we did for the Strawberry Park trip recently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford i use&lt;br /&gt;I - 91 north, to exit 35..&lt;br /&gt;take a left onto rte 218..follow it past Copaco, till it runs into rte 185, &lt;br /&gt;take a right onto rte 185 follow till you pass Penwood and Heubelin forsts then  right before the the bridge at the light..take a right into small lot where the tree is.&lt;br /&gt;(Intersection of NOD St and rte 185)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use # 20 Hartford Road (rte 185) Simsbury for a GPS, mapquest location (always compare the info to my directions, if not close, then forget Mapquest and look at a different map..or better yet...get a GPS)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Giant SickoMoore tree is a historic tree and one of the largest in the state , its at the traffic light intersection of Nod Road and rte 185, before the light take a north entry into a small driveway that leads down to the river. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be going to Curtis Park BY THE RIVER side as out take out point and pot luck picknick (if the interest is there), resting, conversation, fire pit area for the rest of the afternoon. So bring some food and beverage if enough decide by RSVP to have it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;The TAKE OUT AND PICkNICK spot. &lt;br /&gt;PRINT THESE DIRECTIONS &lt;br /&gt;Where you will drop off the cars at the ending spot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;~~&amp;gt;&amp;gt; From the Sicko Moore Tree,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;take a left out of the driveway, &lt;br /&gt;Get back onto rte 185 (heading to Hartford) but take the very first left, this is Weatogue Rd,&lt;br /&gt; follow Weatogue Road till it intersects with Terrys Plain Road, &lt;br /&gt;stay on Terrys Plain Road to the end, it intersects with another road and continues as it turns left so here you stay on Terrys Plain Road till it intersects with Rte 315 right at the bridge..&lt;br /&gt;take a right onto 315, Curtis park is on the right and a smaller part of the park on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;.take the first left dirt road (the one with a gate)&lt;/b&gt; into smaller part of Curtis park, go all the way to the end,,this is our take out point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE INDICATE WHETHER YOU WANT A POT LUCK BARBIE-Q AT CURTIS PARK.&lt;br /&gt;I WILL THEN LOAD THE GRILL AND FIRE PIT FOR AFTER THE PADDLE EVENT.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Paddle &amp;amp; Paddle Leash, Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doughnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any &amp;quot;Wide Butt&amp;quot; (greater than 17&amp;quot;~18&amp;quot; butts) yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;Don't laugh, its serious, some will not fit in a yak thats too small (ie the Greenlander Pro--maximum butt and hips width of 12 inches limit) of an opening and i will feel sad you cant go..etc..the other option is to maybe trade with someone, etc, if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;This has worked in the past very well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please if using my yaks avoid stepping on the floor of them to get in and out and NEVER DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. (Kate has to repair all the damage you make to the fiberglass and Gel coatings by doing this.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only Novices in short wide cheap plastic boats do that kind of thing because they simply don't know any better or don't care.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way &amp;amp; you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro to impress the others who don't know how. Then you may laugh at the ones that fall in on entry - exit who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: Always enter- exit any kayak while being parallel and close to shore.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for most of you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes , paddling  style, and  fit adjusted, if you have your own please bring it.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;I only have one &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; life jacket for someone that can fit in it.&lt;br /&gt;Its a Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit  Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for me, but i like the way it works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/pr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with the &amp;quot;CHEAP&amp;quot; Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles because they are Hollow and light (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.) of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;You choose your preference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some  SOLID metal ones for that.)&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite &amp;quot;Yak Pad's&amp;quot; optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILABLE-----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---   ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is not a beginners boat but in calm conditions will be a good skills learning boat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--- if you are ready for it..---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; --Maybe AVAILABLE to a experienced sea paddler--&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--- AL -R --.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Advanced Composite  (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the medium size cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (43 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----AVAILABLE  ----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--- ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light Version (Very Thin Fiberglass and floor reinforced), Yellow, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest of the Eliza Series and also with the smallest cocpit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--RESERVED FOR JOANNE----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped 15.3'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and largest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED FOR DAN   ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cedar Strip Night Heron by Guillemot Kayaks 18'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with NOVICE/INTERMEDIATE and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (50 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----AVAILABLE------&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;------&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See some of you soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my Bright color ORANGE HAT &amp; Orange Traffic Cones.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289097686000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288807763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak Farmington River --Slow Flat Water--Sickomore Tree to Curtis Park section</name><id>15326396</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289055600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/15326396/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/f/global_16262175.jpeg</photo_url></item>