<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The annual Wedeln Ski and Outdoor Club Canoe Trip will take place Saturday July 14th. This is our famous paddle and float down the sandy Saco River. Its a day full of fun and we take care of all the details so you can relax and enjoy the river.  The total trip is just under seven miles but our mellow pace means we have a full day (about 5 hours) on the river. Please feel free to RSVP on this site BUT to reserve your spot you MUST mail in the Registration form. This Meetup site is ONLY to show interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost includes canoe rental(including paddle, pfd), dinner, lunch, breakfast, and a bus to and from the river. We also host a bonfire that night. Cost for the weekend ($85) does not include guest fees so please add $25 dollar per night for guests staying at the Wedeln House. I recommend guests stay both Friday and Saturday. Friday night is the best time to meet people. If you have your own canoe or kayak then cost for the weekend is only $55(no bus) + room fees, there are no other substitutions or savings even if you plan to skip meals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mail checks and form by JUNE 20th to: Jennifer Vecchi {email tom_lane@harvard.edu to get full address} 3 important things:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Check must be made out to "&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Please use the Registration form (I will send if you respond "yes")&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. No LATE people, Guest fees and canoe trip must be paid ahead of time: IMPORTANT - This is a huge weekend for the canoe outfitters on the Saco. If your check/letter is not postmarked by 6/15 it is highly likely that we will not have a spot for you. If you are late please do not show up with your own canoe and hope to "tag along", This trip is difficult to organize and supervise and having people who are "kind of with us but not really" can lead to problems. Thank You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE Here is the basic schedule - All times are aprox. and everything usually runs a bit late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FRIDAY July 13th - 7PM meet and greet at the Wedeln Ski Club House&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SATURDAY July 14th 8 am to 9am Full breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:45am Buses arrive at Wedeln.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1pm - Lunch on the river: sandwiches and snackfood&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4pm Takeout: be patient it can take a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30pm - BBQ - steak tips, chicken lots of vegi and sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30pm - Bonfire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SUNDAY July 15th - optional day at at a swim spot on the Saco or a short hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you or your friends do not have a canoe partner we will find you a paddle buddy. We pair several people up that morning and it can actually be more fun to be put in a canoe with people you do not know. No guest will get stuck alone (unless you want a single kayak). If we have an odd number of paddlers I will paddle solo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the ski house on Friday night,</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jenn V</member_name><member_id>6144735</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342483147000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338484027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saco River Canoe Trip</name><id>67123652</id><headcount>70</headcount><duration>165600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342220400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/67123652/</event_url></item>