<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Granite Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03857</zip><lat>43.078904</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.292.3546</phone><name>The Stone Church </name><city>Newmarket</city><id>1395277</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Friday, May 16th at 7:00 pm at the Stone Church in Newmarket, NH to help raise money for Seacoast Concert For A Cure ? an annual concert to benefit breast cancer research and survivor support. Tickets can be purchased online at www.thestonechurch.com. $18adv/$20dos&lt;br /&gt;The Stone Church Meeting House is a unique, small music venue and dining facility that has been hosting some major local and national artists since the 1960's. This is also a dining venue of people so choose, the doors open at 5:30 for the dinner/show. A member, Theresa will be at this event and organizing. If interested respond yes and she will contact you by the email link next to your name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For 16 years Bellevue Cadillac has been heating up stages nationally and internationally with high-energy performances of their wildly original, yet familiar songs that have been heard in major motion pictures and TV shows such as Shallow Hal, The Sopranos, Las Vegas and Crossing Jordan.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A member, Theresa will be at this event and organizing. If interested respond yes and she will contact you by the email link next to your name.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211151802000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>A good band for a good cause.</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210300778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BELLEVUE CADILLAC CONCERT</name><id>7903431</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210978800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7903431/</event_url></item>