<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;**Note: This group is for folks who are currently integrating Abraham teachings into their lives. Intention is to support each other in putting into practice Abraham's teachings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new to the &amp;quot;Abraham&amp;quot; materials and ready to actively integrate the teachings, you're welcome to join us. We strongly suggest that you take the time to go to the following &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; resources to learn about Abraham Hicks:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) &amp;quot;About Abraham Hicks: the Teachings in Brief&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/teachings_brief.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) &amp;quot;Introduction to Abraham Hicks&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/mp3downloads.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(3) Free Video Clips on LOA by Abraham Hicks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/videos.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some light snacks &amp;amp; refreshments will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;To help keep the cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up.&lt;br /&gt;Much thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 7 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Belmont  (will be provided)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Susan Conley and Suzy Spivey, BostonLOA members and &amp;quot;Abraham&amp;quot; practice-tioners,&lt;/b&gt; look forward to facilitating our continuing practice of the Abraham materials. Come to co-create, have fun, raise vibration and move closer into your Vortex and to a more joyful, fulfilling life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be working with some of the newer terms and phrases that were presented in the recent workshops as well as the new book, &lt;b&gt;The Vortex, which is about relationships of all kinds&lt;/b&gt;.  We will listen to one question from an Abraham workshop regarding Relationship issues and hear how Abraham guides the questioner to be more allowing and focus on the Vortex of the relationship, as well as the creation of focus wheel for the questioner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then turn the focus inward, to each of us personally and we'll utilize 3 processes together as suggested in the Vortex book and in workshops.  &lt;br /&gt;- Each of us will do a focus wheel regarding some contrast we feel in a relationship.  &lt;br /&gt;- Then we will write in our Book of Positive Aspects regarding the same issue, making a list of those things we do like and do appreciate about the relationship or person, and &lt;br /&gt;- finally we will end with a written Rampage of Appreciation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This three step process will raise the vibration relative to the relationship for each of us and move us up the&lt;br /&gt;emotional scale on the subject, so that we are more focused on what we want and are more forward-looking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) We ask that each participant bring your own copy of the book Ask and It Is Given, since the exercises we will be doing and the Emotional Guidance Scale are all contained within that book and it can be utilized as a&lt;br /&gt;reference while doing the exercises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Also, please bring a notebook, journal or notepad so that you can add to your Book of Positive Aspects and Rampage of Appreciation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be molding the clay here, focusing positive thoughts that feel better and having fun with our individual desires.......as Abraham says, &amp;quot;We are always expanding so you never get it wrong because you never get it done!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Suzy's address will be emailed to participants</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1257899265000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253671134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Abraham Hicks Practice Group: Aligning Desired Relationships in Your Vortex</name><id>11442811</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255474800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/11442811/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/c/global_11109020.jpeg</photo_url></item>