<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Longfellow Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375559</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Friends Meeting House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>702100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.127120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[b]Winter Soldier: Eye-Witness Accounts of the Occupations[/b]

[b]Sponsored by:  New England United, United for Justice with Peace, Stop the Wars Coalition, Massachusetts Peace Action, the American Friends Service Committee, Iraq Veterans Against the War-Boston (IVAW), and Veterans For Peace-Smedley Butler Brigade.[/b] 

July 16: Hear and Support the Voices of Anti-War Veterans!

This past spring, Iraq Veterans Against the War gathered in Washington DC to give direct testimony about their war experiences and to disclose the realities of U.S. war policy in a public investigation called ?The Winter Soldier Hearings.?

Their demand was clear:
?Bring All the Troops Home Now ? and Take Care of Them When They Get Here!?
Now it is time for us to take this powerful testimony and make sure it is seen far and wide in our communities, schools, churches and TV stations.

Join us on Wednesday evening, July 16th:
·       to view some of the most powerful testimony given by the vets in Washington, 
·       to find out how you or your group can help amplify the voices of these courageous soldiers and support their resistance, 
·       and to learn about the ?Soldiers of Conscience Support Network? being organized by IVAW and allies in the Boston area.

7:00 PM on Wednesday, July 16th
Cambridge Friends Meeting House
9 Longfellow Park, Cambridge
(off of Brattle Street out of Harvard Square) 

Click here to download a .pdf flyer - and invite others to attend.  

Click here to RSVP and spread the word on Facebook.com  

Click here to spread the word using Boston.com  

For more information on the event, call the AFSC at 617-497-5273. 
Learn more about IVAW and Winter Soldier at www.IVAW.org  .</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217438710000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215126707000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Soldier: Eye-Witness Accounts of the Occupations</name><id>8273346</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216249200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8273346/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>