<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From 10 until noon, you can progress through a series of stations to learn and practice reading a map for scale and declination; using your compass to navigate to features on a map; using your map and compass to return to a point; how to determine the distance traveled using the scale on the map; and how to navigate around impassable obstacles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 11 until 1, small groups or individuals can practice these skills on an orienteering course in the woods.&amp;nbsp; All people must have checked out of the woods by 3:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost is $5 payable to Up North Orienteers for the maps and insurance.&amp;nbsp; You will be asked to sign a waiver.&amp;nbsp; You can find out more at upnoor.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 4 in Durham, exit at Route 155A (UNH -Whittemore Center).&amp;nbsp; Turn towards Durham and travel 1.2 miles.&amp;nbsp; Turn right onto College Road at the traffic light.&amp;nbsp; Follow that to the end, and take a sharp right and go under the railroad underpass.&amp;nbsp; Look for signs for parking and registration.&amp;nbsp; DO NOT PARK in an unauthorized spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is held outdoors rain or shine.&amp;nbsp; Restroom facilities are in other campus buildings which may be some distance away.&amp;nbsp; Bring your own compass, or there will be some available to borrow.&amp;nbsp; Bring reading glasses if you need them to see detail on a map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Registration will be outside in front of the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Faye</member_name><member_id>3391935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304859507000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Do you know how to use a map and compass to know where you are, to take you where you want to go, or to help you survive an emergency situation?  If not, or you want more practice, this event is for you!</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302542223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Map and Compass Workshop</name><id>17264216</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304776800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17264216/</event_url></item>