<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellow drinking buddy, Priti has a great idea, let's check out Drink for drinks, cocktails to be precise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drink doesn't have a&amp;nbsp;beverage menu because bartenders craft cocktails based on your tastes. You say what kind of liquor you like such as dark, light, strong or weak as well as the flavors you like such as&amp;nbsp;sour, savory, fruity,&amp;nbsp;chocolaty, tropical, coffee or minty. You may be asked a few additional questions and are also free to add more detail. You will receive a delicious concoction, however, if after a sip or two, you don't like it, no worries, try again...their aim is to satisfy. Let me also add they're serious about their ice because it effects your beverage enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I stopped in for a few minutes, asked for something spicy and refreshing and was served a Ginger Breeze that satisfied my craving. They offer fresh herbs as well as&amp;nbsp;homemade ginger beer,&amp;nbsp;which will turn an ordinary mixed drink into an extraordinary cocktail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are presented an appetizer menu which lists mainly sandwiches and fries. I enjoyed a very delicious Cuban sandwich which was a great complement to my Ginger Breeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drink is in the basement of an old underground art gallery, has three square, minimalist&amp;nbsp;bars, which means the liquor is stored out of sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you go to or come from home, the gym, work, dinner, or wherever, meet up with a few drinking buddies for a minute or two or three or four or more...however long you're able. I'll stick around for 120 minutes. So don't be shy, say hi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to create your route by public transit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail) subway station is about a ten (10) minute walk to Drink&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walking directions from South Station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walk approx. 2 blocks SE on Summer St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn left on Dorchester Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walk approx. 1 block NE on Dorchester Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn right on Congress St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walk approx. 2 blocks SE on Congress St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The building in which Drink is inside, will be on the left side of the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for the Sportello sign on the sidewalk. Drink is downstairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'll be wearing a one (1) inch&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;sparkly peace sign sticker on my right shoulder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/e/f/event_46701231.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There aren't any signs indicating Drink much like speakeasies of yore. Look for the Sportello restaurant sidewalk sign which is at the entrance (348 Congress Street). Drink is downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319187811000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314818619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drinks at DRINK</name><id>31743992</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318973400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/31743992/</event_url></item>