<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This meeting will hopefully allow previously participating members to get re-acquainted and discuss ideas for the future of this group....  now that the previous organizer has resigned.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please come and share your individual backgrounds and ideas for future meetup's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to lack of RSVP's to the original announcement for a September 11 Meetup, the date has been changed to October 3. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This change permits a very interesting topic to be added to the agenda... since now a presentation will shared with another group already scheduled to meet at the same time.   This also means you will have a chance to meet some new people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you can attend, since I think you will enjoy the presentation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An introduction to a new kind of energy healing will be presented.  This is totally consistent with Reiki, which uses healing currents from dimension 2 (Ki) and dimension 3 (Rei). Reiki Masters appreciate this new modality, since it permits them to access and apply currents emanating from the 12th dimension.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These higher dimensional energy currents are much more powerful, since they can clear miasms in all lower dimensions.  Also, there are more symbol codes, and they are in color.  These symbol codes can also be used in conjunction with toning.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256250015000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Awakening Indigoes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IndigoInsights</urlname><id>1319438</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Indigo Insights: Awakening to our Full Potential</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252100630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reiki Follow-on: Bringing in Higher Levels of Healing Energy</name><id>11292468</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254610800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IndigoInsights/events/11292468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/0/global_10538896.jpeg</photo_url></item>