<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"Superbly crafted and astonishingly powerful. . . . It will thrill readers who cherish their worn copies of &lt;em&gt;To Kill A Mockingbird."&lt;/em&gt; --People &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a suspense, lyricism, and moral complexity that recall &lt;strong&gt;To Kill a Mockingbird&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Presumed Innocent&lt;/strong&gt;,  this compulsively readable novel explores what happens when a woman who  has devoted herself to ushering life into the world finds herself  charged with responsibility in a patient's tragic death. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The time  is 1981, and Sibyl Danforth has been a dedicated midwife in the rural  community of Reddington, Vermont, for fifteen years. But one treacherous  winter night, in a house isolated by icy roads and failed telephone  lines, Sibyl takes desperate measures to save a baby's life. She  performs an emergency Caesarean section on its mother, who appears to  have died in labor. But what if--as Sibyl's assistant later charges--the  patient wasn't already dead, and it was Sibyl who inadvertently killed  her? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As recounted by Sibyl's precocious fourteen-year-old  daughter, Connie, the ensuing trial bears the earmarks of a witch hunt  except for the fact that all its participants are acting from the  highest motives--and the defendant increasingly appears to be guilty. As  Sibyl Danforth faces the antagonism of the law, the hostility of  traditional doctors, and the accusations of her own conscience, &lt;strong&gt;Midwives&lt;/strong&gt; engages, moves, and transfixes us as only the very best novels ever do.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location TBA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie</member_name><member_id>1543974</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310071008000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paradisecityreaders</urlname><id>1404829</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Paradise City Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302625276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July: Midwives, Chris Bohjalian</name><id>17277512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309820400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paradisecityreaders/events/17277512/</event_url></item>