<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Boston SEO Networking Group meets the first Monday of each month.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite local Boston seo, affiliate marketing and search engine marketing professionals in New England area to join us.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robbins Library   &lt;br /&gt;700 Massachusetts Avenue   &lt;br /&gt;Arlington, MA 02476   &lt;br /&gt;ph 781-316-3200   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;@ Community Room That holds a 100 people  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take The elevator to the basement  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Try on Mass Ave if not there is a lot across the street behind Bank of America &amp;amp; Not Your Average Joe's restaurant   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda: &lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm to 7pm:  Open Networking  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Card Buffet:  drop you card on the networking buffet   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm to 7:45:  2 Min Elevator Pitch:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Tell us about you and your business or website interest   &lt;br /&gt;* Any networking goal your trying to achieve out of this meeting?    &lt;br /&gt;* Optional: Share a general marketing tip to the group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guest Speaker &lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:45pm to 8:15pm:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy Sweet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.andysweet.com" target="_blank"&gt;Domain &amp;amp; Click Fraud Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy is the owner of New Tune Media, a firm focused on traffic generation and monetization via PPC, SEO and direct navigation and has over 10 years experience in web marketing.  Aside from developing his own portfolio, Andy also provides consulting services for a number of clients, guiding their web channels to attain high profitability by campaign optimization as well as reducing exposure to click fraud.  Andy has written on web marketing for DM Weekly and been interviewed for articles on click fraud in publications such as the Wall Street Journal and Business Week.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Previously, Andy was in charge of all aspects of web related operations and marketing for the Law Offices of James Sokolove. His responsibilities included website development, vendor management, media buying and keeping the firm on the front line of new web marketing technologies and practices.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining the Law Offices of James Sokolove, Andy was the owner of Metacrown, an internet marketing agency for law firms throughout the United States. Andy earned his Bachelor's degree in Psychology from Clark University in Worcester, Massachusetts and attended the F.W. Olin Graduate School of Business at Babson College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speakers Topic: &lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Andy will discuss his experience with how to leverage domain names for traffic and protect your pay per click ads from click fraud. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Open Round Table Discussion&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:15 to 8:30pm:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: Domain Names &amp;amp; PPC Click Fraud &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 to 8:45pm  Open Round Table Challenge Discussion:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get Free SEO Consulting From The SEO Pro's That Attend! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be specific about your challenge in your website. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:45pm The End &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all at this informal Boston search engine round table discussion!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge SEO MeetUp   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------   &lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker's Wanted:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working hard to find industry experts and to develop a formal agenda to keep it interesting for all those that attend at this new big meeting room. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Event Sponsors:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEO Pro's, will work for food!  Contact us about sponsoring the event with goodies and drinks in exchange for publicity.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup pins &amp; signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Hawkins</member_name><member_id>2319452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223335340000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><why>You'll walk out with a few good contacts and lots of great internet marketing tips. People come all the way from Springfield, MA, RI, NH, just to share and learn from this Boston SEO networking group.</why><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215516011000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization August Meetup</name><id>8297876</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217890800000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/8297876/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/7/global_3054519.jpeg</photo_url></item>