<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last fall we ended our DVD/potlucks for the year with Dr. Greger’s Clinical Nutrition Volume 3. &lt;br /&gt;Then in January we watched volume 1 so it’s time to wrap it up with volume 2! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About half way through the DVD we’ll  take a break for the potluck and enjoy all the dishes that everyone brings.  Please have a card with list of ingredients for your potluck item. We’ve had A LOT of wonderful dishes that naturally lead to many ingredient questions, so the cards will make it easier for sharing/swapping recipes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re not familiar with Michael Greger, M.D., he is a physician, author, and internationally recognized professional speaker on a number of important public health issues and serves as the Director of Public Health and Animal Agriculture at the Humane Society of the United States. &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Greger is also licensed as a general practitioner specializing in clinical nutrition and was a founding member of the American College of Lifestyle Medicine. &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Greger was featured on the Healthy Living Channel promoting his latest nutrition DVD and honored to teach part of Dr. T. Colin Campbell's esteemed nutrition course at Cornell University. &lt;br /&gt;His books include Heart Failure: Diary of a Third Year Medical Student and Carbophobia: The Scary Truth Behind America's Low Carb Craze and Bird Flu: A Virus of Our Own Hatching. &lt;br /&gt;www.drgreger.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272395578000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269479680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck and DVD/Dr. Greger’s Clinical Nutrition Volume 2 </name><id>12985265</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272222000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/12985265/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>