<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1019 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06405</zip><lat>41.281631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Branford Green </name><city>Branford</city><id>963428</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.811409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Branford is once again hosting several talented and staged Jazz evenings for the next nine Thursdays&lt;br /&gt;following opening night of Thursday July 1st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music is always good, the weather will change but can be so delicious when you catch one of those perfect balmy summer evenings . . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your pic-i-nic basket or grab some take out on the way over,  your cooler ( discreet alcohol consumption is permitted), your chair, a friend or two and lets all laugh and breathe and enjoy . ..despite the stresses of the day . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starts at 6;30pm and does not go very late, but should be very fun and relaxing night,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you here!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glennn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info for this weeks scheduled performance ( subject to change)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan Pereira &amp;amp; Sabor Brasil - Brazilian Jazz - July 29!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vocalist, pianist, percussionist, composer and arranger Susan Pereira, a New York native, has been one of the most versatile musicians on that city’s Brazilian music scene since 1983.  She is a cum laude graduate of Wesleyan University in Middletown, CT, where she earned a B.A. in Music and English with High Honors in Music.  Since its inception Sabor Brasil has appeared at many of New York’s leading clubs including Dizzy’s Club Coca-Cola, Iridium, B.B. King’s, Birdland, Smoke, Zinc Bar, The Kitano, 55 Bar and Enzo’s, among others. The band has also appeared at a variety of festivals and special events including the Rochester International Jazz Festival, the Savannah Jazz Festival; the Hartford Jazz Festival; New Jersey Performing Arts Center’s “Sounds of the City” Festival; the Wall St. Festival in Kingston, NY; the Jazz and Roses Festival at the Brooklyn Botanic Garden; the Mayfair Festival; Riverside Park’s “Sunset Concerts” series; the Hudson River Museum’s festival “Summer Sounds Goes Global;” and the Central Park/Harlem Meer Music Festival.  We're pleased to bring Susan and her band to the 2010 Branford Jazz on the Green Series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Listen to Susan Pereira and Sabor Brasil on Blue Plate Radio!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>probably some type of purple balloon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glennn</member_name><member_id>8036405</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280516673000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275506448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday night JAZZ series on the Branford Green</name><id>jnwsnynkbmc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280441700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/13674397/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>