<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>181 Mitchell Dr</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.324030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wilbur Cross High School  </name><city>New Haven</city><id>664411</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.908610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See my other site first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: POTLUCK AFTER PARTY IS at a Members Home In Durham/Madison line, Its between exit 14 and 15 off of 91, actually close to the Gouvia Vinyard, but the easiest way is by exit 15 and apx 5 miles east then 4 miles south. Other roots may be suggested by my map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions and address (for your GPS , i know everyone has one now) will be given out at the event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a simple look and watch event, not really that far south for most of us..and a chance to see what is new on the safety front..&lt;br /&gt;There was a dead kayaker right up there in Maine this weekend, kind of cold for being 6 or so miles from shore..details..i dont have enough..but lets not  join him..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find us, (we will be partially split up since some will be more interested than others and talking to the demonstrators..etc....) but i will put on my orange hat and leave a Meetup sign in some view.&lt;br /&gt;Eventually im sure you will find us before the water demonstration part..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have gone to this event a few years back and found it to be informative and the demonstration entertaining well worth the time to go. Just seeing the demonstration is such a big help for beginners, and when i and a few of us do it in the lake, you will understand why its good to know..then its your turn..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, OUR kayak group will do a similar demonstration event up at Bolton Lake (about in the beginning or mid of April) showing how to re-enter, how recreational boats sink and cant be re-entered (unless you have float bags/compartments or help) and how cold water feels if you do go in, but we will be near the boat launch, clothes nearby, fire pit and your car with heat if you need it..&lt;br /&gt;Its a simple demo and a time for you to get out your yaks for a get ready for the season paddle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But this March 7 , New Haven Demo event can be an excuse for a reason to get out, learn a few things, meet a few representatives, see a demonstration, talk boats with the ConnYak.org people (they say dont buy junk also), ( IE. recreational boats..LOL) and give you legitimate reasons why and suggestions based on a life of kayaking experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I propose 1 pm for now, you can go earlier if interested ( they do the demo stuff about 2 pm or so) the overall event goes on during the day but i dont think we will be there for more than 2 hours or so, then its off to another location for Pot Luck time..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    SAVE THE DATE - MARCH 7 - PADDLESMART SAFETY EVENT - 10 am to 4 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Place: Wilbur Cross High School, 181 Mitchell Drive, New Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    This fifth annual event is sponsored by the CT DEP Boating Division, in cooperation with ConnYak, the City of New Haven Dept of Parks and Recreation, and the US Coast Guard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is free of charge and will feature in-pool rescue demonstrations from 2-4, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;safety topics such as choosing the right craft, and activities for children. For more information, contact Jean Trapani, a member of the Coast Guard Auxiliary, at 203-606-9459 (cell).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its right below East Rock Park for a landmark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Wilbur Cross High School: &lt;br /&gt;1. Take I-91 Exit 6 (Willow Street) -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; (it's a left exit if you're coming &amp;quot;from the south&amp;quot;.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 2. At the end of the exit ramp, turn right onto Willow Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Take Willow Street to the 2nd light (counting the first light as the return to I-91). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 4. Turn right onto Mitchell Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.  Pass the Wilbur Cross Athletic Complex on right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6.  At second set of tennis courts, take right- Parking in school lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have to see where in the school the event is located by some signs that should direct you to the area to be used for the exhibits and stuff, i know the demonstration should be the POOL...not the river..LOL...but ya never know...the river sounds like a real test..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok see you there if you are interested,&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing my flourecent orange hat in the place, hard to miss that one.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238260634000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234284859000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Paddle Smart &amp; Safe Demo and Info event With Pot Luck Party after at a Home</name><id>9713097</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236448800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/9713097/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>