<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your Home</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.373188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your Home</name><city>Boston</city><id>1000833</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPCOMING CLASSES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 20th - 7:30pm Eastern Time&lt;a href="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/2011/04/11/if-she-doesnt-pay-will-he-be-a-good-partner/paying/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/PAYING-300x200.jpg" width="300" height="200" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 11th - 7:30pm Eastern Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REGISTER HERE: &lt;a href="http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/date-smarter-teleclass-for-men-women/"&gt;http://andthatswhyyouresingle.com/date-smarter-teleclass-for-men-women/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be    sure to register with your valid email and  cell phone number. The  day   of the class you will receive the call in  number and PIN code to   access  this teleclass. You will receive this  notification via email   AND text.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Only 10 spots available for this teleclass.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Must call in to the teleclass no later than 10 minutes before the advertised start time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Class will last 75-90 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;These   are my favorite types of events!! Singles getting together  to discuss   and get feedback from other singles and the opposite sex.  Hear  insight  from other Manhattan daters, get some tips on how to work   through  certain challenges and, best of all, meet new people. There's  an   outline of topics I like to discuss.(See below.)  But everyone gets  to   share what their particular confusion or question is and we then  discuss   it in an open forum&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;You live in a major metropolitan city. You'd thinking finding someone special would be a breeze, right?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Well..it   can be. You can meet  the love of your life at the corner bodega, at   the gym, on Facebook or  Match.com or on the L train. &lt;strong&gt;You just  need  to know how to  optimize your opportunities, learn how to spot and   avoid the time  wasters and make the right impression. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Join   other singles - male and female - to learn how to navigate the  current   dating landscape. You'll be in a room full of people who share  similar   questions, concerns and issues. Get feedback from the opposite  sex  and  get inside their mind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;There will be a seminar AND open forum portion so you can discuss specific issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; POPULAR/FREQUENT TOPICS OF DISCUSSION&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;~Dating &amp;amp; Social Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; *How has social media (texting, Twitter. Facebook, Online Dating) changed dating? Has it made it easier or more difficult? &lt;br /&gt; *Online dating - Learn how to decode and decipher someone's profile, feel someone out and set up the date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~Online Dating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; How to spot and deal with the time wasters, what behaviors are common, tips about your profile and photos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~What Are The Best Ways/Places to Meet People?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Bars? Classes? Social Groups? Online? Which has a better return on investment and why?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~How to Tell What Are They Looking For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Discuss how to manage expectations and learn how to determine what sort of relationship they're looking for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~The Fade&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Why did they just disappear without warning? Is there really such a thing as closure?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Not   sure you get to read these.  Well, if you do, Thanks for giving me the   confidence to get back out  there. After being married for many years,   it was strange to get out and  attempt to meet someone. I attended  your  dating group Q&amp;amp;A about  reading signs etc and right after the   meeting had dinner with someone  from the group. After that I had the   confidence to follow through with  some other women. It has resulted in   being with my girlfriend for over 3  years now. We have a great   relationship. Thanks for helping me bring  out the best in me. - C from   NY"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mariann &lt;br /&gt; &amp;ldquo;  i really enjoyed this workshop as it was definitely  insightful. i was   ready for the constructive criticism to get my  dating profile up to  par.  chris had great advice and a gave us all a  handbook on how to  perfect  our profile. looking forward to improving  mine and getting more  hits  from quality men! &amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shannon &lt;br /&gt; &amp;ldquo; I found the meetup very informative. I liked the hand-out, and I enjoyed getting to know new people. &amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;   This was a very worthwhile event, it was very interactive,  everyone   felt at ease and the discussion was very animated. I think the  best   part was the ability to have the current profile critiqued. I even    learned from the critique of other people's profiles, not just my own.    Well done! &amp;rdquo;  - Jyothi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Hey Chris-Just wanted to let you know that  maybe it's a coincidence but &lt;br /&gt; I feel like I'm already getting more responses to my profile &lt;br /&gt; since I changed some things you told me to change :)  Thanks for all your advice! - DeDe"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303346582000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialnetworking</urlname><id>251346</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302634997000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Date Smarter Teleclass for Men &amp; Women</name><id>17279672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303342200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialnetworking/events/17279672/</event_url></item>