<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 6</address_2><address_1>163 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02053</zip><lat>42.147101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 533-0669</phone><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name><city>Medway</city><id>911296</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Karma Healing and the Chakra with Dr. John Wyrick

About Dr. John
&lt;img src="http://www.solsticehealing.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/01/johnwyrick.jpg" alt="John Wyrick" width="278" height="307" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Wyrick&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr John Wyrick is a Healer, a Sufi spiritual teacher and the founder  of Nirodha Karma Healing.&amp;nbsp;He has been an alternative health practitioner  since 1973. He began his career as a massage therapist, acupuncturist  and Chiropractor. In 1984 he discovered he could guide his clients into a  deep state of meditation called Nirodha. In this deep state he was able  to help people clearly identify and silence particular karma patterns  (called Samscaras) held in their light body. In Nirodha, a profound  change of vibration occurs; specific, difficult karmic impressions,  carried in a person&amp;rsquo;s energy field, stop emanating into existence. As a  result of resetting the vibrational field; deep, lasting, positive  change occurs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr John Wyrick&amp;rsquo;s home practice is in Acton and Watertown, Ma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information &lt;a href="http://www.nirodhakarmahealing.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nirodhakarmahealing.com/&lt;/a&gt; or call Maura at 831.277.6705.&lt;/p&gt;
About The Class
&lt;p&gt;Dr Wyrick is now teaching at the Solstice Healing Arts Center at  Medway, Ma. He is presenting a 6 part twice-monthly class on how the  chakras relate to the various karma patterns and how to heal them. Each  person&amp;nbsp;is born with a unique combination of karma patterns (the  difficult ones) and dharma patterns ( gifts and life purpose). These  patterns emanate from the light body which governs all the other layers  of a persons energy field, Including the chakras. To change one&amp;rsquo;s  chakras one must silence the karma patterns and increase the radiance in  one&amp;rsquo;s energy field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conjunction with the seven-chakra Hindu system (which many people  are already familiar with) Dr. John will teach&amp;nbsp;the secret Sufi chakra  system (know as the Latif system). This Sufi Latif system is remarkable  for its understanding and accuracy in pinpointing where and how the  karma patterns show up in all aspects of a person&amp;rsquo;s life, health and  relationships. Class participants will learn to diagnose karma and  dharma patterns and begin to learn how the chakras can be healed through  Nirodha. This class will teach you to see yourself and others in a new  way. Come and join us for this rare and fascinating exploration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Karma Healing and the Chakra- 6 Week Workshop with Dr. John Wyrick&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Every other Monday February 28th &amp;ndash; May 9th, from 7-9PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_flow&amp;amp;SESSION=Yz5CffgVQEgUSWoXdxA8KV6LpLysDVSjbi28kC3t5_WZtVwNqlQt4EWXQl0&amp;amp;dispatch=50a222a57771920b6a3d7b606239e4d529b525e0b7e69bf0224adecfb0124e9b61f737ba21b08198d70e9d8c4be72a2b45eb322c89203d65"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Register online for a discount!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Or pay as you go &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Contact Ashley at Solstice for more info&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.solsticehealing.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;solsticehealing@yahoo.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;508 533-0669 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Campion</member_name><member_id>9185187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298942138000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This guy knows all kinds of cool things about the Chakras. He is really a master!</why><group><who>People interested in healing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Metrowest-Reiki-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1415890</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Metrowest Reiki and Energy Healers Share</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297782817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Karma Healing and the Chakras with Dr. John Wyrick</name><id>16572266</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298937600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Metrowest-Reiki-Meetup-Group/events/16572266/</event_url></item>