<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For questions, contact: Alex Nedzel, 617-461-7823&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/strong&gt; before you RSVP.  Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself and others at risk – consider this before you decide to register.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You also need to register at &lt;a href="https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/334"&gt;https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/334&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, as this is an official AMC outing.  YOU WILL SHOW AS WAITLISTED HERE UNTIL YOU COMPLETE YOUR REGISTRATION ON THE AMC SYSTEM.  You do not need to be an AMC member to participate, but if you haven't used the AMC Boston Chapter registration system before, you'll first be asked to take a couple of minutes to create an account profile for yourself, which you can then also use to register for future trips. When registering for this trip, be sure to&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;answer all questions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for an especially in-depth visit to the Osceola ridge! All four of Osceola's peaks are on the New England Trailwrights 72 NH 4000-footer list.  Starting on the Mt. Osceola Trail, we will hike from Thornton Gap up to Osceola (4340), bushwhack over to Middle Osceola (4220) and West Osceola (4114), and then return to Thornton Gap either the same way we came, or via a bushwhack down to the East Pond Trail. 8 miles (including 1.5 miles of bushwhacking), with 2700' of elevation gain at a moderate pace. Depending on time, while atop Osceola we will have the option of making a side trip to East Osceola (4156), which adds 2 miles and 900' of elevation gain onto the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must register individually.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.09325657615601&amp;amp;lon=-71.44752502441406&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(noaa.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. If you fail to bring the necessary gear, you are putting yourself and the rest of the group at unnecessary risk -- and hence we will not allowed you to participate.  &lt;strong&gt;If you have any question as to whether your gear is sufficent, contact the leaders.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standard summer/fall day hiking gear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Spring_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf"&gt;http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Spring_Dayhike_gear_list.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In dense tree/brush areas, there is the potential for your outer layers to snag and tear, so your outer body/arm/leg/head layers should be rugged and/or fully amortized. In addition to the standard gear, you should also bring glasses or goggles to protect your eyes from flailing or hazardously positioned branches.  Due to the low light levels in dense forest, &lt;strong&gt;sunglasses will not work.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because we may run out of daylight, be sure you have a working headlamp, complete with a spare set of batteries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pack 3 liters of water, along with plenty of energy food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the trailhead, you will need to sign the standard AMC liability waiver. If you are not familiar with this document, you can preview it at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease.pdf"&gt;http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 8:30am, at the Mt. Osceola Trailhead parking area on Tripoli Road in Thortnon, NH:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lat,Lon 43.983482,-71.558837&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:  Take I-93 Exit 31, Tripoli Road, and proceed east 6.7 miles.  The parking area will be on your left near the height-of-land in Thornton Gap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expect to complete this trip within 8-9 hours. Of course, there is the possibility of signficant delays in the event we encounter unexpectedly challenging bushwhacking conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While carpooling is encouraged, you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Once your registration is approved on the AMC system, you will see the contact info and geographic info for all participants.  If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip</member_name><member_id>5187997</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1349537892000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347572597000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Osceola Trailwrights Bushwhack (ADVANCED)</name><id>82283552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349526600000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/82283552/</event_url></item>