<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>HI Incubators, I just wanted to throw this out there to you all too as my friend Namaya is putting on an awesome off broadway show this Friday in Arlington at the Regent Theater.  Definitely for those interested in poetry or the beatnik generation, but also for anyone who's interested in seeing some great theater!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see some of you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s. Let me know if you have any questions about the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Beatnik Café: Musical Revue of the Jazz Beat Generation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NYC Off Broadway Show live at the Regent!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;June 25th  at 8 PM&lt;br /&gt;Regent Theater&lt;br /&gt;7 Medford Street&lt;br /&gt;Arlington, Massachusetts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 781-646-4TIX (4849)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.beatnikcafemusical.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Beatnik Café by Namaya live from New York! It is a musical revue of the Jazz Beat Generation, based at the Richmond Shepard Theater, this off-off Broadway revue has played to  a sold out audience in NYC with terrific reviews.. The Beatnik Cafe is the scene of cool jazz music, Jack Kerouac, Lord Buckley and the culture of the 40s to the 60s that bred the baby boomers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Beatnik Café stars living legends of the Beat Generation: Lillie Bryant Howard jazz &amp;amp; blues singer of Swan Records fame with her hits in the l950’s; Richmond Shepard appearing as Lord Buckley who performed with Lord Buckley in the l950's, will perform the Nazz.  The all star jazz ensemble led by Chris Sullivan on bass, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/christopherdeansullivan)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;, Andrew Bemkey on piano (&lt;a href="http://andrewbemkey.com/)" target="_blank"&gt;http://andrewbemkey.c...&lt;/a&gt;, Michael T.A.Thompson on percussion, Allen Won on Saxophone &lt;a href="http://www.allenwon.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.allenwon.c...&lt;/a&gt;. Maggie Kus and Kat Gang are the other featured jazz vocalist. Jake Lewis portrays Jack Kerouac. Namaya the playwright is the Beat Poet who guides the audience through the cultured and stories of the beat era.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NiteLife Exchange, “The heart of the Beat Generation was recreated by intertwining it with authentic bebop jazz running from 1940’s to 1960’s….The music was terrific. Richmond Shepard portraying Lord Buckley (the hipster monologist). His jazzed up, skewed retelling of the Biblical story regarding “Jonah and the Whale” was a delightful sort of verbal be-bop’&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Franklin said, “Riveting! I loved it.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ovation: “With reverence, fun and a hip style Beatnik Café salutes an era.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Rutland Herald said: &amp;quot;The Beatnik Cafe is an artistic simpatico that's tough to cultivate in a multimedia ensemble piece of such complexity.&amp;quot; Beatnik Café &amp;quot;Is one hip, high-caliber theatrical event.&amp;quot; This unconventional cabaret is part homage, part history lesson, part pop-culture happening, weaving renowned gems such as &amp;quot;Take Five,&amp;quot; Monk's &amp;quot;Round Midnight&amp;quot; into the socio-political fabric of Ginsburg's &amp;quot;Howl, Beatnik Café is an engaging timeline of the musical, literary, and trend-setting luminaries.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277514830000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277205992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday night theater! The Beatnik Cafe!</name><id>13873323</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277510400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/13873323/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/2/global_15900834.jpeg</photo_url></item>