<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come listen to &lt;b&gt;Andrew Cohen&lt;/b&gt;, physics professor at Boston University, talk about Cinema Physics before the screening of the epic and graceful martial arts film Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Science on Screen, Coolidge Corner site:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Winner of four Academy Awards (Best Foreign Language Film, Best Cinematography, Best Art Direction, Best Score), &lt;b&gt;Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon&lt;/b&gt; is internationally acclaimed director Ang Lee’s homage to the Hong Kong wuxia (martial arts) films that fueled his love of movies as a youth in Taiwan&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7:00 pm showtime (get in line at 6:15 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $9.75 [ &lt;b&gt;Buy tickets online&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Release Date:&lt;/b&gt; 12/22/2000&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duration&lt;/b&gt;: The movie is 120 minutes long. The program is listed on their site as 2 hrs, 35 minutes, so the first 35 minutes might be the lecture.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, T.J. Maher will get there at 6:00 pm if anyone wants to hang out and socialize before. Rain or shine, the Coolidge Corner forms a line starting at 6:15 pm, which quickly wraps its way down the brick wall next to the theater and turns the corner. We can all get in line by 6:15 pm, giving us more time to say hello to each other. The doors open at 6:40 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... We should be getting out of the Theater by 9:40 pm. Anybody up for the Jewish Deli Zaftig? Or the great dessert place, Finale? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about the presentation:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Based on the novel by Wang Du Lu, Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon revolves around the theft of a legendary sword named Green Destiny and the quest to retrieve it – a quest that leads to a face-off between good and evil. Set against the gorgeous landscapes of nineteenth-century China, the film combines exhilarating martial arts and action sequences choreographed by the great Yuen Wo Ping (best known to American audiences for his work on The Matrix) with dramatic soul and epic romance. &amp;quot;The superior cast includes Chow Yun Fat (once dubbed the coolest actor in the world by the Los Angeles Times, Michelle Yeoh, Zhang Ziyi, Chen Pei-pei (an iconic martial arts star of the ‘60s and ‘70s) and Chang Chen. (2 hrs. In Mandarin and Cantonese with English subtitles)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon, self belief overcomes conventional physics. In sequences that are part adrenaline rush, part poetry, combatants soar over rooftops, run up walls, step on water, and battle atop the branches of bamboo trees. Before the screening, guest speaker Andrew Cohen explores how the laws of physics are bent and why this may enhance the film’s impact. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Andrew Cohen&lt;/b&gt; is professor of physics at Boston University, where he created &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Cinema Physica&lt;/b&gt;,&amp;quot; a course that introduces non-science majors to the principles of quantitative scientific reasoning through the analysis of popular films. A former Junior Fellow of the Harvard Society of Fellows, a fellow of the American Physical Society, and president of the Aspen Center for Physics, Professor Cohen conducts research on the physics of elementary particles. He holds degrees in music and physics from Stanford University and received his Ph.D. in theoretical physics from Harvard University&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science on Screen:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, we present a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Cinema-Physica website: CAS class blends film, physics:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bu.edu/cas/features/cinema-physica/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bu.edu/cas...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An out-of-control cruise ship slams into a busy pier. As wood splinters and screaming bystanders flee, Andrew Cohen, a College of Arts &amp;amp; Sciences professor of physics, assesses the mayhem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The purpose of analyzing all the explosions and heroics, he explains, is to give humanities majors a truer sense of what science is — a quest for discovery rather than memorized formulas and definitive answers. 'Yeah, yeah, we’re all running. OK, we’re doing a lot of damage,' he says, as if he’s seen it all before. Actually, he has, several dozen times, and all in the name of science.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This particular maritime disaster is a scene from Speed 2: Cruise Control, one of the action flicks that features prominently in Cinema Physica, an introductory physics course for nonscience majors. Every week, Cohen’s students watch movies such as Unbreakable, The Sixth Sense, and Armageddon, and use class discussions and labs to examine the basic physics driving the high-octane scenes.&lt;br /&gt;'The subtitle of this course should be Bruce Willis Saves the World,' Cohen tells students with a laugh. The purpose of analyzing all the explosions and heroics, he explains, is to give humanities majors a truer sense of what science is — a quest for discovery rather than memorized formulas and definitive answers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'When you do an experiment, you don’t know what the answer is going to be,' he says. “And because we don’t know whether the movies actually obey the laws of physics, they are our experiments. They are our laboratories.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Cohen uses The Abyss to discuss fluids and pressure, for instance, and X-Men to talk about electricity and magnetism. Last fall, after the class watched The Matrix scene where Morpheus tells Neo that the machines behind the matrix want to turn humans into nine-volt batteries, Cohen talked about the physics of batteries and whether humans would really be nine-volt — or much larger — batteries, leaving aside the movie’s more existential questions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'We didn’t much go into the idea of whether we are all just pixels in a digital universe,' says Adrian Coyne (CAS’11). &amp;quot; [ &lt;b&gt;More from Boston University's Alumni Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.bu.edu/alumni/buforward/archives/May_2008/articles/cinema.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bu.edu/alu...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Parking&lt;/u&gt;: Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Center St. one block from Harvard St.) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 6:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;By train&lt;/u&gt;: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270679037000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269375834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Andrew Cohen, Cinema Physics, Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon @ Coolidge Corner</name><id>12971189</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270505700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12971189/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/7/global_13866791.jpeg</photo_url></item>