<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/5/8/event_225796472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Distanace: 5+ miles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Duration: 2 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Difficulty: easy &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Before signing up for this hike read the whole write up and by signing up for this hike you (and guest if applicable) are agreeing to the liability waiver below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;The East Bay Bike Path is the first multi-town bike path built in Rhode Island. The bikeway travels 14.5 miles from India Point Park in Providence to Independence Park in Bristol. The path connects&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.dot.ri.gov/img/content/bikeri/maps/ebbp2013.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dot.ri.gov/img/content/bikeri/maps/ebbp2013.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;neighborhoods, schools and business districts and is a popular route for cyclists who commute to Providence.  We will walk South from the parking lot winding along the parkway and down to the river where we will walk along the bike path for an hour before turning around and heading back twoard Providence before it gets dark. We should be able to get 5 + miles in. This is an easy flat walk w/ lovely views along the way. Bring water and snacks. If you have a head lamp or small flash light it would be a good idea to bring it along.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;Veterans Memorial Parkway&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;      &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt;From I-95 North and South: &lt;br /&gt;

Take Route 195 East to Exit 5 Warren Ave. (exit 4 closed) at the bottom of the exit take a right onto Warren Ave. Take the 1st left onto 1st Street. At the 2nd stop sign go right up the Veterans Memorial Parkway about .25 miles to the 1st parking lot on the right. It is across from Mercer St.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002842"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>1st parking lot for the East Bay Bike Path, across from Mercer St. in EP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leanne</member_name><member_id>10321441</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366941247000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366796987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WALK ALONG THE PROVIDENCE RIVER AFTER WORK</name><id>115919642</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366923600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/115919642/</event_url></item>