<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>343 Washington Terrace</address_2><address_1>Mansfield Freeman Center</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 805-2078</phone><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship</name><city>Middletown</city><id>437051</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Buddhism 101 Course 2013 for beginners &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - a course geared for people with busy schedules - &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - enrollment on an ongoing and limited basis - &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - Registration extended Jan. 15, 2013 - &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have room for a couple of more students. If you have been interested in taking this 101 course, now you have another opportunity to do so. Let 2013 be the year for you to engage the Buddha’s teachings for lay people in a direct and structured way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the tenth year of our most popular and comprehensive course on the Buddha’s teachings. It surveys the Buddhist life, his disciples and teachings, and how they may be applied to daily living in 21st century America. This non-sectarian course covers the vastness of the Buddhist religion through Theravada and Mahayana traditions. Begins January 27, 2013. It will meet for 6 sessions in 6 months. Open to Buddhists and Non-buddhists. No pre-requisites. This course is oriented to beginner’s who are looking for a concrete, practical and sequential study of Buddhism. See web site below. Registration closes January 15, 2012. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Furthermore we offer intermediate and advance courses like our Buddhism 201, 301 and 401 courses. &lt;br /&gt;

 To keep the courses engaging, there is limited enrollment in all of our courses. We highly suggest that if you are interested in registering that you do so, sooner than later. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Visit our New England Institute of Buddhist Studies, located in Middletown Connecticut for more details and online registration. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://dharmaquest.bffct.net/" class="linkified"&gt;http://dharmaquest.bffct.net/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359317281000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351616933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhism 101 Course (Discover the Buddha's Teachings)</name><id>89191752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359306000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/89191752/</event_url></item>