<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Commercial Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.990201</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PSNH Parking Lot</name><city>Manchester </city><id>1036388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.468365</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Manchester Historic Association is offering its second annual historical walking tour of the entire length of the Amoskeag Manufacturing Company Millyard on Saturday, October 10. The “Mile of Mills&amp;quot; Walking Tour will honor all of the people who have lived and worked along the banks of the Merrimack River in Manchester. These include the Penacook Indians who fished at Amoskeag Falls, the early Scots-Irish and English settlers, and the many thousands of mill workers who toiled in the mile of brick factories along the river in the 19th and 20th Centuries. As this is the year of the Lincoln Bicentennial, and as Abraham Lincoln toured the Millyard in 1860, the buildings that he would have seen will be pointed out. Local historian and author Robert B. Perreault and Aurore Eaton, Executive Director of the Manchester Historic Association, will lead the tour. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk will begin at 9 a.m. at the north end of the Millyard, and will end at the Manchester Historic Association’s Millyard Museum at around Noon (total walking distance of around 2 ½ miles). Participants will enjoy a light lunch in the Millyard Museum. The tour fee includes admission to the Museum, where a special exhibit is on view: “Abraham Lincoln: Manchester Remembers.” Pre-registration is required. MHA MEMBERS $15 - GENERAL PUBLIC $20 (lunch included).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Manchester Historic Association</member_name><member_id>10139829</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313088084000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>History fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-History-Network</urlname><id>1505455</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester History Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250171418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Mile of Mills" Walking Tour </name><id>11102898</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255179600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-History-Network/events/11102898/</event_url></item>