<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Moody Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.366220</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 647-7977</phone><name>Masao's Kitchen</name><city>Waltham </city><id>862804</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.238006</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If you're interested in seeing the documentary &amp;quot;Food, Inc.&amp;quot; this weekend, I am coordinating a screening at the Waltham Embassy this Saturday, June 27th in partnership with Laura McJohnson of the BostonMacro Dinner Club. We're meeting at Masao's for lunch at 12:30 and seeing the 2:10 matinee.    &lt;br /&gt;My cell # is 508-361-7978 incase you need to get in touch with me.   Hope to see you there!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Waltham Embassy Cinema is at 16 Pine Street, just off Moody Street #781-893-2500 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Food Inc,&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hoping to do more than just make meat-eaters feel guilty, angry or both - this film will explore the essence of a variety of different widely available foods, everything from vegetables and fruit to beef and bacon. The main focus of this film is not the food itself though - it is the corporate industry that controls the sourcing, processing, production and sale of food. Not only are animals being mistreated, abused and treated as slaves in the name of food production, but Humans are too. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loosely based on Eric Schlosser’s non-fiction book Fast Food Nation: The Dark Side of the All-American Meal, but different to the fictional feature film of the same name starring Greg Kinnear, “Food, Inc.” will hit screens on a limited release in June and will be available to buy on DVD shortly after.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246293523000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245939387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lunch at Masao's then see "Food,  Inc." 2:10 matinee at  Waltham Embassy Cinema </name><id>10733347</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246120200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/10733347/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>