<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ (978) 808-1932&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;07/10 UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; I have updated this entire event. Recent reports (and previous experience) lead me to believe that we will (a) be moving slower than normal because of the trail conditions between the Willard and Bunnell Notch and (b) I want to make sure we find a spot to set-up our tents near a water source.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While we will be backpacking the ridge and hitting ML Starr King, Waumbek, the Weeks, Terrace, Cabot, the Bulge, and the Horn, I have changed where we will meet, the direction that we will travel, how far we will go, and the place where we will end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will NOT be staying at the Cabot Cabin, instead we will be staying in tents that we set-up in the woods. There are no “designated” sites so we will have to find our own. Space will be limited so we won’t all be able to set-up our own individual tents – sharing is not only encouraged, it’s required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP.&lt;/strong&gt; Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself and others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;What we're doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to backpack the Kilkenny Ridge from the south to the north – along the way we will climb ML Starr King, Waumbek, the Weeks, Terrace, Cabot, the Bulge, the Horn, and Unnamed Pond Peak (easy bushwhack).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be setting up camp in Willard Notch. Because we will be finding our own camping “sites” we need to follow the backcountry camping rules which require us to be 200 feet away from any water and the trail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt; (~1.5 MPH) backpack trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 20.6 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 7,100 feet&lt;/strong&gt; - it &lt;strong&gt;will take us two days to complete this trip&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On Day #1 we will travel about 9.8 miles and climb about 4,000 feet (Starr King Trail lot to Willard Notch). On Day #2 we will travel about 10.8 miles and climb about 3,100 feet (Willard Notch to Unknown Pond Trail – South lot).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Warm_Weather_Backpacking.pdf"&gt;Click for a list of required items needed for a warm weather backpacking trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Group_Backpacking.pdf"&gt;Click for an idea of the required group gear needed for a warm weather backpacking trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;TENTS&lt;/span&gt;: This is not car camping – we won’t have unlimited space to set up our tents. Unless you will be using a one-person bivy sack or a one-person hammock you will need to share a tent with someone - use the comment section for this event to coordinate this among yourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;WATER PURIFICATION &amp;amp; STORAGE&lt;/span&gt;: I have a water filter, a 10 liter &amp;amp; a 20 liter water buckets for bringing water back to camp, and a 10 liter water bag for storing clean water. We could use one more filter so let me know if you have one that you want to bring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;FOOD&lt;/span&gt;: Each person is responsible for his or her own food – you will need to carry it and cook it yourself. You will also need to bring a way to hang it (i.e. “Bear Bag”) or protect it (i.e. “Bear Canister”).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;STOVE &amp;amp; FUEL&lt;/span&gt;: We should bring at least two stoves and fuel. It would be good if we brought the same type so we could share fuel. I have two Jet Boils that I could bring and I have enough fuel canisters for the group. I also have a pot and a frying pan. Let me know if you have a stove that you want to bring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;KITCHEN TARP&lt;/span&gt;: I have a tarp that we can set-up over the kitchen area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will finalize the details before the trip but be sure you have extra space in your backpack after you pack your gear. I will coordinate with everyone to make sure we have the necessary group gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet at 7:00 AM at the Unknown Pond Trail lot on the north side of York Pond Road near Berlin, NH. According to Google Maps this spot is about 195 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 45 minutes to drive there. This is the end of our trip so we will leave a few cars here and then drive to reach our starting point.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;• &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.498149,-71.358444(Unknown+Pond+Trailhead+-+south)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.498149,-71.358444&amp;amp;sspn=0.009091,0.0209&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFeX8pgIdFCi_-w&amp;amp;oq=Boston&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;Click for customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (google.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will try to coordinate a place for people to stay on Friday night. I will let you know more information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Chiurri</member_name><member_id>46583982</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1344098474000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337972118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K: Two-Day Backpack of the Kilkenny Ridge (INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED)</name><id>66342392</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>129600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343473200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/66342392/</event_url></item>