<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Arrow St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371070</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.868.2033</phone><name>Pierre Menard Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>347668</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a reading to celebrate the publication of Little Star's second issue. Little Star, an annual journal of poetry and prose, was founded in 2009 by Ann Kjellberg and Melissa Green. Readers will include Eugene Ostashevsky, Melissa Green, Steven Cramer, James Stotts, Nora Delaney, George Kalogeris, and Daniel E. Pritchard. Refreshments will be served after the reading and copies of the issue will be on hand to purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: Sunday January 23, 7:00pm - 10:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Pierre Menard Gallery&lt;br /&gt;10 Arrow Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven Cramer is the author of four poetry collections: The Eye that Desires to Look Upward (1987), The World Book(1992), Dialogue for the Left and Right Hand (1997), andGoodbye to the Orchard (2004), which won the 2005 Sheila Motton Prize from the New England Poetry Club, and was named a 2005 Honor Book in Poetry by the Massachusetts Center for the Book. His poems and criticism have appeared in numerous literary journals, including The Atlantic Monthly, The Nation, The New Republic, The Paris Review, Partisan Review, Poetry, and Triquarterly; as well as in The Autumn House Anthology of Contemporary American Poets and The POETRY Anthology, 1912–2002.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eugene Ostashevsky's books of poetry include Iteratureand Infinite Recursor Or The Bride of DJ Spinoza, both available through Ugly Duckling Presse. His work has also appeared in Best American Poetry, Jubilat, Boston Review, and Fence. A recipient of a 2005 poetry fellowship from NYFA, he translates Russian absurdist literature of the 1930s, and is the editor of OBERIU: An Anthology of Russian Absurdism, published by Northwestern University Press. His new chapbook, Enter Morris Imposternak, Pursued by Ironies, was published by Ugly Duckling Presse in January 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Melissa Green  is the author of The Squanicook Eclogues, Color Is the Suffering of Light, and Fifty Two. She has received the Norma Farber Award from the Poetry Society of America and the Lavan Award from the Academy of American Poets. Her work has been published in AGNI,  The New York Review of Books, FULCRUM, and Little Star and other publications. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George Kalogeris teaches English Literature and Classics in Translation at Suffolk University in Boston, Massachusetts. He is the author of a book of poems based on the life of Albert Camus, Camus: Carnets (Pressed Wafer, 2006). His poems and translations have appeared in Literary Imagination, Poetry, The Oxford Gazette, Agni, Harvard Review, and elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daniel E. Pritchard is the Marketing Director of Boston Review; founder and editor of The Critical Flame: A Journal of Literature and Culture; and the managing editor of Fulcrum: An Annual of Poetry and Aesthetics. He runs the U 35 poetry series. His poetry and essays have been published in Fulcrum, Little Star, Dark Sky, The Quarterly Conversation, The Millions, and elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James Stotts is the youngest of five; poet, translator, jongleur, and father. His work has been published in Little Star, Action Yes, AGNI, Critical Flame, and 1913. He is currently engaged with Russian poetry between the wars (Esenin, Vaginov, Mariengof, etcetera).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nora Delaney is a Boston-based writing instructor, Dutch-English translator, poet, and essayist. She is a founding member of the Boston Poetry Union and Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press. Her work has been published or is forthcoming in Fulcrum, Absinthe: New European Writing, Jacket, Literary Imagination, Critical Flame, The Arts Fuse, and other publications. Her chapbook of poetry Tiles Kissing Close was published by Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press in 2010.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295885074000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295287613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Little Star 2 Launch</name><id>16079850</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295827200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/16079850/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_8983348.jpeg</photo_url></item>