<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Nashua Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.764412</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-883-0996</phone><name>Margaritas</name><city>Nashua</city><id>730685</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463126</lon></venue><fee><label>Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The New Hampshire Coalition for Limited Government is comprised of concerned citizens who desire that those individuals elected to represent them in local and state government promote and implement the principles of limited government.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Greater Nashua chapter of the NHCLG focuses on the City of Nashua and the surrounding towns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHCLG believes that government derives its power from the consent of the governed. That those representatives in government should be open, accessible, accountable and responsive as outlined in Article 8 of the New Hampshire Constitution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHCLG believes that government should be limited in scope only to those functions which serve to protect the life, liberty, and property of the governed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHCLG accomplishes its goals through activism, involvement, and educating both local representatives and voters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHCLG will strive to hold all locally elected officials accountable for their actions in order to ensure that they act on the behalf of the people.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our group will have exclusive use of an off-hours section of Margaritas.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg Surbey</member_name><member_id>3479382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229274654000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226891895000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coalition for Limited Government - Greater Nashua Monthly Meeting</name><id>9176345</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228667400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/9176345/</event_url></item>