<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm &lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;so&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt; glad I scheduled this meetup on Saturday -- I need a break! &lt;a href="http://joyofgeocaching.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Our book&lt;/a&gt; is due to the publisher on Monday, so we're going NuTz trying to finish it up. My eyes are crossing, my shoulders are sore from more hours at my computer than a human should tolerate. I need a movie with my peeps!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO... the 3D version starts at 8:10 on Saturday night. Let's meet outside the theater doors &lt;b&gt;BY 7:30&lt;/b&gt; so we can buy tickets and treats and grab our seats (why didn't I come up with that little rhyme before now?!). This showing will probably be crowded, considering it's a Saturday night, so if you're late, gimme a call so I can keep the rather largeish group together for the movie. Also, pls keep your RSVP up to date online, so I know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another note: The 3D version will undoubtedly be worth it. And by &amp;quot;it&amp;quot; I mean an extra $3 per ticket. It's the theater -- not me. Sorry! So the total is going to be $11 per ticket (as opposed to $13.25 at the window). The good news is you get to keep the wicked cool 3D glasses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who's &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810014785/details" target="_blank"&gt;Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; for seeing the latest Disney/Pixar movie? Apparently this is the production studio team's first foray into 3D and I hear it's fanTAStic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Carl Fredricksen spent his entire life dreaming of exploring the globe and experiencing life to its fullest. But at age 78, life seems to have passed him by, until a twist of fate (and a persistent 8-year old Junior Wilderness Explorer named Russell) gives him a new lease on life.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Up in 3D!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246219539000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243993177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Up in 3D</name><id>10561346</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244935800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10561346/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>