<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>58 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01038</zip><lat>42.372700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Dike</name><city>Hatfield </city><id>761794</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.594704</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This walk is along the Connecticut River in Hatfield, Massachusetts.  This walk will take place September 21st at 3:00 PM.  It is people and dog friendly.  All dogs must be leashed.  There is a wide path that provides plenty of space for several walkers with their doggy companions.  The Town of Hatfield is a historic agricultural river town on the west bank of the Connecticut River. The Connecticut River forms the eastern and southern boundary of the town. It is also part of the Mill River Watershed.  There are incredible views of the Connecticut River on the left side of the path.  On the right side of the path, you will view the farmlands of Hatfield.  There is a spot where our dogs can take a dip in the river if weather permits.  While driving to this location, you will view the remarkable historic character of Hatfield made up of a dense concentration of well-preserved 18th and 19th century family homes.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This walk can last endless hours.  Plan to walk an hour out and an hour back.  We will walk one hour and turn around to walk the same path back.  However, there are a few other paths back that we can choose to take as a group.  It is a very easy walk that everyone can join.  We can stop at anytime for a rest and fuel up for energy.  I think this is a great walk where everyone can meet, get to know one another, and discuss further walks/hikes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be holding a "Meetup" sign...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279046839000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221264691000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A WALK ALONG THE CONNECTICUT RIVER</name><id>8747114</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222023600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/8747114/</event_url></item>