<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;EAT GREEN, BE GREEN, AND WEAR GREEN&lt;br /&gt;featuring Anna Forkan and Kristen Overlook&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://rawyum.googlepages.com/clover.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the spirit of St. Patrick's Day, we will be celebrating all things green.  Join us for a lecture on the power of greens in a raw and living foods diet, how eating green can heal the planet, and how wearing green is just plain fun.  We will share facts and figures but also anecdotal information to inspire and motivate all of you to take charge of your health.  We will share 20 years of education, experience and passion about wellness and the raw food lifestyle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.revitalive.com" target="_blank"&gt;Revitalive™ Health &amp;amp; Wellness, LLC&lt;/a&gt; was founded by Kristen Overlock &amp;amp; Anna Forkan to provide a full service raw and living foods education and wellness center in Newburyport, Mass. Their wellness practice draws on the pioneering research and expertise of Drs. Ann Wigmore, Norman Walker, Bernard Jensen, Arnold Ehret, and many more. Both Kristen and Anna have worked at the world renowned Ann Wigmore Natural Health Institute.  Dr. Wigmore is widely recognized as the mother of the raw foods movement, and is responsible for popularizing sprouts and wheatgrass into our diets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 PM Registration, 6 - 7 PM Gourmet potluck, 7 PM lecture&lt;br /&gt;Admission Fee with Food: $10;  $10 extra without food.  &lt;br /&gt;Bring an organic, raw, unprocessed, vegan, plant-based dish to serve 8 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions, call&lt;br /&gt;Betsy Bragg, Executive Director&lt;br /&gt;Optimum Health Solution &lt;br /&gt;337 Newton Street, #4&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02453&lt;br /&gt;Office 781-899-6664/Cell 617-835-2913&lt;br /&gt;Fax 617-663-6868&lt;br /&gt;Email betsy@optimumhealthsolution.org&lt;br /&gt;See Calendar of Events in &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com&lt;/a&gt; for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128: Take the Trapelo Road exit (one exit south of Route 2) east toward Belmont. Route 60 is about 3 to 4 miles down the road. Turn right.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Transportation&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge/Harvard Square: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the 73 Bus to the final stop at Waverly Oaks Square in Belmont. From Waverly Oaks you can make a connection to the 554 Bus, which goes to Waltham, and runs directly past the farm. The bus stop is located on Trapelo Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternately you can take the 70 Bus from Central Square, Cambridge toward Waltham. Ask to get off at the intersection of Routes 20 and 60. Follow Route 60 away from Main Street, all the way until you get to Beaver Street. Take a left onto Beaver Street; the farm and building will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Waltham Center: Take the 554 Bus which runs directly past the farm on Beaver Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Commuter Rail: Take the Fitchburg line to Waltham Center and follow directions above. The Fitchburg line also stops at Waverly Square where you can catch the 554 Bus to the farm (not all trains stop at Waverly though so check schedule)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Driving Directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge: Take Mount Auburn Street past the cemetery and bear right onto Belmont Street (this is just past the Star Market). Travel on Belmont Street (this becomes Trapelo Road) to the intersection with Route 60, about 3 miles. Turn left onto Route 60. Follow Arlington/Belmont directions below. Alternately take Route 2 to Route 60 and follow Arlington/Belmont directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Arlington or Belmont: Take Route 60 West to Beaver Street. Take a right onto Beaver Street. The UMass Field Station is about 100 yards up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Waltham or Watertown: Take Route 60 East from Main Street Waltham (Route 20). Beaver Street will be the first traffic light, turn left onto Beaver St onto Route 60, then follow Arlington/Belmont directions above. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posted by Mara &lt;a href="http://www.rawyum.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.rawyum.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please tell Betsy you are with the Boston Rawfood Meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4177857</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237498900000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235009165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck/Talk: EAT GREEN</name><id>9772637</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237325400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/9772637/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/e/global_7633262.jpeg</photo_url></item>