<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Bigger Than Life&lt;/b&gt; USA 1956 95 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm unfamiliar with this film, but it does look interesting....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the director of Rebel Without a Cause, In a Lonely Place, and Johnny Guitar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film Comment magazine recently chose Nicholas Ray's &lt;b&gt;Bigger Than Life&lt;/b&gt; as one of the 20 greatest films not available on video. Martin Scorsese included a clip of it in his great documentary A Personal Journey With Martin Scorsese Through American Movies. Jonathan Rosenbaum recently chose it as one of the 100 greatest American films of all time, and Jean-Luc Godard chose it as one of the ten greatest American films of all time during his Cahiers du Cinema days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A superbly shot critique of the suffocating conformity, repression and materialism at the heart of middle-class life, &lt;b&gt;Bigger Than Life&lt;/b&gt; is the American Beauty of 50s cinema.  BBC Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bigger Than Life&lt;/b&gt; by Nicholas Ray  Ed Avery (James Mason) lives with his family in a quiet suburban neighborhood. But in his pursuit of the American dream, he secretly works a second job, and quietly suffers from painful physical spasms. One day he collapses, and the doctors discover he suffers from a serious arterial disease. His only hope of survival is cortisone treatments, a new drug at the time. Avery jumps at the chance and makes a gradual but seemingly full recovery. Not until a few weeks later does it become clear that he's not quite the same. The film is “one of the best, most radical, least-known American films of the 1950s. A canny retelling of the Jekyll and Hyde story…a series of immaculate hedgerows, picket fences, and modern kitchen appliances transforms into a dystopian, surrealist expanse” (Village Voice).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nicholas Ray’s adaptation of a New Yorker article about one man’s descent into prescription-drug hell nearly derailed his Hollywood career. But if you need proof of Godard’s assertion that “the cinema is Nicholas Ray,” it’s all here, in every claustrophobic close-up and looming low-angle shot. The suits wanted a torn-from-the-headlines melodrama; what they got was the director at his expressionistic best, subverting the suburban fantasy and leaving nothing but tattered gray flannel and scorched earth in his wake.  Time Out NY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While on the surface&lt;b&gt; Bigger Than Life&lt;/b&gt; is a warning about the use of untested and possibly dangerous drugs (Avery's psychosis is brought on by dangerously high dosages of cortisone, still in the experimental stages at the time), what's most memorable about the film is Mason's superbly modulated performance (one of the best of his career), in which he gradually transforms from a typical high school teacher and suburban dad into a megalomaniac who refuses to accept anything less than perfection from his students or his family -- even going so far to suggest he can do better than God in his judgment of his son's worth. Mason and Ray took the typically over-ambitious father who pesters Junior for good grades and a home run in his next little league game, and exaggerated him into something truly terrifying. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should make for an interesting conversation to say the least-we'll stroll down Huntington Ave and find a place for lunch and our discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252632989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nicholas Ray's Bigger Than Life</name><id>11343497</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254061800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11343497/</event_url></item>