<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>172 Exchange St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.879723</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-723-4266</phone><name>GAMM Theatre</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>450230</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.379850</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>47.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We got a lot of votes in our recent poll for this show, and it looks pretty popular -- it's almost sold out! It should be amazing - it features music from Pink Floyd, Rolling Stones and the Grateful Dead. **This will be one of the last Meetups of the season, as I typically take a break over the summer and we start up again with the fall season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rock_%27n%27_Roll_%28play%29" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Or read the New York Times &lt;a href="http://theater.nytimes.com/2007/11/05/theater/reviews/05rock.html" target="_blank"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Meetup details:&lt;/span&gt; Tickets are $40 + outrageous handling fees (theatre, Amazon payments) = $47. When you RSVP, please pay online. If I can't get tickets, I will refund your money. Don't wait -- there are still seats left, but I'm sure they will sell out. The deadline to RSVP is &lt;b&gt;5 pm April 9&lt;/b&gt;. If you miss the deadline, but still want to go, send me an email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show starts at 8 pm, and we will meet in the lobby of the &lt;a href="http://www.gammtheatre.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Sandra Feinstein Gamm Theatre&lt;/a&gt; at 7:15 p.m. There is limited parking on the left side of the theatre and on the streets around the back of the theatre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the show, we will head up the street to &lt;a href="http://www.dohertyseastave.com/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Doherty's East Avenue Irish Pub&lt;/a&gt; for food and drinks -- a fun local pub.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Summary:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You won’t want to miss the Rhode Island premiere of an extraordinary theatrical event from four-time Tony Award winner Tom Stoppard (Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead, Travesties, The Real Thing, The Coast of Utopia). It's August 1968, and Russian tanks are rolling into Prague. Jan, a recently repatriated Czech student, lives for rock music. Max, a Cambridge professor and dyed-in-the-wool Marxist, lives for Communism. By 1990, revolution has taken hold, the tanks are rolling out and idealism is nowhere to be found. All that remains is love...and loud music. A sweeping drama spanning two countries and 22 turbulent years—punctuated by the soul-stirring sounds of legendary groups like the Stones, Pink Floyd and the Grateful Dead—Rock ‘n’ Roll is a complex, moving and electrifying exploration of society in the throes of transformation. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274013933000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268584382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rock n Roll - Gamm</name><id>12873102</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273965300000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/12873102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/5/global_12093749.jpeg</photo_url></item>