<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Fenway Park</address_2><address_1>82A Lansdowne Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.347164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 262-2424</phone><name>The Bleacher Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>735764</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;'Let's go back for the newest game in town at Bleacher Bar, Trivia + Bingo = Trivingo. ' Two classic games combined to form an exciting, nonstop, group game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff, is an awesome game host because he keeps the game moving and entertaining while DJ Frank drops great interlude jams. Ryan, the Bleacher Bar manager has been so accommodating and Joe has got to be the BEST bartender bar none (pun very intended). He's saved our seats at the bar with glasses of water waiting for us and is always so very welcoming,&amp;nbsp;attentive and pleasant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Hour team, Unstoppable Force Isabel, Cliff, Melissa and newbie Sean) won the big prizes ($50 gift card as well as $25 from a billion $ scratch card). They also were the smahtest team in the room because they got the most correct answers. Let's bring more teams so we can win more prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;ADMISSION IS FREE AND THERE IS NO COST TO PLAY TRIVINGO&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 21 AND PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Trivingo begins at 8:00 PM&lt;/span&gt; but you're welcome to arrive when you can and stay as long as you're able.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're interested in joining a team...please answer the question which appears after you RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you come hungry, here's the &lt;a href="http://bleacherbarboston.com/pdf/bleacher_menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;food and beer menu&lt;/a&gt;. There is also a special bucket of ponys for $18 in addition to a respectable assortment of bottled beer as well as on draft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bleacher Bar is unique because it is located beneath the Fenway Park bleachers in center field. There's a window which has a great view through centerfield into the park, it is the only view of its kind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Nearest subway station Kenmore on the Green Line, which is about a ten (10) minute walk.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the Meetup Crews at the bar</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298598286000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296252909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivingo Happy Hour on Thursday February 24th 7:30 PM</name><id>fwdkqypdbgc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298593800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/16349304/</event_url></item>