<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Last year on  July 30th,two of our greatest film artists passed away- Ingmar Bergman and Michelangelo Antonioni. While both The Brattle and The HFA have screened retrospectives of Bergman's works there has been none as of yet in the Boston area for Antonioni. While I am unsure why ( my own guess is for legal and/or copyright laws) the HFA is screening two of Antonioni's films in February. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Antonioni is probably best known for ?Blowup,? a 1966 drama set in Swinging London about a fashion photographer who comes to believe that a photograph he took of two lovers in a public park also shows, hidden in the background, evidence of a murder. But his true, lasting contribution to cinema resides in an earlier trilogy ? ?L?Avventura? in 1959, ?La Notte? in 1960 and ?L?Eclisse? in 1962 ? which explores the filmmaker?s tormented central vision that people had become emotionally unglued from one another.&lt;br /&gt; NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;L'eclisse&lt;/b&gt;  123 minutes 1962&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this challenging drama by Michelangelo Antonioni, his characteristic long, significant periods of silence punctuate the message that people just cannot seem to communicate with each other. Capping off Antonioni's previous two films (L'avventura and La Notte) in much the same style, this tale involves a woman, Vittoria (Monica Vitti), who has just suffered the break-up of an imperfect relationship with a staunch intellectual (Francisco Rabal). Piero (Alain Delon), a stockbroker, casts his romantic gaze in Vittoria's direction and the woman gradually relents and they begin a tentative affair. There is much to appreciate in this man who is not overly intellectual and is blessedly free of complications, and the same can be said of Vittoria. Yet their innermost fears play upon both of them in ways that go against an honest expression of their love ? and against a lasting relationship.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the obligatory review:  &lt;a href="http://www.sover.net/~ozus/eclipse.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sover.net/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is still yet another free screening at the HFA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film should provide for an interesting conversation afterward-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200710547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Michelangelo Antonioni's L'eclisse</name><id>7147628</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204156800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7147628/</event_url></item>