<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>156 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>12542</zip><lat>41.592745</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>845.236.4265</phone><name>Benmarl Winery</name><city>Marlboro</city><id>672534</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.980867</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's join the Fairfield singles for a fun grape stomping wine tasting day. &lt;br /&gt;This was a blast last year!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ctsingles/calendar/13824480/"&gt;Fairfield singles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come join us and share a laid back Sunday afternoon. Let's take in the beautiful vistas and Fall foliage, eat, dance or just relax and enjoy the company of so many of our Meetup members! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a multi-group event so keep in mind there will be over 6 other various Meetup groups attending&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is adults $15.00, $10 for non drinking adults and Children under 21, FREE! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a lawn chair, a jacket and something to share like cheese and crackers fruit or anything you can think of that would compliment the event. There will be food there to purchase but some nosh food is always welcomed! Last year we had quite a spread from all our members so please bring what you can to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also keep in mind that it's right over the Newburgh/Beacon Bridge so you may want to carpool with a friend and split the gas. I will post this on the message board so that members can communicate with each other for carpooling purposes. Please post from which location you'll be leaving from and how many you can accommodate.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>""Look for the MeetupTable Signs and the organizers!""</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286834657000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281648644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multi-Group Meetup ANNUAL HARVEST GRAPESTOMPING FESTIVAL </name><id>14405742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286726400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/14405742/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/9/global_17138217.jpeg</photo_url></item>