<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Prospect Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367650</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)354-5287 or (857)417-4021c</phone><name>Out Of The Blue Gallery</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>839245</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101909</lon></venue><fee><label>suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>KIM ADRIAN (“Famous Cake”), PAUL STONE (“Home to Train a Rock”), and poet DIANE LOCKWOOD&lt;br /&gt;Hosted by Timothy Gager&lt;br /&gt;www.direreader.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim Adrian's essay &amp;quot;How to Buy Peaches&amp;quot; appears in the current issue of Tin House. Excerpts from her memoir-in-progress are due out soon in Ninth Letter and the Gettysburg Review.  She was recently featured in the Improper Bostonian in an article called &amp;quot;Minds that Matter: Boston's 11 Brightest Young Scientists, Artists, and Thinkers.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Stone will be reading from &amp;quot;Or So It Seems&amp;quot;, his innovative, comic romp of a novel, as well as from “How To Train A Rock” (just released!), his collection of short insights and fiction flights. Both books are published by Blind Elephant Press.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Diane Lockward is the author of What Feeds Us, (Wind Publications, 2006). The collection received the Quentin R. Howard Poetry Prize. Diane is also the author of two previous collections, Eve’s Red Dress (Wind Publications, 2003) and a chapbook, Against Perfection (Poets Forum Press, 1998). Her poems have been published in several anthologies, including Poetry Daily: 366 Poems from the World’s Most Popular Poetry Website and Garrison Keillor's Good Poems for Hard Times. Her poems have also appeared in such journals as Beloit Poetry Journal, Spoon River Poetry Review, Poetry International, Poet Lore, and Prairie Schooner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.timothygager.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.timothygag...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call 617-935-4951</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244848731000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241222870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dire Reading Series: Adrian, Stone, and Lockwood at Out of the Blue Gallery</name><id>10315717</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244246400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/10315717/</event_url></item>