<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Redstone Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.801041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rave Motion Pictures Buckland Hills</name><city>Manchester</city><id>664343</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.547752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I've decided to cross post this because some of our members aren't in the Hartford Movies Meet up.  This is one of my top ten movies of the year. (1939 was a great year). Thanks to Karen for posting first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NCM Fathom, Warner Home Video and Turner Classic Movies present The Wizard of Oz 70th Anniversary Hi-Def Event featuring the first ever High Definition presentation in movie theatres nationwide. This One Night Event will take place in over 440 movie theatres nationwide on Wednesday, September 23rd at 7:00 p.m. (local time). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to the feature presentation of The Wizard of Oz, this exclusive event will include a special introduction by Robert Osborne, a classic film historian and host of Turner Classic Movies, followed by We're Off to See the Wizard, a look into how Frank L. Baum's classic novel was transformed into one of the most beloved films of all time including archival interviews, behind-the-scenes footage and rare musical outtakes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also featured will be an exclusive clip of the Scarecrow, Ray Bolger, dancing in High-definition for the very first time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ncm.com/Fa.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ncm.com/Fa...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks Margo Lynn for the suggestion!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"The movie starts at 7:00. Let's meet in the lobby by Chatter no later than 6:45."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253919257000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252097463000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wizard of Oz</name><id>11292076</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253745900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11292076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>