<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25A Portland Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.196813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-516-3276</phone><name>The Farm Bar &amp; Grille</name><city>Dover</city><id>4790072</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870963</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Brave-Boat-Books/"&gt;Brave Boat Book Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, a non-fiction book discussion group!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We&amp;nbsp;read and discuss most any genre of non-fiction including, biography, memoir, history, science, nature, the arts, cooking, travel, current affairs, interpersonal relations... you name it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll learn about all sorts of new ideas, things,&amp;nbsp;trends, and cultures - and to open our minds and make new friends in the process. The only ground rules are that everyone is at all times respectful of the ideas and opinions of others, and that everyone be conscious of allowing others time to speak. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Book Selection&lt;/strong&gt;: In order to get things started, I'll select the first couple of titles. After that, each (regularly attending) member (who wants to) will have a month to propose a list of three books. The rest of us will then vote on the following month's selection from among those three. This way, everyone will have a chance to propose books that interest them, and the rest of us still have some choice from month to month. This will also reward regular attendance. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;JANUARY SELECTION:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Dreams-My-Father-Story-Inheritance/dp/1400082773"&gt;Dreams from My Father: A Story of Race and Inheritance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;by Barack Obama&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/b/2/event_79410642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;-Our first selection is a memoir about growing up black in a white family, about the importance of fathers to the development of boys, and about how young men come to define themselves as they mature. This is not a book about politics or political ambition. That the author later became president of the US is interesting, but not necessary to the discussion. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 (Whether you agree or disagree with Obama's politics, I challenge you to read this memoir solely for the insight into race and the lives of young men that it can provide.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 -The Guardian: "honest, daring, and ambitious" -Toni Morrison: "a writer in my high esteem" -2006 Grammy for best spoken word (audio book) -Time Magazine's Top 100 non-fiction books since 1923. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Last Wednesday of the month - 6:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: The Farm Bar &amp;amp; Grille in Dover, NH. &lt;br /&gt;

 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Membership&lt;/strong&gt;: I'd like this group to be self-sustaining. Next month, I'll institute a nominal membership fee of $2/meeting (half a beer!) or $12/year (1.5 glasses of wine!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;If you have questions or comments, please don't hesitate to contact me!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;*Regarding religion and any other sensitive topic: I don't think we should shy away from them, necessarily. We read to learn about new ideas, after all, and controversy is often a part of that. But we should be especially sensitive to the views of others both in book selection and in our discussions. Also, we'll probably want to stay away from any faith-based texts including&amp;nbsp;non-science-based&amp;nbsp;healing, or other metaphysical topics&amp;nbsp;unless we are reading them in the spirit of an historical or comparative discussion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327849726000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323821038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brave Boat Book Group!</name><id>qxbpjcyqcbhc</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327534200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/44380502/</event_url></item>