<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi Journeyers to wholeness,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know you could turn a persistent self-judgment into an icing on a cake?&lt;br /&gt;Come and celebrate you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever felt they you could be living from a place of authentic self but something &amp;quot;is holding you back&amp;quot;?&lt;br /&gt;If you have time to join us this Thursday I have a yummy surprise for you. During the meetup I am going to teach a brand new, extremely powerful and effortless technique I have just came up with. It allows you to extract all the wonderful, colorful and multifaceted parts of you lost to old and persistent self-judgment or anger, or past trauma.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of us are faced with physical and emotional challenges on our life path, some more then others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all want to overcome blocks, once and for all &lt;br /&gt;And be healthier, happier and more fulfilled.&lt;br /&gt;But many of you who are coming to this meetup have arrived just at the point when they thought all hope was lost, not sure any longer you could &amp;quot;pull it off&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However there is a tool, EDR – Energetic Displacement reintegration, so powerful, so transformation, so life-altering, that everything changes.  You can be living your will again with all the passion of the authentic re-integrated YOU.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a SUPER valuable stuff, and as always we have great time learning it.&lt;br /&gt;So sign up early and Join us this Thursday for more powerful skills and techniques needed on your journey to freedom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273789373000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269144871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Icing On the cake - Celebrate You!</name><id>12944666</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269558000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/12944666/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/7/global_13786183.jpeg</photo_url></item>