<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-459-0802</phone><name>Heritage Farm Ice Cream &amp; Restuarant</name><city>Lowell</city><id>1314481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I thought it would be interesting to see where we've come since we first met by the river to &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Walk &amp;amp; Talk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, as my friend Eva would say; “&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;let’s recap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;”. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 1;&lt;/strong&gt; The “&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;Walk &amp;amp; Talk by the River&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;” meetup started on October 1st with just four of us – no frills, but the start of something great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 2;&lt;/strong&gt; We grew, by a whopping 300% or 12 new folks! Dogs were making a debut on the scene, and we all started sharing some wild &amp;amp; “&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;&lt;em&gt;interesting&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;” stories. Our dinner routine started here at the Heritage Restaurant making new friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 3;&lt;/strong&gt; 10 of us walked with still new faces appearing, and now 3 dogs! Went to our next simple dinner at the bowling alley and really got to know each other a little better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 4;&lt;/strong&gt; We had a “&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;meetup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;” visitor from across the pond join us; Solomon from the UK. This was fitting for we had already planned to have dinner and a surprise B-day party at the BBC (&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;&lt;em&gt;British Beer Company&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;)…. and what a time it was, Solomon set us straight with the food &amp;amp; BEER!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 5;&lt;/strong&gt; I answered the question people were quietly asking; “how long will we keep doing this walk?” Ha, I said in so many words; “never, we’ll walk, snowshoe, hike, or whatever till the FREE concerts come back in the spring!” Well maybe I shouldn't have said that too loud. What a surprise we had in store; SANDY! With my limited technical communications that I could muster up under this time of duress, I manage to get a few emails out and reschedule for that Wednesday. So what do we call that; week 5a?. Okay, sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 5a;&lt;/strong&gt; Even though only two of us showed for the walk, we had a great time walking with our dogs and dinner at "&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;Pho 88&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;" (a Vietnamese restaurant) where we met another member of our walks who is Vietnamese and ordered these incredible meals for us. Another good time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 6;&lt;/strong&gt; Cold evening for a walk. We must be crazy! But again just a great time even without a key member or two. Back to the “&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;Pho 88&lt;/span&gt;” for those who missed out. Wow, four new faces appeared, and now we even have a musician among us. I think we’ll start calling him: “&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;fiddler on the Walk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;”! Hey, you know who you are, please bring your fiddle and play as we walk this week. Irish I think he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 7;&lt;/strong&gt; Well now, that would be this week. So let’s meet at the same place, at the same time, and enjoy the incredibility warm weather that’s planned. After the walk, and the musical entertainment (hint, hint), we’ll be heading to the “&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;Athenian Corner Restaurant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;” @ 207 Market Street, Lowell. Now as it turns out, Monday is discount night. That means for every point the Patriots win by, they'll discount that % amount from the bill! Example; If the Patriots win by 20 points, your bill will be discounted by 20%. I’m told anything much over that and the place goes &lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;N&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;u&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; font-size : x-large"&gt;t&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #87cc9f ; font-size : medium"&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;. So let’s see what happens!......and NO, if they lose we don't pay extra!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/f/8/event_178870232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry no pictures of last week, but here’s a cool pic of what’s coming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Interesting; I've found that few, if any, “regulars in our group” actually read this stuff I post every week. As a result, they always ask questions that are answered herein. So, this week when they ask where we’re going for dinner, I’ll say "MacDonnells", and they can wait for the rest of us there! :{o Now would I do that?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; lol&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352818348000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352652822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Walk &amp; Talk Along the River!</name><id>90925422</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352759400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/90925422/</event_url></item>