<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>67 Kirk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.647323</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-970-5200</phone><name>Lowell National Historical Park</name><city>Lowell</city><id>710080</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.309705</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Am heading back to the Lowell Folk Festival this year, to get another great opportunity to experience a vast amount of truly diverse music.  The Festival runs from July 25-27th, but we'll be heading there on Sunday to close the place down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the details at the website: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available at a number of garages in the area for about $10 for the day.  It's going to be a crowded day, but will provide my cell phone so folks can catch up with us as the day goes on (you must reply yes or maybe to have my number sent your way).  There are a few spots I'm planning to be at at certain times to try and facilitate meeting.  My apologies for forcing my music choices upon you:-)  Check out the festival map to find us:  &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/festival_map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the schedule at: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/schedule.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And check out the performers at: &lt;a href="http://www.lowellfolkfestival.org/performers.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lowellfolk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Initial meeting spot:   Framingham park and ride at 10 am: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonmpo.org/bostonmpo/info/pnr/Framingham-west.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonmpo....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Second meeting spot: JFK stage to catch Lonesome River Band, a blue grass band from 12:00-12:45.  All kinds of ethnic food is available all around this location which is why it seemed a great stage to start at.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As most know, we hit the festival yesterday and have some must sees to catch, but folks can split up if their musical stylings don't fit our own.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll probably be seeing Reveillon's at the Dutton St. Dance Pavillion from 1-1:45; then camping out at the JFK Stage between 2-4:15 for Whitetop Mtn Band and Redd Volkaert and Cindy Cashdollar.  We may see a little more Whitetop at St. Anne's Churchyard b/w 4:15-5 before making sure we catch Reveillon again b/w 5:15-6 p.m.  Definitely one of the best groups at the festival and worth catching as many times as you can.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival ends at 6 pm and will contemplate dinner to end the day if folks desire.  No worries, we'll get ya back to Boston with plenty of sleep time for work on Monday:-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet up at any of the listed spots, or call me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217345036000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215970108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lowell Folk Festival</name><id>8332689</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217171700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8332689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>