<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last year at the sactuary we saw several deer, a turtle laying her eggs, and had chickadees feeding from our hands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich River, Mass Audubon?s largest sanctuary, offers more than 10 miles of interconnecting trails that invite you to explore the forests, meadows, and wetlands. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other features in this sanctuary: Canoe along eight miles of the Ipswich River that run through the sanctuary and camp on Perkins Island, located a half-mile up the river (members can rent canoes from May through October). Members can also rent a cabin that is conveniently located close to the sanctuary?s office and program facilities and sleeps four. In April, listen for the chorus of American toads and pickerel frogs. Watch for river otters, painted turtles, and great blue herons at various times throughout the year. Climb the drumlin and esker, landscape features created by a glacier 15,000 years ago. Huge rocks and exotic trees and shrubs that were part of a former arboretum provide an adventurous walk along the Rockery Trail. This sanctuary has the following universally accessible facilities: Restrooms, Barn, Education Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;87 Perkins Row&lt;br /&gt;Topsfield, MA 01983&lt;br /&gt;978-887-9264&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged, please ask for or offer a ride in your rsvp comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ipswichriver@massaudubon.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massaudubon.org/Nature_Connection/Sanctuaries/Ipswich_River/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massaudubo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission:&lt;br /&gt;$4 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember children (3-12) and seniors &lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston and the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 50 and follow Rt 1 north. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97, turn right onto Rt 97 south (toward Beverly and Danvers). Follow Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 53A and follow Rt 97 south. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97 in Topsfield, stay on Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at this great family run italian restaurant:&lt;br /&gt;Trattoria Ponte Vecchio&lt;br /&gt;435 Newbury St # 101, Danvers, MA (2.82 miles away)&lt;br /&gt;978-777-9188&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209481662000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208641984000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary walk</name><id>7771199</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209308400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7771199/</event_url></item>