<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>S.E. 10th Avenue</address_2><address_1>Port Everglades</address_1><state>FL</state><zip>33301</zip><lat>26.096199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-419-5179/7418 </phone><name>Emerald Princess</name><city>Ft. Lauderdale</city><id>978281</id><country>us</country><lon>-80.113655</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FABULOUS SINGLES CARIBBEAN  CRUISE ON THE MAGNIFICENT   EMERALD PRINCESS DEPARTS ON OCTOBER 25 2009 FROM FORT LAUDERDALE WITH THE IRA, AS YOUR GRACIOUS HOST!!!!!      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                  &lt;b&gt;LOVE BOAT INFO BELOW   &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7 GLORIOUS DAYS OF FUN, TERRIFIC ALL YOU CAN EAT  FOOD  ( No Cooking for 7 Days)  24/7 NON-STOP ENTERTAINMENT, ISLAND ADVENTURES, AND WHO KNOWS- &lt;i&gt;YOU MAY MEET THAT SPECIAL PERSON OF YOU LIFE!!!!!     &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: Under $100.00 a day!!!  From:$675.36 Per Person. Rooms are filling up very quickly; a small deposit will hold your space. &lt;b&gt;The sooner the better that you sign up, as rooms go very quickly.&lt;/b&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For  Complete Details, and of course the Fine Print, please see the web site below:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;                                   &lt;a href="http://www.vacationstogo.com/singles_c3.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vacationst...&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                 DETAILS:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHIP:                              The Emerald Princess    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosting Information: I have traveled with Vacations to Go on their Single Cruises many times. They do an awesome job, generally getting a few hundred singles from around the county. In addition to their scheduled activities, I will host and organize smaller parties for “our group”, and if you are on the shyer side, or first time cruiser, I will be sure you are well introduced into the group. If you see someone of “interest”, where the “spark” is, yet “shy” or “apprehensive” of introducing your self to, I will be happy to do a “ classy” introduction.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                RESERVATION INFORMATION.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Please DO NOT BOOK  on line, as RJ and I need to know who is from  “our group”. See Below for Reservation Information.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Contact:  For Reservations and Information, Please contact:  RJ Hightower, rhightower@vacationstogo.com, 800-419-5179, extension 7418, from Monday to Friday, 10am to 7pm, CST .     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. When making the reservation, Please let him know you are part of The Ira Singles Group.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.  Send me an email at mistrchrming@aol.com,  or a phone call- 860-604-5792,  with any questions, and or if you  have booked this awesome cruise .    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Oct 25th    &lt;br /&gt;Sail from beautiful Fort Lauderdale at 5pm (boarding is from 1pm to 4pm). Join us poolside for the sail away festivities and meet lots of other fun-loving singles!     &lt;br /&gt;Monday, Oct 26th    &lt;br /&gt;From 9am to 4pm, enjoy Princess Cays, Bahamas, Princess Cruise Line's private destination on the southern tip of the island of Eleuthera in the outer Bahamas is full of activities promising a great island adventure! With a beautiful beach with barbeque and bar facilities, and a basketball court and water sports pier, everyone will enjoy the day on their own private tropical island!     &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, Oct 27th    &lt;br /&gt;Day at sea. Join in all the exciting singles activities hosted by your Vacations To Go host.     &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, Oct 28th    &lt;br /&gt;From 9am to 6pm, experience St. Maarten. Flying two flags, this island is half-French and half-Dutch. Cruise ships more commonly call on the Dutch side of St. Maarten, known for its shop-lined, narrow lanes and daytime casinos. Island tours, cruising on an America's Cup yacht and snorkeling excursions are offered in Philipsburg. Golfers should check out Mullet Bay.     &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, Oct 29th    &lt;br /&gt;From 7am to 4pm explore St. Thomas, U.S. Virgin Islands. This beautiful tropical island offers pristine beaches lapped by turquoise waters. The picturesque harbor town of Charlotte Amalie is known for its great duty-free shopping. The most popular shore excursions include island tours, a day at the beach at Magen's Bay, scuba diving and snorkeling expeditions, and explorations of the undersea world aboard an Atlantis submarine.     &lt;br /&gt;Friday, Oct 30th    &lt;br /&gt;From 1pm to 7pm, visit Grand Turk, Turks &amp;amp; Caicos Islands. This small island, only six miles long and three miles wide, provides all the activities sun lovers need. Spend time scuba diving, snorkeling, horseback riding on the beach or playing golf.     &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Oct 31st    &lt;br /&gt;Another day at sea. Take part in exclusive singles activities and mingle with friends.     &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Nov 1st    &lt;br /&gt;At 7am, the Emerald Princess returns to Fort Lauderdale. Be sure to gather those phone numbers to keep in touch with your new lifelong friends, and don't forget to plan ahead for your next cruise with Vacations To Go!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A Huge Ship on the Pier, called the EMERALD PRINCESS</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1256664244000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243605422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FABULOUS SINGLES CARIBBEAN  CRUISE-EMERALD PRINCESS </name><id>10522224</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256490000000</time><rsvp_limit>250</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/10522224/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/0/global_2943360.jpeg</photo_url></item>