<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE ADVANCED SCREENING &amp;amp; Actor Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** The Visitor **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please print out the pass located in the group's file for admission, each pass admits two - feel free to print as many as you need.  Just as an FYI: seating is not guaranteed and is available on a first come first served basis, so arrive early!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Synopsis:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thomas McCarthy's second film, after the charming Station Agent, is a quiet, hard look at several different aspects of humanity. The Visitor centers on Walter Vale, masterfully portrayed by Richard Jenkins. A solemn economics teacher, he spends his time pretending to write on his book and learn piano. Walter finds himself in New York on business and runs into two illegal immigrants, Tarek (Haaz Sleiman) and Zainab (Danai Jekesai Gurira who were tricked into renting his apartment. Tarek and Walter strike up an unusual friendship when Tarek begins to teach Walter how to play the drums. This is interrupted by Tarek's arrest and detention while it is decided whether he will be deported or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Visitor is a wonderful piece that brings together some of the best performances I have seen this year. McCarthy disarms us with wry humor and quiet wit and before we know it we've found ourselves immersed, not always so much in the plot, but in the characters themselves. The four leads have incredible chemistry. Tarek and Zainab who have only a handful of scenes together, share incredible chemistry. Richard Jenkins gives a soft but powerful performance of a man trapped inside the ambiguity of himself. Hiam Abbass, as Tarek's mother adds even more heart with her touching supporting role.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The title &amp;quot;The Visitor&amp;quot; lends itself to interpretation giving the film. It might be pegged at first sight as a political film, but it's more about people and their interactions with the people in their lives, as well as the world around them. Thomas McCarthy brings the charm of his previous film coupled with brilliant performances in this quiet, thought provoking drama that should not be missed.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opening: April 18th&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;object width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;embed src=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/v/9Ax3zvt_guo&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;quot;" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; type=&amp;quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&amp;quot; width=&amp;quot;425&amp;quot; height=&amp;quot;355&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/embed&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/object&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screening Stub here (print this out):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/225256/TheVisitor.4.9.08.jpg"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Remember, these aren't SOCIAL events, so there'll be no formal meeting afterwards.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chelsea</member_name><member_id>3861711</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212077786000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Get an early look!  There will be a brief Q&amp;A session with Tom McCarthy after film ends.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207372474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FreeAdvanced Screening The Visitor (Q&amp;A afterwards w/actor)</name><id>7677151</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207782000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7677151/</event_url></item>