<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>200.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Photographing the Painted Figure: A One Day Workshop with Scott Erb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a unique experience! If you are fascinated with the art of body painting and always wanted to learn more about studio lighting an extraordinary subject, this workshop is for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will be allowed the freedom of creative expression and can click creatively as painter Paul Roustan unveils a spectacular, one of a kind- for this workshop only- living canvas. Scott Erb will teach you about lighting this extraordinary subject, communicating effectively with the model, and how to craft your personal visions using different lenses and perspectives. Then the participants will take turns in creating their own portfolio quality imagery. The paint goes on ? the model brings the canvas to life, and you should be one of the photographers there to capture it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registering early is absolutely essential and limited to just 12 participants. Please be sure to register and have your deposit in by Sept 17, 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information will be sent you once we have a confirmed registration. But here are some details you need to know now?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $200.00 per person Deposit of 100.00 to hold your space and is not refundable unless we can fill your space.&lt;br /&gt;Payments- Can be made by check, money order, or PayPal and should be&lt;br /&gt;send to: Scott Erb, 380 Bridle Path, Worcester, MA 01604 with your name, address, email, and phone number.&lt;br /&gt;If you have a PayPal.com account and would like to send your payment this way, please got to the PayPal.com web site and click on the ?Send Money? tab. You can then send payment to scott@erbphoto.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Sept 22, 2007 from 12:00 pm to 6pm Note: Please arrive by 11:30 am for meet and greet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: The workshop will be taught in a professional studio space located in an industrial area with plenty of parking. The studio is fully equipped and will be set up and ready to go when participants arrive. Studio is located at 140 Kemble Street, Boston, MA 02119&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Workshop is available to serious photographers of all skill levels.  Attendee?s must have their own digital cameras. No point and shoot cameras will be allowed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to check out the body painter we have hired to come in and create our model?s canvas? www.PaulRoustan.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To see more details please visit Scott's other website: www.theintimateportrait.com and check the workshop section.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190649833000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188845492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photographing the Painted Figure: A One Day Workshop with Scott Erb</name><id>6290792</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190476800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6290792/</event_url></item>