<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Atlantic Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.361829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Christopher Columbus Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>927019</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051575</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This year continues the eight year tradition of the Waterfront Performing Arts Series at Christopher Columbus Park in the North End. Concerts are held on Tuesday evenings, 6 – 8 pm, from August 3rd to August 24th, and are &lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On August 10th, the artist will be &lt;a href="http://www.sarahborges.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sarah Borges and the Broken Singles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah's music is hard to define, but most often falls into the Alt-Country genre.  In 2009, she was nominated for the New and Emerging Artist award by the AMA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has been said that, &lt;i&gt;if Sid Vicious and Dolly Parton had a kid, she might sound something like Sarah Borges, who's making some of the most punked-out alt-country around&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Madison, WI - Isthmus - The Daily Page&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Sarah Borges made her name as a modern-minded honky-tonker with a retro streak. Her third album, “The Stars Are Out” (Sugar Hill), includes one tune apiece by the Lemonheads (her idea) and the Magnetic Fields (her producer’s), as well as Smokey Robinson’s “Being With You.” On these and a couple of other covers she sounds high-spirited and at ease, and her working band, the Broken Singles, backs her with just the necessary degree of twang.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a songwriter Ms. Borges lets in a bit more darkness, casting moods both defensive and reflective. Two of her most personal entries arrive at the album’s close. “Better at the End of the Day” is a weary self-exhortation, while “Symphony,” which includes sampled violin and analog synthesizers, assumes a philosophical tone. Both songs are striking for what’s missing: the bright certainty that Ms. Borges elsewhere exudes.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nate Chinen - New York Times&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email my cell number to all yes and maybe RSVPs the day of the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281539336000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280932270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sarah Borges and the Broken Singles (Waterfront Performing Arts Series)</name><id>14316276</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281476700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/14316276/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/e/global_16952046.jpeg</photo_url></item>