<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1150 Douglas Pike</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02917</zip><lat>41.911508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bryant University</name><city>Smithfield</city><id>1083344</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.515164</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Is &amp;ldquo;freethinker&amp;rdquo; just a euphemism for &amp;ldquo;atheist&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prof. Tony Houston&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unistructure 358&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This presentation explores some of the tensions between atheists and people of faith. It treats some of the more common defenses of religion based on intelligent design, faith in faith, non-overlapping magisteria, sacred texts as allegory and multiculturalism, as embraced by religious fundamentalists, religious moderates, agnostics, rationalists and universalists, respectively. The presentation differentiates between the more pernicious religious fundamentalism and the more benign moderate doctrines that merely enable it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inherent tension between science and religion is treated in the exposition of religious doctrine that conflates credulity with faith and skepticism with cynicism, resulting in habits of mind that are contrary to the precepts of critical thinking. Common logical fallacies in religious thought are refuted, including circular reasoning, solipsism, self-contradiction, bias and misplaced burden of proof. The paper also addresses common objections that people of faith raise about atheism, including the perceived arrogance of atheist disdain toward sacred beliefs, the stridency of atheist critique, the human desire for moral guidance and ultimate truth and the prospect of a world without divinely-inspired purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biography&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony Houston is Associate Professor of Spanish and Second Language Acquisition at Bryant University in Smithfield, RI. His research interests include psycholinguistics, classroom discourse, outcomes assessment and computer-assisted language learning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334775011000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Skeptics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>skeptics-133</urlname><id>357970</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Skeptics Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332810571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bryant University Research and Engagement Day</name><id>57996212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334770200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/skeptics-133/events/57996212/</event_url></item>