<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Broad Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.769672</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Welcome Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>432767</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.490380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We have made a severe dent in the 'to be done' lists for Nashua! Thanks to everybody who helps. It would take up most of this box just to list your names.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This canvassing will be coordinated with the 'BIG EVENT' canvassing day which appears on the Concord meetup board and others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We already have the walking lists and goodies so our packets are in Nashua and we will meet at 10:00 in the morning to start at our usual pad - the welcome Center at exit 6.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; After the canvassing, instead of just going home. we will meet up with the folks who canvas all over the state that day for some TBD activities. This will be the 'special' part of the day for us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make your needs for signs, flyers, buttons etc. known ahead of time and these will be delivered to you on Saturday morning..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please RSVP with these needs by tomorrow afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;If you have a TomTom or portable GPS - please RSVP so that we can know ahead of time for matching you up with those who may need it - or according to the most difficult lists. Also, if you want to help some newcomers to get into this, please RSVP and we will match you up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Thanks!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196694321000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193929995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BIG EVENT (local part) Canvassing in Nashua, NH</name><id>6655822</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196521200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6655822/</event_url></item>