<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay guys, next book's been chosen...straying from the polls with enthusiastic support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Common Ground: A Turbulent Decade in the Lives of Three American Families by J. Anthony Lukas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopses copied from:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alibris.com/booksearch?S=R&amp;amp;qisbn=9780394746166&amp;amp;qsort=p&amp;amp;siteID=iXJLaS8dYMs-tzNGkVTlNBkyozKNS3r2MQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.alibris.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;The climax of this humane account of 10 years in Boston that began with news of Martin Luther King's assassination, is a watershed moment in the city's modern history--the 1974 racist riots that followed the court-ordered busing of kids to integrate the schools. To bring understanding to that moment, Lukas, a former New York Times journalist, focuses on two working-class families, headed by an Irish-American widow and an African-American mother, and on the middle-class family of a white liberal couple. Lukas goes beyond stereotypes, carefully grounding each perspective in its historical roots, whether in the antebellum South, or famine-era Ireland. In the background is the cast of public figures--including Judge Garrity, Mayor White, and Cardinal Cushing--with cameo roles in this disturbing history that won the 1986 Pulitzer Prize for nonfiction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also: Winner 1985 — National Book Awards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner 1985 — National Book Critics Circle Awards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's timely, it's local, and it's a winner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in our typical spot (weather's clearly not up for an outside meeting yet), but always plan a trip across the street to Au Bon Pain (1100 Mass Ave) if ya don't find us and the crowds are crazy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the date may change!!  Figured I'd get this up and posted, but am guessing a little on my work schedule.  Will keep you posted:-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and the book on the table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240161584000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236695539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:Common Ground: A Turbulent Decade...</name><id>9922875</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239231600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/9922875/</event_url></item>