<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meetup Announcement&lt;br /&gt;The New Hampshire 912 Project&lt;br /&gt;Your group has a Meetup Wednesday, October 21, 2009 9:00 AM!&lt;br /&gt;What&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INCOME TAX PROTEST &amp;amp; FORUM - CONCORD STATE HOUSE&lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, October 21, 2009 9:00 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Hamphhire State House&lt;br /&gt;107 N Main St&lt;br /&gt;Concord NH 03303&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oct 21 from 9:00 AM - 4:30 PM in LOB 202-4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;House Ways and Means Committee Chairman Susan Almy is putting together a joint legislative summit to consider changes to the state's tax laws. Almy is one of the most vocal income tax supporters in state government. But she doesn't stop there. She likes lots of other taxes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year her committee recommended, and she advocated, an estate tax and a capital gains tax. She's spent years searching for ways to raise taxes on Granite Staters. That she's organizing the summit is worrisome. That she deliberately kept it a secret because, she acknowledges, she didn't want the income tax information to get out, is troubling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Almy claims that &amp;quot;If your impression of it is what the Union Leader editorial said, however, that is not going to be the subject matter. We are looking for input on our current revenue structure as a whole, how it affects businesses' ability to grow and provide decent jobs for all segments of our citizenry, and whether businesses and NH economists and tax critics have suggestions for improvement.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: This meeting is open to the public although we will not be allowed to ask questions or speak. We should at least plan to crowd the room to show our disdain for the mere consideration of ANY new taxes. Signs in the room will likely not be appropriate, but there is always the sidewalk for those who cannot fit inside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At issue: Taxes and more taxes... If you remember how the horse owners reacted when there was going to be a tax, and the dog breeders, the gunowners, and the campground owners, there really isn't a group who hasn't been affected by some rise in taxes or fees or a PROPOSED tax or fee. This affects everyone folks! Start spreading the word.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FEEL FREE TO CALL HER &amp;amp; TORELLI&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALMY CONTACT INFO:&lt;br /&gt;Home Address:&lt;br /&gt;266 Poverty Lane Unit 4B - LOOK SHE LIVES ON THE STREET SHE WILL PUT US ALL ON!!!&lt;br /&gt;Lebanon, NH 03766-2730&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (603)448-4769&lt;br /&gt;Email: susan.almy@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/house/committees/committeedetails.aspx?code=H28" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gencourt.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;==================================================================&lt;br /&gt;TORELLI CONTACT INFO LINK:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gencourt.state.nh.us/house/members/member.aspx?member=376154" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gencourt.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Home Address:&lt;br /&gt;35 Middle Road&lt;br /&gt;Portsmouth, NH 03801-4802&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (603)436-2108&lt;br /&gt;Email: terie.norelli@leg.state.nh.us&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256303793000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254938726000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Income Tax Protest &amp; Forum - Concord State House</name><id>11572914</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256130000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/11572914/</event_url></item>