<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you been frustrated by your inability to shake off certain persistent behavior patterns? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;At our last "Group Wisdom meetup, folks had shared that this has happened to them. Has this happened to you?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 --&amp;gt;You're not consistently attracting more of what you want &amp;amp; you don't have any ideas of what the real issue is &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&amp;gt;you know what the issue is, but not sure what to do to resolve it (even though you thought you did) &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&amp;gt; you are triggered by an experience, &amp;amp; suddenly what you thought you've made peace with or overcame is right there, smack in your face again. You feel you are back to where you were, down the rabbit hole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next you start judging yourself. "Unattractive" feelings come up again, like "I'm not deserving, I'm not worthy." You might even get panicky, scared &amp;amp; distressed again, feeling a loss of control, wondering whether this will ever end or get resolved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So why does this happen &amp;amp; how do you finally put these “unattractive” dissonant feelings &amp;amp; behaviors &amp;amp; root issues to rest? (&lt;em&gt;And you know this is important since this can keep you from attracting more of what you desire.&lt;/em&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yuliya Cohen&lt;/strong&gt;, energy healer, has a surprising explanation. &lt;em&gt;You, in fact, might not at fault&lt;/em&gt; for these persistent yucky feelings or behavior patterns. That's why all the personal self development “work” you've done might not have worked. &lt;strong&gt;You keep blaming yourself for something that is not you and is not yours!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Yuliya has been amazingly successful in helping folks discover the root issues easily &amp;amp; energetically in a safe, easy &amp;amp; lasting way, so that they could be whole again. You can become a vibrational attraction magnet again!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us next Tuesday where Yuliya will share with us this &lt;strong&gt;eye-opening 4-step exercise&lt;/strong&gt; based on her innovative Energy Restructuring system that allows us to "unblend" from "unattractive patterns." She will also discuss how the new generation of therapies, such as Internal Family System, are using similar approaches.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 You will be learn how... by using Energy Psychology principles of “energetic boundaries” to: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;strong&gt;identify&lt;/strong&gt; the unattractive distressed feelings &amp;amp; behaviors &amp;amp; then &lt;strong&gt;separate&lt;/strong&gt; yourself from them very quickly (so that you can shift into a more “neutral” vibrational place to deal with what's really going on) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;strong&gt;dialog&lt;/strong&gt; safely with these feelings &amp;amp; behaviors to identify the source of the trauma. You'll be very surprised who is at fault! These deeply entreated emotions could have come from other people in your present life, as early as in the womb. Or These could also be inherited burdens from an ancestor in your family tree among other sources. (Keep an open mind!) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - &lt;strong&gt;disengage&lt;/strong&gt; from the root source of the trauma that's not caused by you ( so that they no longer "energetically cling” to you) &amp;amp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 - most importantly, &lt;strong&gt;recover the lost energy&lt;/strong&gt; of your true essence, your attractiveness. Feel again that you are worthy, no more self judgment, fully healed! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;As we move deeper into Spring time, discover how motivating, powerful &amp;amp; energizing this practice is as you become fully re-integrated &amp;amp; aligned with your wholeness, and even reset your genetic code.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;****************************************************&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Yuliya Cohen&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;www.healingwithouteffort.com&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Yuliya is an internationally known expert in the area of anxiety and trauma. Over the last 25 years, she has developed a pioneering system, presented at the International Energy Psychology conference in USA &amp;amp; Canada and recently at a conference on Genetics in Turkey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has enabled thousands of people to heal from most severe fears, anxiety &amp;amp; trauma in a way that is safe, lasting &amp;amp; with a sense of ease using her groundbreaking method for correcting energetic displacement. Formerly a computer scientist &amp;amp; an engineer, she is the founder of the Energy Restructuring Institute, where she carries out research in the emerging fields of Energy Medicine &amp;amp; Energy Psychology. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 She is the author of "Energetic Boundaries: The New Paradigm in Effortless Healing" &amp;amp; an upcoming paradigm shifting book "The Four Gateways to Recovery - The Forgotten Path of Returning to Wholeness from Anxiety, Panic and PTSD". Her research article on healing schizophrenia has been published in a peer review journal. She is an author of numerous articles for various publications, including British online journals - Quantum Health and Choice Point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;****************************************************&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;RSVP "YES" ONLY if you know you are coming.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;We provide appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep "green" &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP "Yes" only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up. Many of you have been wonderful with this &amp;amp; we very much appreciate your support!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;****************************************************&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;For parking &amp;amp; directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;(via T or driving) info to Dave's loft :&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;(1) Go here:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/files"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/files&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;(2) Log in&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;(3) Scroll down and open file "Directions &amp;amp; Parking_BostonLOA Meetup"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Boston Law Of Attraction Meetup</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365735181000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363378518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Releasing the Blocks &amp; Reclaiming Your Power of Manifestation</name><id>109447932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365548400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/109447932/</event_url></item>