<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Valentine's Day!!!!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a moment to read the complete update below.... Thank you to all who attended (and posted photos) our January Meetup! It was a great success and nice to see some new and familiar faces.      &lt;br /&gt;Our winter meetups continue to be held at Doggie Day Playcenter at 1PM, Tremont Street (South End) Boston.     &lt;br /&gt;Also,  I will be holding a special FREE MAGAZINE SUBSCRIPTION GIVEAWAY  for &lt;b&gt;Chihuahua Connection Magazine&lt;/b&gt;!!! &lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Yes, I know what you are all thinking &amp;quot;there's actually a dedicated publication for chihuahuas out there?&amp;quot; !!!!&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Yes, there is.......and here is your chance to win a subscription for free...  At 8pm  tomorrow (01.27.08), I will be posting 3 questions on our message boards on the meetup site.  Just login and  the 1st  &lt;b&gt;TWO MEMBERS &lt;/b&gt; who POST all three answers correctly will win a free subscription....... Only registered Boston Chihuahua members can participate and the certificate will be given to the winners at our next Meetup! &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;  Please check out ChihuahuaConnection.com for more info regarding the publication, they are also holding a special for a one year's subscription at $14.95....    &lt;br /&gt;It's something fun and the magazine offers some insightful info from nutrition to breeders to adopting pets....and it's all about chihuahuas&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;I am also updating our &amp;quot;Polls&amp;quot; section, so please take a moment and offer up some feedback...it's multiple choice, so be honest!!! I have no way of knowing who agrees or disagress!!!! It really helps me, help our group!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:    &lt;br /&gt;There is some free parking located behind Doggieday Playcenter and the CVS, for non-residents of the area there are also plenty of metered spots near DoggieDay located on Tremont street as well as &amp;quot;South End visitor parking spots&amp;quot; located on each end of the street in the South end . Although those may be harder to come by.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay well....ST    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER ( 400 Tremont Street, South end, Boston,02116 ...our usual location 1:00PM ONLY!      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.doggieday.com/playcenter.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doggieday....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203102225000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200251268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua February Meetup</name><id>7105534</id><headcount>49</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202666400000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/7105534/</event_url></item>