<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This section is about 2.9 miles, is estimated to last 1.5 hours, and the staging location to meet at is Xavier High School (see address below) at the appointed start time.

Mattabesett is the Indian name for Middletown meaning “a resting place,” “place of a large brook”. The Mattabesett Trail, over fifty miles in length,  begins and ends in Middletown after taking a long horseshoe-shaped loop south through the towns of Durham, Haddam, Guilford, North Branford, Wallingford, Meriden, Berlin and Middlefield. There are six (6) sections of the Trail planned for the spring. Each hike is unique and varies in length from 2.4 to 6.2 miles. 

Meet-up is at a staging location and people will condense into fewer cars to carpool to the trailhead. For thru-hikes, some autos will be positioned at the trail end for carpooling to the trailhead to get those autos and then back to the original staging location. There is usually no formally organized lunch/dinner afterwards though some people may arrange an informal meal. For the morning hikes, you may wish to bring a lunch.

This hike brought to you via an alliance between the Hartford Area Hiking Group and an informal outside hiking group hosted by the First Church of Christ in Middletown. Roughly 5 people hike from that group. This hike is run by Thomas Chace  and he is the contact for most questions on this hike. 

Meetup location for staging:

Xavier High School
181 Randolph Road
Middletown, CT 06457

On the Trail

* Stay on the right of way. 
* Leave all flowers, mushrooms, wildlife, rocks, etc., for the next hiker to enjoy. 
* Respect peace and quiet on the trails. 
* Leave all gates and barways as you found them. 
* When hiking with your dog, keep your dog under control at all times. 
* Pick up litter you find on the trail - 'Carry In - Carry Out' - everything 
* Be friendly with those you meet on the trail. 
* Give horseback riders the right of way. 
* Report any dangerous trail conditions:
Call CFPA at (860)346-2372 or send an e-mail.
CFPA will forward the information to the party responsible for the trail. 

The Connecticut Forest and Park Association (CFPA)
&lt;a href="http://www.ctwoodlands.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ctwoodlands.org/&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1142738466000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tom's Mattabesett Trail Hikes #2, Coginchaug Cave Section in Middletown CT Area</name><id>4879822</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1145725200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4879822/</event_url></item>