<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our next meeting is &lt;b&gt;Thursday, August 28th from 7:30pm to 9:30pm&lt;/b&gt; at the Prudential Mall food court.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to talk about a variety of topics as well as do an exercise or two to help strengthen our communication.  Here's the agenda for the meeting: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opening circle:&lt;/b&gt; Members will have an opportunity to introduce themselves and become familiar with how the group works&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; How to approach people and start conversations - proven openers that work in the real world&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;5 minute break&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Personality feedback&lt;/b&gt; - We'll break up into smaller groups, and everyone will have an opportunity to both give and receive feedback to help improve the way they come across to people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Closing circle:&lt;/b&gt; Members will have a chance to share and discuss what they learned about themselves at the meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Munchies:&lt;/b&gt; I always go to Legal Seafoods after the meeting.  Anyone who wants to come along is welcome.  The last time 15 of us went and had a great time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Do you get nervous about approaching someone new and starting a conversation with them?  Do you wish you knew how to approach people that you're attracted to, and talk to them in a way that will make them interested in getting to know you?&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you answered yes to either of those questions, then you're going to love this month's meeting.  You'll learn simple, proven conversation starters that are non-threatening, and practically rejection proof.  Once you master this simple skill, you'll have the confidence to approach people in any situation, because you'll know what to say to get them talking.&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;You'll learn:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to become confident at approaching people and starting conversations (there's more to it than you think).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The pre-approach checklist.  These are the things that should be handled before you begin approaching people at any social gathering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven openers - I've spent the last two months interviewing some of the best dating gurus in the world.  I'll teach you some of killer openers that they shared with me as well as openers I've been testing in my own life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to practice approaching people and starting conversations in a way that almost completely eliminates the risk of rejection.  If you're scared of walking up to people and talking to them, this section can completely change your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Then we'll go into one of the most valuable sections of the meeting. We'll break up into smaller groups, and each person will have an opportunity to receive direct, honest (and extremely rare) feedback on how you can improve the way you come across.  Be prepared for a fun, interactive meeting.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;It's important that I get an accurate head count, so please RSVP if you plan on coming.  I'm looking forward to meeting you in person.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Jason King&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - The cost of the meeting is only $10 cash.  This will include the cost of the meeting and any take home materials I provide you with.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the table with the large Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226367405000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218715131000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Skills Meeting - How To Approach People And Start Conversations</name><id>8542600</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219966200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/8542600/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/b/global_4864315.jpeg</photo_url></item>