<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 25 Francis Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.334541</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outside former Peter Bent Brigham Hospital entry</name><city>Boston</city><id>1632332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105318</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Boston has a very long tradition of leadership in the medical profession dating back to the legislation for medical studies by the Great and General Court in 1647, the introduction of the smallpox inoculation into the colonies by Dr. Zabdiel Boylston and Cotton Mather in 1721, and the founding of&amp;nbsp;Harvard Medical School&amp;nbsp;by Dr. John Warren in 1782.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this tour, explore today's world-renowned community of hospitals, academic institutions, and biomedical research centers of the &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Longwood"&gt;Longwood Medical Area&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walk among the Joslin Diabetes Center, Children's Hospital and two of the flagship teaching hospitals of Harvard Medical School:Brigham and Women's Hospital&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn of their landmark medical contributions such as the iron lung, the first successful kidney transplant, and the introduction of insulin to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This walk is $15 per person but $5 for Boston By Foot card holders. See www.bostonbyfoot.org for information on &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/"&gt;Boston By Foot membership&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tour meets outside the former entrance of the Peter Bent Brigham Hospital building at the corner of Francis Street and Huntington Avenue, near the Brigham Circle T-Stop on the E branch of the Green Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312204360000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292609248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Longwood Medical Area</name><id>16292839</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312135200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/16292839/</event_url></item>