<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Loveland Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.857269</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rockville High School</name><city>Vernon Rockville</city><id>1581593</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.482430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Based on the success of the last time we did this, let's try it out again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet to do some interval training at the Rockville High School track in Vernon, CT. If you haven't run with other people outside of races before, this is a nice introduction to it. There will be many places where slower runners can catch up to the faster runners, so we will generally stick together throughout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where to meet us: The track is immediately behind the school. Let's meet at the little straightaway that comes off tangential to the track -- I think it's called the "chute," but I'm not sure. If you're standing in the big bleachers, it'll be to your left as you face the track. Park in the lot to the north side of the school. You'll see a sign for student parking. The entrance to the track is near the back of that lot, near the llamas (I'm not kidding).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interval training is alternating high-intensity and low-intensity workouts. In our case, it'll be alternating running and walking. If you've done the Couch-to-5K program, you'll know what I'm talking about. Thanks to Eric's suggestion, we'll do a "ladder," meaning the following....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;400 meter warm-up walk &lt;br /&gt;

 100 meter run with 100 meter walk recovery &lt;br /&gt;

 200 meter run with 200 meter walk recovery &lt;br /&gt;

 400 meter run with 400 meter walk recovery &lt;br /&gt;

 800 meter run with 400 meter walk recovery &lt;br /&gt;

 1600 meter run? If we're up for it :) &lt;br /&gt;

 And then back down through 800, 400, 200, 100, followed by a 400 meter cool-down walk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The benefits of this workout will be three-fold: 1) This is good cardiovascular training for runners, 2) This will get us practice running with others, 3) This is both a running AND a social event. Brilliant!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3979797</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335109009000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>5K-Runners-Meetup</urlname><id>1354697</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>5K Runners Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334503139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Interval Training at Rockville HS Track</name><id>60655052</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335018600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/5K-Runners-Meetup/events/60655052/</event_url></item>