<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>State Route 53/Lake Dunmore Rd.</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05769</zip><lat>43.848854</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Falls of Lana Trailhead</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>8838652</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.058296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the trailhead at 10:30am. We'll go by the Falls of Lana and connect to the Rattlesnake Cliffs trail which will take us up to a cliff area that has great views of Lake Dunmore and over into the Adirondacks. Bring a lunch and we can eat there. We'll then take the Aunt Jenny trail back down and come out at the falls again. The trip will be about 3.2 miles round trip and will be a gain of about 870 feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone is interested afterwards, we can go to Cattails in Brandon for a drink, food, or dessert. &lt;a href="http://cattailsvt.com/"&gt;http://cattailsvt.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: Take route 4 west into Rutland, turn right onto Route 7 north. Follow Route 7 for about 16 miles and bare right onto McConnell Road which is at a 'Y' by a Citgo station. Continue 3.3 miles and turn right onto VT-73 (Forest Dale Rd). After a half a mile, turn left onto State Route 53/Lake Dunmore Rd. After about 5.5 miles, the trailhead parking lot will be on your right. From White River Junction, this should take about an hour and a half.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CARPOOLING: This can be hashed out later but a good place to meet is the Woodstock municipal parking lot at Benson Place, just off of Pleasant Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: For those who went to Silver Lake back in March, my Aunt Judy (a.k.a. the little mountain goat) is planning to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348434510000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345597355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rattlesnake Point</name><id>78787462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348324200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/78787462/</event_url></item>