<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 49</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03215</zip><lat>43.955712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sandwich Mtn Trail Head</name><city>Waterville Valley</city><id>819567</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.507879</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Noon Peak and Jennings Peak provides fine views into Waterville Valley Village and out towards the Sandwich Range. We will start the hike at the trailhead roughly .4 miles south of the road that departs Route 49 towards the Waterville Valley ski area. The trail immediately crosses Drakes Brook and then moderately climbs up to a lookout at 1.7 miles overlooking the Valley Village area. From there, it follows a curving, gradual ridge towards Jennings Peak. At 2.7 miles it intersects with Drakes Brook Trail and follows right up to the bare summit for Jennings Peak where there are terrific views North and West. On the return, we will come down the gradual Drakes Brook Trail that follows the brook along an old logging road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Round trip approximately 6.0 miles &lt;br /&gt;Moderate up to Jennings Peak and Gradual on the hike down via Drakes Brook Trail. &lt;br /&gt;Approximate time to complete the circuit about 4.5 to 5.5 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to uncertain weather, you should be prepared with layers of warm clothing and winter gear. No cotton gear.  Make sure to bring traction devices (Yaktrax, Stabilizers, or Micro Spikes) and Snowshoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please know your own ability before signing up.  Winter hiking is more demanding then three season hiking.  In addition please read the the Hiker Responsibility Code and disclaimer on the Web Site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that all maybe's will be changed to no's at 4:00 on January 30, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come enjoy a terrific day hike in Waterville Valley!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to contact me if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK FOUR DOOR ECHO WITH MAINE LICENSE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233881541000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232984498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JENNINGS PEAK</name><id>9603475</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233414000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9603475/</event_url></item>