<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>133 Elm Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308689</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Haven Free Public Library</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1575537</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925179</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Into Thick Air by Jim Malusa is a travelogue of a series of bicycle trips to the lowest points on earth - from Cairo to the Dead Sea. The stories, in journal form, first appeared on Discovery Channel Online. Barbara Kingsolver wrote: &amp;quot;I've followed all of Jim's amazing and hilarious journeys, and am happy to claim him as one of my favorite writers.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jim Malusa has reported on assignments for The Discovery Channel and Natural History, including travels to Mount Pinatubo in the Philippines, the Atacama Desert in Chile, and Three Gorges Dam in China. A botanist and a lover of maps, his specialty is the biogeography of southern Arizona flora. Malusa lives in Tucson with his wife and their two children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Library/WritersLive.asp" target="_blank"&gt;see the New Haven Public Library's Writers Live! page for details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've never been to one of these, but I think it's just like a book-signing...the author talks about writing the book, tells stories, answers questions, then since it's at the library, will probably check the book out for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Meet me at 5:50pm at the Ives Main Branch Public Library (in the lobby), which is across from the New Haven Green, for some literary indulgence. If you can't find me there, or you're late, ask a librarian to help you find us! We'll be seated according to the Screwy Decimal System.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric is the contact for this event; my phone number will be in the RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm tall, handsome, and intelligent. I also like falafel, long walks... :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>2576129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212184266000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209241347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Writers Live! presents "Into Thick Air" with author Jim Malusa</name><id>7818026</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212011100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7818026/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/2/global_3924770.jpeg</photo_url></item>