<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2011 Winding (Refn) Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.262592</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chris &amp; Alyssa's</name><city>Worcester</city><id>11157302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802292</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="http://filmspotting.net/top-5/goldenbricks.html"&gt;most underseen&lt;/a&gt;, and polarizing releases of year 2012, yet still grabbing &lt;a href="http://oscar.go.com/nominees"&gt;4 major Oscar nominations&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://oscar.go.com/nominees/best-picture/beasts-of-the-southern-wild"&gt;Best Picture&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://oscar.go.com/nominees/directing/beasts-of-the-southern-wild"&gt;Director&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://oscar.go.com/nominees/writing-adapted-screenplay/beasts-of-the-southern-wild"&gt;Adapted Screenplay&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://oscar.go.com/nominees/actress-in-a-leading-role/quvenzhane-wallis"&gt;Lead Actress&lt;/a&gt;). And even more amazing is the fact that the Oscar Nominated lead, Quvenzhané Wallis, is only 9!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.welcometothebathtub.com/"&gt;Beasts of the Southern Wild&lt;/a&gt; has been getting a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beasts_of_the_Southern_Wild#Accolades"&gt;ton of awards&lt;/a&gt; as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, this is out of theaters right now, but... it's already available for home release, and I own the Blu-ray (haven't gotten around to watching it yet). Let's figure out a time, before the Oscars, to get get together and watch it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My wife and I would love to have a group over for this. Generally speaking, a weekend would work best for us, but we could also do a Monday or Thursday. Chime in on the comments for when works best for you! Runtime is 90 min, so I'd anticipate a 7:30p start so we're not done super late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assuming this goes through, like Dan's been doing, I'll let confirmed attendees know our actual address the day before the event (we're near Greendale Mall in Northern Worcester). &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0780504/"&gt;The posted one is fake, of course&lt;/a&gt;. We have a 1080p front projector w/ ~90" screen, and a nice 5.1 surround setup. Our movie room isn't huge, but we can fairly comfortably fit 5-6 on couch/chairs, and a little less comfortably fit 3-4 more on beanbags on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll try to have some popcorn on hand, and of course we'll have unlimited water to drink. Feel free to bring your own beverages and/or snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah, just in case, since &lt;span&gt;I hear bird allergies do happen,&lt;/span&gt; we have two parakeets here as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358884808000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-579</urlname><id>797632</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8099975586</group_lon><name>The Worcester Movie Fans Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357838516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beasts of the Southern Wild</name><id>98935262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358812800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-579/events/98935262/</event_url></item>