<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>corner of Berkeley Street</address_2><address_1>44 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The College Club of Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>431102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073586</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;EVENT SOLD OUT Here is a great Holiday Wine Tasting from Boston Uncorked. It takes place from 7:00 - 9:00 PM. It will sellout so purchase your tickets from Boston Uncorked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Members from my Red Sox Natives and Cathy's Boston Wine groups will also be joining us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;"Truly Magical" is an apt description for Boston in December. The rush and anticipation of the holidays are combined with warm, festive gatherings of friends old and new. The chilly weather and spirit of the season allure us to don some elegant evening wear and turn out for enticing gatherings with flair and cheerful anticipation. Boston Uncorked invites you to join us in your cocktail attire as we enjoy the tastes of some exceptional wines and delicious bites -- all among captivating, friendly people -- in a toast to the holiday season at the College Club of Boston. We'll enjoy the classy Grand Room of this historic club in a beautiful Back Bay brownstone -- overlooking the sparkling white lights of the Commonwealth Avenue Mall. This walkaround tasting affair will feature an array of delectable hors d' oeuvres prepared by Chef Jessie Wolkiewicz to accompany the list of fine wines being assembled for this evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Tickets are $45.00 per person. There are no Maybe RSVPs since you must purchase a ticket in advance. To purchase your ticket go to www.bostonuncorked.com [url=&lt;a href="http://www.bostonuncorked.com][/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bostonuncorked.com][/url&lt;/a&gt;].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not call or contact the College Club of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please allow extra travel, parking or T time as there are many Holiday events taking place in the area that evening.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will E Mail those who have purchased tickets before the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324046507000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321477252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SOLD OUTHoliday Toast Wine Soiree with Boston Uncorked at College Club of Boston</name><id>41426742</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323992700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/41426742/</event_url></item>