<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Amherst, New Hampshire</address_1><state>Ne</state><zip>03031</zip><lat>42.864399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ponemah Bog Wildlife Refuge</name><city>Amherst</city><id>8024492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.626335</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/1/0/event_135678192.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;No need to respond if you can't attend! &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/7721728740974823239/img/smileys/tongue.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Ponemah Bog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.svlt.org/Trails/TownMap.asp?TownName=Amherst"&gt;Amherst&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.svlt.org/Trails/Default.asp"&gt;N.H.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An extensive peat bog with walkways and observation platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Trail Length: 0.5 mi. Max. Elevation Change: 0 ft. Avg. Difficulty: Easy Access Point(s): Rhodora Dr. at bend in road. Activities: Hiking, birding, plant study Prohibited: All motorized vehicles, biking, snowmobiling, pets, alcohol Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This true quaking bog reached from Rhodora Drive is owned and maintained by the &lt;a href="http://www.nhaudubon.org/"&gt;Audubon Society of New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt; (ASNH). A boardwalk resting on the bog surface circles the unique wetland. Plants that thrive on the acid bog soil and many neotropical birds can be found here. A substantial observation stand affords an excellent view of the bog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="http://merrimack.wildnh.com/ponehmahbog/"&gt;http://merrimack.wildnh.com/ponehmahbog/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhodora Drive, Amherst, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sanctuary features a 3-acre pond surrounded by a floating sphagnum mat, all encircled by oak and pitch pine woods. The bog is in a kettle hole created by the retreat of the glaciers. Classic bog plants such as leatherleaf, bog laurel and tamarack grow here. Visit in mid-May to see a spectacular display of Rhodora. You can also find insect-eating plants; pitcher plants, sundews and bladderworts. A trail, a boardwalk and a viewing platform allow you to get a close-up view of life in the bog, but be prepared for wet footing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://merrimack.wildnh.com/images/viewing-information.png" alt="Viewing Information" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summer bird life in the sanctuary includes rufous-sided towhees, blue jays, tree swallows, common yellowthroats, mourning and Canada warblers, and song sparrows. Watch for green herons and other waterfowl, woodpeckers and belted kingfishers. Occasionally, muskrats make their home in the bog. You can sometimes find signs of red foxes, raccoons and other visitors from the nearby woods. There is an assortment of native New Hampshire orchid species in the bog, which can be seen in late spring to mid-summer. Birds are visible throughout the year. Additionally, the bog is home to many dragonflies and damselflies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://merrimack.wildnh.com/images/directions.png" alt="Directions" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GPS – N 42 o49.047’ W 071o 35.164’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Nashua take Route. 101A west for 5 miles. Turn right on Boston Post Road. Go 2 miles, then turn left on Stearns Road. Go .3 miles, and then take a left on Rhodora Drive. Go straight ahead to parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Milford/Amherst go east on Route. 101A for .5 mile, then turn left on Rte. 122. Immediately turn right on Sterns Road and to 1.1 miles. Turn right on Rhodora Drive and go straight ahead to parking area.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341799722000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341317083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ponemah Bog, Amherst NH Let's stroll through the Bog.....</name><id>71775792</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341604800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/71775792/</event_url></item>