<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.855291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978.388.1907</phone><name>Our Neighbors Table</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1411475</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.932291</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>11.19.20 UPDATE:  Hey everyone sorry for the delay in posting this update but it just came in from the woman who I talked to about setting this up she is advising us to dress warm as it may be a little chilly.  I will be bringing an extra pair of gloves if they are needed for anyone!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Calling all Meetup volunteers:&lt;br /&gt;We have a new volunteer opportunity that suits our desires to volunteer.  The Organization is called Our Neighbors Table in Amesbury.  The following is the upcoming opportunity:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Saturday before Thanksgiving Our Neighbors Table has a huge food drive at Stop &amp;amp; Shop in Amesbury.  The Thanksgiving Drive is called “Fill a cruiser” where the police department has a cruiser out in front, and encourages everyone shopping to make a donation to Our Neighbors’ Table.  They usually have enough volunteers at Stop &amp;amp; Shop, but what they do is fill up a big truck, and the truck comes back to the food pantry about 3 times on Saturday.  They need a crew of volunteers to unload the truck, and weather permitting, roughly sort into categories (pasta, soup, vegetables, etc.), label and bring down to their cellar.  They need a group of up to 15 people.  They will accept kids that are 11 or 12 and up, as long as mom or dad is there to supervise.  The stairs into the cellar are a little dicey, so they don’t like taking kids much younger than that.  If the day is miserable, they sort the food in the cellar – a little more cramped but it’s doable.  &lt;br /&gt;So if you would like to help Donna &amp;amp; Janet assist this organization, please come on out to the location.  This event is limited to 15 people and is scheduled on all 3 of our sites, so please make sure you sign up for this quickly.  If you get shut out, please sign up anyway, you will be placed on the waiting list and we will be notified.  If we have openings on one of the other sites we can move that opening over so that you can attend.  If there are no openings on the other sites we can call the organization to see if we can fit you in.&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;Nov/Dec:  November 1-Dec  11 we will be collecting donations for the Lazarus House in Lawrence.  If you need a list of needed items please see the Message Board on the Meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.  If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer”&lt;br /&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank You&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290345261000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287928967000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer Event @ Our Neighbors Table</name><id>15209958</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290269700000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15209958/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/8/global_18997048.jpeg</photo_url></item>