<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Exit 19 off Rte. 495. Turn at BKing</address_2><address_1>11 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01757</zip><lat>42.149307</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-478-7010</phone><name>DOUBLETREE HOTEL</name><city>Milford</city><id>871306</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.486671</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for Project Smile's 5th Anniversary Celebration. This exciting event will feature special guests Gail Huff and J.C. Monahan from News Channel 5, Boston and an incredible silent auction featuring over 100 items, including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Southwest Airline tickets&lt;br /&gt;TV Diner, &amp;quot;Diner for a Day&amp;quot; certificate- be featured on the NECN Show with Billy Costa&lt;br /&gt;Colbert Report tickets&lt;br /&gt;Daily Show with Jon Stewart VIP tickets&lt;br /&gt;Iridesse pearl necklace&lt;br /&gt;Celtics tickets&lt;br /&gt;Autographed Red Sox, Patriots, Bruins and Celtics items&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHDH, Channel 7 news experience package. Have a tour of the station with Randy Price, anchor, watch a live broadcast of the news, then go to dinner with Randy and 3 of your friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam Adams Bucket of Cheer. Merchandise and Gift certificate for 1 case of Sam Adams beer per month for a year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;restaurant gift certificates, golf outings, ski passes, jewelry, movie tickets, store cards, limo rides, Panasonic flatscreen TV, and much, much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event will also feature live music, food, complimentary Beija Rum cocktails, debut of the Project Smile 2009 fundraiser calendar and debut of the Project Smile song. Tickets are a $10 donation which includes a calendar and raffle entry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of the proceeds benefit Project Smile, the Hopedale based non profit organization started by Catherine, your Meet Up organizer. Project Smile works to help children involved in traumatic events by donating stuffed animals, books, coloring books and small toys for police, fire fighters and paramedics to give to children. Project Smile also works with Department of Children and Families to donate stuffed animals for children entering foster care. Since October 2003, Project Smile has collected over 24,000 stuffed animals and works with 141 police and fire departments across New England. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So please show your support and join us for a fun evening and help support a local charity that really needs your help!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224805511000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221710469000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Project Smile 5th Anniversary Celebration</name><id>8781224</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223073000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/8781224/</event_url></item>