<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Pennybrook Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01905</zip><lat>42.476158</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lynn Woods Reservation</name><city>Lynn</city><id>710792</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.986000</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to Lynn Woods !&lt;br /&gt;Lynn Woods Reservation is the second largest municipal park in the greater Boston area. This 2,200 acre forest reserve consists of ponds, wetlands, streams, deciduous/evergreen forest and rocky ledge. The ponds provide the drinking water for the residents of Lynn and surrounding communities. Wildlife abounds in the forest. Well over 100 species of birds inhabit or seasonally frequent the woods. A large rodent population supports such predators as hawks, owls and red tail fox. More than an aquifer, more than a wildlife preserve, more than a wilderness experience, Lynn Woods is a rare and unique adventure.&lt;br /&gt;Lynn Woods awaits your exploration and enjoyment. You will come to love and appreciate the woods as did the early settlers and citizens who wisely preserved it for all generations. For more information on events in Lynn Woods, contact the Ranger at 781-477-7123.About Lynn Woods&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1881, Lynn Woods Reservation, a 2,200-acre municipal forest park located in Lynn, Massachusetts, is the second largest municipal park in the United States. The City of Lynn's Department of Public Works, Park Commission and Lynn Water &amp;amp; Sewer Commission share jurisdiction and management of Lynn Woods Reservation. The park encompasses nearly one-fifth of the entire land area of the city and represents a significant natural, watershed and public recreational resource in eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Main Entrance (west): Take Walnut Street to Pennybrook Road.&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Eastern Entrance: Take Lynnfield Street (Route 129) to Great Woods Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find out how to get involved in the protection and improvement of Lynn Woods, call Friends of Lynn Woods at 781-477-7123 or click here to visit our website: &lt;a href="http://www.flw.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flw.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a detailed map of Lynn Woods visit our website. There are also maps available at City Hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get involved in advocating for responsible bicycle use in Lynn Woods, call New England Mountain Bike Association (NEMBA)  at (800) 57-NEMBA, email to 72773.2557@compuserve.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272846025000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269278079000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LYNN WOODS </name><id>12956918</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271602800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/12956918/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>