<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>At the Palm Spring Film Festival, this film received mixed reviews.  Some people hated it, some liked it.  I didn't see it, but it won a Best of Fest film award. It is said to to be brutally violent.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Italy, 2009) Directed by Matteo Garrone. screenplay by Maurizio Braucci, Ugo Chiti, Gianni Di Gregorio, Matteo Garrone, and Roberto Saviano, based on the book by Roberto Saviano. Cast: Marco Macor, Ciro Petrone, Salvatore Abruzzese, Carmine Paternoster, Maria Nazionale. Martin Scorsese was so impressed by this new Italian movie that he introduced it at the New York Film Festival and immediately signed on as the American 'presenter.' No surprise: Gomorrah is a shocking, revelatory look at organized crime in Naples, that strips any semblance of romance from its Mafia connection. Gomorrah is based on the expose by journalist Roberto Saviano, who has been living undercover with 24 hour police protection since he blew the whistle on the violence, exploitation and toxic pollution that has a grip around the throat of one of Europe's busiest port cities. &amp;quot;I hope this movie will finally show people the ferocious face of Italy, which is the face that really runs things,&amp;quot; Saviano says. &amp;quot;I think many American moviegoers will be surprised.&amp;quot; 135 min.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting outside on the bench.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241741187000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240280590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gomorrah</name><id>10231082</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241393400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/10231082/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>