<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join myself for an afternoon of Candlepin Bowling fun at Lanes and Games. For information on costs,  for shoes, bowling strings, etc.... Please view the websight at :Lanesandgames@verizon.net &lt;br /&gt;     There had been a BIG request for bowling with this group,  however PLEASE only RSVP a yes if you are 90 percent sure you are going to attend. I did have 4 no shows at my last event and it wasn't too fair to others who wanted to attend.   &lt;br /&gt;I will have two lanes reserved. I hope for twelve attendees so we can have two equal teams of 6 people. &lt;br /&gt;     There is a lounge area, some billiards, and an arcade if members did want to hang out afterwards. Of Course as always, I will leave this optional. &lt;br /&gt;    Please meet me in the downstairs lobby area where we will get our shoes, etc.... &lt;br /&gt;    Lastly, this particular event does not require clean up, however IF a future event does require clean up, I would appreciate some help before you depart. I personally was left with all the clean up at the last event.  &lt;br /&gt;     Thanks again for your cooperation and I hope to see you on the 29th for my second event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a balloon and a red meet up t shirt on. Please meet in lobby area</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239197127000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237060293000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon Bowling </name><id>9954186</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238346000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/9954186/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>