<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kendrick St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.295688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cutler Park</name><city>Needham</city><id>722069</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.214567</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ption&lt;br /&gt;The parking area for Cutler Park is located in Needham MA. But the park itself extends into Dedham, Newton, Brookline and Boston. The park consists of a few hills and a lot of trails near an 800-acre marsh along the Charles River and beside route 128.&lt;br /&gt;There is a large lake near the parking area and the more challenging singletracks are located between it and route 128. The singletracks nearest to the highway go up and down Cutler's only hill. They are quite fun and include one roller coaster section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many more trails however, stretching out into the marshes on plank bridges. So expect to spend a bit of time exploring. If you do that you'll eventually make your way out of Cutler Park and into Riverdale Park, Millennium Park, The Brook Farm Conservation Area, and Newton's Nahanton Park. Succeed in doing this and you'll do a 16-mile loop. Cutler Park itself has about 9 miles of trails.      MAP   DCR Website&lt;br /&gt;Southeast Mass NEMBA has been doing trailwork at Cutler for many years. These pix were taken at a recent trail day where we replaced some of the planks on one of those long bog bridges. Future Trail Days will be listed here.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cutler's singletracks range from moderately technical to the most buffed singletracks imaginable. There are also some wide dirt roads that are fine for beginners and families. The road around the lake is the best example of that. My favorite trails are on Powell Island which is located after the first long wooden bridge. The trails on Powell's Island roughtly form a figure eight, are very fast and are fun to ride in both directions.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearby NEMBA Shops &amp;amp; Links      International Bicycle Centers    Bike Barn      Bicycle Link     Dave's Bike Infirmary      Wheelworks      Landry's      EMS    The Bikeway Source    SEMASS NEMBA      BV NEMBA   Greater Boston NEMBA&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Take exit 19A from route 95 (route 128) in Needham (heading east). &lt;br /&gt;Turn right on 2nd Ave into the industrial park. (There will be a Staples and a PetCo at this intersection.)&lt;br /&gt;Turn right on 4th Ave. &lt;br /&gt;Then turn right on Kendrick St.&lt;br /&gt;The DCR's Cutler Park parking lot is about 300 yards ahead on your left.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cautions&lt;br /&gt;Lots of pedestrians and dogs use this area. Especially on weekends. Have fun at Cutler. But remember the trails, just like those in The Blue Hills, are closed from January 1st to April 15th.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This page was last modified on Tuesday, May 19, 2009 at 7:24 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Copyright © 1987-2&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285038616000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284333607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CUTLER PARK WALK - KENDRICK ST,  NEEDHAM,  MA</name><id>14746181</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284908400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/14746181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>