<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another Movie Night! Come see a film for free at this great location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees: I will also need your &lt;strong&gt;FULL NAME (and that of any +1) for the Concierge&lt;/strong&gt; to let you in. Please Provide when you RSVP. (Email, Event Comment, or Text me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, there should be NO Maybe's for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Events &lt;em&gt;Main&lt;/em&gt; Film Is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0085334/"&gt;"A Christmas Story"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(1983 Comedy)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMDB Description: Ralphie has to convince his parents, teachers, and Santa that a Red Ryder BB gun really is the perfect gift for the 1940's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Staring: Peter Billingsley, Melinda Dillon and Darren McGavin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;will&lt;/span&gt; see &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;how&lt;/span&gt; people &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;are&lt;/span&gt; feeling &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;after&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;possibly&lt;/span&gt; put &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;in&lt;/span&gt; any &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;other&lt;/span&gt; films &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;tha&lt;/span&gt;t are &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;lying&lt;/span&gt; around &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; there &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;is&lt;/span&gt; time!&amp;nbsp; I.&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;. the &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Cartoon&lt;/span&gt; films &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;are&lt;/span&gt; usually &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;relatively&lt;/span&gt; short, &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;so&lt;/span&gt; easily &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;addable&lt;/span&gt; to &lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;the&lt;/span&gt; mix.&lt;/strong&gt; (I've also requested thier presence as a backup if for some reason we have problems.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : line-through"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suggest &lt;strong&gt;Holiday films&lt;/strong&gt; that you can bring! (i.e. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;you have the &lt;strong&gt;DVD or Blu-Ray&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to share)...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event start time is 7:15 for the social portion, so you can start showing up then. But we will not start the film until 7:45 or shortly there after, but don't plan to be any later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. If someone else backs out you can be automatically added, just provide your full&amp;nbsp;name for the concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just Please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are &lt;span&gt;instructions with a phone number on the door and&lt;/span&gt; a call box with bell button. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call/text AJ at 315-345-9348&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street (some with Credit Card slot available.).&amp;nbsp; If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.) 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only, the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the building main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the building door, Ring the Bell Button, Concierge will Direct you. If you have more problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324154308000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316565630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie:  Holiday Movie ("A Christmas Story" and possibly more.)</name><id>34346772</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324080900000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/34346772/</event_url></item>