<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 High Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02809</zip><lat>41.670167</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bristol Statehouse</name><city>Bristol</city><id>1467219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.273287</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The start of 2nd Story's summer season involves a well known courtroom drama by Aaron Sorkin.&amp;nbsp; "A Few Good Men" will be performed at the Bristol Courthouse.&amp;nbsp; I'm sure you're all quite familiar with the plot, but just in case:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Few Good Men&lt;/strong&gt; is a play by Aaron Sorkin, first produced on &lt;span&gt;Broadway&lt;/span&gt; by David Brown in 1989. It tells the story of military lawyers at a court-martial who uncover a high-level conspiracy in the course of defending their clients, United States Marines accused of murder.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It opened on Broadway at the Music Box Theatre in New York on November 15, 1989, in a production directed by Don Scardino, with Tom Hulce as LTJG Kaffee, Megan Gallagher as LCDR JoAnne Galloway and Stephen Lang as Col Jessep.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sorkin adapted his work into a screenplay for a &lt;span&gt;1992 film&lt;/span&gt; directed by Rob Reiner, produced by Brown and starring Tom Cruise, Jack Nicholson, and Demi Moore. The film was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Picture, and the Golden Globe for Best Screenplay.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The play's signature catchphrase is "You can't handle the truth."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $25. Seating is General Admission. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For reservations, please call the 2nd Story Theater at 401-247-4200.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note that Saturday nights at do sell out early.&amp;nbsp; In addition, the Courthouse has less seats than the main theater. Please do not wait to order your tickets! I strongly recommend that you order your tickets now.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will try Agave in Bristol for dinner.&amp;nbsp; Their address is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Agave Restaurant&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;805 Hope Street&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bristol&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span&gt;RI&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;02809&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that will be attending dinner, reservations will be made under "RI Theater Group" for 6:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost of dinner will be handled as follows:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinks will be consigned to a separate check from the meal. Each person will add 30% to the price of their drink to cover the 8% RI Tax plus a 20% tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meal will be on one check. A 20% tip will be added to the total and meal check will be divided evenly by the number of people attending the dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will send an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVP "yes". If you will not make it to the restaurant by 6:00 PM please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner is optional and is not included in the price of the ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be at the theater NO LATER than 7:30.&amp;nbsp; Seating is general admission and since this is not part of the season ticket package, they will not be holding seats for us.&amp;nbsp; Seating is first-come;first-served, so please be prompt so we can all sit together. When you RSVP, I will provide my cell phone number in case you're running late or get lost.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby of the Bristol Statehouse</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339712048000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333474199000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Few Good Men</name><id>59082542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339284600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/59082542/</event_url></item>