<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2370 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.344635</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hess Gas - Intersection  Mass Pike,  Rt 128, and Commonwealth Ave</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>880225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.257942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Scoot out to Wachusetts Dam/Reservoir in Clinton MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then eat lunch at the famous Old Timers Restaurant (Clinton). You will think you are in a 1930s time warp.      Go anywhere and say you are from Clinton, Massachusetts and the first thing you will hear in response is “I’ve been to the Old Timer.”   The Old Timer Restaurant has been the landmark restaurant for two generations of Clintonians. Every politician, sports star and celebrity who has visited Clinton since 1929, has been to the Old Timer and that includes the Kennedy clan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Started by John and Helen McNally in the 1929, they converted the street-side flower shop into a bar called the “Tap Room.” The name “Old Timer” derived from the old patrons who became daily fixtures when the bar first opened. The greatest honor  the ‘Tap Room” can bestow on a patron is to retire their hat above the bar. There are dozens of hats on display and they will be glad to tell you the story behind each one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dining room was added in 1934 and is virtually unchanged today. Even the murals done by German artist Fred Gentsch are still intact. In 1941, the McNallys opened the Clinton Hotel next door (see opposite page) which was connected to the Old Timer Restaurant.  The 33 room hotel has since been converted to condominiums.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dressed in Scooter Gear</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Alden</member_name><member_id>5206555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241367711000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232933325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wachusetts Dam/Reservoir (Clinton, MA)  Lunch at the Old Timers, Havard...</name><id>9600494</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240754400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/9600494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/e/global_7075214.jpeg</photo_url></item>