<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Silber Way, 9th floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349705</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston University Trustees Ballroom</name><city>Boston</city><id>12138352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Alexander Kjerulf has introduced hundreds of thousands of people to the Danish word “abejdsglaede,” which translates “happiness at work,” through his popular blog, The Chief Happiness Officer, his book, Happy Hour is 9 to 5: How to Love Your Job, Love Your Life and Kick Butt at Work, and his popular TED talk. He makes the case that happy people are more successful than unhappy people and that happy businesses are more efficient than unhappy ones. His research draws on numerous real life examples of companies that have achieved success through happiness. Alex presents workshops on happiness at work at businesses and conferences all over the world. His clients include companies like Hilton, Microsoft, LEGO, IKEA, Shell, HP and IBM.His popular blog about careers and leadership is read by thousands daily. [Video of Alex at TEDxCopeanhagen]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will be moderated by Tim Sullivan, editorial director of Harvard Business Review Press. Tim’s book, The Org: The Underlying Logic of the Office, coauthored with Ray Fisman, was just published.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free and open to the public | Reception and book-signing to follow&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364560852000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>52</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362705661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happiness at Work with Denmark's  “Chief Happiness Officer” Alexander Kjerulf</name><id>108192082</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364421600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/108192082/</event_url></item>