<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Camels Hump Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05462</zip><lat>44.298019</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Camels Hump Road (Burrows Trail Trailhead Parking Lot)</name><city>Huntington Center</city><id>1586883</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.948601</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*** IMPORTANT*************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read entire event description before you sign up.&amp;nbsp; When you sign up, you'll be asked several questions.&amp;nbsp; Answering questions is NOT an option during your RSVP process on my hiking event.&amp;nbsp; If you omit it, you'll be eventually moved out from "On-Going" list by the event organizer. [Only exception is that if you think I hiked with you already in past and you know about your hiking experience, you may not have to answer to my questions. ]&amp;nbsp; You'll receive reminder to answer to the questions through e-mail in advance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to hike Camel's Hump(4083 ft), one of 5 4K footers in VT on 10/22(Sat).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've done Camel's Hump hike from East and West side, however, I haven't done from North side.&amp;nbsp; So let's try it out....from Bamforth Ridge (Long Trail).&amp;nbsp; I hope to see beautiful foliage view on the way to Camel's Hump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Hiking Route &amp;amp; Description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We meet at Burrows Trail (Side Trail of LT) Large Parking Lot at the end of Camels Hump Road in Huntington, VT at 9:30AM.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; We leave some cars here for car spotting and drive to Long Trail parking area on Duxbury Rd, Richmond.&amp;nbsp; This is North Side of Camel's Hump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* After we reach to the parking area on Duxbury Rd, we'll start hiking within 10-15min.&amp;nbsp; So please be prepared.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Hike on Long Trail via Bamforth Ridge about 6.4 miles to reach Camel's Hump summit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Eat lunch and take a break, then, hike out on Burrows Trail approx. 2.4 miles or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* This is approx. 8.8 miles Traverse Hike. I'll hike with slow to moderate pace (1.5-2 mph pace) but will spend enough time to take a break or take some pix on the way to the summit.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This is my usual hike as I take a lot of pictures.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Rules to follow:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please don't bring your friends who are NOT the member of this meetup group as I need to make sure liability as well as hikers capability who are going to join my hike in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Weather Check Point:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather check point will be done on Oct 21st (Fri), 7PM.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Note:&amp;nbsp; At the higher elevation, temp might be colder than you assume.&amp;nbsp; Please don't underestimate the cold weather in higher elevation and make sure to bring appropriate gear such as waterproof/windproof jacket (in case of rain) etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please bring enough water, snack and lunch. Also bring First Aid Kit for your use.&amp;nbsp; I carry gear for my use.&amp;nbsp; Needless to say, please don't forget to bring your headlamp, although I'd like to come back to the parking lot before getting dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please feel free to drop me an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Assistant Organizer,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomoko&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V(Blue, VT plate)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319493420000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319124896000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VT/Camel's Hump(4083 ft)  Hike via Bamforth Ridge(Long Trail)</name><id>38093622</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319286600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/38093622/</event_url></item>