<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Near Rice Field</address_1><state>CT</state><lat>41.308151</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Rock Park</name><city>New Haven</city><id>9210392</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928154</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for our first Fall hike... we will cover the northeast section of East Rock Park with optional biking after the hike, so if you have a mountain, hybrid or road bike, please bring it. We'll check out a long stretch of paved roadway as well as Indian Head peak (310') and Snake Rock peak (205'). From Indian Head peak, there are great views of both the New Haven city skyline and the Soldiers &amp;amp; Sailors Monument on East Rock peak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will take approximately 2 hours including a snack so we should be back before 12 noon. The trails are easy to moderate in difficulty level but have a few steep or rocky sections here and there. We'll be hiking at a moderate pace so you should be relatively healthy and physically fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see a map of East Rock, please visit... &lt;a href="http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/media/2008EastRockMap.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/media/2008EastRockMap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or take an interactive tour... &lt;a href="http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/eastrockTour.asp#_self" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/eastrockTour.asp#_self&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting location will be near Rice Field. The exact Meeting location will be sent to Yes RSVP's on the night prior to the event. Please note that RSVP's will close on Saturday Sept 22 at 8 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring water and a snack. Post-hike activity also includes biking the East Rock red trail OR we can ride on the paved roads through the park if more people want to do that. You will need to ride (or transport) and secure your own bike until after the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions? To contact me, please email me on my profile page.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348629650000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347406455000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Rock - Indian Head and Snake Rock</name><id>81961762</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348407000000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/81961762/</event_url></item>