<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Chianti is 285 Cabot Street 978 921 2233</address_2><address_1>Theatre is 286 Cabot Street 978 927 3677</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.552044</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>978-921-2233</phone><name>Cabot Street Theatre and Chianti Restaurant </name><city>Beverly</city><id>463810</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.878760</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come to Beverly, Massachusets to the famous &amp;quot;Le Grand David Magic show&amp;quot; at the Cabot St. Theatre, located at 286 Cabot St. in Beverly, Massachusetts. and diner at Chianti Restaurant after the show... &lt;br /&gt;The show is only $20.00 at the door I'll reserve the amount fo tickets acording to the RSVP's we have by Jan. 16th... So you can just go give them my name and they will have a ticket reserved for you ;-) or you can order by mail, check the web link for this... &lt;br /&gt;Check the web page for more Info.:&lt;a href="http://www.legranddavid.com/show_schedule.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.legranddav...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the show around 5:30 pm we will go for diner at Chianti Tuscan Restaurant in Cabot St. directly across the Theatre, They have GREAT food here and they also have live entertainment, an acoustic Jazz band &amp;quot;Who's muddy shoes&amp;quot; will be playing from 6:30 on...   We will all meet, mingle, laugh and coment the show...   Do not have link for Chianti, sorry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please specifie on your RSVP if you are coming to the Magic Show AND diner or just one or the other, since I'll need to reserve tix and arrange seatting at Chianti&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Le Grand David and His Spectacular Magic Company is the longest consecutively running stage magic show in the world, according to Guinness World Records, and celebrated its 30th anniversary on February 20, 2007. Marco the Magi (Cesareo Pelaez) started the show in the 1970s. The family-oriented stage magic show runs most Sundays at the Cabot Street Cinema Theatre. For almost ninety years the Cabot Street Cinema Theatre has been an important part of the Boston's North Shore community. Harris and Glover Ware, two brothers and former vaudeville musicians from Marblehead, Massachusetts, built the Cabot eight years after the construction of their first Beverly theater, the Larcom Theatre. The Cabot was originally known as the Ware Theatre when it opened in 1920 and was described as having ?the most impressive auditorium of its size east of New York.? Erected with ballyhoo and great expense in 1920, it was immediately Beverly?s grandest playhouse. Large enough to accommodate any kind of entertainment, from silent pictures to opera, the Cabot was also grand enough?with its frescoes, filigrees, golden dome, and full balcony?to rival big-city show palaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;From Boston -- Follow Route 1 North to Route 128 North &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128 -- Take Exit 22E (marked as Route 62), follow Route 62 for 2.5 miles, and turn right on Cabot Street. The Cabot Street Cinema Theatre is two blocks ahead on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is abailable for free on street (No metters), also you'll have free parking on 2 big parking lots on Pond St. which is 2 blocks pass (going South) the Theatre, turn right on Pond St. and you'll see the 2 BIG lots on each side of the street, you can use bout parking lots for as long as you wish.... 8 min. walk to Theatre&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also you can take the commuter rail from North Station (Newburryport/Rockport line) into Beverly Depot from here up you'll see Town Hall, and it is a 15 min. walk to Theatre,  go up 2 blocks to Cabot St. and turn left 2 blocks to the Theatre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any problems pease call my cel.  1 (978) 473-9358&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the mural on the left side (Corner) of Theatre..</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lettie G.</member_name><member_id>2715523</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201030435000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Because it is the BEST keept secret show... You'll LOVE it...!!!</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199127855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Magic Show at Cabot Theatre in Beverly and Dinner after the show at Chianti</name><id>7000590</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200857400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7000590/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/1/global_2883553.jpeg</photo_url></item>