<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>about two miles east of Lowe's Store</address_2><address_1>Route 2 in Randolph</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.406425</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Appalachia Trailhead parking lot</name><city>Gorham</city><id>175098</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.212944</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Presidential Traverse is traditionally run on the weekend closest to the Summer Solstice every year and consists of hiking the ridge line from Mt Madison to Mt Pierce in the White Mountains of NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Randolph NH to Crawford Notch NH &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Time :4:45 AM Appalachia Parking Lot – Randolph NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The traditional route is about 20 miles of distance and 8500 feet or vertical and usually takes 12 hours. There really isn't anything like it in the Northeast. The Presidential Traverse “lite” is an unrecognized event that runs above treeline, skipping the summits along the way, reducing the mileage by about 2 miles and the elevation gain to approximately 5000 feet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to get the planning right, this meetup will be closed late Thursday night &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the logistics for the routes are identical, I am posting this meetup for either hike and hope that when you sign up, you express your interest level on which route and based on the interest of those signed up, we will firm up the route the week prior to the hike. My intent would be to start out hitting the summits and then see how the group is feeling to gauge the rest of the day. The nice part of the route is that those who don’t want to visit a summit can walk around it and meet the group on the other side.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike will be run at a consistent pace starting out slow and adjusting the speed as the day goes on. The intent is to take our time dong the ridge versus trying to meet an arbitrary goal time. End time of the event can range from 5 to 8 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Either hike is in the advanced category of hiking compared to many of the hikes listed in this meetup group. It is double the elevation gain and distance of many of the 4000 footers in NH and the majority of the route is walking from rock to rock on exposed trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not out actively hiking on a frequent basis, this trip isn't for you  The trade off for the great potential views is that the route is fully exposed to the westerly winds and weather, therefore the trip is very dependent upon weather conditions and the trip could be canceled a few days in advance if the forecast is poor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; In order to run the hike, I would like a minimum of two other folks with vehicles, in order that we can spot a car at the end of the route and at an intermediate “bail out” location at the Ammonoosuc and Jewell trail parking lot. This gives the group the option to head down off the ridge at several locations if need be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do note the start time of 4:45 AM, this is not a misprint. The group will leave Appalachia at this time. I have some limited tenting or floor space available at my home or the motels in Gorham or Hikers Paradise Hostel are nearby the trailhead.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given the timing, I would like to spot the cars on Friday evening.  Most likely all or some of the participants may need to ferry cars at the end of the hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As discussed, the actual trails are variable but the core route would be Appalachia Trailhead to Madison Hut via the Valley Way, Gulfside (the AT) to Mt Washington and then Crawford Path to Crawford Notch.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look For Dennis P at the trailhead</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277136337000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275941976000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presidential Traverse or Traverse Lite</name><id>13727946</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276937100000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13727946/</event_url></item>