<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The fall season is upon us, and we are bringing back the nightlife in full force!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us this Friday night at one of Boston's best bars, Tia's on the Waterfront!  This is a great place to meet new and current members in a relaxed setting, before heading out to one of the near-by clubs in the area.  This is a great event to meet new people and to get your hip-hop groove on!  New and current members welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 9pm in the bar area at Tia's.  We will head over to one of the local clubs (to be determined - but likely Sanctuary, 189 State Street) around 10pm to beat the lines.  Please meet us at Tia's, and get there early as to have time to meet folks and beat the lines later.  Cover:  None for Tia's, but there will be a cover for the club.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For questions or help finding the group, please call my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as these are upscale venues.  If traveling by T, Government Center on the Green Line and State Street on the Blue Line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224199626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222752852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Downtown Boston Nightlife Mixer and Dancing This Friday, Oct 3!</name><id>8862547</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223082000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8862547/</event_url></item>