<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>125.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;10:00 am-5:30pm - This is a full day workshop &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Not only lack of love and nurturing, but also a very wide spectrum of various complicated and chronic conditions such as depression, phobias, and anxieties, skeleto-muscular injuries, cardiovascular problems, harmful addictions (drugs, alcohol, smoking) and eating disorders can be traced to some karmic dysfunction on one's family tree.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This premise is derived from the universal law which states that major physical and psychological ailments are manifestations of destructive actions that took place at some time in the past in the family history, or in one's past lifetimes.&amp;nbsp; In other words, these ailments are a form of your genetic inheritance. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;So how do you go about fixing this?&amp;nbsp; The opposite of what we usually do - which is alienate ourselves even further from our family members and family history. In other words, cutting the energetic cords that bind us to our heritage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;You know only too well, that when family relationships seem not to work,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;the most&lt;/span&gt; common approach, of cutting your connections to another person, can be painful and shocking to both your energy system and the person on the other end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Most often, instead of bringing about the desired lasting healing, cord cutting creates a host of unwanted painful sensations, feelings, and emotions. Besides, you can never really cut the "blood connections" to your family members without producing a devastating effect on your family tree - your are essentially breaking off the branches of the tree.&amp;nbsp; And while you can disconnect from non-family relationships, the right approach in most family related cases is to simply release the dysfunctional parts of your relationship and keep the connection by repairing and restoring your multi-generational tree structure.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Take this opportunity to heal your Ancestral Tree using Energy Restructuring&amp;trade; a ground-breaking pioneering methodology that reorganizes and repairs the entire ancestral tree as well as existing family structures based on a set of physical, emotional and spiritual problems you may be experience that you were unable to heal using other methods.&amp;nbsp; This work is derived from the universal law which states that major physical and psychological ailments are manifestations of destructive actions that took place at some time in the past in the family history, or in one's past lifetimes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332703626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323700882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Heal Your Life by Repairing Ancestral Tree</name><id>44192992</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330182000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/44192992/</event_url></item>