<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>984 North Colony Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.487835</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On Track Karting</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>5682112</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.809593</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Bill for some Go-Carting this Saturday!&amp;nbsp; Bill will host this meetup and post additional info (contact) as it approaches. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This Event is being Cross-Posted from "The Connecticut 20's-40's Social Group".&amp;nbsp; The Below is copied from their Event Posting &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/connecticut20sto40s/events/37584692/"&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; (The 20's-40's Group appears to have a fee, so let him know you're from the NHC posting.)&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please see the website listed below for fees before signing up!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Its go cart time!&amp;nbsp; On track in wallingford is pretty good. They are fast! 40mph&amp;nbsp;and it gets chilly cuase its so fast so be sure to dress warm!&amp;nbsp; Please check&amp;nbsp;out the site for all information. Looks like you have to get a membership which&amp;nbsp;you can do for a month or a year. &amp;nbsp;If we get enough people or enough races bought at once&amp;nbsp;(20)&amp;nbsp;we can get a group discount.&amp;nbsp; So please&amp;nbsp;please make sure you show up if you put yes. I am&amp;nbsp;going to try to make a reservation for us&amp;nbsp;cause if we dont its not guaranteed&amp;nbsp;well get on if we have a lot of people.&amp;nbsp;(group info is below)&amp;nbsp;After we&amp;nbsp;can head to humpreys right down the street or head to&amp;nbsp;the area where all the bars are and grab some food and drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the site to check out all the info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ontrackkarting.com/"&gt;http://www.ontrackkarting.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions let me know. If anyone is organizer or anything of any other groups feel free to cross post with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Here is the info from the site about groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note our group pricing has changed effective 1/1/2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Round up your friends, family, and/or coworkers to take advantage of our group rates. Buy 20 or more races (in a single transaction) and you&amp;rsquo;ll save 25% Monday through Friday and 20% on weekends and holidays. All additional races purchased and run by any member of your group during that same visit will also qualify for this discounted rate. All participants must have a valid membership. In addition to the discount on races, non-members in your group can obtain a 1/2-price trial membership to get them started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note head socks are not included with the group rate, although one is included with each paid membership. Additional/replacement head socks are available at a cost of $2 each. Remember that once purchased, head socks are yours to keep and reuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reservations are recommended and require a $50 deposit. Our group rate is available to walk-ins, but track availability isn&amp;rsquo;t guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Bill, whom will post his contact information soon...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Olender</member_name><member_id>3028434</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329618000000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329200314000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Go Carts - On Track Wallingford</name><id>52275562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329613200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/52275562/</event_url></item>