<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FINALLY Overcome Your Fears That Have Been &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Destroying&lt;/span&gt; Your Dating Life... &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eliminate&lt;/em&gt; Inner Game Challenges Like Nervousness, Self-doubt And Anxiety That Are Holding You Back From TRUE Success In Your Dating Life...This Will Be The Most Important Meetup Ever!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever screwed up an important situation with the opposite sex that could have led to a good date or great relationship? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be honest with me here. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I want to know&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been talking to someone you felt attracted to but got so nervous you stumbled over your words or didn't know what to say at all?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or have you ever been in a relationship with someone and wanted them to be a certain way so much that you literally drove them away? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Or have you ever saw someone that you wanted to start a conversation with but your emotions went CRAZY at even the THOUGHT of approaching them and you just decided that it would be easier to walk away than to overcome your fear...Only to beat yourself up over not approaching them later?  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Or have you ever felt like a certain person could actually control your emotions and your happiness was dependent on whether they liked you or not? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Have you ever had one of these things happen to you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you answered yes to   either of those questions, then read this description very carefully&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BIG SECRET - Why is dating so difficult?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I found was that everyone tries to fix problems in the moment&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp; Like what to say to start a conversation or how to get that date BUT you&amp;rsquo;re not SOLVING the problem itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, you probably already know how you could just say "hi" to an attractive person when you wanted to meet them BUT you &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;still get nervous&lt;/span&gt; every time the chance to meet someone your really attracted to comes along and your stuck without the date you really want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The real &amp;ldquo;Secret&amp;rdquo;Uncovered!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;I realized that instead of trying to deal with a problem IN THE MOMENT&amp;hellip; You can fix most problems before they happen.&amp;nbsp; Completely eliminate anxiety, fear, nervousness, self-doubt and then dating problems disappear and what once felt impossible is almost effortless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;That's why I decided to put on a special "inner game" work shop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll learn simple, proven psychological tricks that eliminate fear, anxiety and nervousness almost over night.  Once you master these    simple skills, you'll have the confidence to approach people in any    situation, date the type of people you want to date, and be in control of your own emotions.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Imagine    being at a Meetup event and gliding around the room talking with   anyone  and everyone.  You'll surprise yourself with how easy and   effortless it  is to get the type of dates you want once your fear and anxiety is gone.&amp;nbsp; You'll be able to make   friends and  attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A detailed, step-by-step process to build self-esteem that works every single time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An almost magical way to break your stubborn destructive habits quickly,  easily, and permanently&amp;hellip; in just under 5 minutes and the best part is you replace them with constructive habits that  FORCE you to become successful &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A powerful exercise to eliminate any &amp;ldquo;inner block&amp;rdquo; that      has held you back since childhood &amp;ndash; &lt;em&gt;fast and forever&lt;/em&gt; (Unfortunately most people will go their entire lives without REALLY      eliminating the things that prevent them from true success)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A step-by-step simple exercise that cures      anxiety FAST&amp;hellip; so you&amp;rsquo;ll never again hesitate when you see someone you      want to meet again. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The    meeting is limited to 20 people due to the size limitations of the    classroom (we'll be moving around a lot).  Our meetings usually sell out    quickly, so here's what I recommend.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your   calendar right now, and see if you have &lt;strong&gt;Sunday, May 15th&lt;/strong&gt; available.    The meeting runs from &lt;strong&gt;3:30pm to 5:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; and is conveniently located in   Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#2    - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this  workshop   right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They  always do.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#3   - Write it in your calendar so you remember to  attend, and please   arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal  networking.   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The   cost of the event is only $20, which is a  bargain for a professional   training that includes these skill-building  drills + personality   feedback.  Please remember to bring:  &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Eric &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S.    - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the    event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you    should have no problems.  My cell is: 617-903-7371 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door. The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick Richards</member_name><member_id>12716842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305577235000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>FINALLY Overcome Your Fears That Have Been Destroying Your Dating Life... Eliminate Inner Game Challenges Like Nervousness, Self-doubt And Anxiety That Are Holding You Back From TRUE Success In Your Dating Life...</why><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304909366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Breakthroughs In Psychology Help You Eliminate The Anxiety and Fear</name><id>17661521</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305487800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/17661521/</event_url></item>