<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-973-5200</phone><name>New England Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1260294</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050617</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Friends - &lt;em&gt;can you image this  will be our 3rd time with this special memorial weekend event - the weather has always been spectacular - so here's to Memorial Day Sunday 2012&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our plan is to take the water taxi, enjoy the harbor views, walk around the Charles Town Navy Yard and USS Constitution property. Finally, we can end the afternoon having  cocktails on the outside patio at Legal's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we make our way over to  &lt;strong&gt;Sinatra Sunday at Lucky's&lt;/strong&gt;,  for dinner and show before 7p.  (&lt;em&gt;If you've already made your rsvp for Lucky's and you'd like to spend the afternoon with this group too, let me know so you can bypass paying the rsvp fee twice.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 3:30p we will walk down the gang plank to the "MBTA Water Taxi". This ride is $1.70 each way, free with a Charlie Card Link Pass. MBTA Water taxi leaves every 30 minutes , so if you miss the 3:30p; take the next taxi and ride back to Long Wharf with the group on the 5:15p. The MBTA Water Taxi Route F4 leaves from Long Wharf to Charles Town Navy Yard (short 10 minute ride) After we will arrive on the dock we walk [i]10 minutes[/i] to the Navy Yard Pier and go through a security screening to enter the Navy yard. This could take time depending on crowds/wait times. You must have a valid ID. Note: You do not have go to through security screening to go visit the USS Constitution Museum which is also FREE. This may only be a museum visit as there could be long lines to board the USS Constitution. Make plans to get there earlier if you'd like to make the tour.   We will board the taxi at 5:15p and arrive at Long Wharf at 5:25p or when you're done, simply meet us at Legal's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/8/1/event_23200321.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at Legal Seafood across from the Aquarium.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diana</member_name><member_id>7792036</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338256355000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Baby Boomers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun</urlname><id>1347228</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Baby Boomers Meetup Group-Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336916099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Memorial Day Weekend 2012, Water Taxi, Harbor Views, Tours and Drinks</name><id>64598492</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338146100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Baby-Boomers-Meetup-Group-Social-Fun/events/64598492/</event_url></item>