<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>350 Asylum St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767597</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-278-Ribs (7427)</phone><name>Black Eyed Sally's</name><city>Hartford</city><id>664319</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.679497</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>FIRST AMENDMENT ROCK OFF IN HARTFORD OCT. 2&lt;br /&gt;Books are not the only form of expression subjected to censorship. As part of Banned Book Week – Celebrating Freedom of Expression – the ACLU of Connecticut and the Connecticut Library Association are hosting a performance of censored music on October 2nd: the First Annual First Amendment Rock Off. &lt;br /&gt;The event will feature live performances by the Teague McDonald Band, playing music that has been censored throughout the United States at some time within the last 50 years, including music by Jefferson Airplane, The Beatles, The Rolling Stones, Bob Dylan, and others.&lt;br /&gt;Acknowledging the influence music can have, authorities have repeatedly tried to silence alternative views in music:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1955, Elvis Presley was threatened by the police in California with arrest and obscenity charges if he moved at all during his performances. &lt;br /&gt;By 1963, the FBI had files on singers like Phil Ochs, Bob Dylan, and Jim Morrison who were under surveillance for their anti-war and “subversive” attitudes. &lt;br /&gt;Following the September 11th attacks, Clear Channel Radio released a list of over 150 “lyrically questionable” songs to radio stations to consider removing from their playlists. The list included Pat Benatar’s “Hit Me with Your Best Shot,” Steve Miller Band’s “Jet Airliner,” Billy Joel’s “Only the Good Die Young,” and Dave Matthews Band’s “Crash Into Me.” &lt;br /&gt;The First Annual First Amendment Rock Off is dedicated to appreciating the music and the artists who refused to let authorities dictate their art and freedom of expression. Tim McDonald and Burt Teague are part of a four-person band that has performed across Connecticut for many years. Burt Teague has won the Hartford Advocate’s Best Guitarist Award three times and Guitar Player Magazine’s award for best blues guitarist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their performance will take place on Thursday, October 2, from 8:00pm – 11:00pm at Black Eyed Sally’s at 250 Asylum Street in downtown Hartford. There will be a $10 cover charge at the door/$5 dollars with student ID and the proceeds will help support the ACLU’s longstanding fight against censorship.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Get Ready to dance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223165416000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222871925000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FIRST AMENDMENT ROCK OFF IN HARTFORD OCT. 2</name><id>8871773</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222992000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8871773/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>