<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Church Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.386906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waverley Square, Belmont</name><city>Belmont</city><id>10363672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Temps in the 40's and sunny, sounds like fine ridin' weather for November!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Route: &lt;a href="http://www.gmap-pedometer.com/?r=5739873" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.gmap-pedometer.com/?r=5739873&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is a 27 mile loop with a little bit of everything thrown in. Starting in Waverley Sq, Belmont (in front of Dunkin Donuts, around the corner from Wheelworks), we head into Waltham for a couple of short but steep uphills. We cross over I95 and do a scenic section along the Cambridge Reservoir. Then we turn way off the beaten path in Lincoln, using a short off-road section to connect two lovely dead-ends. The next 7 miles through Lincoln and Weston are leafy and very low on traffic. Our tallest hill comes just after Lincoln Center, then it's all downhill until our rest-stop at mile 18 in the Minuteman National Park. Mill St is another of my favorite roads, all leafy and quiet. The last 6 miles have a couple of significant climbs, and one looong downhill at the end!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When: &lt;br /&gt;

 Let's meet up at 9:45am and be ready to start at 10am. Aiming to be back 1 to 1:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: &lt;br /&gt;

 Waverley Sq, Belmont. Let's meet right in front of Dunkin Donuts, across from the commuter-rail stop (Wheelworks is around the corner, but they won't be open until we get back). Parking is free on Sundays in the commuter-rail lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who: &lt;br /&gt;

 You need to be okay with a 12-14 mph pace, and some significant hills. We will wait for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's required: &lt;br /&gt;

 * Road bike (or equivalent) in good repair &lt;br /&gt;

 * Bike helmet &lt;br /&gt;

 * At least one full large water bottle &lt;br /&gt;

 * Warm gloves and socks! &lt;br /&gt;

 * Layers appropriate for riding in 40 degree weather&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's recommended: &lt;br /&gt;

 * Energy bar or some other snack &lt;br /&gt;

 * Spare tube, air, and basic repair tools &lt;br /&gt;

 * Cell phone&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Magnus</member_name><member_id>56071382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353335508000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353128372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>27 mile loop: Waltham-Lincoln-Weston-Lexington-Belmont</name><id>91764382</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353250800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/91764382/</event_url></item>