<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://xtcboston.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;eXtreme Thursday Club Boston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The original eXtreme Tuesday Club is a weekly gathering of eXtreme Programming practitioners that has taken place in London for 8 years or so. It has provided a great community for like-minded software developers, managers and coaches to get together in a very informal way to discuss the ups and downs of using XP and other agile Software Development methods on a wide variety of projects in all sorts of organisations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A similar group formed in New York in January 2007, and the Boston group formed in September 2007.  The Boston group has since decided to move its meetings to Thursdays because of conflicts with other things on members' schedules.  We are currently planning to hold meetings on the first Thursday of each month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In February, five of us met at An Tain and had some quite good conversations, but changed venue half way through because the bar was quite load.  We're going to try the bar we switched to again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll keep trying out different locations in hopes of finding one more conducive to discussion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next meeting will be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Thursday, March 6th from 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;    * The Place, 2 Broad St., Boston, MA 02110&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My photo and those of some other regulars are on the blog at http://xtcboston.blogspot.com as well as here at Meetup.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Don Roby</member_name><member_id>5713230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205019076000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Extreme Programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>xp-28</urlname><id>840210</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>eXtreme Tuesday Club - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202431297000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>eXtreme Thursday Club - Boston March Meeting</name><id>7286761</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204846200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/xp-28/events/7286761/</event_url></item>