<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;VERY IMPORTANT:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the interest of safety &lt;u&gt;all participants should be able to hike at a MODERATE PLUS PACE, equal to book time or less.&lt;/u&gt; This is a long, strenuous route with no room to add time for participants unable to hike at the designated pace. If your hiking ability is not at this level you should consider a different hike that is shorter and less strenuous. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMC classifies this hike as a strenuous.  Certain sections of the trail are steep and challenging.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;starting at North Twin Trailhead ( end at Gale River Loop)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 4.30 mi/3 hr 39 min/+2917 ft on the North Twin Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The trail leaves the parking area and &lt;b&gt;crosses the river three times,&lt;/b&gt; ascending easily on an old railroad grade with occasional bypasses. After the third crossing, the trail begins to climb away from the river and railroad grade, crossing and recrossing a tributary brook. The long, steady climb continues, and the trail becomes quite steep, reaching the ledgy end of the ridge. The trail now climbs easily, passes a superb outlook ledge, and reaches the summit of North Twin. The North Twin Spur continues straight ahead to South Twin, and a side path leads right 60 yd. to a fine outlook from the western edge of the summit area.&lt;br /&gt; to North Twin Mtn&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  4.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  3 hr 39 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3007 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -90 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  +2917 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 1.30 mi/49 min/+129 ft on the North Twin Spur&lt;br /&gt; to South Twin Mtn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  5.60 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  4 hr 28 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3453 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -407 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  +3046 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 0.80 mi/59 min/-1128 ft on the Twinway&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The North Twin Spur begins here, turning right and running 40 yd. to the north knob and then on to North Twin, while the Twinway turns left (west) and begins a steady steep descent toward Galehead Hut. At the bottom of this descent, it crosses a small sag, passes over a ledgy hump, and soon reaches a junction 40 yd. from the hut, where the &lt;b&gt;Garfield Ridge Trail enters on the right and the Frost Trail continues straight ahead to the hut.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Frost Trail and Garfield Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.03 mi/1 min/+5 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; to AMC Galehead Hut&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.11 mi/3 min/-29 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Twin Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.36 mi/20 min/+268 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; After a short distance, the Frost Trail ascends a steep pitch, at the top of which a side path leads left 30 yd. to an excellent outlook over the Twin Brook valley. The main trail continues at a moderate grade to the rather flat and nearly viewless summit.&lt;br /&gt; to Galehead Mtn&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  6.90 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  5 hr 51 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3780 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -1619 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  +2162 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.36 mi/20 min/-268 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; The Frost Trail &lt;u&gt;descends steeply from the viewless summit of Galehead&lt;/u&gt;. It reaches an excellent outlook over Twin Brook Valley.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Twin Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.11 mi/3 min/+29 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; to AMC Galehead Hut&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.03 mi/1 min/-5 ft on the Frost Trail&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Garfield Ridge Trail and Twinway&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.60 mi/30 min/-356 ft on the Garfield Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Gale River Trail&lt;br /&gt; A bridge 1.7 miles from the trailhead was lost. WMNF crews have constructed a rock crossing that should serve well in low or moderate stream flows.&lt;br /&gt; hike 4.00 mi/2 hr 56 min/-1806 ft on the Gale River Trail&lt;br /&gt; From the &lt;b&gt;Garfield Ridge Trail, the Gale River Trail descends steeply down the north side of the ridge on rough terrain.&lt;/b&gt; The trail emerges at a gravel bank at the base of a slide where there are fine views up the valley and toward the Twins. The trail then passes the gravel outwash of an overgrown slide and descends the bank of the North Branch, which it crosses on large stepping stones (difficult only in very high water). It then joins an old logging road. It crosses a major tributary and passes through an old logging-camp site. It then becomes somewhat rougher, with several bypasses of muddy sections and washouts. It comes to the edge of the stream, crosses it on large rocks near the site of a bridge that was washed away in 2005. The logging road descends easily along the west side of the North Branch of the Gale River, some distance away from the stream. It turns left, leaving the old road, and crosses a tributary brook. It ascends the bank then leaves the woods arriving at its terminus at the Gale River Loop Rd.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;to Gale River Trailhead&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Totals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance   12.00 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  9 hr 41 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3932 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -4175 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  -244 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220369481000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217035327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Galehead and The Twins, strenuous hike</name><id>8413196</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220096700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8413196/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/7/global_4794087.jpeg</photo_url></item>