<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>299 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.343120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 738-1909</phone><name>Panera</name><city>Brookline</city><id>591193</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The votes are in from our last poll, and the winner is author Gregory Levey! We'll read his memoir &lt;i&gt;Shut Up, I'm Talking&lt;/i&gt; in August. The author plans to call us to answer our questions about his book. I have his email address if you want to contact him individually.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also decided the books we will read over the next few months (tentative meeting dates included):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Lovely Bones&lt;/i&gt; by Alice Sebold (September 28)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Two Weeks Since my Last Confession&lt;/i&gt; by Kate Genovese (October 26, author visit confirmed)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Three Weeks With My Brother&lt;/i&gt; by Nicholas and Micah Sparks (December 7)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a short description of &lt;i&gt;Shut Up, I'm Talking: And Other Diplomacy Lessons I Learned in the Israeli Government--A Memoir&lt;/i&gt; by Gregory Levey (Hardcover, $16.32)&lt;br /&gt;Shut Up, I'm Talking is a smart, hilarious insider take on Israeli politics that reads like the bastard child of Thomas Friedman and David Sedaris. Now a political writer for Salon, Gregory Levey stumbled into a job as speechwriter for the Israeli delegation to the United Nations at age twenty-five and suddenly found himself, like a latter-day Zelig, in the company of foreign ministers, U.S. senators, and heads of state. Much to his surprise, he was soon attending U.N. sessions and drafting official government statements. The situation got stranger still when he was transferred to Jerusalem to write speeches for Prime Minister Ariel Sharon.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll bring the book and my meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charis</member_name><member_id>3696786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264377239000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217279447000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August book discussion: Shut Up, I'm Talking!</name><id>8429351</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219608000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/8429351/</event_url></item>