<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Travel 3.1 miles west on Passaconaway/Dugway Road</address_2><address_1>1000 Passaconaway Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.995388</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Moat Mountain </name><city>Conway</city><id>917896</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.174049</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will meet at 9:00 AM at the South Moat trailhead and carpool over to the trailhead at Dianna's bath.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers must have prior winter hiking experience and be able to hike at a minimum of two miles per hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability policy as outlined on this web site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; starting at Moat Mtn Trailhead (south) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.20 mi/38 min/+39 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; Starting from the northeast terminus, a wide, graded, handicapped-accessible path descends slightly then turns left and winds through coniferous woods, intersecting the former route (a gravel road) at the clearing just below the mill site at Diana’s Baths, a series of scenic cascades where Lucy Brook runs over ledges and through large potholes. &lt;br /&gt; to Dianas Baths &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.20 mi/42 min/+153 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Moat Mountain Trail leaves the upper end of the clearing, close to the baths, by a logging road that follows the north bank of Lucy Brook to a fork (sign). Here the Red Ridge Trail turns left across the brook, eventually rejoining the Moat Mountain Trail at the apex of Red Ridge, making possible a fine loop hike. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Red Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.20 mi/46 min/+328 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Moat Mountain Trail crosses Lucy Brook (difficult at high water), and follows the south bank, then turns abruptly left uphill, away from the stream (last sure water), at the point where the Attitash Trail continues straight ahead along the stream toward Big Attitash Mountain. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Attitash Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.90 mi/2 hr 1 min/+2125 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Moat Mountain Trail ascends through the woods, and begins to pass over ledgy areas, reaching the first good outlook. It reaches a shoulder and runs nearly level through a patch of larger trees, then climbs fairly steeply through decreasing scrub and increasing bare ledge to the summit of North Moat, where there is an unobstructed view in all directions. &lt;br /&gt; to North Moat Mtn &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 5.50 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 4 hr 7 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2717 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -72 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2646 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 1.10 mi/37 min/-437 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the summit of North Moat, the trail descends sharply to the base of the cone, then easily along a shoulder with occasional views. At the end of the shoulder it drops steeply, passing over several ledges that require some scrambling, traverses another shoulder where there is a fine outlook to the right in a ledgy area, then descends to a col in a fine spruce forest. Ascending again, it passes the junction with the Red Ridge Trail left (east), just below several large rocks that provide good views. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Red Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 3 min/+7 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail descends to the major col on the ridge, then climbs up to low scrub followed by open ledges with continuous views, and passes east of the summit of Middle Moat (which can be reached in 80 yd. over open ledges). The trail descends to a minor col with a patch of woods that would provide some shelter in a storm, then ascends to the summit of South Moat. &lt;br /&gt; to South Moat Mtn &lt;br /&gt; hike 2.50 mi/1 hr 19 min/-2098 ft on the Moat Mtn Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail then descends into scrub and gradually increasing numbers of beautiful red pines, with views decreasing in frequency. The trail passes an outlook to Mt. Chocorua, and the trail becomes steep with rough footing. Below this section, the grade eases considerably, and then the trail turns right onto a wide, well-constructed relocation. It runs generally west at easy grades, crosses Dry Brook on a bridge, swings left and then right over a small ridge, and crosses a small brook. It climbs over another low ridge, then turns sharp left onto a logging road and leads past a gate to the parking area on Passaconaway Rd. &lt;br /&gt; to Moat Mtn Trailhead (northeast) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 10.70 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 7 hr 6 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3480 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3362 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +118 ft &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a black four door Toyota Echo with Maine plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270595999000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269878706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOATS THRU HIKE</name><id>13024871</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270386000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13024871/</event_url></item>