<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In this free presentation, participants will learn techniques to attend to challenges that often arise around this time of year.  These include:  travel, family gatherings, over consumption, economic pressures, increased alcohol intake, children's expectations, and other seasonally related situations that can sometimes create stress and anxiety.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our teacher, Lisa Blake, will be presenting this free talk about bringing spirituality into our lives for the holidays and winter season using mindfulness meditation. This Friday evening talk will be followed by a full-day workshop on Saturday, November 21.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About our teacher: Lisa Blake teaches internationally, holds a masters degree in contemplative traditions, graduating summa cum laude from Bangor Theological Seminary, and is a member of the National Association of Professional Women.  She has taught meditation to hundreds of students as young as three, as wise as ninety and many ages in between. Currently, she teaches meditation to high school students and adults, both through her private practice and her association with True North Health Center. Her belief is that you are never too young to begin, never too old not to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Lisa and her work, see: &lt;a href="http://mainemindfulnessproject.com" target="_blank"&gt;Maine Mindfulness Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259015796000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256915164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breathing Joy into the Holiday: Meditations for a Thankful Heart &amp; Merry Moments</name><id>11749446</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258761600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/11749446/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/0/global_10129760.jpeg</photo_url></item>