<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>497 Lime Rock Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06039</zip><lat>41.930660</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lime Rock Park</name><city>Lakeville</city><id>1555143</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.379707</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There are actually three races on Saturday 24th September. The website for more information is here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://endurancekarting.com/events/info2011_limerock_september.asp"&gt;http://endurancekarting.com/events/info2011_limerock_september.asp&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are three races on that day - 8 AM, 11 AM, 2PM. Race suits, helmets etc are *NOT* provided - but available for rent. Lap timers are also available for rent. A team can have a maximum of 3 drivers. The cost of a team to race is $450 (so its $150 per head). For that money the team gets a 20 minute practice time and 90 minutes of racing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no requirement to form a team before we head there - they will mix and match people if we so desire. For example, if we end up with 7 people williing to go - we can&amp;nbsp; form two teams of 3 and the last person can just let endurance karting know - so that they can put that person in another 3-person team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last time we raced - this was a blast and its a great technical track -&amp;nbsp;very different from F1 indoors. There are decreasing radius turns, severely off-camber turns, and wide sweeping turns that require braking finesse - all in all tons of fun at a new and exiciting track. Whats more the karts are superb and a lot less tiring on the hands - so many teams actually sign up for multiple enduros on the same day !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the best part is being inside a real track and seeing real cars racing on a weekend - pretty sweet :)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter the track and meet at the kart track trailer inside limerock park main track</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bjoddi</member_name><member_id>7273001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316967596000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Racing Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>racing</urlname><id>1209048</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>Racing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309912017000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Limerock Park Connecticut Outdoor 1.5 hour Endurance Race</name><id>24682051</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316887200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/racing/events/24682051/</event_url></item>