<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=124067744308143&amp;amp;ref=ts" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://profile.ak.fbcdn.net/hprofile-ak-snc4/hs322.snc4/41571_124067744308143_4010_n.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tashina Clairridge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tashina is taking her music very seriously to the point where she will make a lasting impact on the people she touches with her talent in the future. She is in music for the right reasons and we as listeners will benefit from it&amp;quot;. -Mark O'Connor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tashina Clarridge has played Fiddle for 22 years - since the age of two. She has performed throughout the western United States, taught hundreds of lessons and works...hops, and won countless awards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raised in the mountains of northern California, Tashina studied with Megan Lynch and Rob Diggins. Her musical horizons were greatly expanded by frequent visits to Nashville for Mark O'Connor's fiddle camp where she studied with many fiddle heroes such as Darol Anger, Natalie MacMaster, Buddy Spicher, Matt Glaser, and Mark O'Connor. She is the current Grand National Fiddle Champion, a 6-time Grand National finalist, 6-time California State fiddle champion, and 2-time Western Open Grand Champion. Though her contest history clearly distinguishes her as a sparkling clean, studied player in the genre of Texas-style fiddling, it is her enthusiasm for many diverse styles of music that brings such a high level of creativity to her playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tashina has performed at Carnegie Hall as part of Grammy winning bassist Edgar Meyer's young artists concert, and will be touring with Mark O'Connor this fall. She travels and performs throughout the western United States with her brother Tristan, the Bill Evans String Summit, and the contemporary bluegrass outfit, Due West. Together Tashina and Tristan have taught many lessons and workshops and have instructed at Mark O'Connor's Strings Conference for the past 5 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jefferson Hamer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“…sounds like a forgotten Gram Parsons release suddenly discovered….”&lt;br /&gt;-Marquee Music Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jefferson Hamer started performing on music-club stages around Boulder, Colorado in the late 90&amp;#8242;s, where he was immersed in the thriving bluegrass and jamband scene. He toured constantly on the national circuit, first with his original acoustic trio Single Malt Band, and later in the electric country-rock outfit Great American Taxi. After a decade spent living and working in the West, he moved to New York, seeking a broader audience for his original songs. As a newcomer to the big city, he found his way to the traditional Irish and Appalachian Old-Time sessions of lower Manhattan, where his ear, voice, and acoustic guitar playing earned him a seat alongside the fiddles, banjos, and pints of stout. His musicality reflects this breadth of influences, and his own songs echo the distilled melodies and lyricism of British, Irish, and American traditional music. In addition to his own full-band and solo shows, which are often flogged to life by unaccompanied electric guitar, he plays and sings with a decorated roster of performing artists including Anais Mitchell, Kristin Andreassen, Tao Seeger, Tashina Clarridge, and Laura Cortese. His 2004 release “Left Wing Sweetheart” earned a 4-star review from Marquee Music Magazine, who wrote it “sounds like a forgotten Gram Parsons release suddenly discovered.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The artists' websites:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.clarridgefiddlers.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.clarridgef...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jeffersonhamer.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jeffersonh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested donation $12- at the door; $10 if reservation is made at least 24 hours in advance and Tuesday Club members. Addition of a $1/person “preservation fee” that goes to the LG House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Jamaica Plain series' big sister concerts are presented at the Unity Church of God in Davis Square, Somerville.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional information about this and other notloB concerts can be found at the &lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" target="_blank"&gt;http://sites.google.c...&lt;/a&gt; and/or by joining the mail list at &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt; or by sending an email to notlobreservations@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations recommended – notlobreservations (at) gmail (dot) com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See other notloB Parlour Concerts at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=136759883033069" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://sites.google.c...&lt;/a&gt; (website)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt; (mail list)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/notloB-Folk-Concerts/118395891509908" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; (Facebook fan page)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://notlobmusic.blogspot.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://notlobmusic.bl...&lt;/a&gt; (blog)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284772654000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284330575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tashina Clarridge &amp; Jefferson Hamer</name><id>14745680</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284768000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/14745680/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/b/global_5923419.jpeg</photo_url></item>