<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Goethe-Institut Boston and the Coolidge Corner Theatre are pleased to present new films from Germany highlighting young directors who, with their first or second features demonstrate that there is more to New German Cinema than The Lives of Others. Sunday Matinees showcase a sampling of new and award-winning German films rarely shown outside Europe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films in German with English subtitles and shown in Moviehouse 2 at 1:00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Price: All $5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Runaway Horse (Das Fliehende Pferd):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the past 12 years, middle-aged Helmut and Sabine Halm have enjoyed their vacation routine at Lake Constance: she swims, he bird watches, they dine and read. As luck would have it, this year Helmut runs into a former schoolmate, Klaus, and his enchantingly beautiful, much too young girlfriend Hel. Seemingly brimming with virility and overly sociable, Klaus keeps finding ways to intrude on Helmut’s measured reserve. Helmut finds the inevitable comparisons increasingly annoying as the mismatched couples dine, hike, and sail together more often than Helmut is game for. As the uninvited upwelling of tensions and desires intensifies under a thinning veneer of amicability, a sudden squall as they are out sailing provokes a clearing of the air….&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Germany 2007) dir. Rainer Kaufmann, 97 min, color, in German with English subtitles, on DVD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for a discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the exit with a Meetup sign,</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222221757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Runaway Horse (Das Fliehende Pferd)</name><id>8820508</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224435600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8820508/</event_url></item>