<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come along on a hike thats supposed to be to one of the best in New England and was even featured on a travel channel on TV.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the park website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With its thousands of acres of protected highlands, 3,165-ft. Mt. Monadnock was designated a National Natural Landmark in 1987. There are 40 miles of maintained foot trails, many of which lead to the bare rock summit through unique alpine vegetation. Unsurpassed 100-mile views to points in all six New England states are the reward for a climb. A magnet for hikers, Monadnock is said to be the second most frequently climbed mountain in the world, after Japan's Mt. Fuji. &lt;br /&gt;Note - there is a $4 fee for park admission&lt;br /&gt;Camping is $25 a night per site (so split the fee and lets share a site)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going up saturday, time is TBD, maybe do some trails saturday afternoon. 2-3 people possibly camping out Saturday night so far. Nothing fancy, rustic bare necessities, campfire and Irish Hot Chocolate or whatever anyone else may want to bring for themselves.&lt;br /&gt;Sunday the &amp;quot;Official&amp;quot; HIKE meetup, 9 am.&lt;br /&gt;Start on White Dot Trail to Cascade Link Trail, then linking up to the Pumpelly Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link for more information about this trail (and where this info came from):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.qcc.mass.edu/brink/Trav-rec/mt_monad/mmcascade.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.qcc.mass.e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRAIL INFO:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance from parking to summit:   &lt;br /&gt;3.5 miles/5.7 km, via White Dot and Pumpelly. &lt;br /&gt;Ascending time:  &lt;br /&gt;Three hours (estimated). &lt;br /&gt;Descending time:  &lt;br /&gt;Two hours (estimated). &lt;br /&gt;Difficulty rating/rank:  &lt;br /&gt;2–3/– &lt;br /&gt;Crowd Factor: &lt;br /&gt;1–3 (on a scale of 1 to 5, with 5 being near-continuous contact with others.) You will probably meet other people on the trail below the Spellman Trail junction. Above the Spellman, you are unlikely to see anyone else though there may be signs of others. &lt;br /&gt;Access: &lt;br /&gt;White Dot to Cascade Link at Falcon Spring (ascent) or Pumpelly Trail. &lt;br /&gt;Trail marker: &lt;br /&gt;A yellow dot. &lt;br /&gt;Average Grade: &lt;br /&gt;20% &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While this trail is generally climbing as it heads to the northeast, it's a considerably gentler climb than either the White Dot or White Cross trails. This comparative  gentleness makes it one of the easier hikes on the mountain. One of the less traveled trails, Cascade Link is quieter and less crowded than most and it's relatively narrow, usually allowing only two people to walk abreast and sometimes forcing you to go single file. The trail passes through mixed forest, its base mostly soil, though it goes over several easily crossed streams where you have to step on rocks. Cascade Link is a very pretty trail, not as demanding as the other trails, over which you can travel fairly rapidly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The starting point for the hike is the Mt Monadnock State Park Headquarters Parking Lot.&lt;br /&gt;If descent time is a factor a shorter return trail can cut that time in half.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Possibly 4 people so far looking at going up sunday with possible car-pooling.&lt;br /&gt;Contact info for Chris:&lt;br /&gt;cavecrawler83@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;401-864-2217 (don't know how good cell signal is in the park tho)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Chris's Cell: 401-864-2217</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis </member_name><member_id>8755592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>10283481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254573986000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253051528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Manadnock Camp(w/possible hiking) 26th/Primary Meetup Hike 27th</name><id>11381400</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253970000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11381400/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>