<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;TC:&lt;/b&gt; Anne (catwoman@mosaicmass.org )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;EVENT:&lt;/b&gt; Join us in celebrating Chanukah! We will be doing all of the fun things that made Chanukah your favorite Jewish holiday when you were a kid. We’ll light the Chanukia, say the blessings and sing your favorite Chanukah songs. Of course, we’ll eat the traditional holiday favorites, latkes, and sufganiyot (jelly donuts), as well as other treats. Bring your own chanukia and candles (our party will be on the 7th night, so you need 8 candles) so we can light together.  We’ll provide dreidels and “gelt”for those who want to spin.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP:&lt;/b&gt; Please &lt;b&gt;RSVP to the e-mail address above&lt;/b&gt; by December 19 and submit payment via PayPal.  You can use this payment method whether you have a PayPal account or not.  Go to www.paypal.com and follow directions to “Send Money/Send Money Online”.  In the “To” address field, enter mosaic_mass@yahoo.com.  A $.50 fee is added to the price to cover the cost of the PayPal processing fee (approximately the cost of an envelope and stamp, and much quicker and easier!). Party location will be at a private home in Belmont.  Exact address and directions will be provided when both your e-mail RSVP and PayPal payment are received. This event is limited to 40 people, so RSVP early!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEET:&lt;/b&gt; 7:30 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $8.50 for MOSAIC of MA members, add $5 for non-members. If you’d like to join MOSAIC the night of the party, the additional non-member fee will be waived.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP to Get the Details</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231626104000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228874187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHANUKAH PARTY </name><id>9311671</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230424200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/9311671/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/0/global_1883520.jpeg</photo_url></item>