<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Greetings, GMC Volunteers and Friends! It&amp;rsquo;s that time again&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is your invitation to join the fun at Green Mountain Club headquarters for our 16th Annual Snowshoe Festival on Saturday, February 4 from 8:30-3:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year&amp;rsquo;s event will feature a full schedule of beginner, intermediate, and advanced snowshoe trips as featured in GMC&amp;rsquo;s Snowshoeing in Vermont: A Guide to the Best Winter Hikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like last year, full-day admission is $8.00 for members, $10.00 for nonmembers, and free for kids under 12. This year&amp;rsquo;s event will include a winter party from 3:00-5:00 with live music, food, and a chance to win great raffle prizes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nonmembers who join on the day of the event will receive the membership discount as well as a free Snowshoe book. What a deal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to saving the date for this event, we hope that you will consider lending a hand as an on-site volunteer or trip leader! We are looking for volunteers to guide hikes, sell tickets, coordinate parking, lead activities for kids and feed hungry snowshoers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see a mix of friendly Snowshoe Fest devotees from years past and some fresh new faces to make this year&amp;rsquo;s event successful. We are looking for helpers for half the day (shifts run from 8:00-12:00 and 12:00-3:00) in each of the following areas: Parking &amp;ndash; 3-4 volunteers Greeters &amp;ndash; 4 volunteers Raffle tickets &amp;ndash; 1-2 volunteers Membership &amp;ndash; 2 volunteers Floater &amp;ndash; 1 volunteer Registration &amp;ndash; 6 volunteers Facilities Coordinator &amp;ndash; 1 volunteer Education Program Reps &amp;ndash; 2 volunteers Kids&amp;rsquo; Activities Leaders &amp;ndash; 1-2 volunteers Volunteer Registration &amp;ndash; 2 volunteers On-site Trip Leaders &amp;ndash; 4-6 volunteers Off-site Trip Leaders* &amp;ndash; 40 volunteers (1/2 with first aid, 2 per trip) Hot Beverages and Snacks &amp;ndash; 4 volunteers *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We require that at least one co-leader for every hike has Wilderness First-Aid certification, which includes First Aid and CPR training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost to registered Snowshoe Fest trip leaders is $95, which is half price. CPR Training is also offered that weekend for an additional $35. Please reply to this email or call me at the phone number below to sign up. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing and/or working with you! Mari Zagarins Director of Membership and Volunteer Services Green Mountain Club 4711 Waterbury-Stowe Road Waterbury Center, VT 05677 Phone: 802-244-7037 x24 Fax: 802-244-5867&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of the Green Mountain Club is to make the Vermont Mountains play a larger part in the life of the people by protecting and maintaining the Long Trail System and fostering, through education, the stewardship of Vermont's hiking trails and mountains.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328366687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320880235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Green Mountain Club 16th Annual Snowshoe Festival</name><id>40617142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328362200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/40617142/</event_url></item>