<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer Michael Blair @ 9788081932&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The quest for the New England Hundred Highest continues - this time Mount Nancy is our target.  At 3,926 feet it is #51 in NH and #74 in New England. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have never hiked on these trails or climbed to this summit and did all of my current research using the AMC's &lt;i&gt;White Mountain Guide&lt;/i&gt;, a trail map, and the Internet. The link below provides an overview of where we will be going and include topographic maps of the area. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6934" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more information about Nancy from Peakbagger.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will ikely encounter winter conditions on this trip. It will also involve off-trail travel.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow Nancy Pond Trail before leaving the trail to bushwhack to the summit - we will return the trailhead following the same route in reverse.  Along the way we will get to see the cascades and have lunch by the pond. There will be water, mud, snow, and possibly ice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;On this moderate pace trip we will hike about 7.0 miles and climb about 2,900 feet (&lt;i&gt;for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet&lt;/i&gt;). It should take an average hiker about 6.0 hours to complete this hike – this does not include time for rest breaks or lunch. This hike is considered INTERMEDIATE because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the objective of this trip is to enjoy ourselves as we climb as a group, your safety, and the safety of the others in our group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this trip, or overestimate your skills and abilities, you may put yourself and/or others at risk - consider this before you decide if you are going to participate.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker in the group. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire trip please contact me.&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Reaching the summit is optional, getting down is mandatory.&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;(Ed Viesturs on the dangers of mountaineering)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weather&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is winter in the mountains. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel this hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list describing the &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;minimum required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Footwear: Hiking boots or trail shoes. Some form of light traction (e.g. MICROspikes) is mandatory. Don't think we will need snow shoes yet but will reassess before the trip.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket with hood.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay hydrated during the trip. Hydration bladders may freeze during winter - bottles with insulating sleeves work best.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in cold temperatures). Personal first aid kit. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it &lt;u&gt;prior&lt;/u&gt; to this trip.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not certified or trained in wilderness first aid. You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you plan to participate you must answer the questions for both you and any guests when you RSVP - if you don't answer them your RSVP will be removed without notice and you will be prohibited from participating.&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged - indicate in your RSVP if you need a ride or can give one. You are responsible for making your own arrangements so you should check back often and contact others who might want/need to carpool.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP up-to-date - if your plans change please be considerate and update your RSVP as soon as possible.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't have a confirmed ride when you RSVP I would ask that you RSVP MAYBE until you have one - once you have a confirmed ride you can then change your RSVP to YES.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All MAYBE RSVPs will be changed to NO three days before the event so people who might be on the WAITING LIST have an opportunity to make the necessary arrangements in order to participate.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs are welcome on this hike provided they are under voice control, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, and you bring a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin this hike at 8:30 AM from the Nancy Pond Trail parking area on Route 302 about 9 miles south of the AMC Highland Center.  According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 170 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 2 minutes to drive there.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=Crawford+Notch+Rd%2FUS-302+W&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFaEYoQId1zq_-w&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=44.113842,-71.355686&amp;amp;sspn=0.02089,0.038409&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=8" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a Dark Green Toyota Highlander SUV with MA plates or a White Lexus SUV with MA plates. There will be a meetup sign in the window. I pretty much look like the picture from my profile.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293113563000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291228269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH NEHH - Nancy (Cascades, Pond, and Bushwhack)...</name><id>15609974</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292765400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15609974/</event_url></item>