<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On May 2nd, we will watch this incredible one hour long documantary &amp;quot;FORGIVING DR.MENGELE&amp;quot; Could you forgive a war criminal? Could you forgive your worst enemy if it released you from your past trauma?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FORGIVING DR. MENGELE tells the story of a shocking act of forgiveness by Auschwitz survivor Eva Mozes Kor and the firestorm of criticism it has provoked. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eva and her twin sister, Miriam, were victims of Nazi doctor Josef Mengele's cruel genetic experiments--an experience that would haunt them their entire lives. We follow Eva's metamorphosis from embittered survivor to tireless advocate for reconciliation. This unexpected transformation was sparked when Eva, in an attempt to get information about the experiments, met with another former Auschwitz doctor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eva's ideas about justice, revenge and the possibility of healing through forgiveness--as well as the passionate opposition from other survivors--become a window to a larger discussion of the many ways people define forgiveness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link for the trailer: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.." target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Hope you can come to enjoy this surprisingly inspiring movie with us,&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209944454000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209597093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie:  Forgiving Dr. Mengele</name><id>7845815</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209771000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/7845815/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/7/1/global_622209.jpeg</photo_url></item>