<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>435 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.828488</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-875-1344</phone><name>Rein's New York Style Deli</name><city>Vernon</city><id>1349575</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.484213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This time...we go to the New York Deli experience, right here in our own back yard...Rein's New York Style Deli in Vernon! Just like Aunt Sadie used to make in her kitchen...to warm our tummies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For over thirty years it's been just like coming home - Rein's Deli, serving traditional New York style Jewish Deli...food that feeds the soul &amp;amp; warms the heart. TM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1972, Rein's Deli was the answer to the search for a good corned beef sandwich by Bob Rein, who with his wife Betty and brother Bernie, brought authentic New York Style Jewish deli to New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Rein's Deli in Vernon you may indulge yourself with their homemade soups, mounds of savory hot pastrami and corned beef on rye, hand-cut lox layered on cream cheese laden bagels, crisp potato pancakes, knishes, delectable cheese blintzes and creamy hand made cheesecake from New York. And that's just a sampling of their enormous menu! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It is a  family owned and operated business where the customer is always # 1.You may select your favorite deli treat, cheeses, salads, and smoked fish, sandwiches, etc. And don't leave without taking a peek in their display case filled with the most heavenly homemade desserts. Any or all of their goodies are available to take home.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; So, for those who know great deli, coming to Rein's Deli is like coming home.  For the Rein and Hurwitz families and their staff at Rein's Restaurant, it's like opening their home to friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a night in old New York.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rein's is located at 435 Hartford Turnpike (Exit 65 off I-84), Vernon, CT 06066&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the table with the hungry people and the meetup sign! Or ask for reservation "Meetup/Terri"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248911281000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247173009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rein's New York Style Deli...</name><id>10841387</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248390000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/10841387/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/0/global_9574016.jpeg</photo_url></item>