<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Union Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02190</zip><lat>42.174202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Feathers Wellness Studio</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>1575625</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.950699</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Reiki level l Training Certification. $150. with Michelle Paradise, RYT, CRMT, Owner. 7.75 contact hours for nurses. Reiki is an ancient Japanese form of relaxation. It is not affiliated with any religion. Once learned the new practitioner is able to perform Reiki on themselves, children, plants and animals. This is the first of three levels. You can use Reiki in any situation in which pain, anxiety or depression is present. It promotes a good night sleep. Research is available to support these statements. Preregistration is required. Please contact: info@FeathersWellnessStudio.com Purpose/Goal: To train individuals in Reiki level One Target audience: any individual interested in learning Reiki. Objectives: 1. The learner will discuss rationale for wanting to learn Reiki. 2. The learner will recall the definition of Reiki. The learner will recall the History of Reiki. 3. The learner will recall the Nursing Implications of the Nurse Practice Act. 4.The learner will recall the current research available to date. 5. The learner will discuss potential indications for Reiki. 6. The learner will discuss the ethical considerations of Reiki sessions. 7. The learner will recall the potential indications for Reiki. 8. The learner will recall their Reiki lineage. 9. The learner will discuss Reiki integration into practice. 10. The learner will discuss the chakras and related hand positions/disorders/spiritual lessons. 11. The learner will recall the significance of grounding and clearing. 12. The learner will discuss the difference between Attunement #1 and #2. 13. The learner will demonstrate a self seated Reiki session. 14. The learner will demonstrate a full Reiki session. 15. The learner will recall the Reiki principles. 16. The learner will discuss what opportunities exist to support the novice to expert paradigm shift -Benner Nursing Theory. In order to receive CE's: You will attend the class in its entirety. You will demonstrate a Reiki session. You will complete an evaluation form. Disclosures: The Planning committee members do not have a conflict of interest in this topic. There is no commercial support or sponsorship for this activity. Please note that Michelle Paradise, RYT, CRMT, has a vested interest in this subject as she is the owner of the studio. She agrees to provide the information in a nonbiased manner. This continuing nursing education activity was approved by the Ohio Nurses Association, (OBN-001-91), an accredited approver by the American Nurses Credentialing Center&amp;#146;s Commission on Accreditation. for 7.15 contact hours. *Approval valid through 08/18/2012. ONA # 13,745-R10&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335023181000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329887348000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reiki level 1 Certification CEU's for RN's</name><id>53301332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335018600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/53301332/</event_url></item>