<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSIwfe9XVuaQuInT6ACeI57f6N3Ou39br6oGpc2ruY7cFDL6dQR" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please join us for a &lt;em&gt;special edition&lt;/em&gt; of our monthly &lt;strong&gt;Portland Trading Post&lt;/strong&gt; swap event, now running for over two years!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trading Post events (&lt;strong&gt;new venue is the Portland Food Coop space on Hampshire Street in Portland - easy to find and plenty of parking)&lt;/strong&gt; are free and open to all (bring a friend!). You can really bring &lt;strong&gt;anything&lt;/strong&gt; to trade:  food, baked goods, preserved food, handmade items, tools, books, plants, seedlings, seeds, etc. are all welcome at Portland Trading Post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQv-vydNTZUwq5N7y_HWuT35AkGzg2Qz1ldyVohhLf7qN1fKWysIA" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;You can bring an swap anything you like at the February event, but there will be an &lt;strong&gt;extra special focus on seeds!&lt;/strong&gt; Bring seeds to swap (along with envelopes, pens, labeling supplies) as well as a notebook or camera.  There will be &lt;strong&gt;skill-sharing stations&lt;/strong&gt; on how to make seed-starting mixes, start seeds and also about how make 2013 a successful seed saving year (planning matters when it comes to seed saving!).  Any members that would like to share some of their skills or techniques on seed saving or seed starting, contact the organizer.  We already have a couple of people signed up and the more the merrier.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to chat in advance about what you might be bringing and/or looking for from others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW&lt;/strong&gt;:  If you are a member of Hour Exchange Portland (&lt;a href="http://www.hourexchangeportland.org/howtojoin.php"&gt;join here if you're not&lt;/a&gt;) consider bringing more substantial items to trade to time dollar hours!  Consider making some "services" coupons if you'd like to trade your time or skills for some of the goods at the Trading post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main idea is that we are stepping outside of the cash economy and mutually "gifting" things to each other in a way that turns whatever we have in abundance into a diversity of goodness and good will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only rules are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No cash changes hands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't start the swapping until everyone's there and has a chance to look around at what's on offer (usually about 15 minutes into the swap, but it's flexible)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can swap with someone or simply "gift" things to each other without taking a return item. Your choice.  Make sure you've found a home for all your stuff before you leave (or take home what hasn't been gifted).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you bring a food item with multiple ingredients, pls label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to talk about what you might be bringing or seeking. Food/Snacks/Fiddles/Juggling/Attended Children welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very relaxed, social atmosphere.  Even if you have nothing to trade, feel free to come by just to see what it's all about and meet some members.  We are considering combining these with short skill-shares or "show and tell" sessions, too.  These are kid-friendly events but in a "keep an eye on your child" sort of way, as the space is also a functioning business with equipment, etc. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that gifting and bartering is still something many of us are getting a handle on...it requires different thinking for our society which has been so used to "monetizing" every transaction or product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to the &lt;a href="http://www.portlandfoodcoop.org/"&gt;Portland Food Co-op&lt;/a&gt; for offering their space for the monthly Portland Trading Post events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking for this event is either in the parking lot (free) behind Local Sprouts or on either side of the street in front!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aaron Parker</member_name><member_id>6845673</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jesse McAvoy </member_name><member_id>25646832</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360607926000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355414898000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Trading Post - Seedy Sunday! Seed Swapping/Starting/Saving Party</name><id>lccwpyrdbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360530000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/95218602/</event_url></item>