<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meetup is now SUNDAY!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancer is such a tragic thing that effects so many, including my mom. Luckliy she has been in remission for 5 years but there are so many that are still battling breast cancer. In honor of all those people and the upcoming Breast Cancer Awareness Month (Oct) I decided to host a event that would raise money to be donated to the &lt;a href="http://ww5.komen.org/default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Susan G Komen Organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am a Stampin' Up! demonstrator, which is a direct sales company that offers craft and scrapbooking products. Come over to make a FREE card, learn how to stamp, emboss, stamp on candles, much more. All proceeds (20% of merchanise) will go directly to Susan G Komen Org. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great way to meet other members, get a little crafty, learn new things, and donate to a great cause. Plus with the holidays coming up you can get some shopping done for the scrapbookers and crafters in your life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have snacks and drinks on hand. Check out the great things that Stampin' Up! has to offer... address stamps, personalized stamps, card kits, and much more. The best is that you have fun, make a card and all proceeds go to charity!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI-I have 2 rabbits at home. Just want to give the heads up to anyone who is allergic.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green House on the Right. Door is in the BACK of the house. Park on Street.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254589027000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253286789000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charity Fundraiser for Susan G Komen </name><id>11405745</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254078000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/11405745/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/a/global_10810042.jpeg</photo_url></item>