<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 Old River Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.692941</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-975-3600</phone><name>Wyndham Hotel </name><city>Andover</city><id>809493</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.204044</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us this month to learn some great basics regarding Social Media!  My friend Ja-Nae Duane will share the social media basics you need to grow your business!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Social Media 101: Learning the Basics while Growing Your Business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: Learn what is Social Media and Why is it Vital for the Survival of your business; Where is your target demographic spending their time; three pronged attached to social; who should be doing social media within your business and how to make money through your social engagements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Strategist, artist, creative economist, and author of “How to Start Your Business with $100” Ja-Naé Duane, has been written up and seen in dozens of media, including by Associated Press, NPR, Classical Singer Magazine, Boston Globe, and Business Week. Mostly recognized for her diverse skill set and unwaivering commitment to improving the quality of life for our global community, Ja-Naé was nominated as one of New England’s “Most Innovative Leaders of 2007.” She is CEO of Wild Women Entrepreneurs, CEO of Ja-Naé Duane Ventures, Co-Founder of the Massachusetts Artist Leaders Coalition, and Founder of The Leaders. Ja-Naé is also a professional opera singer, social media strategist, and a faculty member at Northeastern University. For more information, visit: &lt;a href="http://www.Ja-Nae.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Ja-Nae.net...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289488405000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286975188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>dqzfpynpbnb</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289406600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/15094814/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/0/global_12349600.jpeg</photo_url></item>