<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Use of Open Source Products and Tools&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just as open source software is gaining wider use in various industries, it is being employed in medical applications as well – such fields as electronic health records, clinical trial data management, and medical devices for therapy and diagnostics. Low cost and easy availability make open source attractive, but FDA-regulated manufacturers face unique challenges. The responsibility to assure safety and effectiveness, and to maintain control over the development lifecycle, lead to tough questions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How can manufacturers meet design control requirements? &lt;br /&gt;What hazards have been introduced by the uncontrolled software? &lt;br /&gt;How do manufacturers gain the necessary confidence in the software? &lt;br /&gt;What can manufacturers use to qualify the software? &lt;br /&gt;If a major issue occurred with an open source component, how will FDA react? &lt;br /&gt;As well, the manufacturer’s need to protect intellectual property contrasts with the open source licensing philosophy of free distribution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The FDA requires full validation of medical device software, regardless of its origin: in-house, bespoke, third party, or open source. In light of proposed changes to the 510(k) process, increasing use of open source software in regulated products could attract greater agency scrutiny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our speakers will explore these topics and others, in the context of their own experience with open source software.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speakers will be:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cal Collins Chief Executive Officer, Akaza Research &lt;br /&gt;During his tenure at Akaza Mr. Collins has spearheaded the development of OpenClinica, the world’s leading open source system for Electronic Data Capture (EDC) in clinical trials. Mr. Collins has also led clinical informatics collaborations with the National Cancer Institute, the National Center for Research Resources, and the NIH’s Center for Information Technology. Prior to Akaza, he served as co-founder and Chief Technology Officer of the technology consulting firm Isovera. Mr. Collins holds a degree in Environmental Science and Public Policy from Harvard University. &lt;br /&gt;(TBA)   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SIG Co-Founders (click web site links for biographical information):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony Raymond New Harbor SQA  tonyraymond@newharborsqa.com &lt;br /&gt;Brian Shoemaker   ShoeBar Associates   bshoemaker@shoebarassoc.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Fee (includes a light supper):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Advance On-site &lt;br /&gt;MedDev Group member $15 $20 &lt;br /&gt;Nonmember $25 $30 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Padanarum Room&lt;br /&gt;Reservoir Place&lt;br /&gt;1601 Trapelo Road&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA  02451&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.memberclicks.com/mc/community/eventdetails.do?eventId=291258&amp;amp;orgId=meg&amp;amp;recurringId=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.memberclic...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296085481000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292992846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Use of Open Source Products and Tools</name><id>15796408</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296081000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796408/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>