<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 N Main St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.454669</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 265-4571</phone><name>Half Moon Coffee and Grille Cafe</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>997418</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.817948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://i225.photobucket.com/albums/dd27/lorenzo66_photos/Half_Moon.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's Italian Meet Up was held at the Half Moon Cafe in Wallingford with 10 members in attendance.  Several members can speak fluent Italian  and several members that speak very little Italian attend  to be part of the wonderful atmosphere of their heritage.   There is no level of speaking skills demanded of any member.  All members speak English and are always happy to help or to just enjoy your company.  Many members have stories to share of parents or grandparents who influenced their lives in a very romantic way in their culture.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Lorenzo indicated in his email to each member, we do notice a stronger turnout of members from the greater Hartford area.  We will reach out to members in southern CT a couple of more times to determine if the attendance demands our travel to Wallingford.  Half Moon has a great atmosphere with everything from a simple coffee drink up to full blown novel dinners.  We encourage a strong attendance on the 12th and hope that members don't feel the pressure of arriving at 7 as we are often there until at least 9:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the future, I will be researching new opportunities for us to attend involving Italian Fests, Wine tasting, and short excursions.  We are hoping to set up one month on the weekend with ample notice. &lt;br /&gt;Any and all recommendations are welcome for any events that a member is aware of involving our Italian heritage.     All organizers are happy to assist anyone with questions or concerns for remaining a member.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shelley </member_name><member_id>8285328</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250351596000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Amici Italiani</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-452</urlname><id>535327</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>Connecticut's Viva Italia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249005462000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Italian Meet Up at Half Moon Cafe In Wallingford</name><id>10998460</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250118000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-452/events/10998460/</event_url></item>