<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Camp Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Trip:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weekend climbing and camping trip to the world-renowned Gunks (Shawangunks), a traditional climbing mecca in NY! This trip is for experienced trad leaders and experienced lead belayers only. It's a social trip for those interested in making more trad-climbing friends and contacts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Gunks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The majority of the climbing cliffs at the Gunks are located on the protected grounds of the Mohonk Preserve. There are over 1000 routes, more than five linear miles of cliff face, single and multi-pitch, ranging from approximately 30 to 300 feet. Tons of varied-feature world-class climbing terrain ranging from 5.0 to 5.13+. (And a bunch of bouldering too). In a word, AWESOME!  More info:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mohonkpreserve.org/climb"&gt;http://www.mohonkpreserve.org/climb&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.gunks.com/"&gt;http://www.gunks.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mountainproject.com/v/the-gunks/105798167"&gt;http://www.mountainproject.com/v/the-gunks/105798167&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Group:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trip is open to 8-ish people, and is first and foremost a social trip for experienced trad climbers. We'll accomodate RSVPs from strong seconds (those without trad racks or trad lead experience, but are strong, experienced outdoor climbers who can follow leaders and have solid lead-belay skills from either trad or sport climbing) only if we have enough leaders with trad gear to go around. Interested seconds, send me a message, and I'll put you on the wait list until we get enough leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camping:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have reservations at a local campground with full bathrooms and hot showers. PLEASE NOTE that we need to check-in by Friday 9 PM. If you cannot leave early enough to get out there in time, this is not the trip for you. (For example, drive time from Boston is approx 3.5 to 4 hours, or possibly longer if you get stuck in rush hour traffic). But it'll give us a chance for meet-and-greet on Friday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Costs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Camping: $24/person (includes Fri &amp;amp; Sat nights).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mohonk Preserve Entrance Climbing Fee: $17/person/day &lt;br /&gt;

      (or $34 total for 2 days, etc) &lt;br /&gt;

      (unless you have or buy an annual pass, $90/year)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Group Dinner in town on Saturday: TBD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Procedure and Cancellation Policy:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I'm not already familiar with your background, please be prepared to answer questions about your experience level when you RSVP. (Only organizers can see answers; or else email me the info). Your name will tentatively appear on the RSVP list, but I'll respond to you directly to confirm your RSVP, assuming you're qualified. ** &lt;em&gt;RSVPs close Sat June 9th at midnight&lt;/em&gt;. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accepted participants will then need to pay for camping fees upfront to hold their spot, but please wait until you get a confirmation message. Upon cancellation, refunds will be given only if another person can fill your spot or if we get a refund from the campground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full trip details will be sent out to the final group the week before the trip. Questions? Feel free to contact me, and/or post comments to this trip page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for more trad partners this season but can't make the trip?  Email me through the link on my profile page; be great to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get Psyched!  Woo-hoo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deb&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Specific camp meetup directions will be provided to final RSVP group a week before the trip.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb</member_name><member_id>9443907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1340632329000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336600814000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend Gunks Trip (Fri Jun 15 - Sun Jun 17)</name><id>64135462</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339808400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/64135462/</event_url></item>