<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Due to inclement weather, our &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/calendar/9911627/"&gt;Atheist Holiday Caroling&lt;/a&gt; has been rescheduled.  We will now be using the original time for a low-key rehearsal and the consuming of holiday beverages and snacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at my apartment in Porter Square at 6pm.  I have a keyboard but not the skills to play it well, so please let me know if you have piano or accompaniment experience and might be able to play parts a bit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get to my apartment, walk north from the Porter T stop (towards CVS), continue past Shaw's, and go down the street that dead-ends into Shaw's.  We are about the sixth house on the right.  617-407-8782 if you need assistance.  We will likely be under two hours, so if you are driving, you may want to park in the Shaw's lot -- at your own risk!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Re: RSVP: we have limited space available -- 15 tops -- so be diligent about following through.  Also, if you will be unable to attend on Saturday, please at least RSVP as a &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; to give other folks the first shot at coming.  We'll gladly welcome extra company... if there's room!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring doorbell #3</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261264502000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260853901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atheist Holiday Caroling Rehearsal</name><id>12087694</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261090800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/12087694/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>