<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Church St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374382</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-864-6100</phone><name>Border Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669139</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>With &amp;quot;And Now For Something Completely Different&amp;quot; at 2:00 pm this Saturday and &amp;quot;Monty Python's Holy Grail&amp;quot; at 7:00 pm, we should break for dinner between the movies. How about the &lt;b&gt;Border Cafe&lt;/b&gt;? Note: Border Cafe does &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; take reservations. It is purely first-come-first serve, though they did mention that between 3:30 pm and 5:00 pm there is a lull, and a large group of 10 - 20 can be accomodated. We'd just have to all be there to wait for a table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Sure, &amp;quot;Life of Brian&amp;quot; is at 4:30 pm, but man cannot live by Python alone. Feel free to add yourself to the list and RSVP Yes if you are 90% sure you can come. If it turns out you can't come, could you take yourself off the list by noon on Saturday? T.J. obsessively looks for new people armed with a printout of thumbnail photos of the people who are goign to be there, waving new people to the group. If he can't find someone who RSVPs yes he automatically thinks that he didn't try hard enough to find people, and starts compulsively waving a bigger MEETUP sign. Seriously. Every nerd is quirky in his or her own way, and this is his own little quirk. He's been that way since he joined this group back in May 2008, and it probably isn't going to change anytime soon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;: Border Cafe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Address&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;Harvard Square&lt;br /&gt;32 Church Street&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;617-864-6100&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.bordercafe.com/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bordercafe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be outside the Border Cafe by 4:45 pm and put in his name for whoever is there. He's guessing that it'll be maybe a 10 - 15 minute wait at that hour before the dinner rush. Border Cafe has a rule where they don't seat large groups until everyone in the group is there. If we get one or two people straggle in soon after, it might be fine. We can head back to the Brattle Theater at 6:30 pm for the 7:00 pm showing of Holy Grail. That'll give us enough time to eat, right? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, an actual &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and an actual red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. It's T.J. the human landmark! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Border Cafe&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bordercafe.com/whoweare.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bordercafe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In 1987, the well-known Border Cafe opened its doors on a cozy corner in the heart of Harvard Square. A true commitment to quality, value and fairness in all respects of the business would be the guiding values.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] The original menu offered traditional Tex-Mex recipes. Shortly after the Border Cafe opened its doors, an exploration into Cajun country began. The Border Cafe adopted the philosphy of an unassuming culinary genius named Jose Creole...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reviews&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/border-cafe-cambridge" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's casual, it's not authentic, it's Tex-Mex, and the fajitas and the margaritas are wonderful.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257803347000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257353444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre-Monty Python's Holy Grail @ Border Cafe</name><id>11793251</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257630300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11793251/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/a/global_11642282.jpeg</photo_url></item>