<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>suite 660</address_2><address_1>460 Totten Pond rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.395260</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Aprigo</name><city>Waltham</city><id>862093</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.256368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>All,&lt;br /&gt;There's a slight change to the agenda tonight. Somu wasn't able to make it and I'm excited to have Alex Barnett  from Intuit do the 2nd talk. This is a great opportunity to hear from two technological authorities about different aspects of the cloud. We'll have one technical presentation and one business / eco-system one.&lt;br /&gt;Also, my colleague and co-founder at Aprigo, Ron Zalkind, will be running the meetup tonight in my absence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the updated agenda is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Topic: How Intuit QuickBase Works: Behind the Scenes with the QuickBase Architect&lt;br /&gt;Jim Salem, Intuit QuickBase’s architect and co-founder will present its unique, highly scalable application engine which seamlessly integrates multiple web services including database, email, workflow, and reporting.  We’ll discuss its patented active-active load balancing technology that has made it one of the most reliable, fast and proven SaaS technologies today.  The engine also drives the Intuit Partner Platform, a service for RIA developers to deliver QuickBooks-integrated applications to small businesses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Alex Barnett leads the developer relations team at Intuit, responsible for Intuit Developer Network (IDN) and developer engagement and evangelism for Intuit Partner Platform (IPP). &lt;br /&gt;Abstract: Today, millions of Small Businesses are adopting the SaaS model. These businesses need their data to connect, synchronize and interoperate across the multiple back-office and front-office applications and services they use to run their business. How will this work? How can the cloud help Small Businesses get more out of their data and leverage the functionality of the cloud? What are the opportunities for ISVs and SaaS providers to connect and program against the Small Business data cloud? This presentation will describe how Intuit’s PaaS offering: the Intuit Partner Platform, is enabling a brand new class of cloud connected services, SaaS and RIA offerings for Small Businesses and partner with ISVs and SaaS providers to solve real problems for millions of Small Businesses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Previously, Alex was VP, Developer Community at Bungee Labs after spending five years at Microsoft Corp. in various community program management and marketing positions. Before joining Microsoft, Alex was at a director at a leading digital marketing and Web development agency (Bluewave) for seven years. Alex played professional cricket for eight years (Middlesex and Lancashire). He blogs at &lt;a href="http://alexbarnett.net/blog" target="_blank"&gt;http://alexbarnett.ne...&lt;/a&gt; and Twitters at &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/alexbarnett" target="_blank"&gt;http://twitter.com/al...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regards,&lt;br /&gt;Tsahy.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tsahy Shapsa</member_name><member_id>8753907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257464337000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-cloud-services</urlname><id>1460349</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>Boston Cloud Services - All things Cloud,  SaaS, PaaS, XaaS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255699612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Updated agenda - Boston Cloud services November Meetup</name><id>11640857</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257291000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-cloud-services/events/11640857/</event_url></item>