<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>265 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5927 </phone><name>MIT Museum </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>777893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mike suggested this.  I read about this exhibition recently and thought it sounded interesting.   Since I work at MIT, it will be easy for me to run a meetup for this.   The museum is open after 5 (5-8PM), with free admission, after 5, on the second Friday of each month.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be in the lobby of the museum at 5:30 and head in to see the exhibits around 6, with anyone who would like to join me.   I realize that some people will not be able to make it right at 6.   If you arrive late, and miss the group, please enjoy the museum exhibits and join us after.    Or look for us inside as you browse the exhibits.  At 8, I will again wait in the lobby for everyone to gather and we can chat for a bit and get a head count of anyone interested in going to a nearby establishment for food and drinks.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's called &amp;quot;MIT 150&amp;quot; and it will showcase technological artifacts that came from MIT's labs over the last 150 years.  From the Museum's web site: &amp;quot;Visitors to The MIT 150 Exhibition will find large scale artifacts – a racecar, a wheelchair, and an outer space control system simulator, as well as simpler objects like the wooden model of the city of Boston used in the wind tunnel experiments that solved the not so simple problem of window panes falling from the John Hancock Tower when it was built in 1976. Visitors will also discover the old and the rare – like the 19th century notes of Ellen Swallow Richards, MIT’s first female graduate student who was instrumental in creating the first water quality standards in America, along with the new – a virus built battery recently shown to President Obama.&amp;quot; The exhibition is open from January 8 to December 31.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2010/150-2011.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recommend taking the T to get there.    The closest T stop is Central Square on the Red Line.   For more detailed directions and/or information on parking: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/visit/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin and also have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296075379000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294243448000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"MIT 150" exhibition at the MIT Museum</name><id>15928507</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295046000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15928507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/9/global_20623737.jpeg</photo_url></item>