<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Heritage Farm</name><city>Lowell</city><id>2172761</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340263</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

On Monday nights Heritage Farm Ice Cream puts on FREE concerts across the street at The Sampas pavilion. They also sponsor a classic car show (begins at 6pm) -cars from days gone by. &lt;br /&gt;

Bring a chair or blanket ( and bug repellent) for the concert while the sun sets over the Merrimack River. It's a great night out! FREE Outdoor Concert On The River: MATT JACKSON &lt;br /&gt;

*We will meetup at Heritage Farm - at the porch. I will have a meetup.com pin (or sign). Then, we can walk across to the Sampas Pavilion for the concert. If you show up later you can find us with a meetup sign in the back of either a chair or my hat. You won’t miss us! &lt;br /&gt;

You can purchase something from the Heritage Farm menu, ice cream, hot dogs, burgers, or beverage.... or you can bring your own snack. www.heritageicecream.com This is a shared event with other meetup groups. &lt;br /&gt;

WHERE THIS IS AN ALL-OUTDOOR EVENT, RAIN CANCELS. I will update as close to 6pm in the event the weather is questionable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT MATT &lt;br /&gt;

Matt Jackson has been involved in music since the age of 8. Starting as a vocalist, Matt found inspiration in his father’s guitar playing and decided to pick up the instrument as well. Matt’s first release entitled, “In Good Company” gave him his launch into the music scene and the reviews came pouring in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matt’s latest release is a full band EP entitled, “Too Far Gone.” The EP has been classified as “Swing-Pop” with a contemporary twist. The lead single, “Too Far Gone” takes people by surprise with a powerful vocal that leaves a very real emotional connection with the song. This EP has launched Matt to a new level both musically and professionally. Matt’s voice always get people’s attention at shows and his onstage presence and personality brings about very loyal fans.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346765597000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345964569000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Outdoor Concert On The River: MATT JACKSON</name><id>79392822</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346712300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/79392822/</event_url></item>