<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be going on a moderate three hour hike at Bigelow Hollow.  We will determine the exact route after we see the state of things after the rain comes (should be something like 4 miles but could be as much as 5 - variation is because rain floods some areas due to beaver dams).  Please plan on wearing hiking boots, bring plenty of water, and some bug spray (or else you WILL be eaten!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bigelow Hollow State Park and the adjoining Nipmuck State Forest offer over 9,000 acres of recreation opportunities, including miles of hiking trails and 3 large ponds (Bigelow, Mashapaug, and Breakneck Ponds) in Northeastern Connecticut. This park is beautiful!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the park itself.  There should not be a charge to enter the park.  When you enter the park, head up the road and we will meet at the 2nd parking area along the road from the entrance, which is a picnic area. It will be on your left side as you drive in (it has the water pump, 2 dark colored outhouses, and a bulletinboard). On the map, it is the 3rd marked parking area from the entrance. If you reach the boat launch and the end of the accessible road you've gone one parking area too far. In the event the parking area is full, we will still meet at that location as the trailhead we are using is there. Please allow some extra time in case you need to walk to this area from available parking. Note that there is virtually NO CELL reception at the park!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs are most welcome at the park &amp;amp; hike! The site for the park says &amp;quot;Pets on a leash are permitted.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location/directions for entrance to Bigelow Hollow State Park off of Rte. 171 in Union, CT via Mapquest: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Bigelow+Pond&amp;amp;city=Stafford+Springs&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.99204&amp;amp;longitude=-72.131743&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=13881594" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/big_nipm.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rough indication of topography via Google Maps (click Terrain button, if needed):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=Bigelow+Hollow+State+Park,+Union,+CT&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.002908,-72.132711&amp;amp;spn=0.016775,0.023947&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=A" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the park: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325174&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one in Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am the 6'2" man with the dark blue Dodge Caravan. ;-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220984912000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220663274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Bigelow Hollow SP and Nipmuck SF, Union CT</name><id>8699174</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220810400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8699174/</event_url></item>