<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1222 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-338-6060</phone><name>The Red Fez</name><city>Boston</city><id>810598</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066704</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;All are welcome to join us at this unique venue. We will have a cash bar and some different food. Come by and socialize with your friends and meet new ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mediterranean and Middle-Eastern inspired hip bistro with great atmosphere and a fabulous, long bar. You'll think you're in Marakesh. Roasted meats, tempting exotic spices ... cold drinks ... heaven. An iconic Red Fez affixed to the facade identifies the South End&amp;rsquo;s most celebrated Middle Eastern restaurant. Inside, Moroccan lanterns cast an alluring light about the earthy hues of the dining room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moorish arches and Persian rugs, fixtures reminiscent of a medieval Kasbah, interrupt exposed brick and give the room a good dose of exotic without diluting its modern vivacity. The striking balance of ethnic nostalgia and contemporary style draws an eclectic crowd to this hip Washington Street institution. Impressive selections of cocktails are available including a citrus vodka version of a mojito called the Morocc...[striped]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excellent Turn By Turn Directions Here. Copy and Past into browser. &lt;a href="http://www.theredfez.com/fez_information.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.theredfez.com/fez_information.html&lt;/a&gt; (Turn left onto Perry St. to find our Parking Lot behind the building.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316811837000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313551881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An "Afterwork"...Life is to be enjoyed and the Red Fez is the place</name><id>29798851</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316556000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/29798851/</event_url></item>