<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>west hartford</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06119</zip><lat>41.764294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>caryl's house</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>462542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.727501</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Three years ago, I started this Meetup. I knew absolutely no one in Connecticut. I essentially was starting my life anew: no real family, friends far, far away, and a bit disappointed with almost everything.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first dinner was in January, six people attended. Two of those people I now count as friends and one of them is one of the best friends I have ever had in my life. At that first dinner, I needed to borrow some vanilla so I knocked on a neighbor’s door. They not only loaned me the vanilla they crashed the party and Paul has never really left. I cannot even explain how much I love Paul (and Angela). He grows on you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next month six people attended and two more people were added to my friends, one of them is one of the best friends I have ever had in my life. In March, nine people attended. I now had regulars but from the new people in March I made two more friends, one of which is one of the best friends I have ever had in my life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time passed, the Meetup grew to have its regulars, and every month one or two new folk would appear. Attendance jumped to 12 by November of 2008. Paul joined Meetup to keep track of us all and that month the new person who came became one of the best friends I have ever had in my life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By March of 2009, we had 10 people attending regularly; more friends had been made, but that month two folk stopped by who were destined to become dear friends. Maybe it is getting bit boring for you but how can I leave anyone out? In May, we had grown to 12 regulars and one or two newbies, one of the newbies in May has become a very dear friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In July of 09, our attendance jumped to 17. Boy was my apartment maxed out from that point forward! That was also the month that one of my favorite people in the whole world started cooking with us. My apartment was jammed with amazing people, wonderful friends, interesting new people and people I truly love. Life was very different for me now than it was at the start of this epicurean adventure and I can tell you for sure that as good as the food always is. The people put the epic in epicurean for me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As many of you may remember in November or 2009, I had to cancel the monthly dinner. It was a difficult time for me, but thanks to the friends I have made through this cooking club I had all the love and support for which anyone could ask. We bounced back together in December with our regular dinner and a special party that was the birth of our gingerbread extravaganza. In January, we celebrated our second year together and the beginning of our third.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This past year we started our field trips, which have been so much fun and so successful! Paul and Angela took over the summer dinners at their awesome new house. Our attendance skyrocketed with waiting lists almost as long as the attendance list. New friends have been made; our regulars number around 20 now. Those who attended will ever forget the 12-hour cooking marathon for Demi Glace (soon to be scheduled for round two?).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been asked to take part in several special events as a group, we are working on a cookbook (just need an artist), we were contacted by Master Chef for auditions (one of us made it to a final cut but they were stupid producers and did not make a good choice). We have a new roomer (better kitchen) venue at my new home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This January we celebrate the third year anniversary of our band of merry chefs. We celebrate the beginning of a new epicurean year, filled with regular dinners; field trips; special events; traditions; and I am very sure, some surprises. The theme, if you are still reading this, is comfort food. It is our tradition for January. It gives me comfort that we collectively have traditions and that one of them is the welcoming of new people as if they had always been part of the regular group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I sincerely hope that you have made friends, and garnered at least a little bit of the bounty that I have from our Cooking Club. I wish you all the joy, love, and good eats you deserve for this New Year and all the years to come.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I celebrate a life filled with wonderful and extraordinary friends, love, and a “made from scratch” family. Life is excellent, maybe even epic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;oh and.......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember there are no rules.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.   We are a drinking club with a cooking problem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295154904000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292181743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The photo has no meaning, Comfort Food is the theme</name><id>vmbmnypcbsb</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295049600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/15713337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/b/global_20197131.jpeg</photo_url></item>