<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Booty Vortex is a great dance band....If you like to dance this event is a must!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last couple times we went to see them we didn't sit down all night so be sure to wear your dancing shoes and be prepared to work up a sweat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan to meet at 8pm for dinner, if you are only joining us for dancing, the band starts at 9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This a &amp;quot;pay-your-own-way&amp;quot; event, suggest that you purchase your band tickets in advance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.villagesmokehouse.com/lowell.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.villagesmo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************** update *******&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was just informed that if we wait until we finish dinner to go into the lounge, there will NOT be any tables left.  I was also informed that we can have dinner in the lounge if we split into smaller groups.  &lt;br /&gt;since we only have 7 definate yes for dinner, I am going to reserve 2 tables in the lounge for dinner &amp;amp; if more people end up coming to dinner, they are going to have to wait for the next available table.  In any case, by having dinner in the lounge, we are garentied to have at least 2 tables to put are items and for people who aren't dancing to sit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can all make it!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the dance floor shaking it....</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281130658000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267407682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dancing to Booty Vortex at Village Smokehouse in Lowell, MA</name><id>12738194</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268442000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/12738194/</event_url></item>