<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>MEETUP IS BETWEEN 6:30and 6:45, SEATING STARTS AT 6:30. The Show starts at 7:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be next the ticket window at 6:30 pm, and our group will be sitting at the CTNites.com VIP Club tables. You can call Robert at (860) 569-8094 for more info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VIP CLUB FUNNY BONE REGULARS - PLEASE KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR THE NEW PEOPLE AND HELP THEM GET SEATED AT OUR TABLES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Buckland Hills Mall&lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040&lt;br /&gt;(860)-432-8600&lt;br /&gt;www.HartfordFunnyBone.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE every Wednesday Nite with a Funny Bone T-Shirt (T-Shirts cost $15)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for Our CTNites.com VIP Entertainment Club Table Signs, and Join Us For A Great Nite Of Comedy!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the show, join us at: &lt;br /&gt;Time-Out Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill &lt;br /&gt;346 West Middle Turnpike &lt;br /&gt;(Manchester Parkade) &lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040 &lt;br /&gt;649-7400 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All CTNites.com VIP Clubbers will receive a 10% discount on everything!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The food is much better and less expensive than at the Funny Bone, so save your appetite for Time-Out after the Comedy show! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Time-Out from the Funny Bone Comedy Club:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:Start out going SOUTH on BUCKLAND ST toward TOLLAND TURNPIKE.&lt;br /&gt;0.1 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;2:Stay STRAIGHT to go onto ADAMS ST.&lt;br /&gt;1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3:Turn LEFT onto MIDDLE TURNPIKE W.&lt;br /&gt;0.5 miles&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;4:Take A Right at light to Manchester Parkade, Time Out is on Left by the Stairs&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Total Est. Time: 4 minutes     Total Est. Distance: 1.75 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get lost, call Robert at (860) 569-8094&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headliner: Gary Owen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTNites.com/Events/FunnyBone.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here For Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Brother's got the WESTSIDE, trailer park's got DOUBLEWIDES!!&amp;quot; Gary Owen is the only white guy to ever host B.E.T.'s &amp;quot;Comicview&amp;quot;. Many people recognize Gary as the dancing &amp;quot;Mr. Broccoli&amp;quot; in the blockbuster movie &amp;quot;Daddy Day Care&amp;quot; with Eddie Murphy. Or as the goofy redneck deputy in the movie &amp;quot;Held Up&amp;quot; with Jamie Foxx. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Owen, was always the &amp;quot;class clown&amp;quot; when he was growing up in Cincinnati, Ohio. After high school, he got serious and enlisted in the Navy. He was chosen for the prestigious Presidential Honor Guard. Spinning rifles and carrying flags for George Bush and Bill Clinton turned out to be the wrong job for a funny guy. &amp;quot;I was always smiling,&amp;quot; he remembers. &amp;quot;So I got yelled at for smiling all the time.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;After leaving his ceremonial position, Owen became a military police officer at the Naval Installations on Coronado Island in San Diego. But he was too much of a pushover to be a cop. He made only two arrests in three years. &amp;quot;I was the worst, &amp;quot; he admits. During that time, though, he embarked on his true calling - stand-up comedy. One night while hanging with his service buddies, Owen worked up the nerve to go at a nightclub. After only a year of doing stand-up, he was named &amp;quot;Funniest Serviceman in America.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In July of '97 he auditioned for BET's &amp;quot;Comic View. &amp;quot; Two appearances on the multi-cultural comedy showcase won him his own one-hour &amp;quot;Grandstand&amp;quot; show. At the end of the season he was selected from the year's four &amp;quot;Grandstanders&amp;quot; to be the host. Owen was excited because he'd always been a huge &amp;quot;Comic View&amp;quot; fan. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gary has numerous appearances on Comedy Central, as well as hosting MUN2's hit comedy show &amp;quot;Loco Comedy Jam&amp;quot;. Not one to sit and wait for things to happen, Gary recently released his first comedy CD &amp;quot; Live from Tampa&amp;quot; and his first comedy DVD &amp;quot;Breakin Out The Park&amp;quot;. One things for sure, when people see Gary live on stage, they keep coming back over and over again. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197070626000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196614918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Nite- Wacky Wednesday At The Funny Bone Comedy Club Dec 5</name><id>6841956</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196897400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6841956/</event_url></item>