<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Upper College Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.858501</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myles Standish Parking Lot #2</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>1248332</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.662430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Buffett has officially declared summer over and the return of cool hiking days perfect for a romp in the woods.&amp;nbsp; We invite you to join us on one of our favorite hikes over some of those trails you see leading away from the Bentley Loop to get a little different perspective on the forest.&amp;nbsp; This hike was designed to cover less familiar territory and provide both pup and owner with a reasonably good workout.&amp;nbsp; It can be done in 2 hours but usually takes us longer as we take time to enjoy the views and appreciate some special forest offerings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll leave parking lot #2 along hiking trails and also travel&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/0/8/event_57006152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; marked and unmarked forest roads as well as bird fields and some hunters' trails that can be pretty over grown if Fish and Wildlife hasn't mowed them for hunting season by the time we get there.&amp;nbsp; In August, the sandy spots&amp;nbsp; in some of the roads are alive with tiny toads that delight my granddaughter.&amp;nbsp; In September the asters, Indian pipe, and golden rod decorated the way.&amp;nbsp; By October, maybe we'll see a hint of fall color along with historical and natural landmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A dog is not required but water for 2- and 4-legged hikers as well as snacks or lunch for a rest stop are advised.&amp;nbsp; We haven't had a problem with ticks but spray and sturdy shoes are always in order.&amp;nbsp; Buffett will be wearing his shiny new bell so we always know when he's coming along the trail.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317669067000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288830974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking with my dog- the First Sunday Hike for October</name><id>16272397</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317569400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/16272397/</event_url></item>