<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We attempted a partial Presi Traverse (Adams, Jefferson, Washington) on the 18th, but came just shy of the peak of Washington.  I'd like to summit Washington and repeat the summits of Monroe and Eisenhower, which we did in the rain a few weeks back.  Washington will be Kelby's 24th Peak (Yes, Kelby is my dog).  Help celebrate this milestone - At age 9, he'll be 1/2-way to his 48 peaks in just under 3 months!  This will be a dog-friendly hike.  We'll meet at the Edmands Path Trail Head and carpool to the Cog Railway lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will ascend via the relatively moderate Jewell Trail.  Below the treeline is mostly moderate grade, but be prepared for rocks once we hit the alpine zone.  This can be hard on the ankles and knees - and the paws!   (Following a tip from another Meetup hiker, I've been treating my puppies' paws with Musher's Secret.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow the Jewell Trail to where it meets up with the Gulf Side Trail, take the Loop Trail to the summit of Washington and then follow the Crawford Path to the summits of Monroe and Eisenhower, passing the Lakes of the Clouds Hut along the way (It will be closed).  We will descend via another relatively moderate trail - the Edmands Path.  If we choose, we can abbreviate this hike by descending via Ammonoosuc and skip Eisenhower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite the moderate nature of the ascent and descent, be prepared for the intensity that it takes to scramble and rock-hop through the alpine zone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views, SO if the weather looks like it will be better or clearer on Sunday, I will reschedule for Sunday instead.  Please plan accordingly.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expect cold weather conditions on Mt. Washington.  DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM.  While it is feasible to &amp;quot;get away with this&amp;quot; in summer, this can be dangerous in colder weather.  And October weather on the Presidentials IS colder.  If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.  Bring plenty of water - sources on this route are scarce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), I will not wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Book time is about 11 hrs, 13.5 miles, .&lt;/span&gt;  Plan on it taking this long +/- about an hour. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit &lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jewell Trail&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.7 mi, 3hr 20min&lt;br /&gt;This trail begins at the parking area on the Cog Railway Base Rod 1.1 miles from its junction wit Jefferson Notch Road.  Base Road is the road that leads from US 302 to the Cog Railway Base Station.  The trail ascends the unnamed ridge that leads west from Mt. Clay and ends at the Gulfised trail high on the west slope of Mt. Clay, .3 mi north of the Clay-Washington Col and 1.4 mi north of the summit of Mt. Washington.  The grade is constant but seldom steep, there are no rock scrambles and the footing is generally very good below the treeline and only moderately rough and rocky in the last section below the Gulfside.  It provides the easiest route to Mt. Washington from the west, featuring a great length of ridge walking above treeline with fine views, but this part is also greatly exposed to the weather and offers no shelter between the summit and the treeline.  In bad weather, or if afternoon thunderstorms threaten, it is safer to descend from Mt. Washington via the Lakes of the Clouds hut and the Ammonoosuc Ravine Trail, despite the slippery and steep footing on the latter trail; descent by the Jewell Trail offers much easier footing and may be preferred when the weather cooperates.  The trail is named for Sargeant Winfield S. Jewell, once an observer for the Army SIgnal Corps on Mt. Washington, who perished on the Greely expedition to the Arctic in 1884.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Jewell Trail enters the woods directly across the road from the parking area, crosses the Ammonoosuc River at .1 mile, then swings northeast and ascends at an easy grade.  At .4 miles, the Boundary Line Trail diverges left, while the Jewell Trail ascends the crest of a low ridge between the Ammonoosuc River and Clay Brook, joining the old route of the trail at 1mile.  The old path (sign) can be followed right to the Base Station.  From the junction the main trail descends slightly to Clay brook, crosses a footbridge, then climbs northeast by long switchbacks.  At 2.0 miles, it passes through a blowdown patch at the edge of the steep wall of Burt Ravine, where there are interesting though limited views.  It then swings somewhat to the north side of the ridge and climbs east, staying well below the ridgecrest until near the treeline.  Reaching treeline at about 3.0 miles, it zigzags at a moderate grade with rough rocky footing up the ridgecrest, which quickly becomes less prominent and blends into the slope of Mt. Clay.  At 3.5 miles, the trail swings to the right away from what reamins of the ridge and angles up the slope at an easy grade to the Gulfside trail.  For Mt. Washington, follow the Gulfiside Trail right.  In good weather, the fine views from the cliffs of Mt. Clay can be reached fairly easily by a scramble directly up the rocks above the junction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gulfside Trail (From the Junction of the Jewell Trail)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...From this junction, the ridgecrest of Mt. Clay can be reached in tood weather by a short scramble up the rocks without trail.  The Gulfside swings southeast and soon sescends slightly to a point near the Clay-Washington col, where the Mount Clay Loop rejoins it from the left.  A little to the east is the edge of the Great Gulf, with fine views, especially on the east cliffs of Mt. Clay.  The path continues southeast, rising gradually on Mt. Washington.  About .1 miles above the col, the Westside Trail branches right, crosses the Cog Railway and leads to the Crawford Path and Lakes of the Clouds Hut.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Jewell Trail to the Trinity Heights Connector via Gulfside&lt;/b&gt; - 1.1 miles, 1hr, 5 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trinity Heights Connector&lt;/b&gt; (Loop Trail to Summit of Washington)&lt;/b&gt; - .2mi, 5min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crawford Path&lt;/b&gt; (Washington to Monroe, to Eisenhower, excluding Summit Loops) 3.7mi, 2hrs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Descending from the summit of Mt. Washington, the path is on the right side of the railroad track.  After passing between the buildings, it leads generally south, then west.  After passing the old corral, it reaches a junction where the Gulfside Trail turns a sharp right.  Here the Crawford Path turns sharp left and zigzags downward through a trench in the rocks.  At .6 miles, the Westward Trail enters on the right and in another 50yd the David Path diverges left, following the original, less sheltered route of the Crawford Path.  The Crawford Path now descends moderately on the NW side of the ridge, well below the crest and the Tuckerman Crossover and the Camel Trail enter on the left at the same point just before the trail reaches the Lakes of the Clouds.  It then passes between the lakes and reaches the hut at 1.5 miles, where the Dry River trail enters on the left and the Ammonoosuc Trail on the right.  The path now climbs up to the base of Mt. Monroe, where the north end of the Mt Monroe Loop diverges right to cross both summits of Monroe, offering excellent views.  The loop over the summits is about the same length as the parallel section of the Crawford Path but requires about 350 feet more climbing...the main path continues along the flat ridge, passing an unmarked path on the left at 2.6 miles that leads in 130yd to the barely noticeable summit of Franklin from which there are excellent views particularly into Oakes Gulf.  At 3.0 mi the trail drops rather steeply off the end of the shoulder, descends moderately to the sag, passing the Mt. Eisenhower Trail on the left at 3.5 miles.  The Loop leaves on the right at 3.7 mi overlooking Red Pond.  The Edmands Path can be reached from this junction... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt Monroe Loop&lt;/b&gt; .7 miles, 350 elev 30 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt Eisenhower Loop&lt;/b&gt; (from Crawford Path to the Summit and back) .8 mi, 350 ft 50 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Edmands Path&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(From Summit of Eisenhower to the base) 3.3 mi, 3 hr&lt;br /&gt;From the Mt. Eisenhower Loop, a few yards from the Crawford Path, the Edmands Path crosses the nose of a ridge on a footway paved with carefully placed stones. It then enters the scrub and contours around the north slope of Mt. Eisenhower at a nearly level grade, affording excellent views through a fringe of trees. It crosses a small brook running over a ledge and descends to pass through a small stone gateway. It swings right and angles down the mountainside on a footway supported by extensive rock cribbing. It descends steadily, undulating down the west ridge of Mt. Eisenhower, carefully searching out the most comfortable grades.  At 2.6 miles, it crosses a wet area and diverges right onto the old logging road.  At 3 miles, it turns sharply left, leaving the old road and crosses Abenaki Brook.  To the trailhead, the path continues to run nearly level across two small brooks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL.  I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). &lt;b&gt;I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286899443000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284905314000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Columbus Day:  Washington, Monroe and Eisenhower</name><id>14820624</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286793000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14820624/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/a/global_16921818.jpeg</photo_url></item>