<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you are interested please email Tom.  I need a confirmation by Monday July 21st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week I was able to secure some larger group sites for this trip.  We can have up to 15 people on this trip so please let me know if you are interested.  Yes - you are free to bring a friend or two.  Please be aware that you must be able to travel to North Conway NH by Thursday night to take part in this trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a 3 day camping trip long the Magalloway and Androscoggin Rivers with a short section on Lake Umbabgog.  Camping (2 nights) will be along the river in private group sites but each site will be close to the road.  We will have access to our cars and only need to pack lunch in the canoe each day.  This trip will give you a taste of wilderness camping with out leaving the security and comforts of car camping.  Both rivers are safe (no whitewater), scenic and with many opportunities to see wildlife.  There is a very good chance that we will see at least 1 pair of nesting eagles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7/24 Thursday night - &lt;br /&gt;Meet up in at the Wedeln Ski House in North Conway, I will arrive by 9pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7/25 Friday  - &lt;br /&gt;7AM   depart North Conway. the Magalloway River is 2+ hours north. &lt;br /&gt;7:30 AM - Buffet Breakfast at AMC Pickham Notch Center&lt;br /&gt;11 AM - Set up camp (will be accessible by road)&lt;br /&gt;Noon - Start 10 Mile trip on Magalloway River, we will paddle downstream to our campsite&lt;br /&gt;5pm - Take out at Campsite&lt;br /&gt;7pm dinner (community dinner cooked by tom - hotdogs, beans, more)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7/26 Saturday&lt;br /&gt;8AM - Breakfest, break camp, Shuttle cars.&lt;br /&gt;9am  - Start 8 mile paddle.  We will finsh the final section of the Mgalloway, paddle briefly on Lake Umbagog, then paddle out along the Androscoggin River.&lt;br /&gt;4pm - set up camp&lt;br /&gt;7pm - Pot Luck Dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7/27 Sunday&lt;br /&gt;This is a flexible day - I am sure that many will want to start the long drive back to Boston.  We will likely schedule a short paddle or hike in the area for anyone who can stay longer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST&lt;br /&gt;Wedeln House $20 per night, per guest - free if you camp in yard&lt;br /&gt;$20 (total) for 2 nights camping&lt;br /&gt;$25 - approx  cost for canoe rental per day.  This will likely be split by 2 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extras  - expect a few more dollars for fire wood, possible shuttle fee, nothing major.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING&lt;br /&gt;Tent (let me know if you do not have, I have extra)&lt;br /&gt;Sleeping bag&lt;br /&gt;Bug spray&lt;br /&gt;Sun Screen&lt;br /&gt;Clothes for canoeing (not cotton), rain and cool evenings&lt;br /&gt;shoes or sandals you can get wet - &lt;br /&gt;Camp/folding chair&lt;br /&gt;Canoe -or Tom can arrange rental&lt;br /&gt;toilet paper&lt;br /&gt;Food - only 1 community meal - You will need to bring enough for 2 breakfest, 2 lunches and 1 dinner + snacks and beverages.&lt;br /&gt;pots pans - if you plan to cook on Sat night or for breakfast&lt;br /&gt;binoculars - if you have already, we have a great chance to see some baby eagles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TOM WILL BRING&lt;br /&gt;Camp stove with propane&lt;br /&gt;River maps&lt;br /&gt;First Aid kit&lt;br /&gt;Trash bags&lt;br /&gt;Firewood&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAR POOL&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you can drive or if you would like to ride with someone.  this is a long drive so if we can combine and share gas $ it would be helpful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRIP MAP&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://www.beoutside.com/magmap.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beoutside....&lt;/a&gt;  for a map of our trip&lt;br /&gt;Our first night camping will be close to the spot labeled &amp;quot;trip 2 &amp;amp; 3 put-in&amp;quot; .  &lt;br /&gt;2nd night camp site will be just before the spot labeled &amp;quot;Errol Dam&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;The homepage off this site will give you a good idea of what to expect on the river.  Our trip will be a bit different from the defined trips on this website.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Best way is to be at the club by 10pm Thursday night.  Trip will begin Friday mo</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217124177000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This is a first official Wedeln camping trip</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208986843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wedeln Canoe Camping weekend</name><id>7798628</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216951200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7798628/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/0/global_3292112.jpeg</photo_url></item>