<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Brookline St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363716</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>TT the Bears</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>577760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101654</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/thefruitbats" target="_blank"&gt;Fruit Bats&lt;/a&gt; @ 11pm, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/iranband" target="_blank"&gt;Iran&lt;/a&gt; @ 10pm, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/kkwkbarker" target="_blank"&gt;Kevin Barker&lt;/a&gt; @ 9pm&lt;br /&gt;tickets - $10 adv/$12 day of show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can be purchased in advance at TT's, in person with cash, during the following box office hours:  Sunday &amp;amp; Monday 7pm-11pm, Tuesday-Saturday 6pm-midnight.  Tickets for most shows are also available via &lt;a href="http://www.ticketweb.com/snl/EventListings.action?orgId=15325" target="_blank"&gt;TicketWeb&lt;/a&gt; or charge by phone at 1-866-468-7619.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fruit Bats&lt;/b&gt; (from Wikipedia):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fruit Bats is an American folk rock band originally from Chicago, but now based in Seattle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fruit Bats were formed in 1999 by guitarist, pianist and singer Eric Johnson, the band's main songwriter and only constant member. Originally part of short-lived Chicago group I Rowboat, Johnson and two of his fellow Rowboat members, guitarist Dan Strack and drummer Brian Belval, created Fruit Bats as a side-project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I Rowboat split up, Fruit Bats became Johnson's main focus. Spurred on by Califone/Perishable Records honchos Tim Rutili and Ben Massarella, the group recorded their first album, Echolocation, released in 2001.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After tours with Gorky's Zygotic Mynci, Modest Mouse and The Shins, Fruit Bats signed with Sub Pop in late summer 2002, recording their second album, 2003s Mouthfuls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group released their third album, Spelled in Bones, in 2005. Their fourth album The Ruminant Band was released on August 4, 2009.[1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric Johnson has now joined The Shins, though according to their web site, he plans to continue working with the Fruit Bats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an interview with Reverb Magazine's Nick Milligan (Australia), Eric Johnson has said of The Ruminant Band:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I shouldn’t say I had any strong ideas about how I wanted [The Ruminant Band] to differ from our other records, but I knew that I definitely wanted it to. Previously, when I did those other albums, I think I set rules for myself. This time I didn’t try to go by the book so much. I also let the other [band members] play, rather than me being in charge. I played very little on this record – I wrote the songs and the vocal arrangements, and played some piano, but for the most part everything else is the band. That trust is something that comes with time. I had four years to sit and think about it. It can get lonely when you’re doing the – quote unquote – solo thing. My band is really talented, so I wanted their voices to be heard.” - Eric Johnson, Reverb Magazine Interview, August 4, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Iran&lt;/b&gt; (with Kyp Malone of TV on the Radio) (from last.fm):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indie rock buried in fuzz and hiss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iran take ultra catchy pop, and drag it through the detritus of lo-fi noise rock, picking up an ungodly assortment of buzz and blur and scuzz. Imagine a Pavement record on Siltbreeze. Or Sebadoh, if Lou Barlow was a jaded fuck instead of a sappy romantic. Or old Smog covering Skullflower. Or Harry Pussy playing Built To Spill. A beautifully cacophonous mess.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iran play damaged folk music, bombarded on all sides by a wild assortment of squeals and shrieks, static and hiss, and speaker clogging grit. Huge and slowly shifting, dronescapes that evolve into perfect little pop songs and then explode into jagged shards of high end skree. Iran are psychedelic and textural and noisey and totally catchy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Add an unhealthy obsession with Brian Wilson, Roman Polanski, indie rock, and Norwegian black metal, a handful of disasterously deafening live shows, and a charmingly fractured obstinance, and you’ve got Iran. Hardcore hook-filled low fidelity un-pop noise. Pop. Plus fucking wicked tiger cover art.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253236505000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250898060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fruit Bats &amp; Iran @ T.T. the Bear's</name><id>11168812</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253062800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11168812/</event_url></item>