<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come while away the summer hours making art at the August Meetup at &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;our new location in Natick!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Now that it's definite, we can let you know!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As some of you know, the Needham church has become unavailable on the dates of the August and September Meetups.  We had the choice of changing the date, or changing the venue.  Since we've had one Meetup (last month) at the Natick church where Pamela is a member, it seems like changing the venue is the best decision. Please see the separate note on the Message Board for directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christ Lutheran Church in Natick is a very open and friendly space, with possible options for breaking into smaller groups (when we do demonstrations, etc.).  The space may or may not be air conditioned, depending on which rooms are available.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is not fixed, as it is at the other church; we donate what we can, and they are OK with that.  (The suggested donation is about $75-$85.) For us, this means that if we fall below 15 members attending, we don't have to scramble to make up the cost.  We'll still ask $10 from each person who attends;  it gives us a bit of a cushion to help out with the cost of the Meetup site, shared supplies, expenditures for materials, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Martha (aka &amp;quot;emelengy&amp;quot;) and friends will be leading us in learning some cool techniques for crayons -- just in time for the September swap, which involves making cards that somehow make use of crayons. Just bring yourselves--we'll provide everything else. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should be lots of fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Name tag</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282220931000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269456182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August 2010 NE ATC+ Meetup in NATICK!</name><id>12981060</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281801600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/12981060/</event_url></item>