<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Southwest Corridor Park is a 4.7 mile, 52-acre, linear park stretching from the Back Bay to Forest Hills. It links the neighborhoods of South End, Back Bay, Roxbury and Jamaica Plain with a street-level, green open space for parkland and recreation. Approximately a quarter of the parkland is decked over the railroad tracks, providing more space for grass and plantings, and such recreational facilities as 11 tot lot areas, 2 spray pools, 7 basketball courts, 5 tennis courts, 2 street hockey rinks, 2 amphitheatres, and approximately six miles of biking, jogging and walking paths. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail brings us right to the doorstep of Firefly, across from the Back Bay Station.  We will have lunch there and then walk back  to our cars at Forest Hills.  Those who want to take the T back after lunch are welcome to do so as well. Parking is free on Sundays in the lot at the T station. Meet inside the station in front of the donut shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History&lt;br /&gt;In the 1950's and 60's, plans were developed for a 12-lane highway along the railroad right of way between Boston and Rte. 128, and on into Cambridge. The residents of the affected areas, including Jamaica Plain, Roxbury, South End, Back Bay, and Cambridge, began community protests and demonstrations against the destruction of their neighborhoods by the planned highway. After hundreds of heated meetings and protests, Governor Sargent scrapped the plans in 1969, and highway funds were used to develop mass transit, open space and recreational facilities. The new, relocated Orange Line and the adjacent Southwest Corridor Park were opened in May, 1987. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Firefly American Bistro &lt;br /&gt;130 Dartmouth St, Boston, MA - (617)262-4393 &lt;br /&gt;The setting resembles the menu: classic, but with a few twists. Consider grilled pecan-crusted chicken breasts with grilled pineapple salsa, tenderloin with onion rings and mashed potatoes, and a rich risotto made with blue cheese, spinach and caramelized onions on the dinner menu; wraps, melts, sandwiches, salads and pizzas fill the lunch spread. Prices are cheap for these parts. Dinner entrees range from $8.95 (for a burger) to $14.95. Most lunchtime sandwiches are under $6. The costliest item on the weekend brunch menu brunch is three eggs and pan-seared rainbow trout with home fries and toast for $8.95.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have reservations for 15 at 11:45 am.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189553767000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185903630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Southwest Corridor Park</name><id>6104093</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188743400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6104093/</event_url></item>