<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's go to the 50th Anniversary with a fun 50?s themed party. This event will feature costumed role-players from the 1950s, a hula hoop contest and other great games, a vintage car show, live demonstrations, activities in the Children?s Garden, a special 50s theme to the activities offered in the Discovery Center, food, and fun for all ages.Each of the exhibit houses will also display cakes that are themed to historic cake recipes for the period of the house. Admission for this very special event is just $1 (the original admission price when the museum first opened). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About The Museum&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Strawbery Banke is about connecting with the past.  Visitors to Strawbery Banke have the opportunity to experience and imagine how people lived and worked in this typical American neighborhood throughout four centuries of history.   Through its restored houses, its featured exhibits, its historic landscapes and gardens, and its interpretive programs, Strawbery Banke tells the stories of the many generations who settled in the Portsmouth, NH, community from the late l7th to the mid-20th century.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Significantly, this site was rescued from the poorly conceived urban renewal policies of the 1950s  by conscientious, far sighted citizens.   Always maintaining its grass roots origins, there has been no single benefactor underwriting its existence.  Strawbery Banke has relied upon and continues to rely upon the generous support of numerous individuals who believe in the importance of preserving a site that so accurately depicts the history of immigrants transforming themselves into a community of American citizens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Strawbery Banke tells these stories today by  preserving an actual community where visitors can connect with the past; serving as a resource for educators, community; and providing a gathering space for the present day Portsmouth community.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.strawberybanke.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.strawberyb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$1.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Strawbery Banke Museum &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From either I-95N or I-95S, take exit 7 (downtown Portsmouth) &lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp, head south towards the center of Portsmouth: left if coming from the north, right if coming from the south. &lt;br /&gt;Proceed approximately one mile, through one traffic light, to a yellow blinking light. At this blinking light veer to the right onto Russell Street. At the stop sign at the end of Russell Street, take a right. &lt;br /&gt;At the next intersection, make a left turn onto Maplewood Ave. Stay in the left lane and go through 2 sets of lights. At the third set of lights take a left onto State Street. &lt;br /&gt;Get into the right-hand lane on State Street. Go through 2 sets of lights and continue to the stop sign where State Street intersects with Marcy Street. &lt;br /&gt;Take a right onto Marcy Street. (Prescott Park will be on the left hand side). Proceed on Marcy Street, past The Dunaway Restaurant and take the next right, which is Hancock Street. The Strawbery Banke Museum parking lot is on your immediate right. Museum ticketing is in the Tyco Visitors Center, conveniently located adjacent to the parking lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nashua Car Pool Location:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitor Center Parking Lot&lt;br /&gt;Exit 6 Nashua, NH 03060&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please park in the parking lot and be there by 8:30 AM. &lt;br /&gt;Look for Robert.  We will plan to leave no later than 8:45 AM.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the ticket booth at 10 AM.  I will be wearing a meetup badge,</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217865317000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215231126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Event: Strawbery Banke's 50th Anniversary Celebration!</name><id>8279291</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217685600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8279291/</event_url></item>