<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Belgrade Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02131</zip><lat>42.286606</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St Nectarios Greek Orthodox</name><city>Boston</city><id>3196751</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132118</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/9/7/event_51018071.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;This September, celebrate Roslindale&amp;rsquo;s diverse food culture in this once a year community event.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;A Taste of Roslindale will take place on Thursday September 22nd 2011 from 630pm-9pm at St. Nectarios Greek Orthodox Church, located at 39 Belgrade Avenue in the heart of Roslindale Village. Hosted by Roslindale Village Main Street, the event will feature mouthwatering samples from 22 of the area&amp;rsquo;s critically acclaimed restaurants. From haute-cuisine nibbles to authentic ethnic fare, there&amp;rsquo;s a little of everything Roslindale&amp;rsquo;s award-winning culinary scene has to offer.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Best of all, the event supports a fitting cause: all proceeds benefit two longstanding community organizations, the Roslindale Food Pantry and Roslindale Village Main Street. And at $30 a ticket, the Taste offers an affordable, tasty and fun night out for everyone.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;In addition to whetting your appetite, Taste goers will enjoy live music by one of Boston&amp;rsquo;s top performing jazz artists, the Patrice Monahan Quartet. A live and silent auction, raffle and cash bar will also be part of the fun. The event&amp;rsquo;s central location, right in the heart of Roslindale Village, allows an easy stroll to any number of the featured restaurants for guests wishing to continue the festivities.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Roslindale neighborhood boasts one of the largest and most robust farmers&amp;rsquo; markets in the city. New culinary ventures continue to open here, drawn by the diversity and vibrancy of Roslindale&amp;rsquo;s gastronomical scene. (Some newcomers include Redd&amp;rsquo;s in Rozzie, and Seven Star Street Bistro specializing in Chinese &amp;amp; Taiwanese cuisine.)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Proceeds from the Taste will benefit the Roslindale Food Pantry, serving families in need in the Roslindale area, and Roslindale Village Main Street, a volunteer organization, which has received national recognition for its work in revitalizing the business district.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Participating eateries include: Bangkok Caf&amp;eacute;, Bel Lounge, Birch Street Bistro, Blue Star Restaurant, Boston Cheese Cellar, Brickhouse Caf&amp;eacute;, Caf&amp;eacute; Rialto, Corrib Pub &amp;amp; Restaurant, Delfino Restaurant, Dunkin Donuts, Fornax Bread Company, Himalayan Bistro, Jimmies Ice Cream Cafe, Masona Grill, MJ&amp;rsquo;s Sub &amp;amp; Pizza, Pleasant Caf&amp;eacute;, Popeye&amp;rsquo;s Louisiana Chicken, Redd&amp;rsquo;s in Rozzie, Seven Star Street Bistro, Sophia&amp;rsquo;s Grotto, Sugar Baking Company &amp;amp; Restaurant, and West on Centre.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;The Cooperative Bank is the Corporate Sponsor of the event. Tickets are $30 per person / $35 at the door, if available For more information and where / how to purchase tickets, please call Roslindale Village Main Street 617.327.4065 or visit &lt;a href="http://www.roslindale.net/taste/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.roslindale.net/taste/&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Commuter Rail to Roslindale Village; Orange Line to Forest Hills - take any bus via Roslindale</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol O'Connor</member_name><member_id>9130755</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317272298000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314319674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Taste of Roslindale</name><id>30969651</id><headcount>250</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316730600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/30969651/</event_url></item>