<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Vernon</address_2><address_1>226 Talcottville RD</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.835667</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>872-1410</phone><name>Little Marks Big Barbeque</name><city>Vernon Rockville</city><id>548629</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.491615</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>When we at Little Mark's Big BBQ opened our doors in 1990 our goal was to make the best BBQ around. To do this was quite simple yet painstaking. First, we smoke all our ribs and meats daily. We don't boil our ribs like everyone else; that would be cheating, besides real BBQ is smoked. Smoking ribs takes over six hours, but the end result is perfect.&lt;br /&gt;Next, we make all our sauces, dressings and marinades from scratch. Believe it or not, all our sauces start out as ketchup. We then add our secret ingredients to produce the tastiest BBQ sauces to be found. Our pork and brisket are smoked for over twelve hours to make them fork tender. We also take the same pride in our desserts as we do in the entrees. Try some of our cheesecke or our apple bread pudding. &lt;br /&gt; All of our food is available for take out. We also have a full line of catering services to bring the BBQ to you. Next time you have a party, wedding, graduation or a little get together, consider Little Mark's Big BBQ to do the work for you.&lt;br /&gt;We have been in Vernon since 1990, and that did not happen by accident. In today's ever changing restaurant market you have to be the best you can be and that's what we're trying to accomplish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you for your patronage. We hope to keep bringing many more years of mouth waterin' butt kickin' BBQ to you. We hope you enjoy Little Mark's Big BBQ.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will make a reservation under Meet Up</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211238353000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Because we are fun.</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205942165000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LITTLE MARKS BIG BARBEQUE</name><id>7563250</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211065200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7563250/</event_url></item>