<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 North Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chace Center // RISD Museum</name><city>Providence</city><id>846995</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408308</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check out Design the Night: Trends series at the RISD Museum!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the last of the Design the Night series that the museum has been doing over the summer months. This looks to be a good one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be checking out the Artist Lab, Hands-On Art: Sculptural Headpiece, "Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy" movie, then checking out the"Dorothy and Herbert Vogel Collections: Fifty Works for RI"exhibit and watching Brown Bird. All are welcome to join me or participate in whatever you like, and come and go as you please. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is NOT an organized meetup, but an FYI instead, since its a large space and everyone may have different activities they would like to experience. However, please RSVP so we know who is coming and can look for you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Perhaps we can meetup around 9:00 to check out Brown Bird in the plaza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy" trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R9oLCUNybQM&amp;amp;feature=relmfu"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R9oLCUNybQM&amp;amp;feature=relmfu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brown Bird: &lt;a href="http://brownbird.net/"&gt;http://brownbird.net/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The schedule of the evening's events are below:&lt;/p&gt;
DESIGN THE NIGHT: TRENDS 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, August 16, 2012&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;5–10 pm | Museum Galleries + Chace Center Plaza&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate identity and image, from 19th-century “It Girl” Madame Récamier to today’s trendsetters. Watch design demonstrations of historic hair styles and clothing. Meet &lt;em&gt;Herb&amp;amp; Dorothy&lt;/em&gt; in a true film about a modest but visionary art-collecting couple—and see part of their vast collection at the Museum. Live music on the plaza keeps the festivities going past closing time!  MORE happenings + details to come!&lt;/p&gt;
The Artist's Lab 5–7 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Museum Galleries 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join an experimental drop-in artist's lab with interdisciplinary artist &lt;strong&gt;Beth Nixon&lt;/strong&gt;, whose work involves puppets, personas, and unexpected interactions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Designers on Design 5:30–6 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Grand Gallery &lt;strong&gt;Robert Babigian&lt;/strong&gt;, owner of the downtown men’s boutique and private-label brand WHARF Clothing &amp;amp; Wares, critiques a fashionable French family painted in the 19th century. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Hands-On Art: Sculptural Headpiece 6–8 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Museum Galleries Construct a fantastical wig or chapeau using commonplace materials under the guidance of art instructor &lt;strong&gt;Paul Carpentier&lt;/strong&gt;. Each session is inspired by works on view. All materials provided, no experience necessary. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Fashion Advice Booth 6:30–8 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Grand Gallery Fashion-challenged? Stuck in a style rut? &lt;strong&gt;Karen Beebe&lt;/strong&gt;, owner and buyer of the downtown fashion boutique Queen of Hearts and sleek shoe store Modern Love, offers expert opinions on wardrobe quandaries. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ‘&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eiyLAlWR95M"&gt;Herb &amp;amp; Dorothy&lt;/a&gt;’ 6:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Metcalf Auditorium, Chace Center Meet the Vogels, a postal clerk and a librarian of modest means who built—and later donated—one of the world’s finest collections of contemporary art. Screened in conjunction with the Museum’s new exhibition, &lt;em&gt;The Dorothy and Herbert Vogel Collection: Fifty Works for Rhode Island&lt;/em&gt;. (2008/85 min./not rated) Co-sponsored by Cable Car Cinema. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Live Music: BROWN BIRD 8–10 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Chace Center Plaza &lt;span&gt;The duo performs original music influenced by the blues, outlaw country, roots rock, early American folk, and Gypsy and Eastern European music. Influenced from a deep understanding of American folklore, tradition, and musical style,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Brown Bird&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;transports the listener through time with bass and tambourine rhythms and direct, powerful vocal harmonies.&lt;/span&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - I will probably be going to the movie and then wander the galleries wearing the usual blue gradaded scarf. Look for me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345301122000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343941700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - Design the Night:TRENDS at the RISD Museum!</name><id>76072472</id><headcount>25</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345150800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/76072472/</event_url></item>