<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>TEACH-IN--Noam CHOMSKY et al: &amp;quot;STOP the MASSACRE of GAZA!&amp;quot; Wed 1/21, 7PM: at Palestine Cultural Center for Peace&lt;br /&gt;The Emergency Gaza Coalition presents:&lt;br /&gt;STOP THE MASSACRE OF GAZA!&lt;br /&gt;The truth about the war on Gaza, the US government's role, and why we must fight back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;featuring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOAM CHOMSKY&lt;br /&gt;ASSAF KFOURY, Professor, Boston University&lt;br /&gt;AHMED SHAWKI, Editor, International Socialist Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;with discussion period for all to input their ideas, ask questions, debate and discuss the issues!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**WITH ACTIVIST BAZAAR OF PRO-PALESTINE GROUPS AND VENDORS!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before and after the event, come to learn, meet activists, pick up new literature and information and get plugged into the movement!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 6:30PM Bazaar opens, 7PM Teach-in with panelists begins&lt;br /&gt;@ Palestine Cultural Center for Peace&lt;br /&gt;41 Quint Avenue, Allston, MA 02134&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=44074303654" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for more information or to endorse/co-sponsor this event, or to be represented at activist bazaar, please email:&lt;br /&gt;emergencygazacoalition@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;or call: 617-970-2701&lt;br /&gt;____________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you outraged at Israel's genocidal war path through Gaza? You and hundreds of millions around the world! Who wouldn't be at the senseless destruction, loss of innocent life, the targeting of schools and mosques, the use of horrific chemical weapons such as white phosphorus, the targeting of aid convoys, youth, power plants that keep water clean and the little food that's around refrigerated, destruction of communications infrastructure, the razing of not only homes but whole neighborhoods and cities... It's an immeasurable catastrophe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order for our movement to be effective and to grow wide and strong, we must come together to learn and exchange ideas. This conflict raises questions of local, national, and international significance:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* What is Israel doing? What actually happening on the ground?  Why is this war happening, and why now? What are Israel's real goals behind the rhetoric?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* What is the US's relationship with Israel? Why does the US give Israel such massive and unflinching support materially and diplomatically, despite international opposition?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Can we do anything about it? What does the grassroots movement against this war look like here and abroad, where is it going? Does what we do in our own neighborhoods and schools really matter?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's educate ourselves to build this movement and really make a difference!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232755948000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232229519000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TEACH-IN--Noam CHOMSKY et al: "STOP the MASSACRE of GAZA!" Wed 1/21</name><id>9545578</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232582400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9545578/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>