<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>590 Gay Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.221947</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Center at Westwoods www.centeratwestwoods.com</name><city>Westwood</city><id>13135132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.196205</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Share in Barbara Brennan [Hands of Light] introductory workshop. &lt;br /&gt;

Friday night evening lecture followed by a wonderful weekend of healing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We invite you to join our certified workshop leaders and learn about Brennan Healing Science in a Hands of Light (HOL) workshop. Brennan Healing Science is an enlightening system of personal transformation that combines spiritual and psychological processes with powerful, loving hands-on healing techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Establish a deep connection with inner spiritual guidance on the way to fulfilling your heart’s true longings. &lt;br /&gt;

• Transform your relationships through awareness of energy dynamics. &lt;br /&gt;

• Learn healing techniques for yourself and others. &lt;br /&gt;

• Strengthen your hara, the intention and ability to accomplish your life goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Workshops range from one to two days plus an evening lecture, and are suitable for beginners and practicing healers alike. Each is taught by BBSH-certified workshop leaders, some of whom are current faculty. Lectures are open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These teachings on human energy and consciousness, health, healing, and self-awareness are at the cutting edge of human development. Come experience this healing event and return to your life renewed, open-hearted, and transformed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368994684000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Healing Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-healers-network</urlname><id>511093</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Healers Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367270851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hands of Light weekend workshop May 17 - 10</name><id>116836862</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>162000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368831600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-healers-network/events/116836862/</event_url></item>