<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197-203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.743869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 246-5700</phone><name>The Alchemy Juice Bar &amp; Growing Green Co-op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1035078</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689453</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Puja Ceremony: Tantric Ceremony Celebrating the Divine Feminine &amp;nbsp;7-9pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Puja is a prayer. In Tantra, a prayer is a way of honoring and adoring the divine that dwells within each of us. The subtle sensual energies residing within our bodies are invoked, revered, and welcomed as honored guests at this feast of love.&amp;nbsp;This evening&amp;rsquo;s Puja is dedicated to women. Though the presentation starts off with an introduction to some of the esoteric practices of Tantra to give us a context for the Puja, we will soon switch gears and actually engage in this heartening practice. We will use breath, movement and sound to enrich each experience throughout the ceremony. You may find yourself turning inwards and becoming aware of abundant love and innate beauty that is part of your being.&amp;nbsp;Women, Shakti, though not required, you are welcome to dress for the evening &amp;ndash; perhaps adorn yourself with jewelry you feel most happy in or wear a scarf you love that you can&amp;rsquo;t wear to work. It is your evening; indulge yourself as you wish, but please be comfortable.&amp;nbsp;Men, Shiva, though not required, you are welcome to dress for the evening too. We invite you to bring flowers to adorn both the space and the Goddesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ran Baron&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a spiritual seeker and public speaker in the fields of theology, eastern philosophy &amp;amp; mysticism. Having ventured through various spiritual paths himself, Baron was ordained as a Hindu priest (Brahmana), certified as a Yoga and Tai Chi instructor and has been studying and practicing Buddhism, Zen, Hinduism and Yoga in many of its different flavors since the age of 14. He has instructed numerous meditation workshops, yoga retreats and has given hundreds of lectures about the nature of spirituality and self-inquiry. Baron's teachings emphasize a non-dogmatic approach allowing for personal growth through an honest thirst for truth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;www.soulbound.me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Vibe Tribe Snuggle After Party in the Luscious Lounge 9-11pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tribe Love is a full immersion into sacred intimacy, intimate connection and just pure fun! Our day of sensual experiences, meditative journeys &amp;amp; celebration of the divine will open hearts for our evening love nest topped with MamaLicious decadent chocolate! Bring pillows &amp;amp; blankets to share &amp;amp; sarong for sauna.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Join the High Vibe Tribe Meetup for upcoming snuggle time dates!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REGISTRATION &amp;amp; LOVE EXCHANGE:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Full Day Program&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(includes workshop, evening puja &amp;amp; organic lunch) $75 per person; $125 per couple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Join us for the Evening Puja &amp;amp; High Vibe Snuggle Time ONLY $20 per person&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pre-registration required with&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:Imani@mamaliciousmarket.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imani@mamaliciousmarket.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;860.983.5276&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ran Baron</member_name><member_id>7795102</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333301880000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331148323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Puja Ceremony: Tantric Ceremony Celebrating the Divine Feminine</name><id>55389822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333234800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/55389822/</event_url></item>