<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>109 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.855965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stage Two Cinema Pub</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>1625345</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.931557</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Let's go have some dinner while watching the movie&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Adjustment Bureau&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;About Stage Two Cinema and Pub:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you like to go to the movies?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Want to grab some dinner while watching the movie?&amp;nbsp; &lt;span&gt;How about a beer/mixed drink?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Stage Two Cinema has it all right in this one place, so grab a comfy seat, get comfortable and enjoy your self. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The movie starts at 7:00 the earlier you get there the better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Coupons:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Did you buy the Mass Pass Coupon book from one of your organizers? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Paying the bill: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are responsible for paying your share of the bill including tax(s) and tip.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Parking/Finding the building:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There is plenty of parking in their lot.&amp;nbsp; This is set off back  from the road, and may be a little hard to find, please allow enough  time to get there and find a parking spot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; Meetup Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will have this on up until 5 minutes before the movie starts  remember this phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t accept texts please plan accordingly the  Meetup phone # is 978-304-2811.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;About the movie:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rated&amp;nbsp;PG-13 &lt;br /&gt; Running Time:&amp;nbsp;1 hour&amp;nbsp;39 minutes &lt;br /&gt; Starring: Matt Damon,&amp;nbsp;Emily Blunt &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do we control our destiny, or do unseen forces manipulate us?  Matt Damon stars in the thriller The Adjustment Bureau as a man who  glimpses the future Fate has planned for him and realizes he wants  something else. To get it, he must pursue the only woman he's ever loved  across, under and through the streets of modern-day New York. On the  brink of winning a seat in the U.S. Senate, ambitious politician David  Norris (Damon) meets beautiful contemporary ballet dancer Elise Sellas  (Emily Blunt)--a woman like none he's ever known. But just as he  realizes he's falling for her, mysterious men conspire to keep the two  apart. David learns he is up against the agents of Fate itself--the men  of The Adjustment Bureau--who will do everything in their considerable  power to prevent David and Elise from being together. In the face of  overwhelming odds, he must either let her go and accept a predetermined  path...or risk everything to defy Fate and be with her. The Adjustment  Bureau is written for the screen and directed by George Nolfi (writer of  Ocean's Twelve, co-writer of The Bourne Ultimatum). It is based on a  short story by Philip K. Dick ("Total Recall," "Minority Report" and  "Blade Runner"). -- (C) Universal Pictures &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; The Adjustment  Bureau is a romantic thriller, but the romance isn't heartstring-pulling  and the thrills aren't whiz-bang. Instead, George Nolfi's film usually  manages a rather remarkable feat: sending us on a headlong pursuit of  life's meaning, even as the banal everydayness of real life closes in on  one side and the anything-goes magic of science fiction closes in on  the other.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304343615000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303955731000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner/Movie</name><id>17461918</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304117100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/17461918/</event_url></item>