<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1329 Middle Turnpike W</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.782111</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 528-0856</phone><name>Wickham Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>738536</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to find us: &lt;/span&gt;Look for signs.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;SCHEDULE FOR THE DAY -- 12:00 - 5:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;12:00 PM - The Conduit Center gongs for peace&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;1:00 PM - Laughter Yoga with Laura Le &amp;amp; Mark Sherry&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;2:00 PM - Afternoon Yoga with Loren&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;3:00 PM - Qi Gong with Erik Harris &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4:00 PM - Closing with Gonging&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : 11px"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;**************************&lt;/span&gt;******** &lt;br /&gt;One World Vibe - Gong for Peace Day &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join us on May 1st as we unite the sound healers of the world in a day to Gong for Peace!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Gong masters and sound healers from around the world will be joining together in harmony for a 24 hour period to sound together for peace.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We invite those who wish to soak in some good vibes to stop by or bring an instrument of meditation and sound with us in harmony. On this day we also celebrate International Workers Day, World Laughter Day and Global Love Day.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Live, Laugh, Love! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.oneworldvibe.com/" target="_blank" style="color : #3b5998"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.OneWorldVibe.co&lt;/span&gt;m/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PARKING at Wickham is $5.00 per car &lt;br /&gt;You can also park for free in front of The Conduit Center and hike up. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is a FREE Event bring your friends &amp;amp; some food to have a picnic! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For Directions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/wickhamparkct" target="_blank" style="color : #3b5998"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://tinyurl.com/wickham&lt;/span&gt;parkct&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Why May 1st? - Live, Laugh, Love! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Live! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;May 1st is officially International Labor Day, in celebration of the working classes victory of establishing the 8 hour day. Eight hours work, Eight hours recreation, Eight hours of rest! Every human being has the right to a fair and balanced work day. Overworked and underpaid employees creates a lot of stress, and a lot of stress means a greater propensity for dis-ease. The best medicine is prevention, and it starts with a balanced body and mind.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Laugh! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;May 1st is officially World Laughter Day&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;World Laughter Day was created in 1998 by Dr. Madan Kataria, founder of the worldwide Laughter Yoga movement. The celebration of World Laughter Day is a positive manifestation for world peace and is intended to build up a global consciousness of brotherhood and friendship through laughter. Its popularity has grown exponentially with that of the Laughter Yoga movement now counting over 6000 Laughter Clubs in more than 65 countries. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;"When you Laugh, you change. When you change, the whole world changes" - Dr. Madan Kataria &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://worldlaughterday.org/" target="_blank" style="color : #3b5998"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://worldlaughterday.or&lt;/span&gt;g/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Love! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;May 1st is Global Love Day &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It is our vision to unite one and all in a celebration of love and compassion. We honor each May 1st as a symbolic day of unconditional love and call upon all people and all nations to gather together in the wisdom of peace and love. &lt;br /&gt;Learn more at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.oneworldvibe.com/" target="_blank" style="color : #3b5998"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.OneWorldVibe.co&lt;/span&gt;m/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;RELIEF FOR JAPAN &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Help us bring peace and relief of suffering to those affected by the tsunami in Japan. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Donations for the American Red Cross will be accepted in support of disaster relief efforts to help those affected by the earthquake in Japan and tsunami throughout the Pacific&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;[b] World Laughter Day Celebration in Manchester, Ct at Wickham Park May 1, 2010&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Come together to Laugh, Picnic, and Help Contribute to Spreading World Peace and Understanding![/b]&amp;nbsp; . This year this world-wide event will be held on May 1, 2010. The event is designed to promote healthy living and create community bonding to foster peace and understanding. Admission is free and open to all. The only requirement is an openness to laughter&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warning: You might laugh so much you&amp;rsquo;ll feel happy for DAYS afterwards![/b] World Laughter Day was created in 1998 by Dr. Madan Kataria, founder of the worldwide Laughter Yoga movement. In each subsequent year, more and more events have been held across the United States and around the world. This coincides with the phenomenal explosion of interest in laughter therapy and the amazing powers of laughter. The celebration of World Laughter Day is a positive manifestation for world peace and is intended to build up a global consciousness of brotherhood and friendship through laughter. Its popularity has grown exponentially with that of the Laughter Yoga movement now counting over 6000 Laughter Clubs in more than 65 countries. Why World Laughter Day? Steve Wilson, founder of the World Laughter Tour, says "The world is so out of balance that it needs to lighten up and laugh more in order to maintain perspective. We set aside this day to send a message to get more people laughing, urging the world to lighten up! Systematic exposure to true mirthful laughter in a supportive environment, can contribute to world peace by fostering attitudinal healing. Regardless of the reason you laugh, the primary purposes of laughter have to do with reducing the terrible effects of stress, and connecting with other people; laughter plays a huge role in maintaining relationships. Actually, we need laughter more now than ever!&amp;rdquo; Laughter causes the body to release endorphins, which are the body&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Feel Good&amp;rsquo; hormones, into the bloodstream which can tend to generate feelings of happiness, warmth, love, bonding, tolerance, forgiveness, generosity, and compassion. The presence of these endorphins counters the production of stress hormones that can correspond with hatred, fear, violence, jealousy, aggression and the emotions associated with war and oppression. &amp;ldquo;When you laugh, you change and when you change the whole world changes around you.&amp;rdquo; Dr. Madan Kataria Celebrating World Laughter Day World Laughter Day is customarily celebrated on the first Sunday of May every year. This year on the 1st of May, the world will once again come together to laugh and spread the word of happiness and joy. The Laughter Clubs movement is a global initiative to unite entire mankind through unconditional love and laughter. It is a non-religious, non-racial and non profit organization committed to generate good health, joy and world peace through laughter. This revolutionary idea has positively changed the lives of hundreds and thousands of people around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COME AND JOIN US!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Laughter-Club/events/17339585/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Laughter-Club/events/17339585/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.oneworldvibe.com/"&gt;http://www.oneworldvibe.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Sherry</member_name><member_id>5650811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304270866000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>“This event wll be a wonderful opportunity to celebrate World Laughter Day, try different healing practices, meet new people, and celebrate other May 1st holidays.</why><group><who>Partners in Laughter</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup</urlname><id>1384386</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Laughter is the Best Medicine and Fun Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303272145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One World Vibe Day - World Laughter Day Sunday  May 1: Celebrate With  Laughter!</name><id>17368869</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup/events/17368869/</event_url></item>