<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Protest March at Christian Science Plaza Oct 2.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA; September 21, 2005&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A group of former Christian Scientists and friends from across the U.S. will be holding a protest march on October 2nd from 9AM to noon at the Christian Science Plaza in Boston.  Organizers abhor the ongoing medical neglect of children of Christian Scientists and other sects with the inevitable suffering and death that follow.  Marchers will carry pictures of victims and signs telling their stories.  Others will carry messages such as “Christian Science: Jonestown in slow motion,” “God gave us medicine, doctors, and nurses for a purpose,” and “not very CHRISTIAN  &amp;amp; not a SCIENCE.”&lt;br /&gt;CJ Hyatt from California will be on the picket line.  CJ was adopted by a Christian Science family and became deaf at age 7 after a series of untreated ear infections.  A sign-language interpreter will assist her from 10-noon for interviews.  Also attending will be Ellen Johnson of New Jersey, President of American Atheists whose group is opposed to religious exemption laws that allow children to suffer and die needlessly, and Dr. Seth Asser, Rhode Island physician and co-author of “Child Fatalities from Religion Motivated Medical Neglect” (Pediatrics, 101(4):1998 pp. 625-9).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1128431040000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lowellatheists</urlname><id>13032</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Atheists of Greater Lowell</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1127867990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>christian scientist protest</name><id>4772731</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1128258000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lowellatheists/events/4772731/</event_url></item>