<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A &lt;b&gt;2-day&lt;/b&gt; hike on the Appalachian Trail (AT) starting at the Long Hill Rd. parking area near East Fishkill, NY (at Shenandoah Mtn. in the eastern limit of Clarence Fahnestock Memorial State Park) and heading southbound to Hudson Highlands State Park, NY and on into the base of Bear Mountain State Park, NY for a total of about 22.3 miles. This is the next segment of the AT southbound for the group. We'll spend the night at a tenting area near the trail (you need a tent or must arrange to share with someone). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We'll meet first at the Dennytown Road Group Campsite dirt parking lot (see location link below) at 10 AM.&lt;/span&gt; We will consolidate all overnight camping gear into one vehicle which will be left there. You can hike with your overnight gear if you like but others who wish to lighten the load can do so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rest of the vehicles will then relocate to the small dirt parking area on top of the hill on Long Hill Rd., E. Fishkill, NY (see location link below) by 11 AM at the latest. The hike for the day will be about 8.3 miles through Fahnestock Sate Park, southbound on the AT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should reach the endpoint for the day by no later than 5:45 PM. We will stay at the Dennytown Road Group Campsite for the night (free for throughhikers as long as we call ahead) off of Dennytown Rd. Water and latrine are available. Janice will lead for this first part of the hike as Kevin has a meeting he must be at but will join everyone for the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next morning we will start by by placing a shuttle at Beartown State Park. Then we'll start hiking at 8 AM with Kevin leading and go about 14 miles through the Hudson Highlands State Park, with a commanding view from Anthony's Nose, down over the Hudson River on the Bear Mtn. Bridge, to the endpoint at the base of Bear Mtn. State Park along the Hudson River by about 7 PM at the latest. We'll shuttle back first to the Dennytown parking lot. Some hikers will opt for the third day of hiking (below) and will offload here. We will transfer gear for those leaving to the shuttle and we'll drive to the cars at the start on Long Hill Rd. We should be at Long Hill Rd. by 8:15 PM or so at the latest. In reality, we'll be there earlier as the hike will likely go faster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Kevin missed the first part of this hike, he and a few others will camp overnight again at the Dennytown Road Group Campsite and hike again on Monday the first portion in reverse to the Long Hill Rd. parking area near East Fishkill, NY. We'd start hiking by 8 AM and should finish up by about 3 PM. Others on the hike are welcome to redo this extra bit of hiking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we should come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES (for 2-days)==&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: It will likely be cold at night so plan accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;* Full pack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of cloathing -Avoid cotton as it stays wet (this includes underwear). Plus second day's clothing.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket or rain poncho-Just in case&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag -3 season or summer&lt;br /&gt;* Bedcloths&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Headlamp or flashlight -LED version best -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent -Or share&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* 3 quarts water -No defined safe water source except campsite&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (6:00 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* Insect repellant -essential! Ticks are out as well as biting flies&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag and 15' min. light weight rope -Hang food at night&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Toiletries &amp;amp; Toiletpaper -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Water filter -To restock water, strongly suggested&lt;br /&gt;* Camera and extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit -For blisters and such&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping pad&lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches -For cooking, campfire, emergency fire (warm up, signal)&lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -If needed&lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils -If needed&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel -If cooking&lt;br /&gt;* Game(s) to play in camp -cards, Jenga, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Only need to pay attention to #1, #2, and #7. Organizers use the rest)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#1 &lt;u&gt;everyone&lt;/u&gt; Sat. morning) Approximate location/directions to the meetup location at the parking area near the Dennytown Road Group Campsite &lt;/b&gt; (Dennytown Rd., in Fahnestock State Park)(use to plug in your starting point)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Putnam+Valley&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=483+Dennytown+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=10579&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.420472&amp;amp;longitude=-73.868988&amp;amp;geocode=LATLNG" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat=41.420472, Long=-73.868988] &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: About 1.2 miles south of Rt. 301 on Dennytown Rd.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#2 most &lt;u&gt;everyone&lt;/u&gt; Sat. morning) Directions from Dennytown parking lot to Long Hill Rd. (20 min.):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/mq/6-1erCCrp_" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#3 for shuttle/transport Sun. morning, prep for end of hike) Directions from Dennytown parking lot to Bear Mtn. Park (30 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/mq/10-9O6lVPJv" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#4 for shuttle/transport Sun. morning, get back to start hike) Directions from Bear Mtn. Park  to Dennytown parking lot (29 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/mq/9-ktLct1crhnQXX7hx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#5 for shuttle/transport Sun., right after hike is done to get equip.) Directions from Bear Mtn. Park  to Dennytown parking lot (30 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use #4 directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#6 shuttle Sun. night, back to cars for those leaving) Directions from Dennytown parking lot to Long Hill Rd. (20 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use #2 directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#7 For &lt;u&gt;those going home&lt;/u&gt; or to pick up vehicles to move) Approximate location/directions from AT starting point parking&lt;/b&gt;, Long Hill Rd., East Fishkill, NY (use to plug in your destination): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=East+Fishkill&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=100+Long+Hill+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#8 for shuttle and other vehicles Sun. night, back to camp for 2nd night) Directions from Long Hill Rd. to Dennytown parking lot (18 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/mq/3-b82BWkW7ChElsDKD216N" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#9 transport Mon. afternoon, at end of 3rd day hiking get gear) Directions from Long Hill Rd. to Dennytown parking lot (18 min.):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use #8 directions &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(#10 everyone who stayed over) Dennytown parking lot to home:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use #1 directions (use to plug in your destination)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: Approximate location/directions to the 2nd day endpoint at Bear Mountain State Park parking area (on Seven Lakes Dr., next to the old Bear Mountain Inn): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Bear+Mountain&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=49+Service+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=10911-2001&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.31332&amp;amp;longitude=-73.989079&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS#undefined" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;MAPS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Clarence Fahnestock Memorial State Park trail map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/attachments/ClarenceFahnestockTrailMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hudson Highlands State Park trail map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/attachments/HudsonHighlandsSouthTrailMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bear Mountain State Park&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/attachments/BearMountainTrailMap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;INFORMATION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Clarence Fahnestock Memorial State Park&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/133/details.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Hudson Highlands State Park&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/9/details.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Bear Mountain State Park&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nysparks.state.ny.us/parks/13/details.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nysparks.s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276740679000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272607899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from Fahnestock State Park, NY to Bear Mtn. State Park, NY</name><id>13338097</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275141600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13338097/</event_url></item>