<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>5322022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/c/event_185283852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Join us to see Ashok's stunning photos and to hear more about this remote region of India. Ladakh, in the Himalayan state of Jammu and Kashmir, is located close to Tibet and is an incredibly beautiful high-altitude desert, with snow capped high peaks, broad valleys, narrow gorges, roaring rivers, and impossibly blue lakes. This slideshow will present pictures from a three-week trip that the AMC members Ashok and Meera Boghani undertook this summer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;They, along with some family members, traveled across the entire region of Ladakh, starting from Manali and ending up in Srinagar. The highlights of the trip included camping on the shores of several high altitude lakes (14,000 feet and above), travelling along heart-stopping roads going as high as 18,300 feet, and visiting monasteries situated in spectacular locations. One key part of the trip was a six-day trek that took the group up to 16,500 feet, the base camp of a Himalayan peak called Stok Kangri.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Ashok and Meera enjoy traveling to remote regions, hiking, and bicycling. They have trekked in the Himalayas four times over the past 25 years and, in addition, hiked in Patagonia, Alps, Canadian Rockies, and of course, our own White Mountains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Doors open @ 6:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Potluck @ 6:30 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Slideshow @ 7:15 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Join our Google Group and get all the latest updates and cancellation notices for all the shows: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potluck Info:&lt;/strong&gt; Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome :) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (with a stovetop, oven, microwave, sink &amp;amp; fridge). Please bring your own cooking pots if needed for stovetop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subway Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the MBTA to Park Street Station. Walk through the Boston Common uphill towards the State House on Beacon Street. To the left of the State House is Joy Street; follow Joy Street uphill to the AMC Auditorium Building (brownstone), #4 Joy Street on the left hand side. Map: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt; Nearby parking is available at the Boston Common Garage, located underneath the Boston Common. Access is off Charles Street, between the Public Garden and the Boston Common. We offer $6 parking tickets at the slideshows (a savings of $5). More info about the Garage is here: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4471089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363462840000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354673786000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Himalayan Hiking Adventure in Ladakh, India (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>94107602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363300200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/94107602/</event_url></item>