<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This has been out for a while, but I haven't been able to see it yet.  I realize that a summer Saturday night is often too crowded for movie-going, at least if the weather is good, but I thought I'd take a chance.  I will cancel if nobody else is interested; Saturday is the only day I can see it.  Feel free to go a different day if you can, it's showing Wednesday-Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WINTER'S BONE (R) (2010)&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Debra Granik. Screenplay by Debra Granik and Anne Rosellini, based on the novel by Daniel Woodrell. Cast: Jennifer Lawrence, John Hawkes, Dale Dickey. &lt;br /&gt;The winner of this year's the Sundance Festival's Grand Jury Prize for Drama is the second movie by exciting indie filmmaker Debra Granik. Made on a bare-bones budget - and all the freedom that can buy - Winter's Bone is a near-mythical epic of a 17-year old girl (the amazing Jennifer Lawrence) who dreams of escaping the grueling poverty - and her meth-dealing relatives - in the Ozarks. First, however, she sets off on a dangerous journey to find her missing father, who has put their home up as bond. The haunting soundtrack features local Ozark musicians and composer Dickon Hinchliffe, formerly of Tindersticks). &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Winter's Bone is what we've been waiting for: a work of art that grabs hold and won't let go.&amp;quot; - David Denby, The New Yorker. &lt;br /&gt;100 min. &lt;a href="http://www.wintersbonemovie.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wintersbon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283263068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282616972000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"WINTER'S BONE" at Cinestudio</name><id>14520280</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283037300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/14520280/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/5/global_14961861.jpeg</photo_url></item>