<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.13relay.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.13relay.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is waaaaay in the future, but I just received an email about this relay race, and I was wondering if anyone would be interested in putting together a team. I have never done &amp;quot;Reach the Beach&amp;quot; or anything comparable, so this would be new for me, but it sounds like a lot of fun. Please check out the link and let me know if you might be interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a brief description of how it works:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How the 13 Relay overnight relay works.&lt;br /&gt;The CAPE Relay: May 1st and 2nd 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each relay team consists of a maximum of 12 teammates. Each teammate will run three inconsecutive legs varying in length and difficulty. Each leg of the 13Relay range from 2.9 miles to 8.1 miles; this equates to each teammate running an average of 14.58 miles. This means the elite runner down to the weekend warrior can come out and be a part of the fun.You can also put together an &amp;quot;ultra&amp;quot; team. This consists of 6 runners, which on average will run 29.16 miles each throughout the course. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vehicle 1 (V1) will start off the relay with runner #1. V1 can drive ahead of the runner cheer them on and give them any food or water they have brought along for the ride. After that runner makes it to the first exchange area, they will hand off the &amp;quot;baton&amp;quot; to the second runner in V1. This pattern repeats itself until you make it six legs of the course to exchange #6, where Vehicle #2 (V2) picks up for the next 6 legs of the relay. This is now your time to get something good to eat or get some sleep... You'll eventually wish you had it. This exchange between runners and the two team vehicles repeats 6 times until all 36 legs are completed. Have fun!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>heidi</member_name><member_id>8485896</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272888435000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253544233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 2010 Cape Relay</name><id>11426210</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272715200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/11426210/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/4/global_2413972.jpeg</photo_url></item>