<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are hiking up the 3,165-ft. Mt. Monadnock to the bare rock (or snow/ice covered) summit. We'll be hiking with the &amp;quot;Northern Central MA, southern NH Walking/ Hiking Group&amp;quot; from Meetup, based out of Leominster, MA (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; ). The other meetup will have about 25 members going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exact trails to be taken and distance are selected by the leader for the trip, Ina, from the other meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****UPDATED TRAIL ROUTE 4/9/10****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;The hike starts at the Old Toll Road parking lot. It is located 2.9 miles beyond the entrance to the Headquarter's parking lot on Route 124, on the same side of the road. There are no facilities there and the $4 fee does not take effect until April 17th. We will hike through the woods on the Old Halfway House Trail to the White Arrow Trail to the summit. We will descend via the Dublin-Marlboro Trail to the Marlboro Trail, then turn onto the Marian Trail/ Mossy Brook Trail/ Cart Path, back onto the Old Halfway House Trail (or optional Old Toll Road, if really tired). The trail up is very rocky and has a lot of ledge with views. The Marlboro Trail is also bald rock with beautiful views. The Marian Trail/Mossy Brook Trail is more wooded and partially follows a beautiful, mossy-banked, clear water, babbling stream. We encountered no snow or ice on the trails, but parts were wet and/or muddy. Wet rock is very slippery. Sturdy, good traction shoes/boots are required. Poles are recommended. This is a loop hike, therefore, no car spotting and shuffling will be necessary. We will end where we started. Time will be an estimated 5 and 1/2 hours. Be prepared for changes of temperature and strong winds on the summit. Dress in layers and have a wind jacket.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;southern parking area at the Old Toll Road gate&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pets are not permitted in the park or on the mountain. Please note that this law includes all trails and areas on Mount Monadnock. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Hurry and RSVP as we must close RSVPs soon!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hikers, please bring micro-spikes or crampons and no cotton is acceptable for this hike. Hiking poles are advised. I also strongly suggest either gators or snow pants for this hike. We will encounter ice and snow. Please dress in layers and bring plenty of water and some foods containing protein and carbohydrates. The wind at the summit is also very strong so the temperatures are much less at the summit, up to 15 degrees coler than at the base. We will hike at a moderate pace with small breaks when folks need them. Once we are on the mountain, no facilities are available. As most places we go do, Mt Monadnock has a bring it in take it out policy. Restrooms available near the visitor's center before the hike. Please bring cash for admission fee. I think it's $4. Rain cancels this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has been said that Mt. Monadnock is the second most hiked mountain in the world after Mt. Fuji in Japan. Whatever the case may be, if you look around the summit on a summer day, you'll see scores of kids and adults enjoying the fine views from this very popular peak. The top half of the mountain is characterized by big slabs and boulders of rock that are fun to climb over. There are many trails of varying levels of difficulty so there is something here for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Monadnock is the centerpiece of the 5,000 acre Monadnock State Park. There are 40 miles of hiking trails, a visitor center, a campground with 21 tent sites and 7 youth group sites, a camp store, bathrooms, and shower facilities. The park is open year-round although services are limited from November through April. Pets are not allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The word &amp;quot;monadnock&amp;quot; originally comes from the Abnacki Indian language meaning &amp;quot;mountain that stands alone.&amp;quot; Because Monadnock &amp;quot;stands alone&amp;quot;, views from the treeless summit stretch far into the distance into surrounding states like Vermont and Massachusetts. Boston and the White Mountains are visible on a clear day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Monadnock forms one end of the roughly 50-mile Monadnock-Sunapee Greenway Trail. It is also the terminus of the 117-mile Monadnock-Metacomet Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park rangers at the park's entrance and displays in the Monadnock Visitor Center onPoole Rd. provide excellent information about the mountain. There is usually a small $4 entrance fee for people ages 6-64, but not until April 17th this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Directions to NEW approximate meetup location at parking lot at Old Toll Road gate (650 Mountain Rd./Rt. 124, Jaffrey, NH)&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Jaffrey&amp;amp;state=NH&amp;amp;address=650+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=03452-6031&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.83469&amp;amp;longitude=-72.113844&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Monadnock State Park:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Rt. 124 &lt;br /&gt;Jaffrey, NH 03452 &lt;br /&gt;(603) 532-8862&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhparks.state.nh.us/state-parks/alphabetical-order/monadnock-state-park/"&gt;http://www.nhparks.st...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://nhstateparks.org/uploads/MonadnockHikingTrailsWeb.pdf"&gt;http://nhstateparks.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hiking safty and equipment for high peaks:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272116800000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269973718000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike up Mt. Monadnock in Jaffrey NH</name><id>13038913</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270994400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13038913/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>