<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2370 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.344635</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hess Gas - Intersection  Mass Pike,  Rt 128, and Commonwealth Ave</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>880225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.257942</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WE CANCELLED THE MAC N CHEESE AND PLACED THIS SHORTER SCOOT SO WE CAN GET BACK PRIOR TO THE POTENTIAL RAINOne of the great rides in Massachusetts !  Riding up Mt Wachusetts and viewing the breathtaking Landscape.  Rising above the surrounding forest to a height of 2006 feet, Mount Wachusett stands as a unique landmark within the central New England landscape. From the summit, a clear day reveals views of Mt. Monadnock in New Hampshire, the Berkshires to the west, and the Boston skyline to the east. The 3,000-acre Wachusett Mountain State Reservation surrounds the summit and offers a wealth of natural and recreational resources. The Reservation's natural resources include forests, alpine meadows, ponds, streams, fields, and even a perched bog. Recreational opportunities abound at the reservation including hiking, nature study, hawk watching, picnicking, and skiing. The Reservation offers 17 miles of hiking and walking trails, including 3.9 miles of the Midstate Trail, which runs from Ashburnham to the Rhode Island border. Mountain Road stretches to the John Hitchcock Visitor's Center at the summit, a short distance from the Wachusett Mountain Ski Area, which is the largest in eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will cruise up Mt Wachusetts then afterwards head over to the famous 1761 Old Mill...&lt;br /&gt;The OLD MILL, from its earliest beginning, has served a useful purpose in the community. Originally a saw mill where logs were processed for the new homes of the neighborhood, the Old Mill and its whirling saw sang a song of progress and industry through five generations of ownership in the same family (the Foster Family), before its wheels were stilled and it fell into disrepair.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wearing scooter gear hanging around scooters :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Alden</member_name><member_id>5206555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240233424000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240038782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Wachusett Summit Run  Great Views and Lunch </name><id>10211450</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240059600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/10211450/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/2/global_7033762.jpeg</photo_url></item>