<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Inman Square)</address_2><address_1>1418 Cambridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373833</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-960-7766</phone><name>First United Presbyterian Church</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1304901</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101746</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Have you considered what sorts of stuff you permit to share your living space ... what seems to &amp;quot;stick&amp;quot; in your home ... and why?  What do you suppose its purpose is - its value to you?  Might it have some lesson that, once learned, could neutralize your attraction for such stuff?  &lt;i&gt;What could be powerful enough&lt;/i&gt; to create such a &amp;quot;sea change&amp;quot; in your life?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup is devoted to such considerations - and will invite and celebrate participants' &amp;quot;guerrilla tactics&amp;quot; to declutter and especially our successes in such ventures during these sultry, waning days of summer, during which we can excavate our living spaces to find &lt;i&gt;Treasures&lt;/i&gt;:  clues indicating what &lt;i&gt;we personally&lt;/i&gt; consider (or did at some point) to have particular value and meaning ... and why; and how we might learn &lt;i&gt;enough&lt;/i&gt; from these &amp;quot;object lessons&amp;quot; to feel free to release them to help others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From what I understand (&lt;i&gt;plz advise&lt;/i&gt; if you can shed light on this question; thanks!), physics today suggests that the basis of everything is Information -- and that matter (including our stuff...) is essentially concentrated* energy, even &amp;quot;frozen light.&amp;quot;  (I can attest that underlying my own clutter challenge is Information - piles of it - and within each page or scrap of paper is at least one action item representing some concentration of my own potential Energy + Time + Space = Life.)  ...Does such &amp;quot;frozen light&amp;quot; constitute the light of our world?  Might focusing attention on it more consciously lend energy to our frozen landscape, shaking things up enough to release excess stuff into places where it might prove more useful and appreciated?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christian Scriptures assert that &amp;quot;if the Son sets you free, you will be free indeed&amp;quot; (John 8:36) and &amp;quot;you will know the truth, and the truth will make you free&amp;quot; (John 8:32).  Such promises can include freedom from the bondage of Stuff.  Indeed, I was gratified to learn that at least one of our last meeting's participants experienced a welcomed breakthrough recently:  prayers were answered when someone materialized to help her more consciously consider her accumulation of stuff.  At this next meeting, I welcome tenets and personal thoughts analogous to the above verses that might be offered by other religions, agnosticism, and atheism.  My own path toward living more simply has been enriched by diversity and many connecting threads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...For example:  this week while reading a memoir of Marine dogs in WWII, &lt;i&gt;Always Faithful&lt;/i&gt;,  I was struck by veterinarian-author Captain William W. Putney's observations (pp. 41-42) of the markedly different results achieved by official vs. unofficial trainings:  the former, based on fear, created such stress in mine-detection dogs that the dogs could work for only short stretches of time before making mistakes and finally refusing to work at all. (Some dogs never could be trained that way - yet could not be &amp;quot;detrained&amp;quot; to overcome fears that such training instilled.)  Dogs that Capt. Putney's men trained unofficially without introducing fear, however, &amp;quot;did not experience any stress because they were taught to do &lt;i&gt;something that seemed both natural and fun.&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot;  Putney further observed that dogs he had seen more recently working at airports and border crossings, probably trained in more the &amp;quot;unofficial&amp;quot; ways his men had employed, &amp;quot;wag their tails and search &lt;i&gt;as if they were playing a game to be relished.&lt;/i&gt;  ...The look on their faces, as they sit in front of you and peer into your eyes, says 'Gotcha.'  Are they motivated by fear?  I think not.  They are &lt;i&gt;playing a game that they always win.&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot;  [Emphases added.]  --How can &lt;i&gt;we&lt;/i&gt; transform seemingly immobilizing challenges presented by clutter into &lt;i&gt;FUN games that we always win?&lt;/i&gt;  Ideas welcomed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As preparation for this next meeting, you are invited to &lt;i&gt;excavate your home to uncover meaningful Treasures&lt;/i&gt; - in whatever space you choose - expecting to enjoy at our gathering ample opportunity to share with others what you find and learn in the process.  I myself am especially interested in &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;breakthroughs&lt;/b&gt; and &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Clutter Victories&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;: instances in which unused stuff that had been stealing space and sapping attention and energy is released to better serve and inspire more appreciation elsewhere - by another person we know (or don't), or animal(s) (e.g., I've taken soft, unwearable clothing to the Animal Rescue League to serve as bedding in cages), and/or the planet (e.g., food scraps for composting are accepted from residents by my town's Recycling Center).  I'd also love to hear how participants transform decluttering into &lt;b&gt;FUN&lt;/b&gt; - GAMES of sorts ... e.g., for awhile, I set a book about vampires on a stool I was using to sort documents for shredding - using the thought of vampires to remind myself of the preciousness and urgency of time - motivating me to finish decluttering as much as possible each day &lt;i&gt;by sunset.&lt;/i&gt;  ...Another time, during a visit with my parents, the movie &lt;i&gt;Saving Private Ryan&lt;/i&gt; that my mother and I watched together one evening motivated me to attack next morning with unexpected vigor a roomful of clutter in their attic that I feared might cause them to fall - considering in an appreciative new light my wealth of time and freedom that American soldiers have defended so ably, and how relatively feeble an enemy clutter actually is:  &lt;i&gt;piles of stuff can't counterattack!&lt;/i&gt;  So &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt; do we permit stuff to assume such a sizable presence in our space, time, consciousness -- lives?  What sort of power has it held over us?  How can we become EMpowered enough to banish excess stuff from our lives ... to better focus on &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt;, in its place?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are welcome to bring a small box or satchel of your own stuff to quietly process during the meeting, if you wish - using our time together not only to become more inspired to declutter, but also to utilize the energy generated at our meeting to &lt;i&gt;take action&lt;/i&gt; to progress toward your own personal goals involving a simplified living space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So...to Arms, Mates!!! We have four short weeks to achieve Clutter Victories that we all can celebrate on August 30th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*I don't quite understand matter's being described as &amp;quot;concentrated energy,&amp;quot; because E = mc2 ... so, that would mean that  m = E/c2 ... which seems to me to be a dramatic &lt;i&gt;diminution&lt;/i&gt; of energy...??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 7:30 pm - Socializing (feel free to bring goodies if you want some!). I might bring a digital camera to post a photo of the meeting on our Meetup web site IF participants grant permission (please notify me of any privacy concerns).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 ~ 8:30 pm - Discussion including Pastor Roger Lier of First United Presbyterian Church, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~8:30 - 9:00 pm - As time permits:  Group problem-solving, buddying up for accountability, consideration of this Meetup's SUCCESSION, future meeting topics (e.g., Health and Wealth aspects of decluttering) and schedule, venue (e.g., The Democracy Center near Harvard Square?), presenters, organization (including assistant organizers), activities, resources ... how best to help YOU?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On-street metered parking is available near the church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public transportation: Bus lines #69 (from Harvard Square ... or ~15-minute walk from there) and #83 (from Central Square ... or ~15-minute walk from there) pass through Inman Square, Cambridge, where FUPC (our venue) is located.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup signs will be posted at the property.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283366799000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280712460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebration + Guerrilla Tactics for Treasure Hunting in these Dog Days of Summer</name><id>14285672</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283209200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/14285672/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/c/1/global_15907729.jpeg</photo_url></item>