<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/6/c/event_74648812.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 10am &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Registration:&lt;/strong&gt; 8:30am-9:30am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Goodnough Dike, Quabbin Reservoir (East Entrance off Rt 9 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Short route:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy 1.8 miles, paved park road &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Long route (a.k.a. "Detour")&lt;/strong&gt;: 5 miles (more if we want, see description!) &lt;em&gt;Entire hike is on paved park road, except walk through Hank's Meadow itself, if that's where we decide to picnic!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://foundation.baystatehealth.org/netcommunity/Mass-NH-Walking-Hiking-Group"&gt;http://foundation.baystatehealth.org/netcommunity/Mass-NH-Walking-Hiking-Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/9/4/event_96154452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Why not make someone's life better while having fun with a great group of people? The "Walk of Champions" benefits Bay State Mary Lane Hospital's Integrated Cancer Services. This program helps pay for medicines, other treatments, counseling, and related services for cancer patients and their families. Fundraiser will be held at Quabbin Reservoir, rain or shine (except in severe weather, such as a lightning storm).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walk details:&lt;/strong&gt; The official walk is a 1.8-mile loop, starting behind Goodnough Dike. As we walk across the dike and enjoy Quabbin Reservoir's spectacular views, we'll get free ice cream from Jeanine's Frostee, plus other goodies. Did I mention the spectacular views?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not enough "hike"?&lt;/strong&gt; Join us for a beautiful trip through Quabbin Park! Since cash is not collected at the event (you must mail physical donations ahead), there is no end-of-walk check-in. &lt;em&gt;(Those doing the 1.8 can complete the loop, those going further will take off from the end of the dam.)&lt;/em&gt; The group will choose the distance together. However far we go, there are several popular viewing areas, and we can picnic at whichever destination we choose. Along the way, enjoy beautiful woodlands...remember to look, the deer are not that shy and often not far from the road! If we're lucky, we'll see hawks, bald eagles, deer, or other wild creatures!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Bring your camera...Quabbin is a rare treat! Also bring water and snacks/lunch if you'll be walking through the park with us (beyond the 1.8 miles). We can picnic at one of several locations. As for the 1.8-miles loop, if that's all you do, there is free ice cream, courtesy of Jeannine's Frosty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join our team! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Team members get free T-shirts with our team name, courtesy of many sponsors&lt;em&gt;. (This deadline is past as of 4/6.) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;If you collect donations in person, do not bring money to the walk. There are an address and deadline to mail physical donations, and they are printed on the phyiscal registration form, which you can download as a PDF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Pre-register online (if you wish) so that friends, family, and acquaintances can also donate via your own personal webpage! To join us online, please click the link below, or search for team "Mass-NH Walking/Hiking Group" at time of registration. Please choose a goal, as your page will show progress toward your (online) goal, and our group page will show the total of our goals and the total of our progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://foundation.baystatehealth.org/netcommunity/Mass-NH-Walking-Hiking-Group"&gt;http://foundation.baystatehealth.org/netcommunity/Mass-NH-Walking-Hiking-Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General facts about Baystate Mary Lane Hospital:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ranked in top 10% nationally for patient satisfaction in overall quality for 1) medical/surgical care and 2) outpatient surgical services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ranked in top 14% nationally (and one of 6 in Mass.) for surgical and pneumonia care.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the nation's top performers on Quality Key Measures in 2011 by the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Healthcare Organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serves Hampden, Hapshire, and Worcester Counties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Source: "Ahmed" named Mary Lane chief operating officer," Spencer New Leader&lt;/em&gt;, 3/16/12&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Quabbin Map calls the park road "Administration Road" but Google maps calls it "Old Ware-Enfield Rd."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from East (Worcester):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 9 West (about 45 minutes from the Worcester/Leicester line). You will pass through Spencer, the Brookfields and Ware. After downtown Ware, the road goes up and down two long, steep hills. At the bottom of the 2nd hill, look for a pull-off with wood gate on the right. After a curve in the road, the East Entrance is on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from West (Springfield):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 9 East through Amherst and Belchertown. Pass the West and Middle Entrances on your left. Finally, take the East Entrance on your left. (It takes about 5 minutes to pass all 3 entrances.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from South of Route 9:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take the nearest route North to Route 9, then follow directions for East or West, above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from North-Central Mass:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Take Route 2 West to Route 202 South. Alternately, take 31 or 140 South to Route 122 North, then turn left on 202 South. Go all the way to Route 9 (20 minutes?) then turn left to go East. Follow directions from West, above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING: IMPORTANT!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once inside the East Entrance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;In less than 1 mile, you'll see a brown sign with "Goodnough Dike" on the right. &lt;strong&gt;Unless you will only do the "official" 1.8-mile hike, please use the small dirt lot before the loop road&lt;/strong&gt; (says "Goodnough Dike") &lt;strong&gt;and walk down.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Although they are suspending their rule and letting cars down behind the dike, your car may be towed if it's there late, if you do the long hike with us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the short woman with dark, curly hair wearing a Meetup badge. Registration is 8:30-9:30 AM below Goodnough Dike.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336515413000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322006974000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk of Champions! (for Bay State Mary Lane Hospital Integrated Cancer Services)</name><id>42112542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336312800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/42112542/</event_url></item>