<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Update:  So we are going to meetup on Northeastern University's campus at 359 Huntington Avenue, The Marino Center.  It's a glass facade builing with a Boloco and Au Bon Pain in it, so you  shoudlnt be able to miss it.  There's a big open area just inside so we'll meet and take it from there, do some improv and grab some dinner and/or dessert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are going to be late or get lost, just call the phone number listed and let me know so you can find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the late notice.  I didn't get too many emails about this and I have had a busier week than usual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey everyone!! I hope Halloween and the warm start to winter is treating everyone well.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm all about setting up for our usual improv on Thursday this week unfortunately however The Democracy Center is booked for their monthly cleaning on Thursday and has been booked for the rest of the November for a few weeks now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So for alternate plans, I'm hoping to find another locale for improv this week.  Any suggestions???  Any ideas??? Let me know.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone has alternate ideas as in something beside improv, feel free to pass that along as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you are all doing great.  I hope we get to relax and get into characer asap!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we'll be there inside at some of the tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227228500000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226339764000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Improv Northeastern!</name><id>9132692</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226622600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/9132692/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>