<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday  February 8th at  REVOLUTION ROCK BAR &amp;amp; LOUNGE !! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Financial District 6:15-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The  Afterwork mixer returns this Thursday February  8th. This time we are taking the party to the new  Revolution Rock Bar &amp;amp; Lounge, one of the premier venues to hit the Boston nightlife scene in recent months. This  multi-level venue offers a bar, lounge, restaurant and multiple entertainment options.  I 've heard great reviews about this venue, so what better way to come out and  have a few cocktails  with the group as we gear up for another festive  weekend in the city!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet at the front bar first floor , please look for me upon entering, my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section.  I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with winter time in Boston this place will fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green Line to  Govt Center &lt;br /&gt;Red Line to South Station &lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to State St/Downtown Crossing &lt;br /&gt;Blue Line to State St/Govt Center/&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1171149842000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1170392725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revolution Revolution!!!   Afterwork Mixer this Thursday!!</name><id>5445983</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170976500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/5445983/</event_url></item>