<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Maple Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01702</zip><lat>42.296818</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St Andrews Episcopal Church</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1035894</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431651</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Gateway Kick Off Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gateway Kick Off Meeting 2010 - 2011&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday September 7th 7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Boston Globe Award Winning Photographer Essdras Suarez&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“We as journalists are duty bound to tell stories with our words and pictures in the hope that others will not forget and to remind the rest of us how lucky we really are”. - Essdras Suarez&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Essdras, a Pulitzer Prize winning photojournalist has been a Boston Globe photographer since 2002. As a Globe photographer, he says his job title includes “strict instructions to find a feature per shift so I'm always on the lookout for something out of the ordinary. This is what I called &amp;quot;listening to the light&amp;quot; where the light makes itself noticeable by its quality and then you start paying more close attention to what is going on. I try to always &amp;quot;listen&amp;quot; to the light around me.”&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nationally Essdras Suarez has covered stories such as the Columbine shooting and space shuttle Columbia disaster. Internationally he has photographed in Sudan, Egypt, Laos, Cambodia, Colombia, Cuba, Venezuela, Brazil, Russia, Panama, Haiti, Guatemala, El Salvador, Mexico, Costa Rica, Honduras, Dominican Republic, Indonesia, Spain, France, Israel, Iraq, Kuwait, and China.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283906995000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282686331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gateway Kick Off Meeting -- talk by Essdras Suarez</name><id>14529203</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283902200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/14529203/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/global_14013533.jpeg</photo_url></item>