<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fleet Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076180</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trolly Stop</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>13157822</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.758781</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Portsmouth, New Hampshire…The kitchens we all dream of – sleek and contemporary, cozy and traditional, packed with innovation and imagination – will become a reality for one day as The Music Hall presents its popular annual Kitchen Tour. Now in its 22nd year, this benefit for The Music Hall will feature kitchens and dining spaces in the neighborhoods surrounding Portsmouth, New Hampshire’s North and South Mill Ponds. The 2013 Kitchen Tour will be held Saturday, May 4th from 10am to 3pm. &lt;br /&gt;

 “This year we will once again offer tour-goers a trolley that will continually loop the route of the Tour, transporting patrons between several parking lots to drop off points along the way,” says Dominique Jackson, Special Events Manager at The Music Hall. “Trolleys were offered for the first time on last year’s tour and were a big hit, so we’re happy to provide them once again this time!” Each year, the tour attracts over 1,200 visitors who come to support The Music Hall and to gain inspiration for their own kitchens. Proceeds from the tour are used toward operating costs to support The Music Hall, an American Treasure for the Arts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Music Hall Kitchen Tour is the perfect opportunity to enjoy breathtaking kitchen designs and see Portsmouth beyond its famous downtown. “The Kitchen Tour is a great way to be inspired, and this year’s tour will provide inspiration like no other” says Peter Squires, a member of the committee planning the tour. “With a focus on historic and green homes this year, guests will get a glimpse at the best that the past and future of kitchen and home design have to offer!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An easy-to-follow map will be provided, and tour-goers can start and finish the tour from any parking lot designated on the Map. The trolley will pick guests up and drop them off at several spots along the Tour that are within walking distance of each featured home. Tickets are on sale now and can be purchased before the day of the tour at the Music Hall Box Office or online at TheMusicHall.org. Maps will be sent to all guests before the Tour who bought tickets ahead of time. Tour-goers can also use their maps to identify great area restaurants where they can grab a bite for lunch on tour day! &lt;br /&gt;

 For visitors looking to turn their own dreams into reality, the craftsmen, artisans, designers and architects involved in the kitchens are noted in the tour’s guidebook along with detailed descriptions of the kitchens. Many of the fine craftsmen will also be available to speak with during the tour. &lt;br /&gt;

 “The Kitchen Tour is a perfect way to enjoy a spring Saturday in the Seacoast, and help to support The Music Hall, says Dominique Jackson." We can't wait to welcome our guests this year!" &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

About the Kitchen Tour &lt;br /&gt;

1,200 visitors attend The Music Hall’s Kitchen Tour each year to get a peek inside the contemporary or traditional homes of a historic seacoast town, and to gain ideas for their own kitchens. Proceeds from the popular tour - now in its 22nd year - are used toward operating costs to support The Music Hall. The tour highlights the work of local companies including architects, builders, carpenters, as well as lighting, landscape and sound designers. In addition, local retail shops and restaurants support the tour through ticket sales and special promotions. &lt;br /&gt;

 Tickets &lt;br /&gt;

Kitchen Tour tickets are $23 for Music Hall members, $25 for non-members, and $27 if purchased the day of the event. Tickets are on sale now and can be purchased by phone at 603.436.2400, or online at www.themusichall.org &lt;br /&gt;

 About The Music Hall: An American Treasure for the Arts &lt;br /&gt;

The Music Hall is a nonprofit performing arts center that entertains 100,000 patrons, including 20,000 school children, annually with acclaimed film, music, theater, and dance performances. Its historic 900-seat theater, built in 1878, is the oldest in New Hampshire and designated an “American Treasure” by the U.S. Senate in the Save America’s Treasures Program administered by the National Trust for Historic Preservation and the National Park Service. Living out its mission to be an active and vital arts center for the enrichment of the Seacoast community, The Music Hall presents diverse and relevant programming, including its signature series and innovative community outreach programs, and hosts numerous community fundraisers and celebrations for the benefit of more than 40 local nonprofits. A cultural anchor in a thriving Seacoast economy, The Music Hall and its patrons contribute $7 million annually to the local economy through show and visitor related spending. The Music Hall is a 501c3 tax exempt, fiscally responsible nonprofit organization, managed by a professional staff with the assistance of a dedicated volunteer Board of Trustees. The historic hall is located in Portsmouth, the seaport city recently named a “Distinctive Destination” by National Trust for Historic Preservation and one of the “20 Best Towns in America” by Outside magazine. For more information about The Music Hall and its schedule of events, visit www.themusichall.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367687367000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364388067000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Music Hall Presents 22nd Annual Kitchen Tour</name><id>111289822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367676000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/111289822/</event_url></item>