<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>On the rotary</address_2><address_1>1 Lowell street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01741</zip><lat>42.529308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978.369.0200</phone><name>Fern's Country Store</name><city>Carlisle</city><id>884146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348982</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Back by popular demand! Fern's is an ideal launch point for a Sat ride - I hear the lunch isn't bad either! Don't forget to try the almond croissant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mary Ellen says.. &amp;quot;Another fun place for warm weather with a nice outdoor patio (complete with little waterfall) (there is no indoor seating) is Fern's in Carlisle.  They don't serve cooked breakfasts, but they have great coffee and muffins etc.  They have a deli with really good sandwiches etc.also.  It is a favorite with the bicycle crowd.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From their web site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Right here sitting on the rotary in Carlisle, Massachusetts proudly stands Ferns Country Store, an establishment that has continued the tradition of there being a country store on this very site since the 1844 when life was simpler, the air fresher, people had time to ponder and friends had time to stop and chat awhile.  At Ferns Country Store, although people come and go, many linger for a spell by the pickle barrel to catch up on the local gossip and goings on around town. Friends buy friends coffee - maybe a yogurt muffin if they like each other real well. You won't find many grumpy people at Ferns because they're not allowed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People are nice and smile a lot, except when they're on their way to work in the morning then they just smile - maybe nod their head in a friendly, country greeting sort of way. Someone called Ferns &amp;quot;The House of Smells&amp;quot; because it's always filled with aromas of fresh-baked cookies, raspberry sticks or home style chili.  At Ferns fabulous delicatessen you can buy yourself a pretty nice sandwich or a wrap or one of our famous ½ lb subs - or a 1 lb sub if you're real hungry. We have lots of nice gift-type things that you could buy for your favorite aunt. But if you run out of something while you're in the middle of baking then you can always count on our &amp;quot;oh-my-god-I-forgot-isle&amp;quot; - it's chock full of the essentials.  Ferns Country Store is especially nice when we put out all of the American flags across the front porch on special occasions - every small town needs lots of American flags. Everyone always wants to know how we named Ferns &amp;quot;Ferns&amp;quot; we tell them to read about the story of Old Lady Fern on our not-too-fancy web site.   Well, that's about it, except that you need to stop by and visit and join in on the conversation 'round the pickle barrel. We're real easy to find, just look for Carlisle, Massachusetts on a map. All roads meet in the center of town at the rotary. And that's where you'll find Ferns Country Store - where things are simpler and we try and live up to our motto:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Work Hahd. Play Hahda.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Scooters</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246284908000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243114043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Take Your Scooter To Breakfast Series  -  Breakfast at Fern's</name><id>10478898</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246111200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/10478898/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/4/global_7397396.jpeg</photo_url></item>