<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>0.019999999553</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Plone CMS Demo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ 90 minutes including Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Nate Aune, Owner and Lead developer of Jazkarta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I. What is Plone?&lt;br /&gt;II. Plone History and Support Community&lt;br /&gt;III. Plone's technical features and functions&lt;br /&gt;IV. Plone's strengths and weaknesses&lt;br /&gt;V. Some popular community sites using Plone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plone is a very popular CMS with a very large support network.  It has hundreds of extensions available and an active full-time product development support group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plone is one of the oldest and best organized open source communities, which is reflected in the high quality of the Plone product.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Plone Support Community is also unique in terms of its strength and technical depth, much of which is facilitated by Plone and the underlying Zope Framework itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nate will cover the following topics on Plone as time permits, using a system the standard installation with a some cool customizations:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) a brief overview of Plone from a user's point of view, giving definitions and examples of content, sections, and categories; and how they relate to each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) the main concepts and distinctions of Plone objects, modules, and components, pointing out some of the most common modules and how they are used.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) the administrator's interface, its standard menus and other interface elements, and what they control.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) how Plone &amp;quot;products&amp;quot; or modules work, including &amp;quot;themes&amp;quot; (templates), modules, and components.  How to install components and switch themes to get different appearances, behaviors, and functionality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) resources for learning, for themes, for other addins, please mention them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6) Cool sites that feature Plone and some of Jazkarta's  neat work with this very powerful CMS product.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting will in the conference room on the basement level of 111 Cummington Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>RichKin</member_name><member_id>3557763</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187477196000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People interested in CMS</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newengland-webcms</urlname><id>422397</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Web Content Management Systems Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185321733000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Web Content Management Systems August Meetup</name><id>6071933</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187218800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newengland-webcms/events/6071933/</event_url></item>