<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Lets get out for some outdoor recreation and relaxation at Crows Hill in Leominster State Forest.  There is a little of everything: fresh water beach, picnic tables, charcoal BBQ grills, walking/hiking/mountain biking trails and even some rock climbing!  This is a joint meetup with the Rock Climbing Boston group. &lt;a href="http://Boston Rock Climbing: Crow Hill, top roping and Picnic" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;a href="http://rockclimbing.meetup.com/77/calendar/8269484"&gt;http://rockclimbing.m...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  Geoff has invited beginners to try it out some top roping &lt;a href="http://Top Roping Explained" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Top_roping" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/a&gt;No special gear needed.  They will have stuff on hand.  You might have to wait a little in line because of limited gear and limited climbing routes, but this is a perfect chance to give it a try!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm not setting up any formal food arrangement.  Feel free to coordinate among yourselves in the &amp;quot;Talk about this Meetup&amp;quot; section below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stuff to bring: Food, frisbee, swim suit, sun lotion, bug spray?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Crows Hill in Leominster State Forest .&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/Leominster.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;LSF Map (PDF)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take route 2 to rt 31 south (exit 28) go south 1.3 miles to park head quarters. There are two parking lots. Go to the first parking lot on the left and pay $5 dollars for the picnic area parking.  Parking is accessed from Main Entrance Rd on the map.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;11 - 2 pm: The Climbing portion of the outing at Crows Hill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11 am - 12: Meet &amp;amp; Greet.  I'll be in the picnic area next to the main parking lot between 11 and 12 to meet &amp;amp; greet folks, then I'll be headed over to Crow's hill across the street to try my hand at some top roping.  Shouldn't be too hard to spot me. &lt;a href="http://Tim (Organizer of this event)" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/members/3305855/"&gt;http://singles.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;   Don't worry if you show up a late you can just chill out in the beach/picnic area or come on across the street and watch some climbers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12 am 2 pm: People who don't want to climb can hang out in the picnic/beach area until 2 when everyone gets together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 pm - ??? : Picnicking and enjoying the day.  People can break off for hikes, biking or just hang out at the picnic area and go for a swim.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://Leominster State Forest" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/lmsf.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Shouldn't be too hard to spot me.  See my posted pic.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>3305855</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216739473000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215711397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Leominster State Forest Recreation &amp; Relaxation</name><id>8314995</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216566000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8314995/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>