<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 Mt Carmel Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06518</zip><lat>41.421894</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-582-8200</phone><name>Quinnipiac University</name><city>Hamden</city><id>222633</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.893524</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>UPDATE: &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/boards/view/viewthread?thread=2659585#7241261"&gt;Potential nudity&lt;/a&gt; at this Event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This may be her most elaborate performance this year, NHCer &amp;amp; full-time professional pianist &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/alexiszingalepianist"&gt;Alexis&lt;/a&gt; has been invited to be the featured soloist at a &lt;a href="http://members.aol.com/HSOrch/#NEXT"&gt;Hamden Symphony Orchestra concert&lt;/a&gt;!  Followed by post-party likely at some location in Hamden near Quinnipiac/Sleeping Giant (possibly Aunt Chilada's since it's close)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come watch her play 30 minutes of classical music FROM MEMORY (that's 10's of thousands of notes folks!)!  Whole concert is one hour-ish, with intermission.  She plays in 1st half, 2nd half is a pops concert.  Suggested donation $5.  Jeans/casual is ok.  More details &lt;a href="http://members.aol.com/HSOrch/#NEXT"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://home.comcast.net/~jasond22/junk/naked_pianist2.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexis chose to play Beethoven's long, difficult, and well-known &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Piano_Concerto_No._5_(Beethoven)"&gt;&amp;quot;Emperor&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;, known as a showcase for virtuoso pianists.  She will play 1 movement, there will be a momentary pause, then diving immediately into the final 2 movements back-to-back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOST: Jason, cell 203-901-4957.  To help you find me...I'll be the one with a tiny camcorder on a tripod.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The HSO is a volunteer orchestra of more than 50 members affiliated with Quinnipiac University (though membership is open to all qualified musicians)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program includes:&lt;br /&gt;Beethoven - Piano Concerto No. 5 in E Flat Major, Op. 71 &amp;quot;Emperor&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Wolf-Ferrari - Overture to the Secret of Suzanne&lt;br /&gt;Brahms - Academic Festival Overture&lt;br /&gt;Enesco - Roumanian Rhapsody No. 1 in A&lt;br /&gt;Anderson - Balladette, The Captains and The Kings, Promenade&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;General directions to Quinnipiac are &lt;a href="http://www.quinnipiac.edu/x28.xml"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  Once at Quinnipiac, the concert is being held at &lt;a href="http://www.quinnipiac.edu/x35.xml"&gt;Alumni Hall&lt;/a&gt;.  To find parking, you will want to enter through the university's &lt;a href="http://www.quinnipiac.edu/x34.xml"&gt;main entrance&lt;/a&gt;.  Guards might not let you enter via any other gate if you're coming to see the orchestra.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To reach the main entrance, after you've turned off Whitney Ave. onto Mt. Carmel Ave, go approx. 0.4 mi. to the entrance labelled &amp;quot;Main Entrance&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The guard can direct you where to park and walk.  Ideally you'll park off to your right, then walk down the main brick walk towards the back of the campus (you'll eventually pass through an arch for the schools of communications and business).  Once you come to a large field (with a tower on the far left), walk down the right side of the field in the direction of the flagpole, you'll come right up to Alumni Hall, and if you look through the large windows on the right you should see the performance hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to arrange car-pools, chat about the event, etc, click &lt;a href="http://newintown.meetup.com/531/boards/view/viewthread?thread=2659585#6918244"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to visit the thread on the message board &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177475014000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1170104393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sun 3/4-THE BIG ONE: Alexis is featured soloist with full orchestra accompanying</name><id>5435419</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173038400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5435419/</event_url></item>