<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>guest lodging fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per night</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone, Wedeln has come back and re-energized from our trip out west to Banff Canada.  Come up to the house and get the scoop from eveyone!  46 people went on this trip out.  The next trip out is already in the planning stages.  Pictures will be floating around up at the ski house this weekend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many members looking to sell some &lt;b&gt;extra discount tickets to either Wildcat, Bretton Woods or Sunday River.&lt;/b&gt;  So chances are, if you come up Friday, I can find tickets for you and a friend! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In terms of this weekend, people are coming up to get some more skiing/riding in.  Not quite spring skiing yet!  Still cold up there and snow piled up next to the road and on the ground!  I was a bit shocked last weekend on how much snow there was at wildcat.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an FYI, need your RSVP ASAP.  Repeat ASAP - email me your real name and phone number so I can call you.  &lt;b&gt;E-mail me at pottebaum.tara@gmail.com by 5pm WED. &lt;/b&gt; So I can get your info in and we can coordinate the weekends social calendar.  (i.e. let me know if your in for the sat night group dinner at $15 bucks a head).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tara&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>4521773</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207677711000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>there is still a lot of snow up there!  Many people have discount tickets to sell!</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206500174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skiing or Riding this weekend?</name><id>7603539</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206831600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7603539/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/e/global_2109326.jpeg</photo_url></item>