<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sunday thru Thursday nights &lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY NIGHTS: PIZZA &amp;amp; BEER - single topping pizza and 2 pints of beer - only $11.95! Game Time 7:00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?I think probably everybody was surprised, with so many teams to choose from it was kind of ironic. I guess Rutgers is the number eight seed in the country and I find that hard to believe but I guess they are. If I was them I would be questioning what is going on. Like I said before if it was a real tournament it would be one versus eight, two versus seven, three versus six but not that it is going to play out that way. There is no guarantee that one plays two at the end but if you project that far, you hope that is the case. I don't know what Rugters? RPI was at the end of the season but I have to believe that it was better than eight.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it was one versus two and they put Tennessee on the other side of the bracket, what is your reaction to this possible match up? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?As I said there are no guarantees for anything so it doesn't matter where they put anybody. When you are a number one, you are a number one. It doesn't really matter what number you are, it is more what your bracket looks like. In the NCAA Tournament you like to play teams that you have not seen before. Certainly like the people said on the telecast, having to play a team that you have played, like the top two teams in the league have to play again then I guess Rutgers was penalized for getting knocked out early in the BIG EAST Tournament. I really was not paying attention to any other brackets, I really didn't look at them well enough.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is your initial reaction of looking at your bracket? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think you are always looking for possible mismatches that don't make too much sense. In generally speaking, when you look at a bracket you like to see a lot of teams that you don't know much about and they don't know you. So I was kind of disappointed about how I feel out but it does not change how I feel about what we are going to try to do. I think it is pretty neat for this group of players and what they have gone through.? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.uconnhuski.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.uconnhuski...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one yelling and screaming.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207692194000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Because we are great Uconn fans.</why><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205940554000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NCAA CHAMPIONSHIP Final 4</name><id>7563101</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207519200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/7563101/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/4/global_3286548.jpeg</photo_url></item>