<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;MUA HA HA HA HAAAA&lt;/i&gt;.... Boston Frisbee is celebrating Halloween with a frighteningly fun-filled festival of frisbee fellowship on Foston Fommon!  Er, that is, Boston Common.  So don't miss out, come one, come all!  Following thusly are the details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Different Start Time: 12 noon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We want to take full advantage of the &amp;quot;warmth&amp;quot; of daylight while it lasts.  So we'll assemble at noon (there will be snacks!), throw around for a while, get ourselves some teams, and play until we're tired.  If enough people want to stick around, after our post-game social, we may even break out the Flashflights and play some night disc!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Costumes, baby&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It wouldn't be Halloween Frisbee without running around in silly-ass costumes.  Anyone who saw Joe as Borat last year knows to come prepared for anything.  And as an extra incentive for you to get dolled up, we will be awarding a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;PRIZE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for the best costumes on the field, to the tune of a $10 gift card to Pizzeria Uno, our time-honored Harvard Square hangout.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crazy Points&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout the games, your friendly neighborhood Organizers will be instituting another time-honored ultimate tradition: calling out rules for Crazy Points at various intervals, to mix things up in a silly fashion.  T-Rex Point, Opposite Hand Point, Walking Backwards Point, Amazing Layout Point.... anything goes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's about it.... Remember: Costumes, prizes, food, fun, starting at noon.  We hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Love (potion #9), &lt;br /&gt;-Jim, Kelli &amp;amp; Joe&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be tossing discs on or near the softball fields.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim O'Neill</member_name><member_id>4585507</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Baz</member_name><member_id>4845259</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelli</member_name><member_id>4908325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225848716000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223560365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Freaky Frisbee Halloween Extravaganza</name><id>8929648</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225645200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/8929648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/f/d/global_6094861.jpeg</photo_url></item>