<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Media Marketing for Face-to-Face Professionals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;with Linda Marks, MSM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our work is rooted in the sacredness of a safe, healing, face-to-face relationship.&amp;nbsp; Many of the approaches we use include touch.&amp;nbsp; How does one integrate the person-to-person nature of healing work with a world that is increasingly relying of virtual tools for communication, outreach and visibility?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explore this question with your colleagues, with some insights shared through Linda's research and efforts to wrestle with this question after 26 years in practice.&amp;nbsp; How do we decide to use Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn?&amp;nbsp; What about e-mail marketing?&amp;nbsp; What is best done on-line and what is best done in more "old-fashioned ways?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, we can support each other in finding the balance of face-to-face and virtual realities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Linda Marks, MSM&lt;/em&gt;, has practiced EKP, a heart-centered approach to body psychotherapy for 26 years, working with individuals, couples, families and groups.&amp;nbsp; She also provides coaching and meditation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You will be welcomed at the door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318610646000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>We live in a world that is becoming increasingly virtual, and where the top sources people use to find resources are on-line.  How do we balance the sacredness of our healing work with the necessity of using internet-based tools?</why><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301438105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Media Marketing For Face-to-Face Professionals:  October Meetup</name><id>17107196</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318606200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/17107196/</event_url></item>