<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone! &lt;br /&gt;Friday is our Concious Movie Night for February! We are going to be watching &amp;quot;Way of the Peaceful Warrior&amp;quot;, a powerful movie about a young man who wanted more and was led to meet a real Teacher. (See the review I copied from Amazon below.) We'll be watching it on our big screen and have time to talk about it afterward. If you haven't seen this movie (or even if you have, and you know how great it is!), come and see it with us. It will be a warm and inspiring evening (just ask the folks who always come...) If you are a member of our group and haven't made it to a meetup yet, Come! We want to meet you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings to all,&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;(from a review on Amazon.com)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on allegedly actual events chronicled in Dan Millman's book `Way of the Peaceful Warrior' the film `Peaceful Warrior' released in `05 takes the audience on a shamanic spiritual journey in the most unlikely of places, a twentieth century urban center, more precisely, Berkley, California. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis: Dan Millman is a top gymnast at U. C. Berkley yet despite his many successes he feels empty and incomplete inside. Plagued by dreams of failure Dan is unable to sleep and finds himself wandering the streets in the early hours of the morning. When he stops at an all night gas station and service mart he meets a man of unconventional wisdom who begins to instruct him on the process of clearing his mind of all the useless garbage it contains in order to view himself and the world around him in a brand new way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;`Peaceful Warrior' is one of those rare films that both entertains and teaches without sacrificing one for the other. The production values are high, the dialogue believable and the performances strong. Scott Mechlowicz was definitely the right choice to play the role of Berkley gymnast Dan Millman and Nick Nolte delivers one of his best performances in years as the mysterious Socrates, garage attendant and &amp;quot;New Age&amp;quot; Zen Master. Add to the mix Amy Smart as Dan's love interest Joy and you have a little romance as well. I did find the film to be slightly uneven here and there, the best moments taking place whenever Nick Nolte (Socrates) is on screen. However the message is so well presented and the actors so amiable any minor gliches are forgivable.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347430000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203711060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie Night: The Way of the Peaceful Warrior</name><id>7387760</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204329600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/7387760/</event_url></item>