<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt. 16</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.256958</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Pinkham Notch Visitors Center</name><city>Gorham</city><id>315923</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.252860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://timefortuckerman.com/gifs/tu9805x.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction To Tuckerman Ravine...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So where is Tuckerman?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuckerman is located on the east face of Mount Washington, the highest peak in the White Mountains of New Hampshire. Tuckerman is accessible from Pinkham Notch which is located on Route 16. Wildcat Mountain, a well known ski resort is located facing Mount Washington on the other side of Route 16.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's all the fuss about?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuckerman is pretty unique. It's a bit elusive considering skiers have to hike up the mountain for a few hours with all their equipment to get there. The mountain setting is moving, the weather forbidding, and the sight of the wall pumps some adrenalin. It has snow long after all the area ski resorts are green. It also attracts a particular cult of free spirits... much like our hiking community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuckerman is known for its 45-55 degree pitches so the challenge to ski it is certainly a factor. &lt;b&gt;During the spring as many as 3,000 skiers and hikers may visit the ravine in just one day!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Picnic? Lets make this fun. The discussion is now open.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is 2.4 miles and 1879 feet of elevation gain to the Hermit Lake Shelter (known as HoJos).  Hiking time is typically 1.5 to 2 hours. From there it is about another 40 minutes over 0.7 miles and 538 feet to the &amp;quot;Lunch Rocks&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Allow extra time to find parking. It is very likely that by 10 AM the parking lot for Pinkham Notch Visitor Center (PNVC) will be full. The Forest Service has issued an &lt;a href="http://www.fs.fed.us/r9/forests/white_mountain/conditions/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;alert here&lt;/a&gt;. Parking on Rte 16 is only allowed if all four wheels are off the pavement which is not possible due to the snowbanks. So if you park on Rte 16 you WILL be towed. There are two overflow lots south of PNVC, but may require 4 wheel drive. These are also fee areas, so have a WMNF parking pass or a few bucks for the day pass. If PNVC and the overflows are full, you can park at Wildcat ski area but use the &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; lot and walk the 15 minutes to PNVC. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers should check the information center for current trail/avalanche conditions before skiing or hiking, in the event that they start earlier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;30%&amp;lt; chance of rain will cancel this event. Pack snowshoes/traction for spring snow conditions. We won't know until we arrive what is recommended for that day.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209478308000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>I have been assured that this is a fun time to hike up to the Tuckerman Bowl to watch the back country adventurer's and skiers with "minimal" effort. Lets hope for a sunny spring day to kick back and enjoy the scenery.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207949601000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time for Tuckerman! Backpack Snow Picnic</name><id>7722191</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209304800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7722191/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/0/global_3581216.jpeg</photo_url></item>