<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, Movie Lovers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just got this email and I thought I'd pass on this great free screening for TOMORROW NIGHT! Please note that seats are not guaranteed, so download the passes, RSVP, and get there early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTW, I won't be there, so you'll have to self-organize if you would like to go!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Dana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good Afternoon --&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

My name is Amanda Riggio and I am the New England representative for Fox Searchlight Pictures. Our upcoming summer release, THE WAY, WAY BACK -- filmed right here in Massachusetts at the East Wareham Water Wizz – stars Steve Carrel and Toni Collette and will hit theaters July 5th; however, we are having a special advance screening of THE WAY, WAY BACK for Framingham-area moms at the Framingham AMC this Wednesday, May 29th at 7:00pm. As this is a great coming of age, family film, we would like to cordially invite the Framingham Movie Meetup to check it out before it hits theaters!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

I have included a link below that you can use to download passes. Please feel free to share this link with other friends and family as well. I have included a brief synopsis of the film below for your reference. Please do note that it is rated PG-13. Thank you and of course let me know if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Visit: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/1auh7MQ" class="linkified"&gt;http://bit.ly/1auh7MQ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Or, go to www.gofobo.com/rsvp &lt;br /&gt;

Enter RSVP Code: LJ9B5D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Best, &lt;br /&gt;

Amanda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

TICKETS ARE COMPLIMENTARY, BUT ARE EXPECTED TO GO QUICKLY AS THERE ARE ONLY A LIMITED NUMBER AVAILABLE. PLEASE ARRIVE EARLY AS SEATING WILL BE ON A FIRST COME, FIRST SERVED BASIS AND IS NOT GUARANTEED. THIS FILM IS RATED PG-13. &lt;br /&gt;

THE WAY, WAY BACK is the funny and poignant coming of age story of 14-year-old Duncan’s (Liam James) summer vacation with his mother, Pam (Toni Collette), her overbearing boyfriend, Trent (Steve Carell), and his daughter, Steph (Zoe Levin). Having a rough time fitting in, the introverted Duncan finds an unexpected friend in gregarious Owen (Sam Rockwell), manager of the Water Wizz water park. Through his funny, clandestine friendship with Owen, Duncan slowly opens up and begins to finally find his place in the world - all during a summer he will never forget.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369875849000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369766081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE SCREENING of The Way, Way Back</name><id>121643232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369864800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/121643232/</event_url></item>