<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Great Meadow Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06109</zip><lat>41.713610</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Putnam Park Office Building</name><city>Wethersfield</city><id>1424664</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.646161</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the schedule for the Great Meadows Conservation Trust winter walks for 2012, co-sponsored with the Connecticut Audubon Society Center at Glastonbury and the Eleanor Buck Wolf Nature Center in Wethersfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;about two hours. Meet Jim Woodworth and Goodwin College's Bruce Morton, Program Director of Environmental Studies, at the Putnam Park parking lot, 100 Great Meadow Road, just north of the Putnam Bridge. We'll explore the 300+ acre Crow Point property owned by Goodwin College. We'll observe the process of nature reclaiming the land and waterways excavated for fill to build the highways across the ancient farmland and wetlands of the great meadows&lt;span&gt;, and observe the &amp;ldquo;before&amp;rdquo; of the hoped for invasive species removal and forest planting from a pending DEP habitat improvement grant&lt;/span&gt;. We will have a van to shuttle the group from the parking lot along Great Meadow Road into the meadows. From I91 N, take exit 25/26 and bear right on Exit 26 to Wethersfield. At the end of the ramp, turn left under the Putnam Bridge to the parking lot. From I91 S, take exit 26, Marsh St. /Old Wethersfield. At the end of the ramp, turn left under the highway, and right at the T toward the Putnam Park lot. From Route 3N/ Maple Street, take the exit toward I91 north, but bear right Exit onto Great Meadow Road, and turn right toward the parking lot. From Route 3S, take the I91N exit at the end of bridge, but bear right Exit onto Great Meadow Road, and turn right toward the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walks will last 2 to 3 hours.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Dress for the Weather and ground conditions.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Many places will be muddy. Weather and water conditions may revise or cancel. Call the CT Audubon Society for the latest information, 860-633-8402.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Free.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry</member_name><member_id>8113327</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328971828000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318367148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brisk Winter Walk, Wethersfield Crow Point</name><id>37024232</id><headcount>63</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328364000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/37024232/</event_url></item>