<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Presented by the Alaska Wilderness League &lt;br /&gt;Simulcast Presentation! &lt;br /&gt;Free and Open to the Public&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bears are an icon of the wild, regarded as among the most successful wild animals on the planet. Three of the eight bear species in the world &amp;ndash; brown bears, black bears, and polar bears &amp;ndash; can be found in Alaska. PBS&amp;rsquo;s Nature joins adventurer and bear biologist Chris Morgan on a year-long motorcycle odyssey deep into Alaska&amp;rsquo;s bear country to explore the amazing resiliency and adaptability of these majestic animals as they struggle to make a living in five dramatically diverse Alaskan ecosystems: coastal, urban, mountain, tundra, and pack ice. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Part 3 of this series, Arctic Wanderers, will follow bears on Alaska&amp;rsquo;s North Slope. This installment will feature the National Petroleum Reserve and will look at how the Reserve is one of our nation&amp;rsquo;s best-kept wild secrets. On May 22, Alaska Wilderness League, the Sierra Club, National Audubon Society, The Wilderness Society, and National Wildlife Federation will be hosting screenings and house parties across the country. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Nature series gives us an amazing opportunity to educate your friends, family, and colleagues about the unique place in America&amp;rsquo;s Western Arctic that is home to polar and brown bears, vast herds of caribou, hundreds of thousands of migratory birds, and beluga whales. We all own our nation&amp;rsquo;s largest block of public land and all have a say in how it is managed. In 2012, the Bureau of Land Management will ask for public comments on the Western Arctic. This PBS show will allow us to educate folks to make smart decisions for the Reserve. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NATURE: Bears of the Last Frontier is a production of Pontecorvo Productions and THIRTEEN in association with Wildlife Media, National Geographic Channel and WNET New York Public Media for PBS. NATURE is a production of THIRTEEN in association with WNET for PBS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://brattlefilm.org/2011/05/22/bears-of-the-last-frontier/"&gt;http://brattlefilm.org/2011/05/22/bears-of-the-last-frontier/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to print name tag &amp;amp; carpool. &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags"&gt;meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Feel free to print name tag &amp; carpool. www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306111519000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305992322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Film: Bears Of The Last Frontier</name><id>19198011</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306107000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/19198011/</event_url></item>