<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.376237</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gordons Liquors</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1180865</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.241326</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Knowing how many wine and cheese aficionados there are in this group, how could I resist when the event director at Gordon's Fine Wines in Waltham emailed me about putting together an event just for us?  Well, actually, what I said was &amp;quot;This calls for further investigation.&amp;quot; They will happily put together just about any type of tasting for us in their new Wine and Culinary Center, but such things are NOT cheap. So. . . let's go to one of their classes as a small group and see what we think about planning a larger, more customized event down the road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Cheese 101&amp;quot; class is offered only three times a year, so although this is rather short notice, I am holding 6 spots for the spring session, this coming Thursday. If we fill all six of our spots, anyone else wishing to participate can always register via the Gordon's main website if space is still available, but you need a credit card for that. Why not just do that? Well, if you sign up here and cancel before March 9th, you can get your money back. I'm not sure if Gordon's web site will give you a refund.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This cheese class will cover how cheese is made, the different types and how they are classified, how to buy, eat, and serve cheese, and lots more. We will be tasting 9 different cheeses. Since this is a fixed-price event, the group's usual reservation fee is being waived but you do need to pay online to RSVP since I'm holding the spots with a credit card.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course will run until 8. If any participants want to do dinner afterward, we can certainly explore the possibilities. . . lots of good restaurants in Waltham!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Please park in the fenced-in lot behind the Culinary Center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Class is in the Culinary Center, not the store. Enter through the doors under the maroon awning. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268523798000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267830711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Say Cheese!  Cheese Tasting Class at Gordon's, Waltham</name><id>12796330</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268350200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/12796330/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/e/global_13464606.jpeg</photo_url></item>