<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;When Angels Speak - Understanding the Angel Financial Process&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfapril2013.eventbrite.com/"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When raising capital for your start-up or early stage company, Angel investors can fill the hole between “Friends and Family” and venture capital. According to the Angel Capital Association, there are 8 million individuals that meet the legal definition allowing angel investing, yet there are just over 300,000 angels. And among entrepreneurs seeking angel investments, only 15% actually get funded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the next EntreTech Forum Our panel of experts will discuss how Angel investors look at investment proposals and the key criteria they use for making investment decisions. They will describe their recommended approach for entrepreneurs to use in pitching potential angel investors as well as discuss their experiences with successful ventures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are looking for a Series A round or small seed investment; learning how Angels investors will look at your proposal can make the process easier, faster and ultimately more successful. Join us for an exciting and interactive discussion on Angel Investing lead by our panel of experienced practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speakers include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jack Derby&lt;/strong&gt;, Chairman Common Angels&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr3013Mtg/derby.jpg" width="149" height="149" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; Prior to forming Derby Management, a management consulting firm specializing in emerging companies and technology businesses, in 1990, Jack’s background included positions as CEO of Mayer Electronics Corporation, President of CB Sports, President of Litton Industries Medical Systems, CEO of Datamedix Corporation and President of Becton Dickinson Medical Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack is a professor at Tufts University’s School of Engineering where he teaches a course in Entrepreneurial Sales and Marketing.  He is also a Lecturer at MIT where he teaches classes in business planning and marketing in the Mechanical Engineering Department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack is extremely active in the New England emerging and middle market business communities. Jack has been named to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Mass High Tech’s&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;All Star Team.&lt;/em&gt;. Additionally, he was Chairman of the &lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/"&gt;MIT Enterprise Forum&lt;/a&gt;,  Vice Chair of the &lt;a href="http://www.sbane.org/"&gt;Smaller Business Association of New England&lt;/a&gt;, President of the University Club of Boston and is currently Chairman of the &lt;a href="http://www.acgboston.org/"&gt;Association for Corporate Growth of Boston&lt;/a&gt;.  Corporately, Jack is currently a Director at the &lt;a href="http://www.aimnet.org/AM/Template.cfm?Section=Home"&gt;Associated Industries of Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="http://www.amsolutions.net/"&gt;Accounting Management Solutions&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.thealliancecompany.com/portfolio.html"&gt;The Alliance Companies&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.beaconhospice.com/"&gt;Beacon Hospice&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://presentation.brainshark.com/"&gt;Brainshark Corporation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.hybricon.com/"&gt;Hybricon Corporation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.romesnowboards.com/"&gt;Rome Snowboards&lt;/a&gt;,  &lt;a href="http://www.smartglasss.com/"&gt;Research Frontiers&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://www.ntirety.com/"&gt;Ntirety Inc&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack is a graduate of Boston College and the United States Peace Corps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr3013Mtg/landry.jpg" width="150" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John Landry, Founder &amp;amp; Managing Director Lead Dog Ventures&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Landry is Founder and Managing Director of Lead Dog Ventures (LDV), a disruptive new-age business accelerator and investor, providing emerging technology enterprises access to a well-developed network of intellectual, relationship and financial capital. Packaging technology vision, business expertise and funding solutions, LDV provides the means for today's entrepreneurs to become the "Lead Dogs" of tomorrow. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Lead Dog's investments are typically complemented by Landry's direct involvement, usually as Director or Chairman of the Board. Landry's track record as Chairman has been notable: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman Agility Systems (acq by Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet) &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman Narrative Communications (acq by Excite/AtHome)  &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman/CTO AnyDay.com (acq by Palm)  &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman/CTO Adjoin Solutions (acq by CA)  &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman/CTO Adesso Systems (acq by Terraine) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Lead Dog continues to aggressively invest in technology companies and other businesses with current holdings numbering over 40 and including Endeca, Sonian, GoodData, ZoomInfo, ParElastic, and Practically Green.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Apr3013Mtg/Sheridan.jpg" width="150" height="188" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Ralph S. Sheridan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph Sheridan is a high technology CEO and business development specialist, skilled in developing strategies to bring new technologies to market and building teams to make firms successful. Through his firm, Value Management LLC, Ralph invests in sensors, software, and systems for commercial markets and energy technologies.  Ralph has been the CEO of both public and venture backed companies.  In addition, he has worked broadly as a business development specialist in energy production, generation and distribution.  He is also a recognized expert in security technology for a broad range of applications form terrorism to cross border trade inspection.  Ralph’s earlier experience includes CEO of Good Harbor Partners Acquisition Corp., American Science &amp;amp; Engineering, HEC Energy Corp., as well as executive positions with Combustion Engineering, Continental Group, and W.R. Grace.  Ralph is on the Board of Overseers for the Museum of Science, the Board of the Boston Council of Boy Scouts and the Presidents Council of the Olin College of Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfapril2013.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 6:30 - 9:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military; &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/7_contact.htm"&gt;Map and Directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366162915000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155730000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>When Angels Speak -  Understanding the Angel Financial Process</name><id>83283742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366151400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83283742/</event_url></item>