<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Permit Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We are hiking in the Shawangunks in the New Paltz, NY area near the Mohonk Mountain House. The path we'll hike will be a looping hike of about 8 miles in length and with a roughly 1,100 ft. altitude gain. Overall, the hike should be about 6 hrs. There will be a fee of $10 &lt;b&gt;cash&lt;/b&gt; per hiker for a permit payable at the hike location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a beautiful area made up of four major owners: Mohonk Preserve, which nearly surrounds the second area, the Mohonk Mountain House lands; The Minnewaska State Park Preserve occupies the wide mid-section of the ridge, and is the largest single ownership; To the south of Minnewaska is the Sam's Point Dwarf Pine Preserve. These lands have 761 miles of trails! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would be starting at the Spring Farm Parking Area. We will hike to the Lemon Squeeze where we will climb the gradually decreasing slot in the rock by ladders and some rock by hand nearly to the top of the mountain. We will then do the final, now easy, ascent after Lemon Squeeze to Sky Top where the memorial tower stands at the peak with a commanding view of the area! We then complete the loop back to the start mostly on carridge roads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike at a moderate pace with small breaks when folks need them. The trail will be steep in places. The parking area will have bathroom facilities and there are bathroom faciliities also at the peak. A picture preview of what to expect can be seen starting at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/photos/890356/#14442512"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No cotton is acceptable for this hike. Please dress in light layers that are loose enough for climbing and reaching. Hiking boots/trail shoes are required and should be appropriate for a small amount of rock climbing and rock scrambeling over large angular boulders. For this hike a small, light backpack is the most you should bring as otherwise it will get in the way while climbing. Bring about 1 qt. water and a snack. The wind at the summit could be occasionally strong. Make sure to have a windbreaker or similar to keep warm there. Hiking poles could be useful for the rock scramble but may pose a storage problem for climbing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This hike is not for beginners or those afraid of confined spaces or heights. Those unable to climb rock using hands and feet as well as those who don't think they can squeeze/climb through 18 - 20 inch slots are not encouraged to attend. This hike has an element of personal danger and people need to have an idea of their limits and participate safely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Because the trail WILL be agressive and vertical at times, I am not going to allow dogs on the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to approximate meetup location at the Spring Farm Parking Area (23 Upper 27 Knolls Rd., High Falls, NY):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=High+Falls&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;address=23+Upper+27+Knolls+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=12440&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.795034&amp;amp;longitude=-74.128434&amp;amp;geocode=LATLNG"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat=41.7950, Long=-74.1284)&lt;br /&gt;(Note: MapQuest has an error for the road name, lists &amp;quot;Upper 27 Knolls Rd.&amp;quot; as &amp;quot;Upper 27 Knwls&amp;quot; in the search feature)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information about the Shawangunks Mountain Region:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/region/shawangunk-mountains-region"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shawangunk_Ridge"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohonk Preserve:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/park/mohonk-preserve-4"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohonk Mountain House:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/park/mohonk-mountain-house"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minnewaska State Park Preserve:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/park/minnewaska-state-park"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam's Point Dwarf Pine Ridge Preserve:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/park/sams-point-dwarf-pine-ridge-preserve"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Available from NY/NJ Trail Conference (&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/product/shawangunk-trails"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;Or at the parking area toll booth (when open)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information about the New York/New Jersey Trail Conference&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nynjtc.org/"&gt;http://www.nynjtc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information about the Mohonk Mountain House resort/hotel&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;(Accomodations from $350/night to $2,500/night)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mohonk.com/"&gt;http://www.mohonk.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273850069000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272335539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Shawangunks (with Lemon Squeeze) in High Falls NY</name><id>13301900</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273327200000</time><rsvp_limit>19</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13301900/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/f/0/global_14668080.jpeg</photo_url></item>