<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 West Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.561977</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>West Beach</name><city>Beverly</city><id>7690922</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.804787</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;What better way to spend the 4th of July with some great friends, and an awesome band.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4th of July @ &lt;a href="http://www.beverlyfarms.org/fourth.shtml"&gt;&lt;span&gt;West Beach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, ON &lt;a href="http://www.dontcallmeshirley.info/West%20Beach%20Airial.jpg"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;THE VERANDA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; overlooking the beautiful Atlantic Ocean and Misery Island (This is going to be an amazing all day event. Shirley will be playing along side DJ  Kevin Wood&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/?ref=hp#!/pages/Its-All-About-The-Music-DJ-Services/131200576911300"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It's All About The Music&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;" . Spend the day with us on the beach and enjoy the finale with the best firework display on the North Shore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;6.28.12 UPDATE:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Here is a link to more information about this event  &lt;a href="http://www.beverlyfarms.org/schedule.pdf"&gt;http://www.beverlyfarms.org/schedule.pdf&lt;/a&gt; IF you do decide that you will be attending, and plan on bringing food then please update what food item you plan on bringing to share.  IF you have decided to not attend please change your RSVP on the meetup site so I am not looking for you.  Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;6.25.12 UPDATE here is the latest updated on this event if more updates come to me I will let you know.  Please make sure you READ ALL the information below, I know there is a lot here but it is best to read it all so you don’t have questions/issues along the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;ROAD CONDITIONS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; I have been told that a good amount of the streets that are facing West Beach will be closed to nonresident parking.  Here are a few suggestions on how you can get there you can take the train in and get off at the Beverly Farms stop, from there it is exactly a ½ mile to the gate or if you decide to drive you can park on any street that is not closed or park at the train station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;TICKETS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; If you purchase it ahead of time the price is $10.ea, IF you get them the day of the event the cost is $15.ea.  You can purchase your ticket in advance at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cork &amp;amp; Casket 37 West Street, Beverly Farms, MA 01915&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dom’s Trattoria 1 West Street, Beverly farms, MA 01915&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweatwater &amp;amp; Company 724 Hale Street, Beverly Farms, MA 01915&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF you are not able to get to these locations, send me an email and I’ll send you an address that you can send your check to.  Please put &lt;strong&gt;7/4 ticket&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line, my email address is &lt;a href="mailto:msdondon2003@yahoo.com"&gt;msdondon2003@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;TIME:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The soonest we can get in is 5:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;WHAT NOT TO BRING:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; There is NO glass or alcohol allowed.  ALL coolers WILL be checked and they will take either of these from your cooler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;PARKING:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Is on marked streets but note that the streets closest to the beach are closed off for safety/residency reasons. You may have to walk a bit with chairs in hand, so be kind to yourself and limit what you are bringing in.  NOTE there is nothing that can be done about this, they block off certain streets for safety/residency reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;FOOD:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; There is a snack stand the sign says that it closes at 5:00, not sure if it will stay open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How about we bring our own food???  IF you do want to bring something put the food item that you will be bringing in with your RSVP so we all know, &lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;to be fair to everyone if you plan on eating then bring another food item with you to share with the group&lt;/span&gt;, (I have this scheduled on 2 of my Meetup sites).  Make it easy to eat/serve nothing difficult and remember that we are outside.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Very important if it is needed make sure you bring something to serve your food.  I will bring plates, napkins, plastic silverware, a trash bag and a plastic table covering for the ground/sand.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Everyone BRING YOUR OWN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The seating area is on beach/sand so that means that is where we will be sitting. Feel free to bring chairs or a  blanket but space fills up quickly, I plan on getting there as soon as the gates open, but I don’t know how much space I will be able to hold so be prepared to get there as soon as you are able to so we all sit together.  The beach will have already been open to the residents and not sure how many of them will stay so space could be limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BATHROOMS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; They have them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;BUGS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Yup they got them even in Beverly Farms bring some spray or whatever you use so you don’t get eaten by those darn bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;If you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Remember if you have not paid your dues this year, this event would be a good opportunity to do so.  We thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in line to get onto the beach OR sitting on the beach.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341696263000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339562359000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't Call me Shirley is going to ROCK the 4th!!!!</name><id>68956642</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341435600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/68956642/</event_url></item>