<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Matt Millers book: &lt;br /&gt;The Tyranny of Dead Ideas: Letting Go of the Old Ways of Thinking to Unleash a New Prosperity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, February 04, 7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Bookstore&lt;br /&gt;1256 Massachusetts Avenue, Cambridge, MA, 02138 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;If Fortune columnist Miller's eerily prophetic book had come out earlier, it could have served as a wakeup call for Wall Street leaders and Washington, D.C. lawmakers before the failure of several venerable financial institutions required government bailouts. The author's prescient observations make a persuasive case for how an American attitude of entitlement and outdated beliefs about government, education, taxes, business, corporate excess and health care threaten our national well-being and our position as a world leader. The author denounces such cherished and longstanding beliefs as Your Company Should Take Care of You, and The Kids Will Earn More than We Do, and examines their historical provenances—for example, he traces the adoption of pensions to the early 20th century, when employers like Proctor and Gamble and G.E. acted as feudal lords offering benefits to recruit and retain employees—strategies that are now strangling these same corporations at the expense of global competitiveness. Rather than a petulant indictment of our political and economic myopia, this book offers a fair-handed critique. (Jan.)&lt;br /&gt;Copyright © Reed Business Information, a division of Reed Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;more about the book and the author here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Tyranny-Dead-Ideas-Thinking-Prosperity/dp/0805087877%3FSubscriptionId%3D13DX9SSZNT4MP1351CR2%26tag%3Dbook0052-20%26linkCode%3Dxm2%26camp%3D2025%26creative%3D165953%26creativeASIN%3D0805087877" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>contact me in advance of this event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233965590000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229668218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Truth Squad: Matt Millers book:  The Tyranny of Dead Ideas: Wens Feb 4</name><id>9362512</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233792000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9362512/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>