<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clear Conscience Cafe/Harvest Co-Op Market</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>687911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Allison has kindly offered to be our MeetUp face for the month of January in lieu of my sorry out of town mug:-)  Look for her on Monday the 11th as we (um, y'all :-) discuss:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guns, Germs and Steel: a Short history of Everybody for the Last 13000 Years by Jared M. Diamond&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/66-9780099302780-0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;A study of how Europe and the Near East became the cradles of modern society, eventually giving rise to capitalism and science, the dominant forces in today's world - and why, until more recent times, Africa, Australasia and the Americas lagged behind in both technological sophistication and political and military power. 32 illus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;This work abandons the conventional distinctions between history and science. Diamond focuses on what ancient people were endowed with in the way of land, animals and plants, and on the confrontations between less and more advanced people to see how this led to today's inequalities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As ever, head to the Clear Conscience Cafe at 7 and try to call some tables your own.  Group votes and numbers will determine if, after assessing the seating situation, everyone heads across the street to Au Bon Pain.  So if it's 7:30 and no ones flipping through this book at the CCC, try there (684 Mass Ave )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clearly, the RSVP thing is failing us regularly as we continue to have numbers less than 10, while having folks cast aside to the waiting list and missing out because we have 20 yes's and maybe's, half of whom don't show.  I hate being a mean organizer about the whole RSVP thing.  Thus, I'm not putting a limit on this one to see if that's better and keeps folks from being kept from joining us.  That said, &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;please RSVP accurately, update accordingly and try to make it if you RSVP as a yes&lt;/span&gt; so Allison (who is doing me the hugest favor, by the way...tell her thanks when ya see her!!) knows how many to actually look for.  Maybes are maybes but if please try to keep the yes's accurate.  &lt;br /&gt;  Your organizer is in your debt:-)&lt;br /&gt;  Thanks!!!&lt;br /&gt;  See you in March!!!&lt;br /&gt;  Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison</member_name><member_id>8327225</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263427846000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260233591000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers, Guns, Germs and Steel</name><id>12039905</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263254400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12039905/</event_url></item>