<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person per night</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>On the heels of Christmas we are having a less intense weekend plan for 12/21 - 12/23 &lt;br /&gt;No big parties, no catered dinner.. just a quiet weekend at the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;There are some things you should know: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you can get up there on Friday 12/21 &lt;br /&gt;- Cranmore is offering a special lift ticket price of only $3.30 per lift ticket. It is literally a 5 minute drive from the Wedeln house! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;- Settler's Green is only 15 min drive from the Wedeln house.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.settlersgreen.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.settlersgr...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There are over 60 outlets with tax free shopping in NH.  &lt;br /&gt;During the holidays, stores are open Friday &amp;amp; Saturday, 10am to 9pm; and Sundays 10am to 6pm... &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;- You can come back after a day of shopping and relax by our fireplace!  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;- With this weekend's snowstorm and cold weather expected during next week, there is plenty of skiing in the best early season conditions seen for a couple of years(8 -10 inches fell on Sunday 12/16) You can always cross-country ski in picturesque Jackson Village only 20 minutes away. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Food - There are plenty of restaurants in the area but if you would like to prepare your own food, there is a common Kitchen with 2 gas stoves and with large refrigerators / freezers to store food and beverages. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Amenities - Our Living room has a TV and a DVD player with a great fireplace! It was recently redecorated with new furniture and is very comfortable... &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Guest Lodging Fee $20/pp/night payable on arrival via cash or check. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;You must RSVP by Wednesday 12/19 9 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP, please send an e-mail to 'membership@wedeln.com'.  When you RSVP, please include your full name, cell phone number, and the names of your guest(s) and dates of arrival and departure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Lane will be your host for the weekend and a few others will be up at the house as well...  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, please send them to 'membership@wedeln.com' &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Regards, &lt;br /&gt;Jonathan &lt;br /&gt;Assistant Membership Chair&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>4521773</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200844129000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197888060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Need to get away! We invite you to Wedeln! </name><id>6925599</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198281600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/6925599/</event_url></item>