<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Anderson St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station</name><city>Portland</city><id>669831</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256200</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for the third film in our &lt;b&gt;2009|2010 Permaculture Movie Night&lt;/b&gt; Series.  This month we will be viewing the &amp;quot;Global Gardener&amp;quot; DVD, made up of four 20-minute segments (approx 80 min total) from the Australian TV show.  Though a bit dated, this is still one of the best introductions to permaculture and will familiarize you with various approaches for different climates.  Well worth the watch and often considered part of the &amp;quot;foundation&amp;quot; for permaculture learning. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info about this film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;BILL MOLLISON is a practical visionary. For nearly two decades he has traveled the globe spreading the word about permaculture, the method of sustainable agriculture that he devised. Permaculture weaves together microclimate, annual and perennial plants, animals, soils, water management and human needs into intricately connected productive communities. Mollison has proved that even in the most difficult conditions permaculture empowers people to turn wastelands into food forests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GLOBAL GARDENER is a series of four half-hour programs on one tape. Each episode looks at examples in different bioregions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IN THE TROPICS - Mollison introduces the basic principles, and shows results in Australia, India, and Zimbabwe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARID LANDS - Reversing desertification in Arizona, Botswana and Australia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COOL CLIMATES - Europe, Tasmania, and the San Juan Islands in Washington State.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;URBAN - New York City and Harare, Zimbabwe.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(Permaculture) involves caring for the whole system of earth and spaces, devising model systems with much design drawn from nature, with the end result being a system that's ecologically sound and economically profitable...Mollison provides practical and motivating information for just about anyone interested in gardening, sustainable lifestyles, and similar topics...Recommended.&amp;quot; Rachel Lohafer, Instructional Technology Center Media Library, Iowa State University, MC Journal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A lively and informative two hour video that will be greatly appreciated by &lt;br /&gt;gardeners, farmers, horticulturists, and agriculturists.&amp;quot; Midwest Book Review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This uplifting production of positive change shows people, in developed and third world countries, in the bush and in the city, turning waste lands into sustainable food production systems....this video teaches not how to do it, but how to think about doing it. This film is probably the next best thing to taking a class with Mollison himself.&amp;quot; Earthworks Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Highly recommended.&amp;quot; Video Rating Guide for Libraries&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a potluck event but feel free to bring a beverage or fruit or sweet treat to share during the film if you so desire!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie will start sometime between 7:00 and 7:10pm.  Optional discussion to follow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Thank you to our friends at Zero Station for hosting the 2009|2010 Permaculture Movie Nights*&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259885422000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254757527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Permaculture Movie Night:  Bill Mollison in Global Gardener</name><id>11551949</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259712000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/11551949/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/3/global_11073395.jpeg</photo_url></item>