<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>6:00 - 6:30 pm - Socialize &lt;i&gt;(please bring your own goodies if you want any!)&lt;/i&gt; ... I &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; bring a digital camera to post a photo of the meeting on our Meetup web site IF participants grant permission &lt;i&gt;(please notify me of any privacy concerns)&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 - 7:30 pm - &lt;b&gt;Releasing Items That Have Had Sentimental Value&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker/Panelists:&lt;/b&gt; To be announced&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 - 8:30 pm - Group problem-solving + input to future Meetups: topics, schedule, venue, speakers, organizers, activities, resources: &lt;i&gt;how can we best help YOU?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 - 9:00 pm -- Wrap-up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unmetered on-street parking&lt;/b&gt; available, + 3 visitor parking spaces nearby. &lt;b&gt;Public transportation:&lt;/b&gt; Take Red Line or bus to Porter Sq., then MBTA Bus #87 from Elm St bus shelter beside Shaw's market, to Union Square; bus stops one block from our venue ... or take Bus #86.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the most special people in life are &amp;quot;Messies&amp;quot; -- blessing many with their riches of caring and spirit while suffering silently under burdens of stuff. I'd love to find ways to declutter that work for us all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For inspiration:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Lessons from a Goose: www.problogger.net/archives/2005/05/19/blogging-in-formation-lessons-from-a-goose&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Seabiscuit documentary (PBS) about the beloved &amp;quot;little brown racehorse&amp;quot; who became proxy for this nation during the Great Depression: anatomically comical in respects (an &amp;quot;equine catastrophe!&amp;quot;), with an abysmal track record as a colt, Seabiscuit appeared best suited for hauling ice carts. But a wise trainer was captivated by a certain look in his eye and took him on, pampering him ... and inspiring generations to come. Tears well in my eyes each time I watch Seabiscuit's spirit spark and then focus, head to head against the magnificent, seemingly invincible War Admiral -- and race &amp;quot;to parts unknown!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Batteries ... plain commodities on store shelves vital for many applications: light, music, fun, work (even TASERS!). Each of us is like a battery: sometimes only one is needed for a job; usually more, to create synergy. Clutter MAY be a clue that more &amp;quot;batteries&amp;quot; are needed to complete a connection for the matter and energy stuck around us to flow again -- helping us do what we most WANT. How to better share the wealth of what we've collected, and attract more batteries to &amp;quot;rock our world&amp;quot;? Consider how you might want to do so. What may be special about your stuff ... what value is in it to keep it around? Might sharing about it help to release it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;i&gt;Saving Private Ryan&lt;/i&gt; movie - opening scene:  military risking their lives for our freedom to create value. (Also: &lt;i&gt;clutter can't fight back!&lt;/i&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Chocolate calcium &amp;quot;chews&amp;quot; vs. chalky tablets ... which do you suppose are used more easily and often?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't attend, let us know your wishes for the group ... and ideas to make decluttering more FUN, increasing our chances for success -- such as (friendly) competitions for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- most $ earned by eBay/selling stuff&lt;br /&gt;- most creative way to reward oneself&lt;br /&gt;- the inspiration/strategy/technique/resource/organization/person most helpful for clearing clutter&lt;br /&gt;- most progress made decluttering quarterly&lt;br /&gt;- most value added to a space cleared of clutter&lt;br /&gt;- best use/home found for stuff&lt;br /&gt;- idea to make decluttering the MOST FUN for the most members&lt;br /&gt;- idea that helps the most people to declutter who canNOT attend our Meetups &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...or find ways to best motivate YOU (even if not representative of our group), to share at meetings or on our Message Board for kindred spirits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who requested suggestions to start NOW -- how about analyzing what's accumulating: is it most related to security (finances, job, work), sentiment (mementos), projects (reminders of to-do's), or...?  Often much of a problem can be attributed to relatively few causes ... e.g., 20% of the organizations sending us junk mail may be responsible for 80% of our clutter! If we determine the Worst Offenders, we can remove our names from their mailing lists to help TURN OFF THE SPIGOT of junk into our lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Resources I've found to be particularly helpful include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Stephanie Winston's and Julie Morgenstern's books on getting better organized&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* David Allen's book&lt;i&gt;, Getting Things Done&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Sallie Felton, www.salliefeltonlifecoach.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Disaster Masters, www.disposophobia.com ... especially their online e-book, &amp;quot;101 Strategies to Master the Clutter,&amp;quot; helped me progress in recent months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other helpful resources (web sites, books, local services) are on our Message Board for those who may not be able to get to Meetups.  Thanks to Pamela, our Assistant Organizer who set up our Board, and to Carol, who secured our venue!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;IDEAS WELCOMED!&lt;/i&gt; You can often find me at FUPC on Sunday late a.m.'s to brainstorm:  www.cambridgepres.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                The portal of our sorrow can become our Gateway to Joy.  -- Elisabeth Elliot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                  Philippians 4:6-9 -- Thanks in All&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please look for our Meetup signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel</member_name><member_id>4671315</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210130534000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Look at your space/yard/vehicle: too much stuff? Or have folks commented on how much is accumulating around you? Want to change? If so -- welcome to our Meetup! Come to meet other like-minded individuals and discuss how our Meetup can most help YOU.</why><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206400312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston-and-Beyond Decluttering Meeting: Releasing Sentimental Items</name><id>7594982</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208383200000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/7594982/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/8/global_3017160.jpeg</photo_url></item>