<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1375 Boston Post Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06460</zip><lat>41.240082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barnes &amp; Noble</name><city>Milford</city><id>664368</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.033989</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please contact Jon Tomlin in our Members section if you have any other questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jon is the Organizer for Book Lovers &amp;amp; Coffee Enthusiast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jons description of this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Book Groupies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing everyone in April. I am very excited about our selection this month. &lt;br /&gt;It is New Earth by Eckhart Tolle. I am knee deep into reading it and it is very fascinating and &lt;br /&gt;should make for a great conversation piece. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read what Amazon has to say:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With his bestselling spiritual guide The Power of Now, Eckhart Tolle inspired millions of readers &lt;br /&gt;to discover the freedom and joy of a life lived &amp;quot;in the now.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;In A New Earth, Tolle expands on these powerful ideas to show how transcending &lt;br /&gt;our ego-based state of consciousness is not only essential to personal happiness, &lt;br /&gt;but also the key to ending conflict and suffering throughout the world. &lt;br /&gt;Tolle describes how our attachment to the ego creates the dysfunction that leads to anger, jealousy, &lt;br /&gt;and unhappiness, and shows readers how to awaken to a new state of consciousness and &lt;br /&gt;follow the path to a truly fulfilling existence&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/1037/calendar/7440644/"&gt;http://bookclub.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;bookclub.meetup.com/1037/calendar/7440644/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A New Earth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://eckharttolle.com/a_new_earth"&gt;http://eckharttolle.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;eckharttolle.com/a_new_earth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In answer to some inquiries regarding this Meet Up...&lt;br /&gt;I do not think that there will be a &amp;quot;chat&amp;quot; regarding this book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am considering rescheduling another discussion for this book for&lt;br /&gt;Later on this summer so that more members can have time to read this&lt;br /&gt;Book and discuss it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some member of our group are showing an interest in this book&lt;br /&gt;But cannot attend an early April Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look to around August or September where I will move a discussion&lt;br /&gt;Of this book to North Haven that is more central to most of&lt;br /&gt;Our members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jon Tomlin is the POC/Org for this Event.  
B &amp; N Cafe is small enough so I am sure that you can find the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273543054000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>You will be at a Book Store that is next to a Mall and many other stores.  
How can you not show up?</why><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206289313000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee Talk has a Cup Browsing A New Earth</name><id>7586968</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207414800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/7586968/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/5/global_2762549.jpeg</photo_url></item>