<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>34 Alder Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.366866</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-893-3087</phone><name>First Presbyterian Church</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1134863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.235809</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*CHANGE OF ADDRESS (U MASS WALTHAM CENTER HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN. AT 2 PM STATE INSPECTED &amp;amp; CLOSED IT. NOT DUE TO FLOODING.) COME TO FIRST PRESBYTERIAN CHURCH OF WALTHAM, 34 ALDER ST, CORNER OF BEECH. Located in the heart of Waltham, one block off Moody Street Parking is available onthe street or in the school lot on the corner of Alder St and Moody St. This is where we held the first potlucks and where the Fred Bisci event was held. Come downstairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tues March 16 -- Brenda Cobb at Dinner Speaker Series  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are extremely grateful to Brenda's donating her time &amp;amp; expenses to OHS* to speak on:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods: Reverse Aging &amp;amp; Heal&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, March 16, 2010&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;with International Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods&lt;br /&gt;Author and Teacher&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Brenda Cobb&lt;br /&gt;founder of Living Foods Institute in Atlanta, GA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.LivingFoodsInstitute.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.LivingFoodsInstitute.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hear Author Brenda Cobb's Inspiring Story of Transformation and Healing Following a Living Foods and Natural Lifestyle!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Healed breast &amp;amp; cervical cancer without surgery, chemotherapy or radiation&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Healed allergies, arthritis, depression, acid reflux, and indigestion&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Lost 75 lbs, gained energy, and turned gray hair back to original color  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U Mass Waltham Center&lt;br /&gt;240 Beaver Steet, Waltham,MA 02453&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Learn how to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Heal even the most serious diseases naturally with organic raw &amp;amp; living foods, detoxification, and emotional healing&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Reverse aging and increase energy and stamina&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Detoxify yeast, fungus, parasites, and chemicals&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      Improve your health and raise your vibration with raw living foods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 pm  Stuart Reiter, head chef at Prana Cafe, will prepare a savory dish and give you samples&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:15  pm Gourmet Potluck&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7:15  Presentation by Brenda Cobb&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Brenda has volunteered to fly and speak here if OHS/RNEC has sold 100 tickets to this event by Jan. 17!  Let's all take advantage of this great opportunity to support our kids and schools!*   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Buy tickets online for $15 for you and your friends at&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog" target="_blank"&gt;www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get a great holiday gift for your friends and family -- the gift of health!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Save $5 and get reserved seats in the front by buying tickets online -- or pay $20 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you wish to help sell tickets and sell 20 tickets for $15 each, you will be given a free ticket.  Call Betsy at 617-835-2913 if you wish to help.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring a raw organic, unprocessed, ready to serve dish for 8 with labeled utensils or pay an extra $10 at the door or here on line:&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*All donations will go to the school gardens and &amp;quot;Optimum Health for Kids&amp;quot; program at the Martin Luther King Jr Public School in Dorchester.  This exciting program includes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Training teachers at Martin Luther King Jr Public School in Dorchester in the natural living food lifestyle, including preparation of healthy nutritious foods, exercise, and support -- with teachers getting professional development credits&lt;br /&gt;    * Students growing sprouts and preparing and enjoying healthy foods and green smoothies in their classrooms&lt;br /&gt;    * Energy medicine training for teachers and students - expanded to the whole school! - already resulting in improved energy, focus, and learning for students!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268948640000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266401043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS Potluck / Speaker: Brenda Cobb *CHANGE OF ADDRESS!*</name><id>12626574</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268775000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/12626574/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/9/global_13164361.jpeg</photo_url></item>