<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(US, 1940) Director: Alfred Hitchcock. Screenplay by Robert E. Sherwood and Joan Harrison, based on the novel by Daphne du Maurier. Cast: Laurence Olivier, Joan Fontaine, George Sanders, Judith Anderson.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;ldquo;Last night I dreamt I went to Manderley again...&amp;rdquo; Thanks to our generous donors, including Friends of Cinestudio, a new audience can enjoy the eerie opening line of Rebecca (and everything that follows) in a classic theater dedicated to cinema alone. As movie fans know, Rebecca was Alfred Hitchcock&amp;rsquo;s first movie made in the States, and it signals the start of a more personal expressiveness, along with his brilliant technical innovations. The young and na&amp;iuml;ve Joan Fontaine marries a brooding widower (Laurence Olivier), who brings her home to Manderley, a windswept Cornish estate. In over her depth, Fontaine is tormented by a fanatically loyal housekeeper (the great Judith Anderson), and the memory of Rebecca, Olivier&amp;rsquo;s first wife. Academy Award&amp;reg; for Best Picture. &amp;ldquo;A gorgeous treat from one of cinema&amp;rsquo;s masters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323048367000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321638970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Alfred Hitchcock's Rebecca</name><id>41640012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323044100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/41640012/</event_url></item>