<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.227803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.540063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sunset is 6:08, moon rise 4:27 at 90.7% full.  Meeting a 5:00 with launch by 5:30, should give everyone a little bit of time to see and enjoy the lake before it is dark.  We'll plan to be off the water by 8:00 at the latest.  We will paddle at a leisurely pace through islands and coves while enjoying the moon rising over and reflecting in the water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a headlamp so that you can see to get your kayak back onto your roof for the trip home.  You will not need light out on the water, as the moon will light our way.  You may want to bring a snack and possibly a hot drink since it will be cool out.  The water is starting to cool down, so keep that in mind when choosing footwear.  The air temperature is predicted to be 54 degrees by 8:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do not come if you are not completely comfortable in your kayak for a few hours.  Everyone should have, at least, some experience paddling and getting in and out of the kayak.  It is too cold to take chances of being wet this time of year.  Everyone will be responsible for their own safety, but we will stay together as a group and make decisions as a group.  State Law madates wearing a  PFD after Sept 15, and so do I!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whitehall is on Route 135 between Hopkinton and Westborough.  If you need a map, search for Dale Road in Hopkinton; it is the road immediately west of the entrance to the parking lot for Whitehall State Park.  Parking is free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a skinny stick (Greenland paddle)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225905889000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223643742000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Paddle at Whitehall</name><id>8936414</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223758800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/8936414/</event_url></item>