<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Introduction to a powerful  photography  tool! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Understanding how to use electronic  flash and how to incorporate it into your photography skill set is an exciting and easy way to produce some dramatic improvements in your digital photography. This class will cover the basics of on camera flash photography, understanding and controlling flash exposure and light modifying and controlling techniques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The use of electronic flash may seem complex and confusing to many photographers so the goal of this class is to break down the technology into its basic components and then show how each affects your image quality. The advantages that digital cameras provide make using electronic flash even easier to understand and master. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Electronic flash is hard directional light and we will teach some techniques to modify the quality and the direction of it to add a remarkable visual dimension to your images. We will explain how to combine flash with daylight/available light a popular technique to improve image quality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TOPICS covered include: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FLASH modes and Settings &lt;br /&gt;FLASH EXPOSURE CONTROL &lt;br /&gt;FLASH Modifiers &lt;br /&gt;BOUNCE FLASH METHODS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be a combination of class room discussion and hands-on practice exercises. Please bring your camera and any flash units.. If you do not own any accessory  hot shoe mounted flash units, this class will still provide you insight in to which products to purchase as well as demonstrate ways to use your built in flash  and to give you the skills to add this feature to your photography&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For directions go to my website -- http://www.testoftimephoto.com/DIRECTIONS.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284595870000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281805991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FLASH PHOTOGRAPHY- using your on-camera flash!</name><id>14421854</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284591600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14421854/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/e/global_16414110.jpeg</photo_url></item>