<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>630 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.415778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Church of Arlington</name><city>Arlington</city><id>1179713</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.154155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You are invited to attend a benefit concert on Sunday, December 16th, 3:30 pm, at First Parish Unitarian Universalist of Arlington, 630 Mass Ave , to benefit people adversely affected by Hurricane Sandy. The suggested donation is $10 at the door, and additional donations are welcome. (Doors open at 3 pm)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;120 members of the Mystic Chorale, directed by Nick Page, will celebrate songs by renowned folk artists including Woody Guthrie, Bob Dylan, and Holly Near. The Family Folk Chorale is a multi-generational chorus led by Chris Eastburn, who will lead us all in Beatles songs. For more information about these choruses visit &lt;a href="http://www.mysticchorale.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mysticchorale.org/&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.familyfolkchorale.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.familyfolkchorale.org/&lt;/a&gt;. Singing along will be encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Proceeds from the fundraiser will be donated to Occupy Sandy, a coordinated relief effort to distribute resources and volunteers to help neighborhoods and people affected by Hurricane Sandy, &lt;a href="http://www.occupysandy.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.occupysandy.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This event is co-sponsored by Occupy Arlington and members of First Parish Unitarian Universalist of Arlington.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 A benefit concert to help those adversely affected by Hurricane Sandy will take place on Sunday, December 16th at 3:30 pm at First Parish Unitarian Universalist of Arlington ( 630 Mass Ave , Arlington at the intersection of Mass Ave and Pleasant Street/Rte. 60). Suggested donation $10 at the door, additional donations are encouraged. Doors open at 3:00 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fundraiser will bring together two Arlington based choral groups. Each is part of a growing movement of alternative choruses, groups that do not sing the standard classical repertoire. Both groups invite their audiences to sing along as chorus and audience become a living community. The Mystic Chorale directed by Nick Page will celebrate folk songs by Woody Guthrie, Bob Dylan, Holly Near and others. The Family Folk Chorale led by Chris Eastburn will lead us all in beloved Beatles songs, including the children singing a mesmerizing version of John Lennon’s “Imagine.” The fundraiser will end with a rousing Gospel-style rendition of Woody Guthrie’s “This Land Is Your Land” in celebration of the hundredth anniversary of his birth. With a hundred and seventy voices plus a full house of fellow souls, our voices will be heard and through our contributions, change will be made. You don’t have to be a singer to attend, but you may find yourself singing along anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For twenty-two years, the Mystic Chorale has thrilled many thousands with their concert-sings. In addition to their three seasons a year performed in Boston , they have toured to Costa Rica , Ireland , Germany , as well as several trips to New York City . Their founder/director Nick Page is a choral composer with over eighty published works, including premieres at Carnegie Hall and Lincoln Center . More info at www.mysticchorale.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Family Folk Chorale is a multi-generational chorus with members aged 3-89, who bring together the spirited energy of children, the honesty of teenagers coming of age, and the experience of adulthood and elders as they all come shining through and raise their voices in harmony. More info at www.familyfolkchorale.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proceeds from the fundraiser will be donated to Occupy Sandy, a coordinated relief effort to distribute resources and volunteers to help neighborhoods and people affected by Hurricane Sandy. For more information or to volunteer, visit &lt;a href="http://www.occupysandy.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.occupysandy.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If would you would like to make a donation to the Occupy Sandy relief effort, you may either donate on-line at &lt;a href="http://www.occupysandy.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.occupysandy.org/&lt;/a&gt; or send a check, made out to Occupy Sandy/AfGJ (addressed to Alliance for Global Justice, 1247 E. St, SE, Washington , DC 2003.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This benefit concert is co-sponsored by Occupy Arlington and members of First Parish Unitarian Universalist of Arlington. For more information, please email Oakes at plimag@comcast.net.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen </member_name><member_id>4834783</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355894177000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354762667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Benefit Concert for Hurricane Sandy relief,  with the Mystic Chorale+</name><id>94265982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355688000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/94265982/</event_url></item>