<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Le Mepris (&lt;b&gt;Contempt&lt;/b&gt;) France 1963 102 minutes  Starring Brigitte Bardot, Jack Palance, and Fritz Lang&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Brilliant, romantic and genuinely tragic. It's also one of the greatest films ever made about the actual process of moveimaking.&amp;quot; - Martin Scorsese&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A film about - among other things - integrity. The basic situation, faithfully adapted from Moravia's novel A Ghost at Noon, concerns a young woman (Bardot) who is gradually possessed by an overwhelming contempt for her husband (Piccoli), a writer beset by doubts when he is called in as script-doctor to a film of The Odyssey, being made by a director (Lang) who wants to capture the reality of Homer's world, and a crass producer (Palance) who just wants more mermaids. Yes, she agrees that the money will be useful; no, she doesn't feel he is selling out since he is interested in the subject; and which ever way he decides to jump is perfectly all right by her. But there still remains that tight knot of contempt which she won't explain and he doesn't understand. Around this Godard weaves subtle parallels with Homer's tale of patient Penelope, the statues of Minerva and Neptune which brood over the modern tragedy, locations which paradoxically set the airy spaces of a flat in Rome against the confines of the Homeric landscapes of Capri, and for good measure a stream of cinematic jokes. Magnificently shot by Raoul Coutard, it's a dazzling fable.  Time Out&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A melancholic riff on the fragility of love, and simultaneously a critique on the superficial nature of commercial cinema, ``&lt;b&gt;Contempt&lt;/b&gt;'' takes us back to the nouvelle vague -- when European auteurs were planting cerebral land mines on cinematic landscapes, and finding ways to combine the sensuality and lyricism of film with intellectual debate. San Francisco Chronicle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The title is undoubtedly a stab at the producers of the film, Carlo Ponti and Joseph E. Levine. It was Godard's first foray into big-budget filmmaking and his first use of a star of the magnitude of Brigitte Bardot. The producers, worried about making their money back, began to request that the director make changes in the movie. Of course, someone as independent and radical as Godard did not take kindly to this. So, when Ponti asked him why he did not have a nude scene exploiting the popularity of Bardot, Godard gave him a nude scene (the one that opens the movie). Of course, he undermines it by making Bardot question whether her husband (Michel Piccoli) likes her different body parts. This change not only makes the scene more about insecurity than sexuality but also interrogates the idea of what makes a nude scene and why somebody would be drawn to it. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://apolloguide.com/mov_fullrev.asp?CID=4457&amp;amp;Specific=5241" target="_blank"&gt;http://apolloguide.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there ,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The time for this has been  moved to 2:45. After the film Tom will be holding a Meetup sign and then its off to a local restuarant to discuss and share ideas.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208199081000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205888093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Godard's Contempt at The Brattle</name><id>7559836</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208025900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7559836/</event_url></item>