<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Belknap Mt. Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03246</zip><lat>43.515434</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whiteface/Piper Trailhead</name><city>Gilford</city><id>1439831</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for hikers who haven't given up on their love of hiking and being in nature despite their age or level of physical conditioning. We hike at a pace 50% slower than the AMC Trailguide book time.Hike ratings: easy, moderate, strenuous,very strenuous. There are three other hiking Meetup groups if you want a faster pace or more challenging hikes (The New England Hiking Meetup, 4 Seasons Hiking Group, New England Over 40 Hiking Group).The hiking Meetup group,(Fellowship of the Tortoise) does easier,slower paced hikes than this group. Our goal is to stay fit while enjoying the camaraderie of hikers who have similar skills and goals. This is a dog free hiking group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 north to exit 20,make a left onto US3 north towards Laconia,stay with US3 on the Laconia/Gilford Bypass,take the exit for Gilford Avenue (NH11A),make a right at the bottom of the exit ramp,in Gilford make a right onto Belknap Mountain Road for about 3 miles (ignore the signs for Carriage Road and Belknap Mountain).When coming to a tee in the road,make a left and stay with Belknap Mountain Road.Head up the road all the way to the trailhead which is at the paved parking circle.We will hike to the summit of Whiteface Mountain(1,660'),some people could return to the cars for hike of 3 mile round trip,620' elevation gain,of about 3 hours,the rest can go on to summit Piper Mountain(2,044'), for a total of 5 mile round trip,1140' elevation gain,5 hour estimated time.Views of the Belknap Mountain Range on both summits.----Steve----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for gray Chevy pick up truck NH2646423</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333418823000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332170970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EASY  OR  MODERATE  HIKE--WHITEFACE  AND  PIPER  MOUNTAINS</name><id>56951702</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333198800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/56951702/</event_url></item>