<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Alton NH</address_2><address_1>4 Homestead Pl.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03809</zip><lat>43.451876</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-3120-6735</phone><name>McDonalds Resturant  at Alton Traffic Circle</name><city>Alton</city><id>296592</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.209624</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers  We will be spelunking Devil's Den and hiking up Devil's Den Mountain (a very easy hike) it takes about an hour to get to the top, very beautiful you can see Lake Winnepesaukee and Merrymeeting Lake, we will have a picnic on top of the mountain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we go into the cave it is very important to bring appropriate foot gear (good mountain boots) a reliable flashlight and a positive attitude (you can't be afraid of the dark!!!).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been leading trips up there for the last 25 years so I know the cave very well. This is an old Indian cave, not a tourist attraction like the &amp;quot;Polar Caves&amp;quot;, everyone I take up there really enjoys the experience!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are welcome for this activity but under their parents' supervision.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be having a potluck on top of Devil's Den, so bring enough food for your leader!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the McDonald's at the Alton Traffic Circle, in Alton NH at 11 am and carpool to the mountain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive before 11:00, say at 10:30 because everyone hates waiting for someone who is late! Besides you can always get something to eat or you can get to know your fellow hikers!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before the hike we will take a short visit to one of the largest fish hatcher's in New England! (it's on the way to the cave), very impressive, and it's free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the hike if anyone want's to refresh themselves we will be going over to my parents lakeside camp and go swimming, sailing or jetskiing, weather permiting of course! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone has any questions do not hesitate to contact me at 603-509-2907.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***If it rains or lightening will occur I will reschedule the trip. &lt;br /&gt;See you there. &lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285026018000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275995903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spelunking / Hiking Trip at Devils Den Mountain</name><id>13734574</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284908400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/13734574/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/f/global_14202751.jpeg</photo_url></item>