<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We will meet in the  Sheepfold parking lot .  For those interested  we will be getting together for lunch after the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fells is a 2,060 acre natural treasure, something all too rare in this urban/suburban landscape. A diverse landscape of rocky hills, meadows, wetlands, oak and hickory forests, quiet ponds, vernal pools, panoramic vistas and intriguing geological features distinguish this woodland. This range of habitat sustains a variety of wildlife including mammals such as coyote, fisher, red fox, and white tail deer. Reptiles and amphibians are also resident. Birds such as scarlet tanager, eastern bluebird, hawks and many neo-tropical migrants nest, find cover and food here. A wide variety of common and rare trees, shrubs, wildflowers and insects too numerous to mention make their home in the Fells and add to the biological diversity. &lt;br /&gt;The Fells has a long and varied cultural history. Native Americans hunted here for thousands of years before the colonial period when trees were harvested, animals were allowed to graze, and town lots created. Timber used by General Washington in the fortification of Dorchester Heights is believed to have been harvested from the Fells. In the 1800's, Spot Pond provided ice for worldwide export. Extensive rubber manufacturing existed at the end of the 19th century in an area called Haywardville. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The impact of 20th century man can also be seen throughout the Fells in the works of landscape architects Charles Eliot and George Olmstead as well as the Civilian Conservation Corp and the Work Progress Administration. Route 93 and many other roads as well as several drinking water projects have impacted the landscape. However, when you walk the many quiet hiking trails and old forest roads that wind through the reservation, you may forget that you are only a few miles from Boston. The Fells includes areas in Medford, Winchester, Stoneham, Melrose and Malden, and is easily accessible from U.S. Route 93 or Mass. Rte. 28, numerous bus lines, rapid transit and commuter rail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Car: &lt;br /&gt;From North&lt;br /&gt;93 South to exit 35 at stop take a left under hightway at next stop sign take a right at first set of lights (rt28) take a right for Sheepfold enterance. &lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;93 South to exit 33(RT28N) take first right onto South Border Road. Bellevue Pond on right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South&lt;br /&gt;93 North to exit 33(RT28N) for Sheepfold or proceed halfway around rotary and take South Border Road for Bellevue Pond. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208003172000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204484650000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Chestnut Hill April Walking Meetup</name><id>7447026</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207501200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/7447026/</event_url></item>