<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373917</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12509672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119385</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MARC Vegan Outreach&lt;/strong&gt; to promote and explain veganism and expose animal agriculture. Event is weather permitting only. Check for postponement email &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;rayshick@msn.com&lt;/a&gt; or call 978-257-7062 on morning of event. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://massanimalrights.org/" target="_blank"&gt;MassAnimalRights.org &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check if the &lt;strong&gt;Smoothie Stand&lt;/strong&gt; inside the &lt;strong&gt;Harvard T Station&lt;/strong&gt; is still there and open. It has received good reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maramore.wordpress.com/2013/03/23/groundwork-marc/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://maramore.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/2013-03-23mmbumarc.jpg?w=490&amp;amp;h=368" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the pigs, chickens, cows, dairy calves, lambs, sheep, goats, and water living creatures. Worldwide, 51 billion (10 billion US) farmed animals are killed each year. The suffering this represents is staggering. Hidden away, animals are abused and neglected in factory farms throughout the U.S. Female pigs, egg laying hens, and veal calves are kept in cages and crates so small that they cannot turn around. Common practices include tail docking, beak cutting, castration, branding, and forced impregnation, all without anesthesia. Starvation for 7-14 days (forced molting) is routinely practiced on laying hens. Animals' deaths are just as bad. They are dragged, terrified, to their deaths. They are often skinned while still alive. Chickens and other birds are killed without even the most lenient protections. Most "food animals" are killed at such young ages, that if they were dogs or cats, they would still be called puppies or kittens, and farmers would be called animal abusers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: (Call on cell, listed above, on day of rally if you need on-the-spot help.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Via Public Transportation (best option): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Take the Red Line to the Harvard stop; or take any number of buses that come to Harvard Square. For more information and schedules, visit the Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (MBTA) &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.mbta.com&lt;/a&gt;. Come up out of the T station and you will immediately need to turn right and right again as walking back above ground over where you just came. (You are basically just going around the station.) We will be across the street to the left (And across the street from Au Bon Pain and "The Pit".) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 By Car: (You can also go to: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.com/&lt;/a&gt; and type in Harvard Square, Cambridge, Massachusetts.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From the Mass Pike - East and Westbound): Take Exit 18 (Allston-or &lt;br /&gt;

 Brighton/Cambridge). Go through toll booth and bear right towards Cambridge, then get into far left lane at set of traffic lights. At 2nd traffic light (before the bridge across from the Doubletree Guest Suite Hotel) turn left onto Storrow Drive; Soldiers Field Road; exit at Harvard Square. Turn right to cross the bridge. You will be on JFK Street headed into Harvard Square. Find parking. (See below for info.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From The South (I-93 North): Heading north on Route 93 take the Mass Pike. Then see above under Mass Pike directions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From The North (I-93 South): Heading south on Route 93 exit onto Storrow Drive west. Take Harvard Square/Cambridge exit, turn right and proceed over bridge and across Memorial Drive onto JFK Street and into Harvard Square. Find parking. (See below for info.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 From Logan Airport: As you leave the airport, follow signs to Rt. 90, Mass. Turnpike West. Then see above under Mass Pike directions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Parking: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Street parking is available on surrounding streets in Harvard Square but spots can be hard to find. One and two hour meters require payment (quarters only) Monday through Saturday between 8am and 6pm. Here is a map showing parking garages/lots: &lt;a href="http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvardsquare.com/maps.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Across from 1100 Mass. Ave. Au Bon Pain &amp; "The Pit". Look for MARC's "Barnyard Trio" (cow, pig, chicken) &amp; MARC people with signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</member_name><member_id>55605982</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364674767000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361658801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MARC Outreach &amp; Smoothies?</name><id>dtjslfyrfbnc</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364666400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/107484522/</event_url></item>