<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Why go ghost-hunting when there are things you can do to have the ghosts come to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;?&amp;nbsp; Physical Mediumship: when objects move and noises are heard for ALL those present. This is the foundation of modern Spiritualism and the entire New Age / Metaphysical movements. Things DO go bump in the night, and watching them go bump when you ask them to is amazing! Join us for an evening of demonstrations of Table-Tipping, the original form of physical mediumship, through special guests Ginny May and Kate Otto. It is truly *SPECTACULAR* to see!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$20 per person, advance registration required to guarantee your seat. Please register early, as we expect this event to sell out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VERY IMPORTANT!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Registration is being handled through the Consciousness Studies Meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/TheCenterNH/events/47943392/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/TheCenterNH/events/47943392/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not registered there, you do not have a guaranteed seat!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ginny May is a Registered Nurse certified in Newborn Intensive Care. She has worked in Boston for the last 17 years, where she continues to provide a holistic approach to healing in the NICU setting. Ginny is also a Usui Reiki Practitioner, and has certifications in many non-traditional modalities, but is currently focusing on the use of directed healing energy through spiritual attunement. She has further studied many forms of mediumship at the Arthur Findlay College in Stansted, England, and continues to advance her education in that regard. Ginny often uses table-tipping when introducing others to the spirit world because the physical manifestation of energy is difficult to deny. She also combines this form of communication with healing intent in specific settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kate Otto is a former law enforcement and forensics officer, and currently works as a dog trainer and a psychic medium. She is certified in Reiki II healing and has studied mediumship extensively, including trance mediumship under the world famous Rita Berkowitz. Kate works as a medium at Hope Floats Wellness Center in Kingston, MA., and also does private readings and spirit connections. She uses table tipping as a means of healing and for people to not only connect to loved ones past, but to their guides and angels as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327799852000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326687269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Table-Tipping: a Demonstration of Physical Mediumship</name><id>48260702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327795200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/48260702/</event_url></item>