<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-9278</phone><name>Central Square Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1044961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100953</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Love Biology? Come hear the co-author who literally wrote the book on it! Joe Levine, author of Prentice Hall's textbook, Miller &amp;amp; Levine, Biology speak about Charles Darwin at 7:00 pm on Saturday, April 10th, 2010 before the play. The discussion is moderated by John Durant, Director, MIT Museum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This talk is free to ticketholders of the 8:00 pm performance of &lt;b&gt;From Orchids To Octopi: An Evolutionary Love Story at Central Square Theater&lt;/b&gt;. Tickets for the play are only $17.50 if purchased from Goldstar.com. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Find out more information about:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Pre-Performance Symposium: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/13058943/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Orchids To Octopi&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;by Melinda Lopez &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Saturday, April 10th at 8:00 PM&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at Central Square Theater &lt;br /&gt;450 Massachusetts Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02139 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by Catalyst Collaborative@MIT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets&lt;/b&gt;: $35.00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Half-Price if purchased using Goldstar.com at &lt;a href="http://www.goldstar.com/events/cambridge-ma/from-orchids-to-octopi-an-evolutionary-love-story.html"&gt;http://www.goldstar.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Catalyst Collaborative@MIT – Underground Railway Theater’s science theater initiative with MIT – presents this World Premiere by award-winning playwright Melinda Lopez, commissioned by the National Institutes of Health to celebrate the 150th anniversary of “On the Origin of Species.” Surprises erupt as a muralist’s work is derailed by hallucinations, pregnancy, and dinosaurs in this witty take on how we understand – or do not – the theory of evolution. Charles Darwin comments on it all. March 31 – May 2; Thu @ 7:30pm, Fri &amp;amp; Sat @ 8:00pm, Sun @ 2:00pm (additional performances: 3/31@7:30pm, 4/7@7:30pm, 4/21@7:30pm)&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... On February 3rd, we saw line readings of various scenes -- some of them days after being written. It was kinda cute, a juxtoposition of sorts. An artist processing the information on Darwin to complete the mural on evolution she is working on has fever dreams as she grapples to understand Darwin and his work. A sideshow barker trying to lure people into playing a genetic lottery! Giraffes! Dinosaurs! In between the absurdity, it depicts the touching relationship between Darwin and his wife, and her own relationship with her husband. Cute, touching, funny, and sweet, that's what I thought about &lt;b&gt;From Orchids To Octopi: An Evolutionary Love Story&lt;/b&gt;. I really want to see what they came up with as a finished product.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J will be at the theater starting at 6:30 pm and will be grabbing seats for the Pre-Symposium at 6:40 pm. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the playwright&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2010/catalyst.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Melinda Lopez was the first recipient of the Kennedy Center's Woollard &amp;quot;Promising New Voice in American Theatre&amp;quot; and has received multiple Elliot Norton Awards (Boston's Tony). Her plays have been performed on NPR and in theaters nation-wide—most recently at Williamstown. Her work in science theater includes a commission from the Boston Museum of Science.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Catalyst Collaborative@MIT&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2010/catalyst.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/mu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CC@MIT is a unique collaboration between MIT and the Underground Railway Theater (URT), a company with 30 years experience creating and touring new works. CC@MIT presents plays that deepen public understanding about science, examining the human condition through the lens of science and technology. CC@MIT award-winning productions take place annually during the Cambridge Science Festival, and have been featured during the New York City World Science Festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Central Square Theater&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goldstar.com/events/cambridge-ma/from-orchids-to-octopi-an-evolutionary-love-story.html"&gt;http://www.goldstar.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Central Square Theater is home to Underground Railway Theater (URT) and The Nora Theatre Company, two professional theater companies with a combined track record of over 48 years of excellence. URT has a 29 year history of connecting high quality professional theater with communities, performing new plays for young audiences, families and adults, and teaching through its rigorous education programming. Combining actors, puppetry and music, URT reaches out to and engages diverse audiences with performances of great beauty and compelling social content. During The Nora's 19 years, audiences and the media have recognized it for its exceptionally high quality work. Mission-driven to bring cutting-edge, thought- provoking, and contemporary productions to New England audiences, The Nora has introduced local audiences to Boston, New England, and/or world premieres. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271116977000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266969973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>From Orchids To Octopi: An Evolutionary Love Story Central Square Theater</name><id>12689227</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270944000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12689227/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>