<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me and Breezy on a hike with Jeff and his black lab Cody this Saturday at F Gilbert State Forest in Foxboro:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at the main parking lot at 45 Mill St.. Great news: Jeff is very familiar with the park and will tailor our trek to fit the amount of time our group wants to be out on the trails.  SO all we have to do is bring bags,  water for us and our pups, a power bar or snack in case we get hungry, and bug spray.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff will be the man with blond hair and glasses, next to his black lab Cody.  I will be the brunette with the little pup of a bichon (Breezy) driving a vintage - old - white audi ... now that it is on the move again =0).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to know more ... Here are a couple of links you may want to check out from Jeff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/fgil.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/FGilbrt.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or if you just want the highlights here is my cut and paste:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;F. Gilbert Hills State Forest &lt;br /&gt;45 Mill St., Foxboro 02035 &lt;br /&gt;508 543-5850&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Covering 1,027 acres in Foxboro and Wrentham, F. Gilbert Hills is a &amp;quot;passive use&amp;quot; pine and oak forest. There are 23 miles of trails for various uses, looping through the forest. One of these leads to the Warner Trail, a long-distance hiking trail that travels through Norfolk County on its way to Rhode Island. Mountain Biking is a widely popular activity and there are also trails for ORVs and horseback riding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The forest is named for a dedicated State Forester and park employee. In the 1930s he produced a series of outstanding illustrative maps of many of the Department's properties in existence at the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Franklin and Wrentham State Forests are minimally developed properties that offer numerous intersecting trails and dirt roads.  Trails are open for hiking, mountain biking and off highway vehicles (not ATVs).  For information call F. Gilbert Hills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chat soon,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeff will be the man with blond hair and glasses, next to his black lab Cody.  I will be the brunette with the little pup of a bichon (Breezy) driving a vintage - old - white audi</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristan</member_name><member_id>8717151</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249306806000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248919101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore F Gilbert Hills State forest in Foxboro. </name><id>10990284</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249133400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/10990284/</event_url></item>