<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The New England Hiking Meetup plans on camping at Lafayette campground on Saturday night, and we will be surrounded by some of the best hikes in the Whites.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lonesome Lake Trail head leaves out of the campground to 3 possible hikes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lonesome Lake hut and hike around the lake&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;Suitable for beginner and easy paced hikers. A four season hut with limited services. Dogs must remain outside. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North and South Kinsman Mountain&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;2 4K mountains on one hike&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9.96 mi 7 hr 30 min AMC booktime&amp;nbsp; add at least 1 hour for casual paced hikers &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cannon Mountain&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;Former home to the NH's state "old man in the Mountain"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;A 2 story tower affords superb 360 degree views. eat at the large heated summit cafeteria (in the $10 price range, or bring your own lunch), watch some skiing, relax, have great fellowship before returning via the same route. The Lonesome Lake and Kinsman Ridge trails to the summit and back to the parking lot is moderate at just 6.2 miles, 2300 feet elevation, with a AMC book time 4.30 minutes. Add at least 1 hour for casual paced hikers to catch their breath.&amp;nbsp; shorter hikes=steeper trails&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A weather advisory will cancel this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;A minimum of 4 hikers will be required. Plan on hiking at a comfortable pace, C1 casual pace is usually longer than "book time" &amp;nbsp;no one should hike alone. &amp;nbsp;Proper "Hikesafe" clothing and gear required. Know your equipment and how to pack your gear, review the weather conditions before you arrive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;In addition to the standard lists, remember to pack "gatorade" drinks or gels to replace your electrolytes. This is advised for any high endurance exercise that lasts for over one hour.&lt;a href="http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1"&gt;http://www.gssiweb.com/Article_List.aspx?topicid=1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Our goal is to start together as a group, hike together and finish together as a group. A winter group can be as small as 4 people, but no one should hike alone. Adhere to the Hike-Safe guidelines. Anyone could need help and stuff does happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/7/event_10322999.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lonesome Lake Trailhead 9am trailhead. restrooms are just past the park and ride.  phone/text so we have real plans to meet you for the meetup, and no question of if your in the right location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335104362000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330118382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lonesome Lake, Cannon Mountain or Kinsman's 1 Trailhead-3 Options, Casual Pace</name><id>dgmrlcyqgbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335099600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/53680662/</event_url></item>