<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Opposite Sears entrance at Galleria Ma</address_2><address_1>59 First Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.368895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>VFW</name><city>East Cambridge</city><id>1276287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077357</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Party with Free Live Music in East Cambridge near the Galleria Mall.&lt;/b&gt;  The venue has very cheap drinks, a relaxed atmosphere, pool table, and free live music with great musicians and an &lt;b&gt;open mike. &lt;/b&gt;  Sax, horns, singers, singer songwriters and improvising are all encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a new Open Mike East Cambridge near the Galleria Mall – it a blues style open mike for all types of music, but we are doing at least 1 least a jazz set and do some well known standards.  There are at least 3 musician/singer meetup groups participating, and other social/meetups/groups,  so we also want to select tunes that are well known and might appeal to a younger crowd also.  We plan to play - What a wonderful world, Over the rainbow, sunshine of my life, summertime, and improvising on themes, and good ideas for future songs could be She’s come Undun, Blue Skies, Take Five, improvisations on great jazz/blues riffs &amp;amp; themes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the ad - we could plan to do a weekly jazz set, and also have a rehearsal meetup - &lt;b&gt;But even if you don't play, come to check it out and network with interesting musicians&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention Party goers,  Musicians, Singles &amp;amp; Singers!!  Come join the party at the Wed Night Open mike! Everyone Welcome. No cover charge - Play pool or music solo or with backing band.  All instruments and styles welcome.  Originals, covers, blues, jazz, classic rock, R&amp;amp;B, Motown, folk, etc.   Back up band with drums, bass, guitar, and Songlist for singers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crystal Bar VFW across from the Sears Entrance of the Galleria Mall near Lechmere. 59 1st St., Cambridge. Weekly open mike Wednesday night - starts at 7:30PM. Bring your friends for the party, network, play pool, and meet, interesting people.  Inexpensive drinks. (bottle beer $2.75 import $3.75 wine $3!!!!)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4" on the keys.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278563711000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans/Musicians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>jazz-190</urlname><id>1202977</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge/Somerville/Boston Jazz Meetup/Jam</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278357638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Music OPEN MIKE, Cheap Drinks, Networking, Pool table.</name><id>jxjznynkbkb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278545400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/jazz-190/events/14007724/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/b/global_6953227.jpeg</photo_url></item>