<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Off Rte 10</address_2><address_1>Hilton Court</address_1><state>NJ</state><zip>07054</zip><lat>40.840450</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hilton Hotel - New Jersey</name><city>Parsippany</city><id>588841</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.452780</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>8/23/09&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can now look at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chillertheatre.com/gt/gtc4.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chillerthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.chillertheatre.com/gt/gtc4.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to see what guests are going to be there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am looking at the New Jersey AAA booklet to see what hotels&lt;br /&gt;That we might consider staying at.  Should know by the end of &lt;br /&gt;August.&lt;br /&gt;We will say what hotels that we will be staying at but members staying the &lt;br /&gt;night must make their own reservations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be updates and reminders when we have more &lt;br /&gt;information regarding the Expo &amp;amp; planned trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween 09 Chiller Theater Expo on Saturday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.chillertheatre.com/main.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chillertheatre.com/main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chillerthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at link for event details; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be contacting those coming with me &lt;br /&gt;Later on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be driving to &lt;br /&gt;Chiller Theatre Toy, Model and Film Extravaganza &lt;br /&gt;Hilton Hotel &lt;br /&gt;Parsippany, New Jersey, 07054&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions can be found on the link.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do go a different way; &lt;br /&gt;From West Haven I 95 to Exit 38 veer left towards &lt;br /&gt;The Merritt Parkway that later becomes the &lt;br /&gt;Hutchinson River Parkway to Exit 26 West on to &lt;br /&gt;I 287 West and I 87. Take exit 15 to get off I 87 &lt;br /&gt;To stay on I 287. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(FYI Exit 55 has a Wendys or Burger King if you need a break. &lt;br /&gt;The Burger King is closer to the High Way Ramp.) &lt;br /&gt;Exit 39B to Rte 10 W towards Dover. &lt;br /&gt;Exit on to Dryden Way. &lt;br /&gt;Left on Campus Drive. &lt;br /&gt;Left on Hilton Ct. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pay attention to turns. &lt;br /&gt;I had missed a turn and had to go back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can Park in the Building Complex on the Left. &lt;br /&gt;Short Walk to the Hilton Hotel beyond the Pond on the &lt;br /&gt;Right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To answer the question of what is Chiller Con? &lt;br /&gt;Chiiller Con has a few things happening; various vendors are selling their products such as DVDs or Model Figurines or Magazines or Autographed Photos, etc. &lt;br /&gt;Newer Genre or B Movie Stars are there to promote their most recent genre movies. &lt;br /&gt;Elder stars come out of their retirement to meet their fans. &lt;br /&gt;Wrestlers, Writers, Artists and other kinds of entertainers also come out to meet their fans. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The October Show has the fans dressed up in all kinds of costumes, esp. &lt;br /&gt;but not limited to Goth outfits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is usually lots of fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring your cameras. &lt;br /&gt;A listing of stars / guests will also come in handy. &lt;br /&gt;There might be long lines to get some autographs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Expo is all weekend from Friday, Oct 30 to &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Nov 1. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am going on Saturday, Oct 31. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If more than one vehicle is going, then the passengers should &lt;br /&gt;Share phone numbers in case the different vehicles have &lt;br /&gt;To contact each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Suspense Day for Ordering Tickets for the Saturday Show is on &lt;br /&gt;October 16th. I will probably be mailing my order around Oct. 3rd &lt;br /&gt;So that I will get my tickets in plenty of time to go to the Saturday Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Send all payments to: &lt;br /&gt;Chiller Theatre, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;P O Box 23 &lt;br /&gt;Rutherford NJ 07070&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chillertheatre.com/c4tickets.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chillerthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.chillertheatre.com/c4tickets.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B &lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will meet Maribeth and her guests at the Expo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257189421000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Coffee Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>coffee-397</urlname><id>570343</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Coffee Talk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249616757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee Talkers Haunt Halloween Chiller Theater Expo from 10/31 to 11/1 </name><id>11056145</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257015600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/coffee-397/events/11056145/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/3/global_1719779.jpeg</photo_url></item>