<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>cross street Center between Chapel and Crown</address_2><address_1>76 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (203) 562-2511</phone><name>Bentara</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1077533</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924828</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Designers - for August we have a great meetup planned.  See the description below, and check out www.structuralgraphics.com to get a taste of the super-cool stuff that will be presented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP - thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: August 1, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Time: 5.45PM - 8PM&lt;br /&gt;Place: Bentara, New Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erik Hluchan and Geoff Matheson, designers from Structural Graphics, will speak about dimensional and package design, and show examples of incredible dimensional marketing solutions created by Structural Graphics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Structural Graphics is the nation's leading designer and producer of high-impact dimensional marketing solutions. They create revolutionary paper solutions for top companies and marketing firms. Their capabilities include paper engingeering, 3D special effects, lenticulars, sound modules and light, plus every job is hand assembled. Some of S.G.'s clients include: BMW, Volkswagen, Ford, HBO, Nickelodeon, Smirnoff, Chase Manhattan, Citibank, Microsoft, Samsung, CIA, among many others. S.G. has done work for large companies in almost every industry, with a large client base in the pharmaceutical industry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erik has worked for S.G. for almost 20 years and is currently the creative director. He is responsible for many of S.G.'s innovative and revolutionary designs. Geoff Matheson just started at S.G. 6 months ago, and is a production artist. Geoff is part of the GNH group and thought the group should be introduced to the amazing work done at S.G.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will discuss how a dimensional design is created, and the steps it goes through from conception to completion. This includes the initial comps created for a potential job, and the following preliminary comps, die drawings, dies and final hand assembled materials, all of which are main stages on the project timeline. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will bring samples from Structural Graphics to hand out and discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to www.structuralgraphics.com to view some of the work Structural Graphics produces. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186177932000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184162749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GNH Design August Meetup - Structural Graphics</name><id>6006786</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186004700000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/6006786/</event_url></item>