<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hear Beethoven's Ninth Symphony at Tanglewood, Sunday August 24th at 2:30 pm.  Guest conductor Christoph von Dohnányi leads the Boston Symphony Orchestra, Tanglewood Festival Chorus and soloists in Beethoven's Ninth Symphony. (August 24)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Hi -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If possible let's meet between 12:30 and 1:00 by the ticket booths.  I will have blueballoons and you can call my cell phone - 617-780-0429. We can find out if people want to sit onthe lawn $19 (bring blankets) or under the shelter $28.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling : Please write the drivers closest to your area.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Chris can take 3 (Roslindale)&lt;br /&gt;Tom can take 4 or 5 max from West Roxbury.&lt;br /&gt;Roberta and Bill have full cars.&lt;br /&gt;I can take 3 if leaving on Saturday and staying overnight (flying in Friday so want to break up the drive)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For meals if you want to pre-order a box lunch, see the Meals-To-Go page at tanglewood.org; &lt;a href="http://www.bso.org/bso/mods/content1.jsp?id=32100002" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bso.org/bs...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the link doesn't work, you can browse to it from tanglewood.org: &amp;quot;Dining at Tanglewood&amp;quot; (left side), scroll to the Meals-To-Go Menu (about 2/3 down the page) and select the specific performance and the type of meal you want (prices range from $19.95 for a &amp;quot;bag lunch&amp;quot; for one, to $103 for a classy lunch with wine for two; Then click &amp;quot;select food option&amp;quot; at the bottom, and you can enter the quantity and the specific selection (e.g. &amp;quot;flavor&amp;quot; of sandwich) and complete your purchase online.  I believe they have to be ordered at least 48 hours in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take care, Susan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----&lt;br /&gt; Previous comments: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please write in and say if you could drive (I think every rider could contribute $5 for gas - does that sound fine?) A couple people I've met don't have cars, so those who do, please say so when you have time. Best, Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will have blue balloons again (that  float this time) near ticket booths.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan C</member_name><member_id>6899147</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219800587000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213660375000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beethoven's 9th at Tanglewood on the Lawn</name><id>8155014</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219595400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/8155014/</event_url></item>