<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>500 College St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.310863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Woolsey Hall</name><city>New Haven</city><id>224202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.926000</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>HURRY TICKETS GO FAST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yale Symphony Orchestra presents &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;VIDEO GAMES LIVE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 31st, 2007 - 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Woolsey Hall, New Haven CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-Show Festival: 4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Concert: 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To buy tickets go here &lt;a href="http://purchase.tickets.com/buy/TicketPurchase?agency=SHUBERT_CAPA&amp;amp;pid=5903950" target="_blank"&gt;http://purchase.ticke...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First video game concert in New Haven!! &lt;br /&gt;Tickets went on sale Friday, December 15th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Video Games Live is an immersive concert event featuring music from the biggest video games of all time including such beloved and popular franchises as Mario?, Zelda®, Halo®, Final Fantasy®, Kingdom Hearts, Warcraft®, Myst®, Sonic?, Metal Gear Solid®, Tron, God of War?, Civilization IV and many more! There's even a special retro Classic Arcade Medley featuring over 20+ games from Pong® to Donkey Kong® including such classics as Dragon's Lair, Tetris, Frogger, Gauntlet, Space Invaders &amp;amp; Outrun! The Yale Symphony Orchestra and Choir will be performing along with exclusive video footage and music arrangements, synchronized lighting, solo performers, electronic percussionists, live action and unique interactive segments to create an explosive one-of-a-kind entertainment experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special events surrounding the show, include a pre-show festival where all guests will enjoy interactive game demos, a costume contest, game competitions, pre-released games and the very popular meet-and-greet with top game composers and designers from all over the world!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you or someone you know is into video games you won't want to miss out on this historic video game industry event! Or maybe you are looking for something cultural and exciting that the whole family will enjoy? Video Games Live is not just a concert, but a celebration of the entire video game industry that people of all ages will adore. Whether it's the power and passion of the more recent blockbusters or the excitement of nostalgic sentimental classics you played growing up, Video Games Live? is sure to be a hit with gamers aand non-gamers alike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.videogameslive.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.videogames...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175824549000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1170349802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TICKETS GO FAST - videogames, symphony, multimedia, contests</name><id>5443836</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175371200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5443836/</event_url></item>