<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Love takes courage and integrity. So, you loved, you gave, you cherished and shared everything. You opened your heart and let someone in, sharing your deepest joys and sorrows, daring to let another into your experience; then things changed. They left, or they found someone else, or you did. The grief of a broken heart allows for either new insights to open or a closing down to the flow of life and love ever moving through again. Mother Clare Watts, Christian Master Teacher, will guide you to keeping your heart open through what can feel like a tremendous task in order to stay connected and real with the people around you. Come, heal your heart and live again.&lt;br /&gt;**************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Mother Clare&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the Sophia Peace Center. She is the author of &lt;i&gt;Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237160259000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236360001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healing a Broken Heart</name><id>9896710</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236987000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9896710/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/e/global_7563742.jpeg</photo_url></item>