<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.misteriosos.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://misteriosos.org/space/snowmen.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's join hundreds of others on the Boston Common and build snow men - and women :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A firm date has not been set as yet and I will update the event as soon as I know, or you can subscribe to their mailing list to be notified. As we never really know when the big snow is really coming the date will not be revealed till the previous night, and so I might not get it to you till the next morning - So the best thing to do is watch for snow, lots on a Saturday or Sunday coming up and then check your email the night before and the first thing those days to find out if it is happening that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS You can click on the picture above to read the following on their website as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;From the: Banditos Misteriosos&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aloha Banditos!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ll notice we used the word “aloha,” because now that it’s wintertime in our fair city, we’re attempting mind over matter. If we talk and dress like we’re in warmer climate, we won’t be so cold… right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok...so a quick step outside makes it clear that New England weather cannot be conquered by mere nice, warm thoughts.  And thus it is with pride that Banditos Misteriosos announces our Build-a-Snowmandito!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is pretty straight forward, our goal is to make a garden of snowmen in the middle of the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But we’re going to try something different with this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since building a snowman depends on well, snow, the exact date of Snowmandito will all depend on the weather.   Thus, instead of picking a date and announcing the location the night before, we're going to tell you the location and announce the date the night before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully weather will co-operate and everything will fall in line!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date:&lt;br /&gt;The event will be on a Saturday or Sunday after a particularly good snowfall. We’ll send an email on the Friday or Saturday before. Be prepared!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Boston Common (exact section TBD)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snowman décor:&lt;br /&gt;Bring whatever you want to decorate your snowman – corncob pipe, top hat, carrot… you name it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to do when you get there:&lt;br /&gt;Start building your snowman! Work in groups or go solo.  Spread the word, the more snowmen the better.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contest:&lt;br /&gt;Snowmen are a work of art, thus there will be a Best-in-Showmandito contest.  Exact details will be announced at the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, spread the word, we hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;3,&lt;br /&gt;Misteriosos&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://misteriosos.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://misteriosos.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_______________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;Events mailing list&lt;br /&gt;Events@lists.misteriosos.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lists.misteriosos.org/listinfo.cgi/events-misteriosos.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://lists.misterio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign by the concession stand</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265026283000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262667209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowman Building with Banditos Misteriosos</name><id>12225925</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264852800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/12225925/</event_url></item>