<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:30 on Wednesday night, so let's meet by 7:00 right outside the theater doors (or right inside if it's raining).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to TGI Fridays with whoever wants to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lesley has also asked if anyone wants to go out to dinner BEFORE the movie (like, meet at 5:30 or 6:00?). So if you'd like to do that, just put a comment in your RSVP that you're game and Lesley will contact you with details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't like Sandra Bullock or Ryan Reynolds? Well, they're teaming up in a cute romantic comedy called &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/summer-movies/the-proposal/1810012112" target="_blank"&gt;The Proposal&lt;/a&gt;. Let's go see it together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Book editor Maggie is everyone's worst nightmare: ruthless, selfish, driven, and tactless. But when a problem with her Visa could potentially send her back to Canada and destroy her all-important career, she comes up with a solution on the spur of the moment: marry her much younger (but all-American) assistant. Unfortunately, the government is understandably suspicious, and so the two faux lovers must embark on a humiliating charade in order to make the marriage seem legitimate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for The Proposal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247007316000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244003729000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Proposal</name><id>10563193</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246489200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10563193/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>