<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372444</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 491 9400</phone><name>Legal Seafoods Outdoor Bar</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>730460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.123748</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Surely nerds pine fondly for the times when intellectual snobs were all the rage around academia!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topics might be: the applied philosophy of the couch potato, (based on GB Shaw!); does Evolution theory imply that humans are the most advanced monkey? Isn't time travel not just possible, but already happening, since we go forth second-by-second? What ash-cloud disruption? Should humans be flying in the first place? And other FUN provocative ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU DON'T NEED TO BE AN INTELLECTUAL TO COME. Just bring your opinions or questions about matters of truth &amp;amp; consequence, and be willing to listen to others. (&amp;quot;Of consequence&amp;quot; here, would not include, say, whether Brittney Spears' magazine photos should be airbrushed or not). &lt;br /&gt;AND: YOU ARE WELCOME TO FAKE IT! a lot of people, including in academia, are really good at this, you just need to bring along an aloof attitude full of irony ...for recommendations I recommend ehow.com, &amp;quot;how to become a pseudo intellectual&amp;quot;. &amp;quot;FAKE MOUSTACHES WELCOME&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE MEET AT THE LEGAL SEAFOOD PATIO in front of the Charles Hotel in Harvard Sq.; in case of sun, there are open umbrellas directed skyward. There is also a bar. Large-size round-table seating is usually not hard to accomplish, and there isn't the pressure to order food; but if you want to order appetizer platters the menu is really reasonably priced. The menu is light fare Raw Bar style, not a full restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;If it is raining we meet just inside the Charles Hotel at the Noir bar &amp;amp; go from there.&lt;br /&gt;For those who arrive early please graciously try to help reserve some table space for later arrivals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Street parking in Cambridge on Sundays is &amp;quot;unrestricted&amp;quot;. Parking is also available at the Charles Hotel garage, ask Legal Seafood to validate your parking ticket for a partial discount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Sq. is easily T-accessible via the Red Line subway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have further ideas, please post them. Wall &amp;quot;discussions&amp;quot; for this Meetup are encouraged!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email cell phone number to Yes and Maybe RSVPs the day of.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1274399271000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272746544000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intellectual Snob Revival Night</name><id>13351522</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274045400000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13351522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/d/global_2910317.jpeg</photo_url></item>