<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1228 Riverdale St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.137860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>On The Border Mexican Grill</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>669419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.625950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, please choose one of the following two books and join us for a great conversation about what you have read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;While finishing the book of your choice is always recommended it is not required.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Choices for March 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Help ~ Kathryn Stockett&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starred Review. What perfect timing for this optimistic, uplifting debut novel (and maiden publication of Amy Einhorn's new imprint) set during the nascent civil rights movement in Jackson, Miss., where black women were trusted to raise white children but not to polish the household silver. Eugenia Skeeter Phelan is just home from college in 1962, and, anxious to become a writer, is advised to hone her chops by writing about what disturbs you. The budding social activist begins to collect the stories of the black women on whom the country club sets relies and mistrusts enlisting the help of Aibileen, a maid who's raised 17 children, and Aibileen's best friend Minny, who's found herself unemployed more than a few times after mouthing off to her white employers. The book Skeeter puts together based on their stories is scathing and shocking, bringing pride and hope to the black community, while giving Skeeter the courage to break down her personal boundaries and pursue her dreams. Assured and layered, full of heart and history, this one has bestseller written all over it. (Feb.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Married Adventure: The Lives of Martin and Osa Johnson ~ Osa Johnson&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Osa Johnson's travel adventures and explorations come across as vibrantly today as they did when they were written in 1940. They're richer now with the added perspective of history, and the added wealth of Martin Johnson's photographs of charging elephants, reposing lions, and head hunters roasting heads, marshmallow-like, over a campfire. The life the Johnsons led was nothing like the life Osa expected. From 1917 to 1937 she and Martin were visiting and filming cannibals in the New Hebrides, orangutans in Borneo, and the rich gamut of wildlife available on safari in Kenya and the Congo. Osa led a life the likes of which won't be seen again, and she tells a good story, too.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272071824000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258992399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Discussion: The Help &amp; I Married Adventure</name><id>11938793</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269986400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/11938793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/c/global_13318044.jpeg</photo_url></item>