<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a posting from another meetup group who invited our group to join them.  If anyone is interested in going sign up so I know how many.  We can arrange carpools as it gets closer.    It sounds like fun.  If it's something people are interested in we can always plan one at a beach nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event was such a relaxing, fun and social success last year, we decided to keep it going!!! THIS EVENT IS ONE NOT TO MISS! Last year we had over 200 people from all over &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at the beach AGAIN on Friday, July 10, as we'll be joining multiple Meetup groups to mingle right on the beach (!) by Seaside Johnnies in Rye, New York! JOIN US! We'll be the crazy bunch of folks squishing our toes in the sand, sharing wine, food and laughter right in front of the First Aid Station smack dab in the middle of the beach. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a blanket or chair, food and beverage to nosh on, and be prepared to chill, laugh and make new friendships in the awesome backdrop of Playland Amusement Park. Lets kick back for a different kind of mingling fun &amp;quot;oohing and aahing&amp;quot; together over a spectacular display of vibrant fireworks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note, this event is &amp;quot;weather permitting&amp;quot; so be sure to check your e-mail and/or circle back to this event post at 3 p.m. on the day of the event to check the status! Parking at the Seaside Johnnies/Oakland Beach parking lot is just $5 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions to the Seaside Johnnies location in Rye, check the following link: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;:)Seaside Johnnies &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're looking forward to another unique and awesome night! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO OAKLAND BEACH PARKING LOT (AND TO OUR MEETING SPOT) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Bronx, Pelham, New Rochelle, Larchmont &lt;br /&gt;Take 95 North ( The New England Thruway ) to Exit 19 which is the Rye Playland Exit. You will get on Playland Parkway to Forest Avenue which is just in front of Playland. At Forest Avenue you will make a Right and take that to Dearborn Avenue where you will make a Left into the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;Take 95 South to Exit 19 which is the Rye Playland Exit. You will get on Playland Parkway to Forest Avenue which is just in front of Playland. At Forest Avenue you will make a Right and take that to Dearborn Avenue where you will make a Left into the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the other side of Westchester ( i.e. Dobbs Ferry ) and Northern Westchester ( i.e. Armonk ) &lt;br /&gt;Take 287 West to the New England Thruway ( 95 South ) to Exit 19 which is the Rye Playland Exit. You will get on Playland Parkway to Forest Avenue which run in front of Playland. At Forest Avenue you will make a Right and take that to Dearborn Avenue where you will make a Left into the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming locally - a la Boston Post Road &lt;br /&gt;Going North on Boston Post Road. Go to the light at Oakland Beach Avenue and make a Right - go straight until you can go no further at which point you will make a right and then the first Left and then enter the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going South on Boston Post Road. Go to Oakland Beach Avenue and make a Left hand turn - go straight until you can go no further at which point you will make a right and then the first Left and then enter the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO THE MEETING SPOT ON THE BEACH FROM SEASIDE JOHNNIES PARKING LOT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you park in the lot, walk down to the beach. The entrance to the beach is just to the left of Seaside Johnnies. When you enter the beach, walk to the left. We will be by the lifeguard stand near the jetty.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"Look for the massive group by the first aid station"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret</member_name><member_id>7957111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247438490000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245355157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multi-Group Meetup Picnic and Fireworks on the Beach. Rye, NY </name><id>10682505</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247265000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/10682505/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/0/global_8204688.jpeg</photo_url></item>