<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Middletown</address_2><address_1>85 Miner Hill Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miner Hill Golf Course</name><city>Middletown</city><id>567976</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><fee><label>4 Lessons -$100 Online</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>$140 day of lesson</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Golf 101 Lessons for New Golfers - Learn From The Pros!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctgolftips.com/Golf101" target="_blank"&gt;CTGolfTips.com&lt;/a&gt; invites us to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 provides the beginner Golfer everything they need to get started on &lt;br /&gt;the course, and the skills and foundation to improve their game&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf is not only a very popular fun and challenging sport, it is also very important in the business world. Many important deals are made on the Golf Course! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;All Golf Clubs, Golf Balls, Driving Range fees, Golf Course fees and Equipment are included!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Please DO NOT RSVP until you pay for the lessons because space is limited&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting with the basics of Golf, you will learn how the game is played, terminology, technique, strategy, and skills to make you a competitive Golfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A CTGolfTips.com Pro will start out by teaching you about Golf, your swing, and technique. After that, it is on to the Golf Course for additional instruction and coaching, to help you improve your game while you are playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This combination of the basics, swing development and practice, and then playing lessons has shown to be extremely effective in developing a good Golfing technique. Playing lessons can help problems that don't appear during regular Golf Lessons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Golf 101 classes are kept small to ensure personal attention.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Golf 101 course consist of 4 sessions, one session per week. All Golf equipment will be provided, or feel free to bring your own clubs because it is better to practice with the equipment you will be using on the course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have never played Golf before, or if you need a complete, balanced, and effective refresher course, Golf 101 will get you on the Golf Course, and teach you to be a competitive Golfer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each lesson starts with 30 minutes of warm-up including stretching, putting &lt;br /&gt;and chipping -or hitting a bucket at the driving range (optional)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class size is limited, and is only $100 for 4 lessons for 6 hours ($17/hour) online or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Your 4 Golf 101 Lessons are:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday May 27 -6:30pm to 8:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday June 3 -6:30pm to 8:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday June 10 -6:30pm to 8:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Tuesday June 17 -6:30pm to 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any space remains, Golf 101 is $140 for 4 lessons ($35/lesson) at the Golf course -call ahead for availability (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pay with Credit Card, click on Paypal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minor Hill is located on 80 Minor Hill Drive, Middletown, CT 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit 20 off 91(Country Club Road), 1 mile from exit and easy to find&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miner Hills Golf Course and Practice Facility is not only a great place for the beginning Golfer,  but an excellent spot for anyone to sharpen their skills. Middletown's only golf course is affordable, comfortable and challenging!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facilities include a practice green, driving range, and a Par 30 executive course. This hidden gem is now being discovered as a most relaxed place to take your game to the next level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com/Golf101" target="_blank"&gt;www.CTGolfTips.com/Golf101&lt;/a&gt; for more info&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.CTGolfTips.com/PlayBetterGolf" target="_blank"&gt; Play Better Golf and Improve Your Score is also available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See You On The Course!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us in the white www.CTGolfTips.com hats</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212119191000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209348877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Golf 101 Lessons for New Golfers - Learn From The Pros! </name><id>7825152</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211927400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/7825152/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/d/global_3724573.jpeg</photo_url></item>