<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP and &lt;i&gt;only sign up for one or two mini-meetups a month&lt;/i&gt;.  See this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt; for more details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Cribbage is an old-fashioned card game with you keep track of your points by moving around a board.  It also requires you to be able to count and do basic math. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an elimination style tournament for 8 people.  The top 3 or 4 players will receive prizes (small, nothing too fancy).  As people get eliminated, we will have King's Cribbage and other related card or board games for people to play.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers are of course welcome, but keep in mind there are some talented cribbage people in this group that will be kicking butt and taking names as this is a tournament.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other than that, this is pretty straight forward, so I shouldn't have to describe it that much. ;-)  But feel free to message me with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Food theme:&lt;br /&gt;The theme for this event will be &amp;quot;cheese &amp;amp; wine&amp;quot;.  Interpret that however you want.  If your diet does not allow for these, feel free to bring something else.  The theme is just meant to be classy and dainty foods and we will have generic drinks and snacks on hand.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;About the location:&lt;br /&gt;This event will be guest-hosted by another member's home in Salem who is graciously donating their space.  Details will be sent out to the YES RSVP's a couple days before the event.  There will be plenty of room and should be a warm, comfortable place for all, I promise.  There will be two cats on the premises, but they will be upstairs and away from people participating in the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294596450000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291578248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Cribbage Tournament</name><id>15649067</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294513200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15649067/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>