<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.permaculturenursery.com/jonathan_bananas.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Jonathan Bates of Food Forest Farm and The Permaculture Plant Nursery returns to Portland for one day only to help us on our way into the world of &lt;strong&gt;propagating plants&lt;/strong&gt; AND lead us through a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on demonstration of planting an Edible Forest Garden&lt;/strong&gt; using many of the plants we'll be discussing. &amp;nbsp;Plus: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/messages/boards/thread/22233182"&gt;Pick-up your pre-ordered plants from Food Forest Farm that Jonathan will bring (delivery no charge).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why learn to propagate your own plants?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save money!&lt;/strong&gt; Learn to use various methods that are free or inexpensive to populate your landscape with productive, multi-function plantings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Produce more food!&lt;/strong&gt; Most of the plantings we'll talk about are food-producing among other things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Become a resource in your community&lt;/strong&gt; for plants and plant materials - very important for maintaining biological diversity and plant genetics being crowded out by consolidation of plant varieties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Become a neighborhood permaculture plant nursery!&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;We need these up and down the state to assist our friends and neighbors in the creation of edible perennial ecosystems that have the ability to feed humans and non-humans alike, indefinitely. &amp;nbsp;Jonathan can speak to this topic better than almost anyone in the Northeast!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10:00 &amp;nbsp;Opening/Coffee/Tea/Introductions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10:15 &amp;nbsp;Introduction to Propagation and Various Techniques&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11:00 &amp;nbsp;Tools of the trade and examples of plants that have been propagated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:00 &amp;nbsp;Demonstration/Practice if time allows&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:30 &amp;nbsp;Closing and Discussion of Resources for further practice/study&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;POTLUCK LUNCH (bring a dish to share and your own potluck kit)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1:30 &amp;nbsp;Introducing Forest Garden Concept (Like a forest, not "in" a forest:)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2:00 - 3:30 &amp;nbsp;Planting a demonstration forest garden (Demo and hands-on) with permaculture plants in designed polycultures&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3:45-ish Closing + Pickup Pre-Ordered Plants&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More about Jonathan:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jonathan runs Food Forest Farm Permaculture Nursery, a source for useful, edible, hard to find plants and seeds. He&amp;rsquo;s been studying, creating and working with rural and urban gardens in the Connecticut River Valley for the last ten years, and is a co-designer and inhabitant of an edible forest garden in Holyoke, MA.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1338338261000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333490434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Propagating Your Own Permaculture Plants &amp; Planting a Forest Garden</name><id>59122512</id><duration>21600000</duration><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338127200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/59122512/</event_url></item>