<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Linden Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01907</zip><lat>42.479916</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781.596.3594 </phone><name>Jacobson's</name><city>Swampscott</city><id>1445352</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.894173</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>LIVING FOODS HOLIDAY POTLUCK&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, December 19th &lt;br /&gt;1:00pm-4:00pm &lt;br /&gt;69 Linden Ave, Swampscott, MA 01907   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll make something special for you, and you please bring a raw food dish large enough to serve 6-8 people. Some ideas include a salad, appetizer, soup or desert... just keep it raw. :) There are tons of recipes on the internet. We'll be having a great time of sharing ideas, trying new foods and spreading the word about healthy living! Decide to feel great, get energy, share your health tips and experiences, and a great raw and living foods meal with friends right here on the North Shore! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP to Leah Jacobson: leahj3k@gmail.com or 781.596.3594  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to call with any questions.... see you then J  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rt. 128 - Exit 25 to Marblehead, Follow 114 to 1A to Vinnin Square.  Left at Vinnin Square intersection.  2nd left to Linden, 4th house on the left, two story. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North - Take 93 South to 128 N. Follow directions above.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South - 93 North to exit 37 to 128 N. Follow directions above.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston - Take 1A all the way up, straight through lots of towns, lights.  After about 20-25 mins road curves right when you hit Lynn (don't go straight at that point to Salem).  Enter rotary, pass entrance to nahant on right.  Go straight on Lynn Shore Drive (water will be on your right the whole time).  Road curves alot (enjoy it!!!). After water ends stay straight (you'll be on Humphrey). Pass Cindy's Pizza on Rt. (no stopping off it's not worth it ;)) you'll come to a little island, bear left, continuing on Humphrey.  At blinking yellow light take a left onto Salem St. Take 3rd riight onto Linden. I'm fourth house on the left 69.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;__________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;We would like to invite you to attend this pot luck to share food and friendship and to have some fun. We'll have a great time sharing ideas, trying new foods and spreading the word about healthful living! Decide to feel great, get energy, share your health tips and experiences and a great raw and living foods meal with friends right here on the north shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Raw Potluck:&lt;/b&gt; All attending are requested to bring a 100% raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based (vegan with no honey) ready-to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people. You do not have to be a gourmet chef to attend; just bring a dish that you like. Please bring a typed or neatly printed recipe to display next to your dish ideally with copies for people to take with them if they so choose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This document explains what is and isn't raw vegan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/587600/Raw_Vegan_Food_List_v6.doc"&gt;files.meetup.com/587600/Raw_Vegan_Food_List_v6.doc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ideas for Raw Vegan Dish (without honey):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;1. organic green salad, &lt;br /&gt;2. raw recipe from online, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com/phpbb2/"&gt;www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com/phpbb2/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.living-foods.com/recipes"&gt;www.living-foods.com/recipes &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://goneraw.com/recipes"&gt;goneraw.com/recipes &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm"&gt;www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawfoodlife.com/Raw_Resources/Raw_Food_Recipes/raw_food_recipes.html"&gt;www.rawfoodlife.com/Raw_Resources/Raw_Food_Recipes/raw_food_recipes.html &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes"&gt;www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm"&gt;www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;3. raw recipe from a raw food book, or&lt;br /&gt;4. organic fruit salad.&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Best Regards, &lt;br /&gt;Daryl&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294555458000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291743688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck: Swampscott, MA; Sun. Dec. 19th 1-4PM</name><id>15668412</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292781600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/15668412/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/2/global_20109682.jpeg</photo_url></item>