<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Bonvini Drive </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.318573</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name> Playschool </name><city>Framingham </city><id>12575782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449524</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will gain a better understanding of how spirituality enhances your children's life and how you can play a major role in helping your children grow with kindness and respect. You will leave this workshop with practical tools. This workshop is interactive and all denominations and faiths are welcomed to participate. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 $25 individual ~ $40 per couple &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This seminar will be presented by Rev. Christine Doucet, director of The center of Light-Boston, a spiritual Center for meditation and mysticism. Rev Christine has been serving as a Priest and Youth Minister since 2006. In her professional life, she was a nurse-midwife for over 10 years in France, her native country and currently works for the Center for Families in Cambridge, Ma., where she teaches parent/child classes and runs family support groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rev. Christine also holds certifications as a massage therapist, specializing in infant message and recently graduated from The Infant-Parent Mental Health Postgraduate program at The University of Massachusetts. She resides in Cambridge, Ma with her husband and teenaged son. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For more information of to register feel free to contact Rev. Christine Doucet at &lt;br /&gt;

 671-794-8208 or Helen Marie Jensen  (Playschool Director) at 508-308-7401&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365213790000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364826683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Parenting From the Heart: How to bring Spirituality into your  children’s life</name><id>112060452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365202800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/112060452/</event_url></item>