<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>68 Jackson Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.395514</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>Rev.Christine's Home</name><city>North-Cambridge</city><id>729576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135557</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This class is the third one of the series. However, you can still join us and make up this class at the next session. here is more info about this course on Meditation and Christian Mysticism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever ask yourself why you are on this earth? What is life about? And is there more?&lt;br /&gt;If yes, this course is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a powerful 6-week introductory course designed for modern mystics. Classes will include teachings on: the Inner Spiritual Path, Meditation, Soul, Light, Prayer and Blessing. Time will be spent teaching the principles of meditation that will allow you to move deeper than the body, beyond thinking and emotions, and into the reality of God's peace and presence within. In each class we explore three areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Understanding the cosmos, the Laws and Beings that govern it, and our roles as living, conscious humans in that cosmos&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Spiritual exercises designed to help you develop skills needed for inner work&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Hands-on experiences, through which you can learn to see, hear, and feel the spiritual world&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This course is free of charge, as are all of our classes. This class will be taught by Rev. Christine in her home in Cambridge. Possibility of childcare available upon request only.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ring the bell of the front door. The house is green with a driveway on the side you can park</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272675496000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270469268000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Another session of the free course on Meditation and Christian Mysticism </name><id>msvjnyngblc</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272494700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/13089312/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/7/global_5061495.jpeg</photo_url></item>