<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Jeff Moroski, Software Consultant at &lt;a href="http://www.CynergySystems.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cynergy Systems&lt;/a&gt;, will lead a discussion on the usage of Adobe Flex with Java.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Jeff says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I'll give a brief overview of Rich Internet Applications (RIA) as a lead in to a Flex overview.  From there I'll mention the technologies available to Flex for communicating with the server, and of those choices, Blaze will be what we focus on.  I'll do a Blaze overview and then get to the meat of the presentation: an example of Flex and Java communicating through a Blaze services layer.  I'll be using the Spring-Blaze project and the application will probably be something related to beer (info and brewing more so that consumption tracking).&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presentations/discussions are held at MIT's EHS Office, 265 Massachusetts Ave, upstairs from the MIT Museum; the office is on the 4th floor of the building; please use the door that is noted in the following picture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/johnarch/2341265278/sizes/m/" target="_blank"&gt;presentation location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the presentation we will head over to The Asgard, a restaurant/bar at the corner of Mass Ave and Sidney Street (350 Mass Ave):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=350+massachusetts+avenue,+cambridge,+ma&amp;amp;sll=42.366487,-71.098816&amp;amp;sspn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;g=Massachusetts+Ave+%26+Sidney+St,+Cambridge,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02139,+United+States&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.366963,-71.097186&amp;amp;spn=0.008815,0.022745&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;cbll=42.362981,-71.099593&amp;amp;panoid=VqQEj12CG6gv-yL4iXehHQ&amp;amp;cbp=1,178.60443018981482,,0,-0.8543880653277005" target="_blank"&gt;asgard location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past, some of you may have parked your car in the lot adjacent to my building, but unfortunately the lot has since become a 24-hour tow zone for non-MIT vehicles. There is usually parking on Windsor street alongside my building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our meetings are personal, engaging and everybody is sharing in the topic at hand. Come and share your experience with your peers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.: Thank you to the many members that RSVP (one way or another). This helps your humble organizer to manage the crowd at the venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>take eleveator to 4th floor &amp;&amp; look for meetup signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Archambault</member_name><member_id>2399674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240875053000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235435727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java March Meetup: Flex with Java</name><id>9807491</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237242600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/9807491/</event_url></item>