<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.864841</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>King Richard's Faire</name><city>Carver</city><id>7786002</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.755196</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entertainment, exciting rides and skilled games abound on the King Richard’s Faire’s enchanted 80-acre site. Hundreds of talented entertainers perform non-stop throughout the day. Visit any of their eight vivid stages and be enthralled by acrobats, aerialists, jugglers, minstrels, dancers, fire eaters, puppeteers and even exotic tigers. Witness the rare Liger, beautiful white lion and cute tiger cubs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll gasp as the King’s mounted knight’s battle on horseback, and laugh as bawdy beggars compete in mud. Strolling performers will engage you all day long as you frolic in our forest and try your skill at our Gaming Glen.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Epicurean pleasures will tantalize your taste buds with the Faire’s unbelievable choices of truly scrumptious treats. Satiate your palate with spit-roasted giant turkey legs, boules of chowder and stew, ringlets of fryes, champagne, wine and brew!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discover over 100 talented artisans who journey from all over the country to display and hawk their magnificent wares. You will be delighted and intrigued by the fantastic glass blowing, portrait painting, hand-spun pottery, sword making, fabulous jewelry, leather and armor, period clothing, moccasins, perfumes and scented oils, face painting, and physic readings.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Tickets: 27.00 at the gate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Carpooling:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  I can fit up to 5 people in my car including me.  If you want to come with me please include it in the notes when you sign up.  Meet me in Kmart plaza in Hyannis at &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;10:30 am&lt;/span&gt; if you are coming with me. (you will be contacted prior to so no worries so you know how to find me)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Otherwise, if you want to go on your own, we will meet near the ticket gate in front of the faire at noon!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350242067000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340062342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kings Richard Faire</name><id>69740542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350230400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/69740542/</event_url></item>