<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2392 Whitney Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06518</zip><lat>41.384387</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-287-1101</phone><name>Eli's on Whitney</name><city>Hamden</city><id>834675</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.901948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Hello everyone - I know that we all love good food and drink, and we all love helping children and families.  I am proud to announce an event where these values are not mutually exclusive! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Richard Manware Humanitarian Award Event is an annual spring event, this year hosted by News Channel 8's Ted Koppy and honoring Adam Francis and Kathy Busch in recognition of their charitable efforts to improve the lives of children.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&amp;quot;The Richard Manware Humanitarian Award is given each year to individuals who have made significant achievements toward protecting and promoting the interests of vulnerable children, women and families.   Past admired award recipients have included author and teacher/volunteer Wally Lamb, activist Naomi Wolf and domestic violence researchers Evan Stark and Anne Flitcraft.  Each year, this event attracts businesses, organizations and individuals that value philanthropy and want to ‘give back’ to their community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are thrilled to be presenting the 2009 Award to Adam Francis and Kathy Busch, community members who until now have gone unrecognized for their continued charitable efforts in support of the children at CCCC. Ted Koppy, News Channel 8 Co-Anchor will moderate this special program, which seeks to raise consciousness about our community’s troubled families and increase awareness about the intervention, prevention and empowerment programs available to them. &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;The Coordinating Council for Children in Crisis (CCCC) &lt;a href="http://www.ccccnh.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ccccnh.org...&lt;/a&gt;) is an amazing new haven based organization which “works to prevent abuse, neglect and victimization across the life span and to serve those affected by providing home visiting and outreach, parenting education, family strengthening activities, counseling and advocacy to children and adults.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHC has done events with them before, so I’m happy to post this event as well.  (In full disclosure, the director of this great non-profit is my mother, Cheryl Burack.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fundraiser was originally $40 a ticket, for two hours of open bar and hors d'oeuvres.  However, there are still some tickets left.  Based on the interest and support that we’ve shown them in the past, they have invited us to attend at a discounted rate of only $30 (Cash only, please.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think this event should be a lot of fun, and it will support a great cause. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell will be in my RSVP.  Please join me at this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239057778000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238436516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>(Charity Fundraiser) at Eli's with open bar and hors d'oeuvres!</name><id>10071083</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238707800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/10071083/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/6/global_7909702.jpeg</photo_url></item>