<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Sorry to say that since we only have 2 people RSVP yes I'm cancelling this meetup. If folks have ideas for topics, activities, please be in touch.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi gang,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE NEW DAY, LOCATION for our next meetup: Tuesday, March 10 at Tavern on the Square in Porter Square, 1815 Mass Ave. There's a parking lot immediately behind the building with validation. It's also one block away from the Porter Square Redline stop. I moved the day to Tuesday since Monday is trivia night both at this location and at Redline. What's up with that, one wonders?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to those who showed up to the Darwin Day bash, quite the crowd. No shortage of Darwinites in Cambridge obviously.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For March I thought we could apply our naturalistic perspective to Jonathan Haidt's assertion that Obama should include conservative aspects of morality in his agenda, see &lt;a href="http://www.prospect-magazine.co.uk/article_details.php?id=10583" target="_blank"&gt;Obama's moral majority&lt;/a&gt;.  Haidt says &amp;quot;President Obama has a unique opportunity to unite Americans behind him and redefine liberalism. But if he is to succeed, he must find a new political language—and broaden the moral register of the political left.&amp;quot;  Must he?  We can also discuss the prospects for naturalism under the new administration, one which acknowledges the existence of &amp;quot;non-believers&amp;quot; (put positively: naturalists) and which supports science, most encouraging! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org  &lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.prospect-magazine.co.uk/article_details.php?id=10583" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.prospect-m...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS: if you have topics you'd like to discuss or other ideas for future meetups, or meeting spots you like, please suggest them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month):   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring and promoting a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I've made a reservation for one of the booths on the far wall of the back room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239147079000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234491085000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cancelled: Should Obama redefine liberalism to reflect conservative morality?</name><id>9732709</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236726000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/9732709/</event_url></item>