<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi thought I'd let you in on a great party, I go every year it is the Seacoast's longest-running annual Halloween Party featuring dancing, apparitions, value-priced cocktails and the Jumbo Circus Peanuts which is set for Saturday, October 27, at the Portsmouth VFW Ballroom, 238 Deer Street, downtown. Doors open at 8 p.m. for the over-21 show. Tickets are $10, no advance sale. The theme for this year's party is &amp;quot;Zombie Ice Capades.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In recognition of its historic twelfth Halloween party, the band is offering several special promotions. Patrons who bring a copy of this article with them to the door will receive a $3 ticket discount. And, guests who purchase 12 drinks at the same time will receive a free drink on the band. &amp;quot;We call it our 13-for-12 drink special,&amp;quot; said two-time band spokesmodel Whitey Brown, a clarinetist and vocalist. (Offer subject to state and local regulations and other restrictions may apply.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brown also explained this year's party theme. &amp;quot;We chose Zombie Ice Capades as this year's theme for obvious reasons,&amp;quot; she said. &amp;quot;The real Ice Capades has been dead for years now but we feel strongly that we might be able to bring it back. We're also hoping that a lot of partygoers will dress like a zombie Dorothy Hamill or Scott Hamilton and dance the night away in their ice skates.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brown pointed out that zombie figure skaters attending the party must wear blade guards at all times to avoid marring the polished parquet floor at the VFW ballroom. &amp;quot;That policy will be strictly enforced,&amp;quot; she said. She added, &amp;quot;You don't absolutely have to dress like a zombie Ice Capades star, but we will be awarding prizes to the best Dick Buttons, Peggy Fleming, and the Shipstads and Johnson.&amp;quot; She also quickly pointed out the band embraces zombie diversity and welcomes the undead and other Halloween characters of any background or persuasion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Jumbo Circus Peanuts are a 10-piece party band with an eclectic repertoire of pop, funk, Motown, R&amp;amp;B, jazz, Latin, and exotic tunes. Styled in the manner of a New Orleans brass band, the Peanuts? distinctive carnival-style dances are well-known at the band?s self-proclaimed ?international headquarters,? the Portsmouth VFW. In addition to an ample dance floor the venue offers ringside seating in a nightclub atmosphere, a cocktail buffet, clean rest rooms, complimentary parking on-site and is smoke-free. &lt;br /&gt;For more information visit jumbocircuspeanuts.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So join us in a wild night of great music and awsome costumes, look for the monster monkey dancing to the monster music! see you there. Peter &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event fee: &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542458000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193277040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Party -Jumbo Circus Peanuts Band</name><id>6612733</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193529600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/6612733/</event_url></item>