<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass, Framingham, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Framingham 15 AMC Theater</name><city>Framingham</city><id>597341</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390236</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;New stuff:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show time is 1:45, so let's meet outside the theater in the welcome scorching heat between 1:15 and 1:30. We'll head in by 1:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're late or can't make it last minute (or if you RSVPed Maybe and can make it last minute), please call my cell phone: 508/308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Old stuff:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who's excited for &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/feature/indianajones.html?showVideo=1" target="_blank"&gt;Indiana Jones&lt;/a&gt;? &lt;b&gt;We are!!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't wait until June 7 and like drive-ins, you may want to go to this &lt;a href="http://yoga.meetup.com/673/calendar/7870526/"&gt;Saturday night's double feature (Indy/Iron Man) at the Mendon drive-in&lt;/a&gt;. Scott would love to have you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet outside the theater and then go in and buy our discounted tickets together. (Tix are $8.50 each to FMM members and their guests; instead of $10.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome. Just be sure to include them in your RSVP so I know how many people to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll go out after the movie to discuss it and chat, if people are game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell number is 508/308-4897 if you need to RSVP last minute (like w/in 2 hours of the show). The exact time of the show will be updated a few days before, as movie times don't come out this far ahead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My email is dana@framesbydana.com. Email me if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at this summer blockbuster movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW, if I get enough people RSVPing and saying they'd rather this movie be Saturday night, June 7, I'm fine with moving it to prime time. I want to be democratic about it... Voice your opinion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my Meetup nametag and waiting outside by the parking lot. We'll congregate there, then we'll buy our (discounted) tickets together. I look like my pic on the FMM site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213103579000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We don't bite, we all love movies and we're all looking to make new friends! (Well, some of us bite a little, but it probably won't hurt!)</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211389174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull</name><id>7984104</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212861600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/7984104/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>