<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.791451</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online Flex Meetup Group Connect Room</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1473709</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661575</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topic&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeffry Houser will present will examine what it took to create components using the MX Lifecycle, then discuss how things changed with the introduction of the flex Spark Components architecture.&amp;nbsp; And finally, it will look at what it takes to optimize componentsfor deployment to mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presenter Bio&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeffry Houser is a technical entrepreneur that likes to share cool stuff with other people.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeffry is the Brains behind Flextras, a set of user interface Flex Components that save you time and help you create better Flex applications.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;He has a Computer Science degree from the days before business met the Internet and has solved a problem or two in his programming career.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;In 1999, Jeffry started DotComIt, an Adobe Solutions Partner specializing in Rich Internet Applications with Flex and ColdFusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeffry is an Adobe Community Professional and produces The Flex Show, a podcast that includes expert interviews and screencast tutorials. He also hosts the Flextras Friday Lunch Podcast, a weekly live Q&amp;amp;A session where you can get your questions answered, and also runs a site www.AskTheFlexpert.com where you can get your questions answered privately.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Jeffry has spoken at user groups and conferences all over the US, is the co-manager of the Hartford CT Adobe User Group, author of three technical books, and over 30 articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his spare time Jeffry is a musician, old school adventure game aficionado, recording engineer, and he owns a Wii. Find more about Flextras at &lt;a href="http://www.flextras.com/"&gt;http://www.flextras.com&lt;/a&gt;, ask Jeffry Questions at &lt;a href="http://www.asktheflexpert.com/"&gt;www.asktheflexpert.com&lt;/a&gt;, or check out his podcast at &lt;a href="http://www.theflexshow.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theflexshow.com&lt;/a&gt;, or you can read his personal blog at &lt;a href="http://www.jeffryhouser.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jeffryhouser.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join At&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can join in at &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;http://experts.na3.acrobat.com/ofmg/ &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Check&lt;/a&gt; what time this occurs in your time zone at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;http://www.timeanddate.com/worldclock/fixedtime.html?hour=18&amp;amp;min=0&amp;amp;sec=0&amp;amp;p1=98 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LOGGING IN:&lt;/strong&gt; When you login to the Connect room (the link above)  &lt;br /&gt;to view the meeting, PLEASE USE THE "LOGIN AS GUEST" option, and USE YOUR NAME, but do NOT  &lt;br /&gt;attempt to use your meetup.com username/password or any Connect account. Just sign in as a guest. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADD THIS TO YOUR CALENDAR&lt;/strong&gt;: Want to add this event to your own personal calendar? Click the link  &lt;br /&gt;on the top of the event page, below the event title, saying, "Export to a calendar", which offers  &lt;br /&gt;calendar downloads for Outlook, iCal, Google, and Yahoo calendars.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeffry Houser</member_name><member_id>2147426</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302183796000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297282882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Building Components From MX To Mobile by Jeffry Houser</name><id>16506734</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302127200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/16506734/</event_url></item>