<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The trailer is amazing.  Seen from the balcony of Cinestudio it seems like the Rolling Stones are playing right in front of you.  (Certainly better than the far away end of Foxboro Stadium in 1989, when I saw them last.)  I 'll be there about 7:15 pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Martin Scorsese. Director of photography, Robert Richardson. With: The Rolling Stones, Martin Scorsese, Buddy Guy, Jack White, Christina Aguilera.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Rolling Stones may have ceded their reputation as #1 enemies of the social order - Tom Wolfe famously wrote “The Beatles want to hold your hand, but the Stones want to burn down your town,” - but there’s still plenty of anarchy left in these soul survivors from London. Martin Scorsese scores his dream job as stage manager to the Stones, joined by Jack White, Buddy Guy and Christina Aguilera for an intimate concert in NYC’s Beacon Theater. How could the set list not be great, with 40 plus years of music from Jumpin’ Jack Flash to Tumbling Dice to Shattered? Don’t miss one of the last chances to see Shine a Light on the big screen, with Cinestudio’s supercharged Dolby sound system catching the magic of Keith Richards’ steady rock and drummer Charlie Watts’ jazz-inspired roll.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222016890000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219289214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shine A Light</name><id>8589303</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220484600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/8589303/</event_url></item>