<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Pub</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>733190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068749</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;*****EVENT UPDATE: Please update your RSVPs as&amp;nbsp;about 100 people from the Red Sox Natives and 5 other groups are attending.&amp;nbsp;We are at capacity. If you are not attending please change your RSVP. We can not open the RSVPs up to any more people until the probable No Shows RSVP out. (If you want to be placed on a waiting list please E Mail Frank of the Red Sox Natives)&amp;nbsp;Harrington's will be closed to the public for 2 private parties with guest lists. We will be on the first floor. Upon arrival, please check in with one of the Red Sox Natives&amp;nbsp;Event&amp;nbsp;Hosts at the front door. They will direct you to the Boston Happy Hour&amp;nbsp;group&amp;nbsp;in the bar area. Harrington's will be packed. Please be considerate&amp;nbsp;of others who&amp;nbsp;want to watch the whole game and the commercials once the game begins! All are encouraged to wear Patriots gear.*****&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The New England Patriots are the AFC Champions and are going to the Super Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Game is on against the&amp;nbsp;New York Giants. Please RSVP now or ASAP as this event&amp;nbsp;is being announced to&amp;nbsp;5 meetup groups and space will become limited. PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE EVENT ANNOUNCEMENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one is for the suburban&amp;nbsp;drinking buddies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives&amp;nbsp;have been organizing Patriots Game Watching Events over the past&amp;nbsp;4 months with up to 65 people attending at Boston, Wakefield and Woburn&amp;nbsp;venues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week we will&amp;nbsp;return to&amp;nbsp;our&amp;nbsp;suburban venue&amp;nbsp;on Sunday,&amp;nbsp;February 5&amp;nbsp;at 5:30pm&amp;nbsp;to watch the Patriots&amp;nbsp;play in the&amp;nbsp;Super Bowl.&amp;nbsp;We watched the&amp;nbsp;AFC Championship Game at&amp;nbsp;Harrington's&amp;nbsp;on January 22 and polled Red Sox Natives and Wakefield Weeknights guests with many&amp;nbsp;wanting to return for the Super Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great and the full menu is available for purchase. Owners Lisa and Dan have offerred us&amp;nbsp;the entire first floor bar and restaurant area and are adding an additional 60 inch television screen for the&amp;nbsp;Super Bowl. Harrington's will provide some complimentary appetizers as well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive early at 5:30pm and get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game time is 6:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's in front of Bank of America and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center and Commuter Rail accessible from North Station&amp;nbsp;by the&amp;nbsp;Haverhill Train stopping at Wakefield Station&amp;nbsp;with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion Street 1 block, right on to to Main Street and 1 block to Water Street. If you are joining us from the City and do not have a car the Commuter rail or bus&amp;nbsp;is the way to go.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own food/drink.&amp;nbsp;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AND TIP YOUR SERVERS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP early if you think you will attend. Invite guests, friends, and co-workers.&amp;nbsp;We are inviting several other groups to join us so space will become limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*****Due to the constant large number of "No Shows" we are limiting RSVPs to members only with "0" guests and&amp;nbsp;reserve the right to further limit members who have more than 1 No Show. To&amp;nbsp;attend the event you must be a member of&amp;nbsp;Tonya's Boston Happy Hour or Red Sox Natives. Wait listed people for our January 22 event were unable to attend because of all the RSVP No Shows.*****&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following groups&amp;nbsp;are participating&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Natives (Frank)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wakefield Weeknights (Melody)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Happy Hour (Tonya)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TWIOP (Ziggy)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Fun (Isabele)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Single Geeks, Nerds &amp;amp; Professionals (Alison)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;nbsp;hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fenway Frank and the Natives Team&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the entire first floor and bar area with an additional new 60 inch screen added for our event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>3178870</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328733217000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>95</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327284184000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl Game Viewing Party - Patriots vs New York Giants at Harrington's Pub</name><id>49196012</id><headcount>69</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328481000000</time><rsvp_limit>95</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/49196012/</event_url></item>