<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;October Lean Workshop at 6:00pm.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Boston Lean Startup Circle is proud to announce a lean workshop featuring two of Boston's premier Startup founders - Julies Pieri, Founder and CEO of Daily Grommet and Rob May, Co-Founder of Backupify.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Jules Pieri, Founder and CEO of Daily Grommet&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dailygrommet.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://julespieri.files.wordpress.com/2007/05/jules_pieri1.jpg?w=100&amp;amp;h=100" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dailygrommet.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.woollypocket.com/images/press/logo.daily_grommet.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daily Grommet is a curated marketplace that launches one inventive product a day.  The product ideas come from people’s submissions, which are vetted by the Daily Grommet team, and distributed across the web, via video stories about the products and their creators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Daily Grommet is Jules’ third startup. Jules started her professional life as an industrial designer working for computer enterprises. She soon realized the majority of our economy is shaped by consumer products companies, so she followed the action over to consumer brands as an executive at Keds and Hasbro. Jules is told she is the first industrial designer to get a Harvard MBA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rob May, Co-founder of Backupify&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.backupify.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://a1.twimg.com/profile_images/1138221677/rob.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.backupify.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://images.maketecheasier.com/2010/06/backupify-logo.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Backupify provides daily automatic backups, archiving, and export for all your social media and SaaS data. Backupify is now backing up over 120 million emails, 78 million tweets, and 41 million pictures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob started his career as a digital design engineer at Harris Corporation, where he worked on graphics processing chips for the Comanche helicopter. After Harris, Rob taught in the business school at the University of Louisville, then moved on to a business development position for a wireless software startup. Rob ran the popular business blog Businesspundit.com for 5 years, before selling it in early 2008. Rob has a B.S. in Electrical Engineering and a M.B.A., both from the University of Kentucky.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;6pm Early Bird Presentation: Customer Development 101, with John Prendergast&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For those new to the concepts of Customer Development and The Lean Startup, please come early. From 6:00 to 6:30pm, John Prendergast, Organizer of the LSC Boston Meetup and CEO of BlueLeaf.com will talk about the basics of customer development and lean startups.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check in at the front desk and come up to the 1st Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Prendergast</member_name><member_id>8455139</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290555722000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lean-Startup-Circle-Boston</urlname><id>1533572</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Lean Startup Circle Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>99</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277488878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lean Startup Circle Boston Monthly Meetup</name><id>dmxdnynnblc</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288130400000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lean-Startup-Circle-Boston/events/13910126/</event_url></item>