<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Meeting time:&amp;nbsp; The movie will start at 7:15 p.m. so please plan to meet&amp;nbsp;at&amp;nbsp; 6:45 p.m. in the outer lobby of the AMC Framingham. I plan to get in line for tickets about 20 minutes before so we can get snacks and then get seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discount tickets: I will have discount coupons available so we can get tickets for $8.00 each. (Retail price is $10.50.) I will collect $8 in cash from each person and then I'll get in line to buy tickets for all. Exact change is helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, those who want to are welcome to go out to a local restaurant to chat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film description:&amp;nbsp; Hanna&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raised by her father (Eric Bana), an ex-CIA man, in the wilds of Finland, Hanna&amp;rsquo;s upbringing and training have been one and the same, all geared to making her the perfect assassin. The turning point in her adolescence is a sharp one; sent into the world by her father on a mission, Hanna journeys stealthily across Europe while eluding agents dispatched after her by a ruthless intelligence operative with secrets of her own (Cate Blanchett). As she nears her ultimate target, Hanna faces startling revelations about her existence and unexpected questions about her humanity. &lt;br /&gt;Cast: Saoirse Ronan, Eric Bana, Tom Hollander, Olivia Williams, Jason Flemyng, Jessica Barden, Cate Blanchett &lt;br /&gt;Director: Joe Wright &lt;br /&gt;Genres: Action/Thriller &lt;br /&gt;Runtime:1 hr. 51 min.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the outer lobby, off to the right as you come in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>6039490</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303176115000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Looks exciting!</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302485195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framingham Movie Meetup: "Hanna," Sunday, April 17, 6:45 p.m.</name><id>17257418</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303081200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/17257418/</event_url></item>