<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>115 Derby St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (978) 744-0991</phone><name>House of the Seven Gables</name><city>Salem </city><id>758750</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884150</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Trip to Salem is my favorite thing to do!  &lt;br /&gt;Let me be your tour guide..........&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will all be meeting either at the Worcester Business Center in Worcester, or at The House of Seven Gables in Salem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first stop will be across the street, at the best candy store in New England, Ye Olde Pepper Companie  down the street near the House of Seven Gables for homemade chocolates  and candy-  You can check out that link at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72898767432323&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=953b4a1&amp;amp;FORM=CVRE" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we will probably split up temporarily into (2) groups: One going to the Witches Dungeons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;The original site of the  witch dungeons is actually below the phone company, however, they have  re-created the dungeons to the specific measurements of the actual  dungeons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dungeons were cold, and foul smelling, and were  kept in total darkness, and the only light that was ever seen, was when  the guards entered the dungeon. The dungeon was also near the north  river, and during high tide would flood, and the cold water would rise  to the prisoner?s ankles, daily. Most of the prisoners were kept in  chains, and it was a stomping ground for large river rats. For the  prisoners, who were poor, and could not afford to pay for their stay in  the dungeon, they were put in coffin like cells, smaller than a phone  booth, in which they could only stand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tour at the witch  dungeons starts out with everyone going into the theater to read the  story of the Salem witch trials on the plaques on the walls. Then there  is a mini play, of a re-creation of an actual trial taken from real  manuscripts that were found in the last several years. The play is done  with the accusers and accused on stage, and the people in the crowd  treated as those from Salem Town attending the trial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the  play, the tour guide will give some facts of what happened in Salem in  1692, and then everyone is taken down into the re-creation of the  dungeons, to see how big the cells were, and the re-creation of things  that happened. The tour ends in the gift shop, and pictures can be taken  in the pillorys outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check out the link for the witch dungeons at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72892362922056&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=ad73f83c&amp;amp;FORM=CVRE6" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other for those who have already gone to the dungeons, can go and tour Salem Village,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;which is a re-creation of Salem Village in the 1690's&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the website at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We  will then be re-gathering for lunch, at my favorite Salem Restaurant, Victoria  Station, which is on the wharf, and specializes in Prime Rib and Sea  Food and has the best prime rib sandwiches and chocolate mousse that I  have ever tasted! They have a wide variety of selections on their menu  which you can check out at:  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72896917143953&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=8958a9e5&amp;amp;FORM=CVRE" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  &lt;br /&gt;We will then do some "witchy" shopping on the wharf at the following stores:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie Cabot's, the famous witch of Salem's current shop:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72852646739696&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=b763a8a6&amp;amp;FORM=CVRE3" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Salem's Tourist Shop at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72854939117628&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=6856f8f4&amp;amp;FORM=CVRE" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A great shop to stock up on reasonably priced herbs at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://localsearch.live.com/localsearch/details.aspx?lid=YN388x6986680&amp;amp;qt=yp&amp;amp;what=herbs&amp;amp;where=Salem" target="_blank"&gt;http://localsearch.li...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;%2c+MA&amp;amp;s_cid=ansPhBkYp02&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pagan singer Gypsy's Shop- Nu Aeon at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72900537886138&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=27155ede&amp;amp;FORM=C" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;VRE2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then to the famous Pyramid Books:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72913339813962&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=250e4498&amp;amp;FORM=C" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;VRE3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we will head down to the mall, and visit some more interesting shops, including:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie Cabot's first shop, now owned by her adopted daughter- Crow Haven Corner-  &lt;br /&gt;Check out the link at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://cc.msnscache.com/cache.aspx?q=72888746115654&amp;amp;mkt=en-US&amp;amp;lang=en-US&amp;amp;w=fd0629f8&amp;amp;FORM=CV" target="_blank"&gt;http://cc.msnscache.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorites,   &lt;br /&gt;The Broom Closet:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.broomcloset.com/index.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.broomclose...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Angel Shop:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.angelicaoftheangels.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.angelicaof...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and  a variety of other stores in the mall, including other places with  witchy stuff, medieval clothing stores, Witchy T-shirt places, and  places where we can have your "witchy" pictures taken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Plan on not returning to  Worcester until&amp;nbsp;  6 or 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring lots of money to spend, and expect to have a great time! :)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be meeting on Millbrook St in Worcester, and at the House of Seven Gables in Salem- Pick your place!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305384057000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We have done it twice before, and we always have an awesome time!! :)</why><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299635735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Trip to Salem</name><id>16852580</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304778600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/16852580/</event_url></item>