<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Yawkey Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.346672</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 267-9440 </phone><name>Fenway Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>567754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098885</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Gobble up breakfast and enjoy a self-guided tour, designed by the design consultant for the Fenway renovations Janet Marie Smith, while hearing firsthand from architects, contractors and engineers about the challenges of renovating this historic venue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore how creative reuse has made Fenway an even better place for good old-fashioned baseball, along with new uses like concerts featuring Bruce Springsteen, Jimmy Buffett and the Rolling Stones. See the impact on surrounding neighborhoods with new housing, hotels, restaurants and upgraded public transportation. Get up close to the last hand-operated scoreboards in the Major Leagues. Learn what?s behind the Green Monster ? and everything else you ever wanted to know about our beloved Fenway Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets cost $70, and you can bring one child at no cost for each ticket purchased. Continental breakfast is included. Tour time is estimated at 2 hours and they run at 7 am, 8 am, 9 am and 10 am. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event, which is held as part of programming for the &lt;a href="http://www.aiaconvention.com" target="_blank"&gt;AIA National Convention&lt;/a&gt;, is sponsored by Lumber Liquidators. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please note, you MUST purchase tickets at &lt;a href="http://www.architects.org/2008/tourStore.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.architects...&lt;/a&gt; to RSVP! You do not have to be a BSA/AIA member or AIA Convention attendee to come.**&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Moser-Booth</member_name><member_id>6447986</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211215647000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Breakfast at Fenway, a behind-the-scenes tour of the ballpark ... this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!</why><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207844280000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast at Fenway Park</name><id>7713906</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211022000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/7713906/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/3/4/global_3751588.jpeg</photo_url></item>