<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for non-members only</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/b/a/event_209899642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join us on March 12th when we will be joined by author and primatologist Richard Wrangham. He will be talking about his book, "Catching Fire: How Cooking Made Us Human"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Amazon: In Catching Fire, renowned primatologist Richard Wrangham argues that our evolutionary success is the result of cooking. Once our hominid ancestors began cooking, the human digestive tract shrank and the brain grew; and pair bonding, marriage, the household, and even the sexual division of labor emerged. A pathbreaking theory of human evolution, Catching Fire will fascinate anyone interested in our ancient originsor our modern eating habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Wrangham is the Ruth Moore Professor of Biological Anthropology at Harvard University where he has worked since 1989. His major interests are chimpanzee behavioral ecology, the evolution of violence, human dietary evolution, and the conservation of chimpanzees and other apes. He has studied chimpanzees in Uganda since 1987 as director of the Kibale Chimpanzee Project (now co-Director with Martin Muller). His most recent book is Catching Fire: How Cooking Made Us Human (Basic Books, June 2009)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard might have a limited number of books available for purchase after the talk. He will be happy to sign any copies if any members of the audience already have one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we will be setting up around 6:30, so feel free to come and socialize. The program is scheduled to start at 7. We ask that non members make a small $5 donation at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please watch this page for changes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364142897000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362241433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Meeting: Richard Wrangham, "Catching Fire: How Cooking Made Us Human"</name><id>107226772</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363129200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/107226772/</event_url></item>