<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Howdy Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Butt and Gut Cut, Chapter One&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just got my Plastic Surgeons Kit in the mail, it comes with a neat diploma and a silver badge saying im a plastic board certified plastic surgeon...it even came with the tools..a variety of plastic straws, a plastic knife and spoon.plastic tweezers..some soap bubbles solution with a applicator that says &amp;quot;blower&amp;quot; that looks like a collar bone....a few plastic forks too..&lt;br /&gt;if i dont use them they will be good for the next picknick....&lt;br /&gt;I played all night with the practice board..if you touch the sides of the cut out areas while taking out some parts a light bulb and alarm goes off..i cut the wires to the light and alarm, so i passed the test faster..it was kind of like pinching off some blood vessels to the brain...it worked really cool when i poured red wine into the device..made it really realistic..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so now im ready to go into practice...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know a lot of you want to look FOREVER YOUNG and im the doctor who can do it now...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just did my own face lift..I look real &amp;quot;cool&amp;quot; now...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok in chapter one of the self practice course it says to... EAT LESS AND GO FOR A WALK... I cant waite to get to chapter 12 where Lipo suction happens.... 13 where i get to administer homemade Boitulism to all the wrinkled areas...14 and 15 is where you get to have replaced joints...20 is about lawyers and stuff...maybe i get to practice on them..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well thats what this meetup event is about...(get rid of that unsightly appendage or firm up what you have already got for maximum impact.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You eat some healty food before or bring some while walking, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is a historic part of town and is lit..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conversations on many different topics are the norm on these walks,&lt;br /&gt;if enough propane is in the fire pit, it gets lit after the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Old Historic Wethersfield has a old style Main Street where Comstock, Ferrie Hart Seed, The Cove House and a bunch of other well known and lesser known Historic houses .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To do a trip down and back and a few other streets is about an hour..more if a few divertion streets are taken...&lt;br /&gt;There is an ICE CREAM SHOP right near by..but remember..this is to get that protruding bulubbery jelllow BUTT and GUT CUT down a bit more so you will actually be a bit younger looking..and not only that younger feeling..&lt;br /&gt;Now do you really want me to try the lipo suction device or do you want to loose it naturally ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Comstock Ferrie out in the front lot by the Gazebo.&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 North:&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 26 off I-91 and turn left at end of exit ramp. Turn left again at stop sign. Pass entrance to highway and turn left at the T-intersection onto Marsh Street. Wind around the cemetery on your right and you'll see First Church. Make a right at the stop sign onto Main Street. Parking areas are just past church on the right or left side of the street. Comstock ferrie is the brick building by the ice cream shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-91 South:&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 26 off I-91 and turn right at end of exit ramp. Make your first left onto Marsh Street. Wind around the cemetery on your right and you'll see First Church. Make a right at the stop sign onto Main Street. Parking areas are just past church on the right or left side of the street. Comstock ferrie is the brick building by the ice cream shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 9: &lt;br /&gt;Take Route 9 to CT-175 EAST (Newington). Stay on 175 for 5.87 miles all the way to the church! (Name changes from Cedar Street in Newington to Wells Road and then Main Street in Wethersfield.) When you cross the Silas Deane Highway (Rt. 99), you'll enter Old Wethersfield. First Church is about 3/4 miles down on the right. Parking areas are just past church on the right or left side of the street. Comstock ferrie is the brick building by the ice cream shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190327844000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190046457000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Re-storative Healthy Walk in Old Historic Wethersfield</name><id>6375392</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190154600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6375392/</event_url></item>