<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Technology Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363772</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Technology Square Courtyard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1049613</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.092004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Change of plans&lt;/b&gt;: Let's meet up inside the Food Court near the Kendall / MIT Station, on the Mariott Hotel side to grab something to eat, and walk over to Technology Square at 6:15 pm. We can break the ice and make introductions, then explore what they have. I'll have small red MEETUP stickers I can pass out for people to wear so an hour later after wandering around, we don't have to puzzle &amp;quot;Did I just meet this person? Are they with the group?&amp;quot; :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I'll be there at 5:40 pm in the Food Court commandeering tables probably in the alcove closest to the T Station, so I can watch people walk in. We can push tables together. I just realized that man can not live by free samples of food alone. ;) I need to grab a bite to eat before checking out this trade show-like &amp;quot;block party&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Walking Directions&lt;/b&gt;: It's a 5 minute walk according to Google Maps. &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Kendall%2FMIT+Station&amp;amp;daddr=400+Technology+Square,+Cambridge,+MA+02139&amp;amp;geocode=FXtmhgIdoE_D-yGio3Eh4Mp5sQ%3BFXxrhgId3DjD-w&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=cc&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.363225,-71.08876&amp;amp;sspn=0.005605,0.008637&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=17" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to drop in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Block Party&amp;quot; is held from 4:30 pm to 7:30 pm. Feel free to meet the group there if you want to go early. Me? I need to grab a sandwich first. With 40+ YES RSVPs, you can just look for the horde of people with red circular MEETUP stickers and introduce yourself to people. No, I am not going to be able to introduce people individually. My brain catches fire, smoke starts pouring out of my ears, and the hard drive of my brain crashes if I need to introduce more than 12 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... If you really want, I can pass out cheap nametags. Watch out, they are water soluable, leaving sticky residue behind in the rain. I found this the hard way during one of last year's Boston By Foot's Boston Underfoot civil engineering tour &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/8308948/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Online Registration:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/projects/forms/techsquare09"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the New Scientist Magazine:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/info/info320?full=true"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Tech Square Block Party 2009&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Date:&lt;/i&gt; Wednesday, September 16&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rain Date: Friday, September 18&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Location&lt;/u&gt;: Courtyard between 300 &amp;amp; 500 Technology Square, Main Street, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Map of Location&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.tech-square.com/location.html"&gt;http://www.tech-squar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free to Attend&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free Food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;FREE BEER: 21+ beer and wine – ID required&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register Now: &lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/projects/forms/techsquare09"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Why should I register to attend&lt;/u&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Registering online &lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/projects/forms/techsquare09"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;enters you into our event raffle, with the opportunity to win fabulous prizes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;allows you to avoid long lines and enter quickly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Who is invited to the Tech Square Block Party?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Science and technology enthusiasts alike including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;employees of Cambridge area science &amp;amp; technology companies and academic institutions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;local high tech, nanotech, biotech and pharmaceutical professionals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;local students from MIT, Harvard, Boston University, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;science journalists, writers and communicators&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Scientist subscribers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Who should support this event?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If your organization wants to make their presence known in our scientific community, then the Tech Square Block Party is the place to be. Attended by over 700 people last year, the Block Party served as a great forum for science professionals and supporters to network, have a drink and enjoy each other's company&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;What goes on at the Tech Square Block Party that makes it different from a regular block party?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I don't think you'd find this much geek chic-ness in one area. On center stage, science pub trivia is lead by professional science communicators. Raffle prizes are geared towards the nerd in all of us with books, tech gadgets and museum tickets - just to name a few. Goodie bags are distributed with cool gear. Our sponsors and supporters connect with the crowd with their own displays of their scientific endeavours. More entertainment details are still to come. Oh yeah, and the beer and wine (21+ only) is free&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Any other questions?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Contact Kimberly Karman here&amp;quot;: &lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/contact/person?recipient=dawi"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be in the Food Court right behind the Kendall / MIT station from 5:30 pm to 6:15 pm grabbing a small bite to eat. Let's meet up there and walk together to the place at 6:15 pm. Or you can just meet us there, since the event is 4:30 pm to 7:30 pm. Whichever you want to do. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About New Scientist magazine:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/data/html/ns/mediacenter/us/intro.jsp"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;New Scientist magazine was launched in 1956 'for all those men and women who are interested in scientific discovery, and in its industrial, commercial and social consequences'. The brand's mission is no different today - for its consumers, New Scientist reports, explores and interprets the results of human endeavour set in the context of society and culture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;New Scientist online was launched in 1996 and now carries an archive of over 76,000 content pieces. Our online content is considerably enhanced by an international online news team, posting updates every day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In November 2008, NewScientist.com has been relaunched in order to provide our content in an organized and more accessible fashion for our readers. Similarly in 2009, New Scientist magazine will also have a more contemporary look and feel&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Review of last year's block party:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sciencemetropolis.com/2008/09/18/new-scientist-block-party/"&gt;http://www.sciencemet...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joseph Caputo, ScienceMetropolis.com:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;UK-based science magazine &lt;b&gt;New Scientist&lt;/b&gt; stepped off the newsstands this afternoon and came to Cambridge’s Technology Square &lt;a href="http://www.tech-square.com/"&gt;http://www.tech-squar...&lt;/a&gt; for a party. In a grassy courtyard surrounded by leading research institutions, locals sampled free drinks and food before heading over to a nearby Wii competition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Although the Block Party was for advertising purposes only, (I am now the proud owner of Pfizer chapstick), New Scientist couldn’t help infusing some geekiness into their event. Dozens entered a science trivia contest to win prizes like a copy of “Why Don’t Penguin’s Feet Freeze,” &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Why-Dont-Penguins-Feet-Freeze/dp/1861978766"&gt;http://www.amazon.co....&lt;/a&gt; a 1.5 G flash drive or an iPod shuffle. Questions on the closest platypus relative, deep-sea vents, and nuclear reactors kept the competition fierce.  (It is no surprise, however, that Team ScienceMetropolis.com won the science in Massachusetts round.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Those who haven’t heard of New Scientist should definitely pick up an issue. It is a weekly publication that covers the latest world news in science, space, technology and the environemnt. Their feature stories are often evocative and timely. Some of the latest include where to find black holes &lt;a href="http://space.newscientist.com/article/mg19826561.800-black-holes-may-lurk-in-unexpected-places.html"&gt;http://space.newscien...&lt;/a&gt; , the psychology of leadership &lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/channel/being-human/mg19826601.900-follow-me-the-origins-of-leadership.html"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt; and racing rockets &lt;a href="http://space.newscientist.com/article/dn14430-rocketpowered-racing-plane-takes-flight.html"&gt;http://space.newscien...&lt;/a&gt; . And unlike the more stuffy science publications, they are a strong supporter of fun&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions &amp;amp; Map:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tech-square.com/location.html"&gt;http://www.tech-squar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Technology Square is situated between Broadway and Main Street just a few blocks west of the MBTA's Kendall Square T-station. Technology Square's proximity to both Storrow Drive and Memorial Drive make the site accessible from all locations including Boston's nearby Financial District, the Back Bay and Beacon Hill as well as points along Route 93 and the Massachusetts Turnpike&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Public Transportation&lt;/u&gt;: Technology Square is situated just a five minute walk from the Kendall Square MBTA stop. &amp;quot;MBTA Red Line – Kendall Square. After exiting the T station, walk 3 blocks west on Main St. (away from the river) and Technology Square will be on your right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Area Parking&lt;/u&gt;: Technology Square Garage, Kendall Square Garage, Cambridge Center Garage&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>29</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253488181000</updated><rating><average>4.07999992371</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251472339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tech Square Block Party @ New Scientist Magazine</name><id>11224391</id><headcount>46</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253139300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11224391/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/global_5310283.jpeg</photo_url></item>