<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2 mile looping hike of higher difficulty for the first half to get the juices flowing. For the first half we'll hike up the steep grade of the Giant's head on the blue trail. then clifftop hiking to the backside of the head and back down again. We'll hike the Tower Trail (a.k.a. dirt road) to the tower and then return on the same dirt road for an easy conclusion to the hike.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the parking lot across from Quinnipiac University at 11 AM. There should be no fee to park (normally $8 for CT residents). The hike would start from the trailhead off of the parking lot.  We would finish at 1 PM at the latest and possibly head out to eat lunch if people feel inclined (Mexican place nearby or ice cream :-P yum). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions for parking lot meetup location&lt;/b&gt; off Mt. Carmel Rd., Hamden, CT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Sleeping+Giant+State+Park&amp;amp;city=Hamden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=200+Mount+Carmel+Ave&amp;amp;zipcode=06518&amp;amp;country=US" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail Map&lt;/b&gt; at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/sleepgiant.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More park information&lt;/b&gt; at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325264&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; ===   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281796607000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281635599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Sleeping Giant State Park in Hamden CT</name><id>14403429</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281711600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/14403429/</event_url></item>