<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Nashs Mill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.604649</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greenfield Swimming Area</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>1125824</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.617836</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a walk and socialize meetup; not really so much a hike as a romp in the chilly air!  Plan for mud and puddles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.townofgreenfield.org/Pages/GreenfieldMA_Recreation/gsa" target="_blank"&gt;Greenfield Swimming Area&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenfield Swimming Area, Nashs Mill road, Greenfield, MA  01301; 22 acres&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:  The Green River Swimming area is one of the most widely used town parks in Greenfield. This property located west of the center of Greenfield is contiguous with Murphy Park and Nims Tree Farm. It is also linked to the center of Greenfield via the Riverside Community Path. Its unique and abundant recreation opportunities include an in stream swimming pool with sand beach toddler play area, athletic courts, concessions and picnic areas. The property is complete with open grass area and mature shade trees that add to its uniqueness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This area is closed to dogs from April 15 to October/November 15. Dogs are allowed after the area has been closed for the swimming season.   We will be mostly using the area on the North side of the river.&lt;br /&gt;YOU MUST PICK UP AFTER YOUR DOG WHEN USING THIS AREA.  The picnic area on the North side of the Green River is accessible via a pedestrian bridge across the river. The north side does not have a beach, but has water access via concrete stairs. There are some shallow river areas accessible  along the banks of the river as well. This picnic area is a large plot of grass covered land and mature shade trees. There are approximately 35 picnic tables with a number designation for rental purposes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Historical Information:  The property for Green River Swimming and Recreation Park was acquired through two transactions. In June of 1929 and December of 1933 two parcels of land were granted to the Inhabitants of Greenfield by private ownership.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking/ Access&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available in a gravel parking lot. The park is accessible by the Riverside Community Bike Path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;From the Greenfield I-91 rotary:&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 2.133.4 mi Time: 5 mins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take I-91 North to Exit 26, exits at the Greenfield Rotary, towards Rout 2 West (MOHAWK TRAIL)) go 0.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn Right on COLRAIN RD towards and past Greenfield Community College - go 1.42 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn Right on NASHS MILL RD - go 0.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Arrive at NASHS MILL RD, GREENFIELD; parking lot on Left&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the intersection of Main Street and Federal Street, Greenfield Center:&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 2.093.4 mi Time: 7 mins&lt;br /&gt;    * Start on MAIN ST (at FEDERAL ST &amp;amp; MAIN ST in GREENFIELD) going West  towards SCHOOL ST - go 0.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn Right on CONWAY ST - go 1.32 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Continue on LEYDEN RD - go 0.10 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn Left on NASHS MILL RD - go 0.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;    * Arrive at NASHS MILL RD, GREENFIELD , parking lot on Right&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a black lab w/blue leash, &amp; vanilla PT Cruiser</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269368243000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268582915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March to the (Green) River</name><id>12872835</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269194400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/12872835/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/d/global_11908205.jpeg</photo_url></item>