<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;Sept 7- 10, the HFA is presenting the works of the great Senegal director Ousmane Sembene who died this past June. Moolade, his last film , had a brief run at Kendall a couple of years ago and I didn't get to see it. There is also a short documentary screening, The Making of Moolade , directed by Samba Gadjigo who will be appearing in person. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The subject matter is difficult: female circumsion, however, Moolaad is told with an assurance and an urgency that raise it far above current-events agitprop. At its warmly beating heart, the film is concerned with the timeless struggle between men and women, or, more precisely, between those people in any society who seek to control and those who are moved to nurture. Boston Globe's Ty Burr&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the 2004 Un Certain Regard Award in Cannes, Sembene?s last film delivers an open attack on the tradition of female circumcision still practiced in Muslim and Christian communities in East and West Africa. A wonderful testament to Sembene?s belief in the cinema as the most effective means of social change in Africa, Mooladé describes the brutal impact of circumcision on adolescent subjects and the ostracisation suffered by the mothers and fathers who resist the violent practice. Mooladé was intended to be the second film in a trilogy designed to honor the lives of African women, who Sembene referred to as the &amp;quot;heroines of everyday life.?     HFA website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Making of Mooladé&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Samba Gadjigo, Appearing in Person &lt;br /&gt;USA 2006, video, color, 20 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This documentary captures Sembene, at the ripe age of 79, working 12 hour days in a remote African village where midday temperatures usually exceeded 100 degrees. Actors, production personnel, camera assistants, and others connected with the film describe the challenges presented by the scarcity of funding and the difficulties of shooting on location.    HFA website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a complete review: &lt;a href="http://metromix.chicagotribune.com/movies/mmx-041201-movies-review-mw-moolade,0,2264201.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://metromix.chica...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some may wish to stay for the second feature, Black Girl, but the group will meet and discuss after Moolade and the short documentary about the film. The HFA is screening 10 films by Sembene in 4 days and so you may be interested in seeing others- I know I will be. Here's the link to the HFA calendar: &lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/films/2007fall/sembene.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://hcl.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom (eh-hem), I will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row. When a theater has a director-led discussion, it is sometimes difficult to find our group-so, don't forget to look for us near the front row.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189379403000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187391794000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moolade by Ousmane Sembene</name><id>6199286</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189206000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6199286/</event_url></item>