<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[From Jonathan Mark]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us when the meeting begins at 6:00 PM to help decide on future events, programs, campaigns, and carpooling to NH May 17 for the &lt;a href="http://www.sst911.org/newsite/events.htm" target="_blank"&gt;2008 New England 9/11 Symposium&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Films begin at 7:00 with excerpts suggested from &lt;a href="http://inlieswetrust.com" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;In Lies We Trust&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;, an interview of &lt;a href="http://heartson.com" target="_blank"&gt;John Heartson&lt;/a&gt; by Jonathan Mark, and his music. More on this will be decided at meeting April 30th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In Lies We Trust: The CIA, Hollywood &amp;amp; Bioterrorism&amp;quot; is a powerful and controversial documentary produced by 'World Leading Intellectual' and drug cartel critic, Dr. Leonard George Horowitz. The film exposes officials, corporations, and American intelligence agencies for historic devil-doing. It takes you inside the policies, politics, and propaganda of genocide with a twist of humor. Horowitz exposes unprecedented fraud, malfeasance, and murder as a clear and present danger to you and your loved ones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Lies We Trust examines the CIA's direction of Hollywood, and modern medicine, and will have you rethinking their impacts on the way you think about current events, increasing threats of outbreaks, cancer, and AIDS. Where do you suppose skyrocketing rates of these and other modern plagues came from?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This award-winning doctor advances compelling analysis of documents explaining our modern maladies as 'socio-political impositions' not made in heaven. In Lies We Trust examines the military-medical-petrochemical-pharmaceutical profiteers behind medical madness; their political prostitutes, and shoddy scientists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stunning evidence, including secreted interviews, explains why millions of innocent and gullible people worldwide have been killed, and billions more are now being frightened into drug addictions, side-effects, profitable illnesses, and premature death. Watch In Lies We Trust: The CIA, Hollywood &amp;amp; Bioterrorism to learn why your life is entrusted to Manchurian candidates who don't even know how and why they aim to kill you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Horowitz brilliantly critiques the government's new 24-hour television network and feature documentary, History of Bioterrorism, which is now broadcasting daily over the Dish Network. September has been declared &amp;quot;National Preparedness Month.&amp;quot; Officials say you must prepare for the worst bioterrorist attacks, yet they use fear and gross inaccuracies (propaganda) examined by Horowitz. This is choice edutainment for your informed decision-making.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Horowitz generously donated this life-saving DVD for widespread free public distribution without copyright restrictions. Viewers are encouraged to make at least two more copies to gift to others. View every part of this production in the low resolution Quicktime files below, or order your high resolution DVD today by calling toll free: 1-888-508-4787. You can also order these DVDs online through &lt;a href="http://www.healthyworldstore.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.healthyworldstore.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After each film excerpt, a different person could lead discussions. If you have a film excerpt in mind, please come on April 30th meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should have information, dvds, and literature in support of many campaigns. For late breaking news and campaign updates see &lt;a href="http://flybynews.com" target="_blank"&gt;FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are at the community meeting space in back of the building behind Woodstar Cafe</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210888946000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Get to see films you would not normally come across</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207147464000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IN LIES WE TRUST - mtg, film, discussions</name><id>7657412</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210716000000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7657412/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/f/0/global_3677872.jpeg</photo_url></item>