<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>8 St. Mary's Street</address_2><address_1>PH0206</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.619667</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-975-0600</phone><name>BU Photonics Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1052903</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129097</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Lighting and the Dramatic Portrait- Michael Grecco- YOU DO NOT WANT TO MISS THIS!&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday October 27, 2009, 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For over a quarter century, portrait photographer Michael Grecco has been taking images and making impressions. From advertising to editorial, Grecco's dynamic work is continually raising the photographic bar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael has created a critically acclaimed book titled “The Art of Portrait Photography”. He is currently working on his “found beach people” series in Miami and Los Angeles for his newest publication. Michael Grecco works with an unrivaled technical ability and a rare sensitivity. Michael couples this technical savvy with a personally engaging style that draws out the people and the potential. He is a photographer’s photographer, always ready with hard-earned advice and willing praise for others. The image he has created for himself is authentic, composed and always striking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Using visual examples from his dramatic and conceptual portraits, Michael will explain the elements of creative imagery, show how he developed his style, and tell you how you can develop yours. He will also answer questions about the business of photography. In addition, Michael will explore the principles revealed in “Lighting and the Dramatic Portrait”, and his third book, using illustrations from the books and personal projects. There will be an opportunity to personally greet the author, and have his book signed, afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;The Boston University Photonics Center&lt;br /&gt;8 Saint Mary's St.,&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02215&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: CIPNE Members, Free; Guests, $10; Full-time Students*, $5 (at the door, no pre-registration required).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Full-time students will be required to present their photo-IDs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a CIPNE Event- we'll be in the crowd!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256857597000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254846825000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Michael Grecco: Lighting and the Dramatic Portrait</name><id>11562600</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256684400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11562600/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/d/8/global_11093080.jpeg</photo_url></item>