<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 2, Gill MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01354</zip><lat>42.606136</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-533-1883</phone><name>Barton's Cove</name><city>Gill</city><id>591699</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.524765</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>June 7th Saturday- Connecticut River Bald Eagle Paddle - Barton?s Cove, Gill MA.   &lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:00 am &lt;br /&gt;Leaders:&lt;br /&gt;  Mark Roberts, MRoberts@CIA.com 401-533-1883 Cell&lt;br /&gt;  Jim Cole, JimCole@hotmail.com 401-377-1033&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a 10 mile paddle. Suitable for experienced paddlers but works with all sizes of boat.  Very short boats and slow boats may not want to go all the way, there is an option to turn back, making the trip shorter. Bring a lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expect a fair amount of boat traffic, similar to the Narrow River in RI. However, much of the paddle is in a wide area of the river where it is easy to avoid the boats. You have to pay attention in the narrow sections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a current which typically runs 1.0 mph at most in this section of the Connecticut in summer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This section of the Connecticut was Henderson Lake for over 4,000 years following the last glaciation. The lake was 100? deeper than the river is now (i.e. the water was 100? higher). The banks of the river are that high. This is a gorgeous paddle. You may pass ducks, egrets, great blue herons, king fishers, and ospreys. You will see eagles or your fee will be cheerfully refunded. (Note: there is no fee, but it will be refunded anyway.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will paddle right under the bald eagle nest at the start and again at the end of the trip. The baby eagles will be in the nest, but probably not flying yet. Bring your binoculars as we can paddle pretty close to the nest high up in a tree. We will have a clear view. This is the only eagle nest in the US with a web-cam. Here is the web site to check on the eagles before you go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         www.firstlightpower.com/eagles/ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The eagles are in a large dead tree on an island in Barton?s cove. You cannot go ashore here. Actually, you can go ashore, but you will be arrested (maybe ? just remember Hitchcock?s The Birds). It?s roped off. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start the paddle at Barton?s Cove at the base of Pisgah Mountain behind you (North). From the cove, we paddle east upstream through the wide cove around the peninsula and eventually north into the Narrows following a natural fault line to the graceful arch of the French King Bridge high above the river. We continue north into the French King Gorge with its 250 foot high rocky banks, and past French King Rock to Riverview Recreation Area. Riverview features a beautiful picnic area at the base of Northfield Mountain. We will have lunch here and then return. Check it out on the aerial view of the map below. Riverview is at the end of Ferry Road off Route 63. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Launch from Barton?s Cove, Gill MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AutoNav GPS address 66 French King Hwy, Gill, MA 01354-9718 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From RI, go north on 146 to Worcester, take I-290 East to I-190 North, to route 2 West to Gill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you cross the Connecticut River (on the French King Bridge) you enter Gill. Barton Cove Public Ramp is on the left about 3 miles or so after the bridge. It is about .4 miles before the traffic light, with a big sign ?Boat Ramp.? If you come to a traffic light (well after Orange), you just passed it. Turn around just past the light on the left at the overlook of the dam. The boat ramp will now be on your right. It?s two hours from Providence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call 401-533-1883 if lost.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MapQuest Link: www.mapquest.com/maps/66+French+King+Hwy+Gill+MA+01354-9718/&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Use my photo in a kayak. I'm 5'9" 200 pounds with a shaved head.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213101163000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><why>This is a very scenic paddle.
  - See the baby bald eagles, siblings from last year, their parents and their nest
  - Lots of other critters: egrets, herons, wood ducks, etc.
  - This section of the CT River has high sides ... was Henderson Lake</why><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209390423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Baby Bald Eagle Paddle - Barton's Cove</name><id>7826993</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212847200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/7826993/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/2/1/global_3953409.jpeg</photo_url></item>