<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fellsway East</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02148</zip><lat>42.431187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fellsmere Pond Park</name><city>Malden</city><id>1383675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Rhythm Friends - The Boston Drum Circle is participating in the annual Harvest Moon Festival this Saturday, Sept. 25, at Fellsmere Pond Park in Malden (near the Medford line). The event, sponsored by the Oak Grove Improvement Association and the Chinese Culture Connection, runs from 10:30 - 4:30. Attendance exceeds 1,000. Parking is pretty good, but bring a cart (or a able-bodied friend) if you're carrying a lot of drums. The site is about a 15-minute walk from the Malden Center T station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit www.OakGroveMalden.org for more information and directions. The drum circle is listed on the website and all publicity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Hayes and Dave Curry have signed up to lead (and maybe Josh Fonseca?), and I'd love to have about a dozen or more drummers and dancers on hand. It's a six-hour event, and I suggest we play four, 45-minute sets -- 11:30, 12:30, 1:30, and 2:30 -- during peak attendance. We'll be situated right next to the pond, not far from the main festival site. There's a big rock right in the center of our performance area, which can serve as our altar; so bring items to 'decorate.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've participated in the festival for the past two years, and it's one of the area's best family events with food, entertainment, pony rides, and activities. Admission is free. Many community groups participate. The organizing committee is excited that the drum circle is participating this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can join us! The weather is supposed to be fabulous. Please RSVP ASAP so we know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and blessings, David&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285559106000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Rhythm Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-drum-circle</urlname><id>617617</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Drum Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285249184000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvest Moon Festival this Saturday</name><id>14869590</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285471800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-drum-circle/events/14869590/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_8679361.jpeg</photo_url></item>