<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Choro Democrático is a newly formed Boston-based ensemble dedicated to playing choro, a traditional and primarily instrumental Brazilian musical genre born in Rio de Janeiro during the late 1800’s.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group is an all-acoustic seven-piece ensemble including flute, bandolim, violin, cavaquinho, violão, violão de sete cordas and pandeiro. In case you already know something about choro -- the group’s repertoire ranges from classic choro compositions by Pixinguinha, Ernesto Nazareth and Jacob do Bandolim to more contemporary works by Hermeto Pascoal, Paulinho da Viola and the group’s flutist, Fernando Brandão.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've never heard choro before then you're in for a treat -- roughly speaking choro is to brazilian samba as ragtime is to jazz...beautiful melodies from an earlier time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music contains a variety of moods and textures and incorporates rhythms from Rio and Northeastern Brazil.  Note: the ensemble hosts a traditional roda de choro (circle jam session) once a month at La Luna Caffé in Cambridge, MA. (which is my current new favorite cafe in Central Square) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Choro Democrático and their upcoming performances please visit &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www. chorodemocratico.com" target="_blank"&gt;www. chorodemocratico.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brad Powell</member_name><member_id>930768</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221955623000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220969128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Choro Democrático </name><id>8720932</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221094800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/8720932/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/2/global_5455490.jpeg</photo_url></item>