<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP and &lt;i&gt;only sign up for one or two mini-meetups a month&lt;/i&gt;.  See this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt; for more details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;This is a *special* event for those members in the group who happen to live north of Salem and find getting to Salem a little bit of a drive.  We are going to have a location up in downtown Newburyport (right near route 1 and route 95) for you to get your game on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to attend and live south, I will be happy to carpool you to the event.  Just let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first satellite mini-meetup will involve strategy and thinking games.  The highlight of this game will be Carcassonne.  This is a map building game using tiles where you have to match the ends of tiles together in order for things to form correctly.  In other words, it is very similiar to playing Dominoes where you have to match the ends of dominoes together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other thinking games are welcome.  We would love to play abstract games like Blokus too.  Or even Pentago!&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;Food theme:&lt;br /&gt;The theme for this event will be &amp;quot;brain food&amp;quot;.  You can go ahead and just bring Smartfood brand popcorn or you can bring salmon and crackers because you researched that salmon has Omega-3 which your brain uses.  We will also have generic drinks and snacks on hand for people with dietary restrictions.&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;About the location:&lt;br /&gt;This event will be guest-hosted by my colleague in beautiful downtown Newburyport who is graciously donating their space.  Details will be sent out to the YES RSVP's a couple days before the event.  There will be plenty of room, nothing like cats to worry about and should be a warm, comfortable place for all, I promise.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298205990000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291579527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Strategy Games up North!</name><id>15649203</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298142000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15649203/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/d/1/global_11205793.jpeg</photo_url></item>