<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>261 Broad St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.850883</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Windsor Town Green</name><city>Windsor</city><id>353204</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.644120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&gt;&gt;&gt;  THU 4:55PM UPDATE: 
1) I just talked to the Windsor Chamber of Commerce about the slight chance of a thunderstorm and discovered that due to construction on the town Green, the concert will still be held on the Green, not on the steps of Town Hall, but on the Library (southern) end of the Green (opposite Geissler's).  Please stake out that area instead.  

2) Also, it's is a "go" re: weather, I was told... but just in case it does get rained out, we can go to Ira W.'s in Windsor Locks for an indoor condo party alternative!
IF SO, please MapQuest directions to:
44 Dibble Hollow Lane
Windsor Locks, CT  06096
Ira's Cell#: (860) 604-5792

3) IF not rained out (assumption) following the concert, we'll set up the Fire-Pit / after-party on the banks of the Farmington River... unless "asked to leave", then caravan to Ira's, as a backup.  Directions to the River location and/or Ira's will be handed out at the concert to those who request it.  Please remember:  BYO chairs, snacks and beverages!

- Rob

Rob Pudney
c: (860) 690-9595

***

Please join us for a fun, BEAUTIFUL evening of "FREE Live Outdoor Music" at what "may" be our FINAL outdoor concert of the season, TONIGHT, featuring the "Glamour Girls" performing the most popular dance hits from the 40's through the 80's.

Thursday, August 30 7:00-9:00 PM &gt;&gt;&gt; GATHER @ 6:30 &lt;&lt;&lt;

&gt;&gt;&gt; LOOK FOR: Al R's four orange traffic cones and/or my red reflectors on white sticks.  As this is both a dance concert and visual show, we?ll try to set up camp closer to the stage located on the steps of the WINDSOR Town Hall (NOT South Windsor, as some thought).  See below for Directions &amp; Parking information.

This is a combined gathering of MeetUp &amp; Single Event social networking groups, typically @ 12-36 of us party together each time (spontaneously, with or without RSVP's), sometimes many more!  NEW FRIENDS ARE ALWAYS WELCOME!

&gt;&gt;&gt; BYOB and snacks/Picnic dinner, if you'd like... bring extra for the post-party that typically ensues as we gather around a propane-fueled ceramic FIRE-PIT at a nearby location!  As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly! 

&gt;&gt;&gt; Please do NOT hit "reply".  To cut down on email updates, check out who's 
coming, more details, &amp;/or to RSVP, please visit my free "FREE Live Outdoor 
Music" calendar posting (by 3PM the day of the event for any updated info):  
&lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/6230077/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/6230077/&lt;/a&gt;

FYI: As the various summer concert series are winding down, please sign up for 
my free online calendar of fun (typically free) upcoming social networking 
events geared at singles in their 30's - 50's.  UPCOMING: Funny Bone comedy 
club, games nights, picnics, walks/hikes, and various parties!  Visit: 
&lt;a href="http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/" class="linkified"&gt;http://livemusic.meetup.com/66/calendar/&lt;/a&gt; 

See you there!

- Rob

Rob Pudney 

***Glamour Girls ***  Performing the most popular dance hits from the 40's through the 80's, The Glamour Girls will turn your party or event into an exciting experience...... Fronted by the lovely and talented Amber, Vanessa and Racquel, this seven-piece band will keep you dancing all night long...... With a show highlighted by costume changes and eye-catching choreography, The Glamour Girls present a song selection ranging from the swing of the 40's to the early 60's Sock Hop to the Motown/Soul era, to the disco dance hits of the 70's, to the pop/rock chart-toppers of the 80's and 90's. Artists covered include The Andrews Sisters, Diana Ross &amp; The Supremes, Aretha Franklin, Sister Sledge, Gloria Gaynor, Madonna, The B-52s, The Bangles and many more.
 
I've seen this group perform a couple of times and highly recommend them! - Rob P.

This may very well be our last "FREE Live Outdoor Music" event of this summer... meet new friends TONIGHT before everyone goes into hibernation mode!  

For more venue information call 688-5165 or visit www.windsorcc.org

***
Please MapQuest DIRECTIONS to:

Windsor Town Hall
261 Broad St 
Windsor, CT 06095

Traveling North on I-91, take x-36.
At the end of the exit, take a RIGHT onto Park Ave.
At the end of Park Ave., take a LEFT onto Rt. 159.
The Windsor Green is located downtown on Rt. 159 ? immediately south of where Rt. 305 and Rt. 75 intersect, south of the Farmington River.  Park along the Green, behind the Town Hall / Post Office, side streets, or in Geissler?s parking lot.</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188685872000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187873795000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>&gt; RAIN ALTERNATIVE: &lt; TONIGHT: "Glamour Girls" Windsor Town Green - 6:30</name><id>6230077</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188513000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6230077/</event_url></item>