<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.303934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Scenic Theater</name><city>Rochester</city><id>709969</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.976582</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come learn the Investigative Basics from a professional Electrical Engineer with repair/design experience, extensive Paranormal investigation background, and an excellent teaching record for an evening of hands-on instruction and exploration as we have the freedom of an entire 3-story Theater (under renovation) in downtown Rochester, NH!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi everyone!  We've had a number of new members as well as interest from team members regarding types of equipment we use on our paranormal investigations, so we're going to have an evening to discuss the equipment as well as basics on how to set up.  This will provide an excellent experience for anyone looking to get involved in investigations in a non-judging team environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm encouraging anyone who is interested in electronics and has attended at least one monthly meeting (or with permission) to attend this event, so that you possess some experience and knowledge regarding some of the tech gear.  I'll be talking about basic electronics, different cameras, types of DVRs, cables &amp;amp; adapters, audio recorders and EMF/Magnetic Field/RF formation &amp;amp; detection methods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basically, this is what I'm thinking:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:00 - 8:15   Arrive/Introductions.&lt;br /&gt;8:15 - 9:30   Basic electrical theory, types of equipment, setup/troubleshooting.&lt;br /&gt;9:30 - 12:00 Team exercise/mock investigation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional Notes:&lt;br /&gt;Bring a notebook, flashlight, a folding chair for the discussion, and snacks to share.&lt;br /&gt;Dress warmly as the scenic does not have its heat turned on.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the individual in jeans and a gray hoodie.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie</member_name><member_id>6000445</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254447319000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252166245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Equipment Training Session and Mock Investigation</name><id>11296817</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254009600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11296817/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/1/global_2599441.jpeg</photo_url></item>