<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 St Marys St</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.349552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston University Photonics</name><city>Boston</city><id>1607829</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106735</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is NOT an official Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. I'll be out of the country and unable to attend. Feel free to utilize our message board or comments section to arrange meeting up with other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Sunday, March 11, 2012 from 9a.m. to 4p.m. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Photonics Center &lt;br /&gt;

Boston University &lt;br /&gt;

8 St. Mary's Street &lt;br /&gt;

Boston, MA 02215&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;You must register via the NGT website,&lt;/span&gt; here's the link:&lt;a href="http://ngtravelerseminars.com/travel/"&gt;http://ngtravelerseminars.com/travel/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost is $195 (includes lunch),&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Members of the Seacoast Group may enter&amp;nbsp;"meetup20" to receive a $20 discount&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Passion for Travel: Photos That Tell the Story&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Let National Geographic Traveler photographers Catherine Karnow and Aaron Huey teach you their secrets for capturing the spirit of a place and bringing back images of enduring significance. Learn how to explore a destination visually, find perfect lighting, and anticipate a great moment. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll help you turn your photos into stories, which will make them much more meaningful,&amp;rdquo; says Editor in Chief Keith Bellows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Photos We Love . . . and Why &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;Train your eyes to look for photos that tell a story &amp;mdash; pictures that go beyond &amp;ldquo;just pretty&amp;rdquo; to become powerful images. Explore how travel photography styles change to reflect the evolving travel world, and what makes certain photos leave a lasting impression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Making Great Pictures: Methods and Tips for Travel Photography&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Get a behind-the-scenes look at how amazing photos are made &amp;mdash; not taken. Learn how to build pictures from the ground up by knowing how to explore a place visually, how to find the perfect lighting, and how to anticipate a great moment. Discover why the &amp;ldquo;decisive moment&amp;rdquo; is such a powerful photographic concept, and how to get both the great views and the telling close-ups. Key points on composition will be discussed as well as how to blend in and get access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Travel Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Camera Bag&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

We&amp;rsquo;ll open up our camera bags and reveal the tools we have selected over the years for getting the most versatility with minimal weight and bulk. Learn what your options are for storing and tracking, and what tools will work best for the photos you want to make.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our Passion for Places: Telling the Travelers&amp;rsquo; Tale in Pictures&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Learn how to prepare yourself for your own photographic adventures by doing research about the local culture and landscape before you go. Understanding the power of photographic style coupled with strong content will make your photos tell the story of the places you&amp;rsquo;ve traveled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bring Your Landscapes to Life &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll show how Traveler photographers bring landscapes to life with drama, flair &amp;mdash; and great light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photographing People &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;Photographing people and telling their story can be intimidating once you get up close. Learn how to capture their character and the special moments in their lives while making it a rewarding experience for both of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Connect with a Culture &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;Build travel pictures that explore the culture of a place, whether it&amp;rsquo;s by savoring food and wine, exploring history and architecture, relishing the arts and folkways, or recognizing the magical moments of everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Great Travel Destinations (And Why They&amp;rsquo;re Great For Photography)&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Let us suggest our top ten great travel destinations, why we think they are especially good for photographers, and how to go about finding your own personal &amp;ldquo;Great Destination.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sharing Your Pictures the Digital Way&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Use your photography to make friends, build understanding, and share your passion for the world &amp;mdash; digitally. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss photo-sharing sites (and how to create your own), printing your photographs for display, creating your own cards and calendars, producing self-published books, presenting your photos to an audience, finding local galleries and venues, producing iMovies on DVD, and perhaps even getting published in a travel magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Great Travel Photos Slide Presentation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Get inspired! Gaze upon the winning shots from Traveler&amp;rsquo;s annual photography contest, and see examples of how amateurs get great shots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331475507000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330098172000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Geographic Traveler-A Passion for Travel: Photos That Tell the Story</name><id>53634982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331470800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/53634982/</event_url></item>