<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Le's Vietamese Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>These will be screening at the Harvard Film Archive. I had all intentions of catching these two films but was wary of posting them for a group event as they are screening on a Monday night. Well, then I thought why not meet for dinner before the films which will get us all back home at a reasonable time. The running time for each fillm is only 45 minutes and so the program will be over at 8:30. Makes sense to me. Silent films with live piano are such a treat- the HFA use to present about a dozen or so a year but have cut back lately. Hopefully there will be more upcoming. If you can only make it to the films and not for dinner beforehand please indicate so when you RSVP so I can make a reasonable estimate for the restaurant reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evgeni Bauer was the most important filmmaker of the early Russian cinema, who made about eighty silent films in 5 years before the Russian Revolution of 1917.  Internet Movie Database&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The greatest director you've never heard of.   L. A. Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His work is informed by the Art Nouveau aesthetics and Symbolist sensibility characteristic of turn-of-the-century Russian culture as a whole. Coming to film relatively late after beginning his career as a set designer for the stage, Bauer experimented with effects lighting, camera movement, complex staging and visual uses of interior architecture, often taking those techniques to new extremes.  HFA description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Child of the Big City&lt;/b&gt; 1914 Child of the Big City is a Russian version of a vamp movie, with a touch that makes it different from other stories about poor girls who drain and ruin rich men. 1914 was Russia's craze year for the tango. Elena Smirnova, as the heartless seducer, and G. Iost, as the lover whom she prefers over the unfortunate (and wealthy) suitor who keeps her, are two Moscow ballroom dancers who were already famous as a tango couple. Watch for the bold overhead dolly-in over restaurant tables homing in on a cabaret dancer who happens to be Bauer's wife, Lina. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Daydreams&lt;/b&gt; A screen version of George Rodenbach's novel Bruges-la- Morte, &lt;br /&gt;Daydreams was cinema's first attempt to handle Symbolist prose. Much as in Vertigo (for which Rodenbach was an uncredited source), a dead woman comes back into a man's life as her exact double, in body if not in soul. Unable to go to Bruges (the famous dead city at the turn of the 20th century, today swarming with tourists because of its fame), Bauer laboriously recreates its empty streets in the usually busy and lively Moscow. Mysterious dolly shots make the settings even more haunting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bauer reached his peak in the genre of social drama, such as Gryozy (1915) (aka.. Daydreams), starring Alexander Wyrubow as Sergei, an obsessed widower who falls for an actress because of her resemblance of his late wife, but soon their characters clash, leading to a tragic end. Movie Database&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And for obscurity's sake, Guy Maddlin (Brand Upon the Brain) cites Bauer as one of his major influences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at Le's ( formally Pho Pasteur). This is located in the Harvard Sq mini-mall directly above John Harvard's Brew House.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203261606000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2 Russian Silent Films With Live Piano</name><id>7348882</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203979500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7348882/</event_url></item>