<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several people have asked me&amp;nbsp;recently, why&amp;nbsp;I haven't scheduled an event lately and when is the next event. I've been in the summer chillin kind of mood. So I'd love to host a get together this Thursday but I think it'll be a let's chip in for Pizza or Chinese food event. I'll have soda here and left over liquor from other events - other than that, it's BYOB. Bring a snacky or dessert food if you want. It's an equal opportunity game playing establishment so bring your favorite game along. I think I personally&amp;nbsp;like to get in one round of Pictionary this week. I need a few good laughs. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it's mega hot and you want to cool down, the pool is&amp;nbsp;open so bring your suit and a towel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allergy alert: I have a dog named&amp;nbsp;Princess - she's been to the groomers so&amp;nbsp;her shedding is not as bad as&amp;nbsp;it was, but still she's a long haired dog that sheds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking logistics: Please park along the side of Main street,&amp;nbsp;the CVS or Funeral home parking lots. No parking in front or along the&amp;nbsp;side of my home, due to cranky neighbors. :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring a $1.00 for Nina our wonderful organizer to help pay for the cost of the meetup group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to hosting you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>163 S Main St. Colchester Ct</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret </member_name><member_id>5111537</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311965764000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311700684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Back by popular demand Thursday night Game night at Margariiiitttaaass</name><id>27102101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/27102101/</event_url></item>