<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Garden St &amp; Waterhouse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7813011791 (Chris' Cell)</phone><name>Cambridge Common</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>442822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boy Howdy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How goes it, home skillets? Y'all remember my purty face? This southern belle been down crackin' whips in the Louisiana Bayou, killin' gators and riding fierce-but-lovable swamp beasties. I wusn't plannin' on stayin' long, but this swamp merman and I got a little ... personal. And I just couldn't get enuff of the grits and chicken! MMM Mmm mmm... grits. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But all good things be comin' to an end always. I mighta got a wee tiddly close to my merman and, like a corndog makin' love, I done did get her gone good 'n knocked up. A little word of advice: don't go get mermen lumpy and refried without foreseein' and expectin' consequences!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shotgun weddings. My my my. Frightenin'! That long barrel pointin' down at my puddy face. Sweat beadin' on my brow, eyes buggin' and red. But I ran. Oh how I ran. Oh how my tuckus stung. Oh how I couldn't sit for a week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So thass right: I be on the lamb. I ran all the way back to Baweston and here I be, orgizgonizing some ultimate doohickey. We be playin' on Cambridge Common as usual, 8 PM sharp is when you'll see my tanned hide. That there baseball diamond, a few furlongs from Hahhvard Esquire. If this be your first time a-comin', y'all shoulds probably read that there &lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/about/"&gt;About Us&lt;/a&gt; section. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we toss some doohickeys around in pitch black, we be drinkin' whiskey and starting fires around the Square. Come on by; it'll be a real southern romp!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, it'd be super rad if you be bringin' some cash money ($$$) for us poor originizer folk. We pay out our butts for frisbees, lanyards, smiles, rum, glowsticks, field cones, and first aid kits. If not, that's cool too: we be free, fo' life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Y'alls could get &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=10+garden+st+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=33.626896,81.738281&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.376807,-71.119566&amp;amp;spn=0.007656,0.019956&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;directions to the Cambridge Common&lt;/a&gt; if need be. If you can't come on the back of a gator, I'd recommend the MBTA. Parkin' can be tricky for them fuel-runnin' vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you gots any questions, I be a friendly folk and y'alls shouldn't worry 'bout comin' over to the ditch I be sleepin' in and wakin' me up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best be seein' you Tuesday,&lt;br /&gt;Chris Croc McC + Amy &amp;quot;gator&amp;quot; Spelz.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amy</member_name><member_id>4875881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209431961000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208187594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Git down, stay down wiff some flying doohickeys this Tuesday night!</name><id>7736850</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208304000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7736850/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/c/global_3460060.jpeg</photo_url></item>