<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Farwell Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01879</zip><lat>42.690052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 649-3854</phone><name>Parlee Farms</name><city>Tyngsboro</city><id>669389</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.426857</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Venez nous rejoindre chez Parlee Farms à Tyngsboro.  Nous aurons l'occasion d'observer une tradition de la Nouvelle Angleterre...la récolte de pommes.  Après la récolte, nous partagerons un dessert et cidre chez Mary's Country Kitchen (qui fait partie de la ferme).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on nearly 100 beautiful acres near the Merrimack River in Tyngsboro, Parlee Farms offers the finest fruits, vegetables and flowers. Owned by Mark and Ellen Parlee, we began in 1988 with two acres of strawberries, a scale set on a plank that was held up by cinder blocks, and a blue tarp over our heads to keep the rain off the fresh picked strawberries, the scale, and us - in that order! Along with our two daughters, Mary and Annie, we worked hard as a family to make our dream of farming a reality. Over the years, we were fortunate to be able to purchase beautiful river-bottom land on Farwell Road. Almost 70% our farm is preserved under Massachusetts' Agricultural Preservation Restriction Program, which means the land will always be used for farming and cannot be developed. As we added land, we added more crops. To sell the crops, we added a Farmstand, Annie's Animal Barns, Mary's Country Kitchen, 10 hay ride wagons and our wonderful employees to keep everything running smoothly. Of course, this would not have been possible without the fabulous customers that return every season. To them and to our new customers, we thank you! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mary’s Country Kitchen offers tasty treats related to each picking season, as well as a great selection of ice cream. The menu changes as the Picking Season changes. During strawberry season, our menu features mouthwatering desserts such as our delicious Old Fashioned Strawberry Shortcake. We start with fresh baked scones made from scratch in our bakery. We then smother the scone with our fresh picked strawberries, and top it with whipped cream. Fresh strawberry smoothies and sundaes are also on the menu. The summer season offers fresh blueberry - raspberry sundaes and fresh fruit frappes. During the fall, our farmstand is filled with the smell of warm apple crisp and hot cider. To warm you up on those cool mornings or just to get a jump-start, pick up a hot cup of coffee. Whatever you choose, we hope you will enjoy every delicious bite!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the farm stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann</member_name><member_id>1968241</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287251989000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>french-584</urlname><id>376538</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Dis-moi French Conversation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286928214000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apple Picking and Dessert/Cider --- Récolte de pommes avec dessert</name><id>15090096</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287241200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/french-584/events/15090096/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/8/8/global_17347416.jpeg</photo_url></item>