<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;This is  one of Ingmar Bergman's films The Brattle is screening  in their tribute to the great Swedish director. The film is only 81 minutes in length and so even though this is on a Friday night we should get to the restaurant at a reasonable time for our  group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Persona (1966,  81 minutes)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a performance, the actress Elisabet Vogler suddenly stops communicating with everybody else. She is perfectly sane in her body and mind, only she has decided to enter an existence of  complete silence. The nurse Alma has to take care of her. Slowly, the relationship between the two women grows; they get closer and, finally, slide and get lost into each other. Persona is an astonishing &amp;quot;existential drama on the topic of the double and the mask&amp;quot;,   to be and to appear, an amazing game of roles in which the two women are trapped; they both lose the role played in their lives, modeling each other, until they completely lose themselves. One of the most upsetting Bergman's movies, always hovering between reality and dream: based on long plan sequences, composed of oscillations between close-ups and long shots that underline the unstable women's relationship, and marked by the wonderful Sven Nykvist's photography (shots against the light, light and shade effects, amazing shadowplays) and by the unforgettable performance of the two actresses (who perfectly manage &amp;quot;to express what can't be expressed&amp;quot;), Liv Ullman and Bibi Andersson.   Wings of Desire Cinema&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A film we return to over the years, for the beauty of its images and because we hope to understand its mysteries.  Roger Ebert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A watershed film in its economy, symbolism, and frank sexuality, Ingmar Bergman's Persona ranks as one of the director's most personal pieces, breaking from his earlier, more explicit work in favor of the abstract, intuitive style that he would continue to develop ...When Bibi Andersson's nurse Alma comes to the bedside of Liv Ullmann's Elizabet one night, the mere suggestion of their hallucinatory encounter is enough to shake the film off its sprockets -- the celluloid literally breaks and melts on screen, before our eyes. At no other time in his career had Bergman seemed more trusting of his performers; he purges Persona of any narrative conventions but its two characters and their seaside setting. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197316622000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195179342000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ingmar Bergman's Persona at The Brattle</name><id>6750583</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197075600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6750583/</event_url></item>