<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus day weekend is peak foliage season. We do plan to have a long weekend of hikes, bike rides, BBQ and bonfires! Saturday we'll have an easy hike and then head over to a nearby social event. Sunday will be open to a moderate hike or a bike ride or the wonderful Fryeburg Fair is on the other side of Hurricane Mountain Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out Last Year's Photos: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/photos/3807942/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/photos/3807942/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never been to our house then this is an ideal weekend to make your first visit. The Wedeln Ski House is located on the Bartlet / N. Conway NH townline, close to the Cranmore Ski Area. The house has hiking and biking trails right out the back side of the house. Accomodations are only $25 per night, bring your own bedding and toiletries. &lt;span&gt;Many people do not have Monday off, so you can come up on Friday and leave on Sunday or stay through Monday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details on food and beverages to be sent out to "YES" RSVPS. There are also many great restaurants in nearby North Conway as well as plenty of tax free outlet shopping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain bike update:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 11th Bike For Books  event run by the North Conway Library will take place Saturday October 6. Bike Loops of 2, 5, 10, 20, 30 miles will be available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details can be found here: &lt;a href="http://www.northconwaylibrary.com/uploads/PDFs/Registration%20Form%202012.pdf"&gt;http://www.northconwaylibrary.com/uploads/PDFs/Registration%20Form%202012.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking update&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday 10/6 - We have 2 hike leaders to lead a hike on Hedghog mountain for the Saturday of Columbus day weekend. The loop over Hedgehog Mountain on the U.N.H. Trail is 4.8 miles with 1,450 feet of elevation gain. A leisurely circuit of Allen's Ledge, the summit and the East Ledges is a day well spent. It should take the average person about 4 hours at a lesurly pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday 10/7 - From Hike leader David B.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a ten mile hike here.  Let's start early 9AM at the trail head.  Not a hike to do with a hangover I would imagine. Can I get an idea on how many are interested?  I could make a loop if we spot cars. Or if the attendees have done Stony we could do an alternate route, say, starting at Gorham and ending at Rte 2 in Shelburne area. The second option I remember, Gorham to Shelburne, was spectacular.  I have not done Stony yet so either way is fine with me. &lt;strong&gt;Wedelns Sunday Hike Columbus Day Weekend&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mt Moriah via Stony Brook&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Recommended Bring Headlamps and dress in layers&lt;/strong&gt; 10 miles 8 hours  Hikers Welcome &lt;span&gt;(understand your limits)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;State:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.outdoor.com/places/new-hampshire/" target="_blank"&gt;New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; White Mountains National Forest &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Length&lt;/strong&gt;, One-Way: 3.5 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Trail Type:&lt;/strong&gt; Out and Back &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Minimum Elevation:&lt;/strong&gt; 934 feet &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Maximum Elevation:&lt;/strong&gt; 3127 feet &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Elevation Change:&lt;/strong&gt; 2200 feet &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Best Season:&lt;/strong&gt; May to October &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Usage:&lt;/strong&gt; Heavy &lt;br /&gt;

 Parking: White Mountains National Forest Fee Site. Trail Information The Stony Brook Trail leads from New Hampshire Route 16 near Gorham to the &lt;a href="http://www.outdoor.com/activities/backpacking/new-hampshire-carter-moriah-trail/" target="_blank"&gt;Carter-Moriah Trail&lt;/a&gt; between Mount Moriah and North Carter. It is mostly easy walking and probably the most popular day hike of Mount Moriah, although there is significant elevation gain due to the low starting elevation. Most of the trail is enjoy with a gradual ascent until it approaches the terminus. From the parking lot, the Stony Brook Trail immediately crosses a bridge over Stony Brook and continues up the far side, crossing another stream over a small gorge. The trail follows an old woods road then suddenly turns right and crossesStony Brook again, this time without a bridge. The trail climbs to reach another woods road at 0.8 miles and turns left. The trail continues up this road which becomes steeper and fainter. At 2.3 miles, there is another brook crossing and the trail ascends to the col between Mount Moriah and North Carter at 3.5 miles, where it ends at the Carter-Moriah Trail. The junction with the Moriah Brook Trail is just to the left. The summit of Mount Moriah is 1.5 miles to the left on the Carter-Moriah Trail. Directions From Gorham, NH: &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive south for 1.8 miles on New Hampshire Route 16 to the parking area on the left just south of the Peabody River Bridge. The parking lot is plowed in winter. From Interstate 93: &lt;br /&gt;

 Take exit 35 off of Interstate 93 near Franconia Notch. Drive 13 miles north on US Route 3 to New Hampshire Route 115. Turn right on Route 115 and follow for about 10 miles to the end at US Route 2. Turn right on US Route 2 and drive 14.5 miles to Gorham town railroad station. Turn right on New Hampshire Route 16 and drive 1.8 miles south to the parking area on the left just south of the Peabody River Bridge. The parking lot is plowed in winter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday 10/8 - Bald Faces - This one is being run by the Random Group of Hikers meetup. Not affiliated with anyone at Wedeln. If you want to go on that one, you will have to RSVP on that meetup site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More Options!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're looking for something to do this weekend:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attitash - Oktoberfest with local beers (Tucks, Moat, etc), Bavarian music, German food, keg toss, stein-holding competition, mechanical bull-riding (not sure what that has to do with Oktoberfest but always fun to watch...) It's being held on Saturday and Sunday starting at Noon. Admission is $10. &lt;a href="http://attitash.com/summer-events.html?id=5163"&gt;http://attitash.com/summer-events.html?id=5163&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attitash - Hills &amp;amp; Hops 5K trail race at 9:15 A on Saturday. &lt;a href="http://attitash.com/summer-events.html?id=5272"&gt;http://attitash.com/summer-events.html?id=5272&lt;/a&gt; Register online for $25, but you can always sign up at Attitash that morning for $30. The race takes place on the mountain, and according to the description, you run up, down, and across ski trails, so come prepared with proper footwear and clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;To RSVP - a $26 non refundable down payment for this weekend will be required for guests by Thursday September 27th. You will be asked to pay this when you RSVP. This is equal to one nights guest fee and an online convenience charge of $1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;No refunds offered!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;Ages - This is only open to guests 21 years of age or older.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not use GPS to find house, you will get lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions will be sent to all attendees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jillfrances and Lynn will be your hosts this weekend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be given out to Meetup Guests who have RSVP'd Yes and paid up in advance by Sept 27</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lynn</member_name><member_id>9159010</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>jillfrances G.</member_name><member_id>10932020</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349987215000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347547600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Columbus Day Weekend at the Wedelns! October 5 - October 8</name><id>82218512</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>219600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349488800000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/82218512/</event_url></item>