<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Mohegan Sun Blvd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06360</zip><lat>41.492584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1.888.226.7711</phone><name>Mohegan Sun</name><city>Norwich</city><id>430928</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.095950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A night out to Mohegan Sun is never a fail. So we're going back on Friday October 14. That night you have the option to see one of the best R&amp;amp;B group of the 90s, the group that bought you the panty droppin' hit "I'll Make Love To You", I'm talking about Boyz II Men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details for Boyz II Men: The show is free. Show time is at 8pm. Location is the Wolf Den. Since the show is at 8, I will assign the meet up time to be at 7pm. This way we have a 1 hour window to gather up whoever, get a drink and get settled by 8. The show should end around 11. Which is when i want the meetup at Ultra 88 to happen. Someone suggested the Boyz II Men concert as an event. I will talk to that person to be the host of that part, if she can't i will step in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultra 88 details: I would like to start Ultra 88 at 11. Of course you can come before and do whatever before then too. Cover Charge is $10. &amp;nbsp;I'll eventually look into VIP service and post up the details to see what people feel about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So to recap... Boyz II Men Meetup is @ 7:00pm (location to meet up in the casino is to be determined) performance is FREE .... Ultra 88 Meetup is @ 11:00pm cover charge is $10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the Mohegan on October 14 for Boyz II Men at 7 and Ulltra 88 at 11!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(860) 357-7264&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318703123000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315282696000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ultra 88 Night Club + Boyz II Men @ Mohegan Sun</name><id>32397842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318633200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/32397842/</event_url></item>