<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>182 Hayden Rowe Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.205910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Meeting at Cassie's House!</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>1578369</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.511398</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A couple safety tips and reminders:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;No Flexi/retractable leashes please.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; There are going to be a lot of dogs and people in close quarters, and we do NOT want leashes getting tangeled together.&amp;nbsp;  Bring poop bags...&amp;nbsp; remember we are representing our breeds and the  NEBBC: classy and responsible!&amp;nbsp; You may want to bring a travel  water/bowl for your pup.&amp;nbsp; It shouldn't be too warm, and there will be a  water bowl provided back at the house.&amp;nbsp; NEBBC T-shirts will be for sale  for $10, which will directly contribute to off-setting the cost of this  event!&amp;nbsp; Lastly, remember that this is a LOT of bully breeds in one place  at one time.&amp;nbsp; The dogs will be able to interact, of course, but be  mindful.&amp;nbsp; Do NOT let leashes get tied together, and respect each others'  space.&amp;nbsp; This is not the event for aggressive dogs.&amp;nbsp; YOU know your dog,  but the public doesn't, and aggressive displays of any kind counter-act  what we are trying to do here.&amp;nbsp; Thank you and read on for the meeting  place change...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Handlers and dogs will meet at Cassie's HOUSE at 182 Hayden Rowe Street, Hopkinton at 12:30p for a meet-and-greet and training opportunity.&amp;nbsp; Park on the street (we have this approved by the town: just don't block any driveways.&amp;nbsp; There is also a pub called Cornell's just barely up the street from my house toward Milford.&amp;nbsp; You can park there if you like.)&amp;nbsp; You will notice the house by all the BALLOONS!!!&amp;nbsp; Walk around to the back yard.&amp;nbsp; Walk to commence at 1:00p, on a predetermined route through town.&amp;nbsp; Once our walk is finished (expect to take about an hour or so), we'll make the loop and head back to my house for food, drinks, and some outdoor play time with our pups; unfortunately the yard is not fenced, so bring some long leashes if you like!&amp;nbsp; Some of you may have travel crates (I have a pop-up variety I got at Target) if your pooch needs a break when we get back!&amp;nbsp; Weather permitting, you may also have him rest in your car. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Guests of any variety (human or canine!) are welcome to this event, and we will be accepting donations to the NEBBC to fund future (larger) events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Reminder: PEANUT BUTTER PLUS Drive...&amp;nbsp; We will take this opportunity to collect items for local shelter BayPath Humane Society, one of the only no-kill shelters in the area who routinely takes (and loves!) pit bulls.&amp;nbsp; We will be accepting peanut butter, dog toys, leashes, food, bowls and even cat supplies.&amp;nbsp; For a complete list, visit BayPath's Wish List: &lt;a href="http://www.baypathhumane.org/content/view/67/69/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.baypathhumane.org/content/view/67/69/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Donatable items can be brought with you and collected pre- or post-walk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Questions or concerns, call Cassie at 508 380 8853.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Punish the Deed, Not the Breed,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;Cassie-Leigh Stock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;President&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;New England Bully Breed Club&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bully Dogs everywhere and our blue and gold balloons!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303040183000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>What a site!  A parade a dogs sporting their NEBBC blue and gold (bandanas will be provided) demonstrating how great our beloved bullies can be on a pack walk through small-town Hopkinton.  Walk to end at my house for food/drinks and play!</why><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>78</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298477257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bully Parade through the center of quaint Hopkinton &amp; Peanut Butter PLUS drive!</name><id>16673871</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301243400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/16673871/</event_url></item>