<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Theater District</address_2><address_1>31-37 Stuart St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351028</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-338-8586</phone><name>Jacob Wirth</name><city>Boston</city><id>50208</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063927</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's (w)ring out one last happy hour in 2012 at &lt;a href="http://jacobwirth.com/pages/beer.html"&gt;Jacob Wirth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WOW! Another wonderful year of happy times with great drinking buddies. THANK YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come out to enjoy friendly conversation with new and familiar folks before you head into 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is another amateur drinking day (as Luis and Vinnie call it), so I'll be there at 4 to get the prime seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive when you can and stay as long as you're able.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first new member who finds me, gets a free drink. Don't be shy...Say hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a Special THANK YOU! for those who sign up by noon on NYE and show up before 8 on NYE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morgan J. White, Jr. is the undisputed Master of the Trivia Universe and will be there with his mesmerizing format. After 30 years he continues to amaze folks with his one-of-a kind trivia show at which you provide categories and he uses his mind-boggling breadth of knowledge to create questions on the spot for your chance at prizes. Along with being smart, Morgan is personable and exudes a geeky coolness. The game format is very simple, the first table to answer three questions correctly in a round wins a prize. There isn't any need to figure out a team name, submit answer sheets nor calculate team scores....it's easy breezy as well as highly entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivia begins at 5:30 PM and ends at 7:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacob Wirth is one of Boston's oldest restaurants and provides the closest approximation to a lively Bavarian bier garten with a great and varied beer selection as well as large communal tables. On Monday's you can get .25 wings all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're more than welcome to show up for the trivia or just the camaraderie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Happy Hour Crew, check out the photos of those who RSVPd Yes so you can find the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU CAN MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER AT THE BAR HOWEVER, IF YOU SIT AT THE TABLES A GROUP BILL BE BE PRESENTED.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vloraboston.com/menu.html"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MBTA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://hopstop.com/"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route five (5) minute walk from Green Line Boylston subway stop or Orange Line Tufts Medical subway stop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be seated at the tables near the host station and next to the Trivia guys table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356998478000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354106967000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our Last Happy Hour of Twenty Twelve</name><id>dhznwdyqqbpc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356987600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/93154042/</event_url></item>