<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Greetings all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though it's very short notice and holiday time, I invite everyone interested to meet informally over French Toast and Cocoa this Sunday afternoon at 3pm at the Portland Public Market on Congress St.     I'll be prepared to stump all comers with my latest quandary, and marvel over the new Word Lens app (thanks Zev) etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you can make it then or not, I'm interested in hearing any thoughts you might have for ways this group can be of use to you.  I've a meeting coming up on Wed. with the Center for Maine Creativity who has offered to help us in various ways and I'd love to be armed with your feedback.  My primary intention is to have them help us find some great places with a projector to meet, including some businesses interested in hosting a particular discussion (complete with buffet) related to our passions, but I'm confident there are ways they could help that haven't come to my mind yet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently: My vision for the structure of one of those more formal meetings still includes having about 1/2 the time upfront for everyone to show, tell &amp;amp; ask re: issues of interest and then a longer interactive presentation about some programming, publishing, and/or marketing issue that's arranged in advance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also: Erik Mitchell of Maine Frameworks has already proposed another kind of meeting, which we're planning to try in January, during which we focus on building something together.  Whatever we end up trying to make, I know that going through the steps needed to make it ready for all the newish iOS devices (ipad &amp;amp; retina) will be very helpful.      One very strong contender for programming topics on which we can collaborate in this way is Core Data, so I have an idea for a data-based app structure we could work on over the course of many such meetings. More details on that to come, but the sooner you suggest the kinds of functionality you'd like to work on, the more likely we'll make it part of the fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thanks for reading and considering sharing your thoughts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;Brian&lt;br /&gt;brianureeves@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be upstairs, probably at the long table toward the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Reeves</member_name><member_id>4215226</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332651979000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>interested parties</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-iPhone-Developers-Network</urlname><id>1454525</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine iOS Developer Network  (iPhone/iPad)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292639009000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>another less formal meeting / soliciting your thoughts for the near future</name><id>15763423</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292788800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-iPhone-Developers-Network/events/15763423/</event_url></item>