<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>write for info</address_2><address_1>New Fairfield  06812</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06812</zip><lat>41.553928</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203 746 2240 </phone><name>20 Cloverleaf Drive</name><city>New Fairfield</city><id>631928</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.485901</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Short version: for those who hate to read all this stuff (See new Bonus Prize update at bottom)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween Costume Party at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's place. &lt;br /&gt;BYO Booze, Food, Music &lt;br /&gt;Party Starts at 10/31/09 at 7PM &lt;br /&gt;Buffet put out as guest arrive &lt;br /&gt;Parking: Pull up front door, unload, drive out and find parking &lt;br /&gt;Kids welcome and can trick or treat the neighborhood &lt;br /&gt;No Drugs of any kind &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Amazing News!!!! Mojo Myles and his band will be joining us with his musical Jazz and Blues magic at this years party.  He's AMAZING!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a look at his site: &lt;a href="http://www.mylesmancuso.com/mylessite_002.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mylesmancu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Short version: for those who hate to read all this stuff&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween Costume Party at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's place.&lt;br /&gt;BYO Booze, Food, Music&lt;br /&gt;Party Starts at 10/31/09 at 7PM&lt;br /&gt;Buffet put out as guests arrive&lt;br /&gt;Parking: Pull up front door, unload, drive out and find parking&lt;br /&gt;Kids welcome and can trick or treat the neighborhood&lt;br /&gt;No Drugs of any kind&lt;br /&gt;You must leave sober: Either have a designated driver or stay over&lt;br /&gt;Costume prizes&lt;br /&gt;Bring friends&lt;br /&gt;See suggestions on what to bring at bottom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: We will be &amp;quot;shooting&amp;quot; some footage of Myles and if you are in witness protection, on the run or camera shy, you may want to wear a good disguise costume.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The LONG Version:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The party is at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's house. This is a special invite to all our friends, their friends &amp;amp; members of all of our closely knit groups,  Plus the throngs of our enemies, And anyone else who knows anyone either as an acquaintance, club member or in the biblical sense. As a mater of fact, this party will be of biblical proportions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It starts on Saturday, Oct 31, Halloween and runs till we kick everyone out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Party Schedule:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Sat Oct 31&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Arrive  around 7 PM.  Stay as long as you like or till we throw you out. If you drink too much you will not be permitted to drive. You must leave with someone else in the drivers seat or stay over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;ANYONE WISHING TO HELP OUT Contact us ASAP. Thanks&lt;br /&gt;Bruce &amp;amp; Deb&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BYOE (Everything) Bottles of booze, a delicious dish for all to enjoy, Music etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffet dinner starts at about 7 PM in the Dining room, eat and drink and be merry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got Karaoke CDs, bring em. We have 12,000 songs in our music library but Just in case, bring your own favorites in either CD format or iPod, 33, 45 or 78 RPM. Records. (sorry but our 8 track is broken)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be prizes for Best Costume, most original costume. funniest looking without a costume.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;ABSOLUTELY NO DRUGS, PERIOD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've got lots of advance notice. Come and be with us as we celebrate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;WHAT TO BRING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Send us what your best dish is in an email or in your RSVP and we'll add it to the list so others will know what to expect. We'll post it on the event calendar of Amazing Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suggestions: 3 to 5 pound lobsters, Filet Mignon, Beluga Caviar. Truffles, &amp;quot;Pâté de foie gras&amp;quot; Johnny walker blue, Extra handsome, smart, wealthy, educated men. (always in short supply so BRING MEN)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If You're are like us and rest of the world and in this economy you can bring Pasta, Burgers, Dogs, Caserole, Shrimp, Ribs, Salads, Chicken dishes, Deviled eggs or your own favorite speciality.. desserts, You name it, we'll all eat it. If you're staying over, eggs, bacon, ham etc.&lt;br /&gt;(bring extra men that are at least breathing)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOOZE: Rum is always in short supply, Also, Tequila, Baileys, Margarita mix, Bloody Mary mix, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are lots of other parties that night. Make the rounds. But we warn you. Once you get here, you won't want to leave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you are in wittiness protection or on the lamb, the party will be video recorded. Persons with ankle bracelets should note that there is no cell service at our place, you should notify the authorities accordingly. Persons with heart conditions, lack of self esteem, anxiety and depression, please leave all that at the door.&lt;br /&gt;You must leave sober: Either have a designated driver or stay over &lt;br /&gt;Costume prizes &lt;br /&gt;Bring friends&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The LONG Version:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The party is at Bruce &amp;amp; Deb's house. This is a special invite to all our friends, their friends &amp;amp; members of all of our closely knit groups, Plus the throngs of our enemies, And anyone else who knows anyone either as an acquaintance, club member or in the biblical sense. As a mater of fact, this party will be of biblical proportions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It starts on Saturday, Oct 31, Halloween and runs till we kick everyone out. &lt;br /&gt;Party Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sat Oct 31. &lt;br /&gt;Arrive around 7 PM. Stay as long as you like or till we throw you out. If you drink too much you will not be permitted to drive. You must leave with someone else in the drivers seat or stay over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ANYONE WISHING TO HELP OUT Contact us ASAP. Thanks &lt;br /&gt;Bruce &amp;amp; Deb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BYOE (Everything) Bottles of booze, a delicious dish for all to enjoy, Music etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buffet dinner starts at about 7 PM in the Dining room, eat and drink and be merry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got Karaoke CDs, bring em. We have 12,000 songs in our music library but Just in case, bring your own favorites in either CD format or iPod, 33, 45 or 78 RPM. Records. (sorry but our 8 track is broken)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be prizes for Best Costume, most original costume. funniest looking without a costume. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always ABSOLUTELY NO DRUGS, PERIOD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've got lots of advance notice. Come and be with us as we celebrate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING Send us what your best dish is in an email or in your RSVP and we'll add it to the list so others will know what to expect. We'll post it on the event calendar of Amazing Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggestions: 3 to 5 pound lobsters, Filet Mignon, Beluga Caviar. Truffles, &amp;quot;Pâté de foie gras&amp;quot; Extra handsome, smart, wealthy, educated men. (always in short supply so BRING MEN)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If You're like the us and rest of the world and in this economy you can bring Pasta, Burgers, Dogs, Caserole, Shrimp, Ribs, Salads, Chicken dishes, Deviled eggs or your own favorite speciality.. desserts, You name it, we'll all eat it. If you're staying over, eggs, bacon, ham etc. &lt;br /&gt;(bring extra men that are at least breathing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are lots of other parties that night. Make the rounds. But we warn you. Once you get here, you won't want to leave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you are in wittiness protection or on the lamb, the party will be video recorded. Persons with ankle bracelets should note that there is no cell service at our place, you should notify the authorities accordingly. Persons with heart conditions, lack of self esteem, anxiety and depression, please leave all that at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BONUS UPDATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention ladies and gentlemen:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a GRAND PRIZE given out for the person who.......... Drummmmm rolllll.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brings the most MEN with them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yup, there is a testosterone shortage at the party.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If a woman wins, there's a real gold and diamond ring in it for you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If a man wins, trust me, you'll like your prize&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rules&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you come in the door, tell Bruce or Deb how many men you've brought to the party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is in addition to prizes for best costume in different categories&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus&lt;br /&gt;If you've got an instrument, bring it or if play the piano feel free to entertain us during the breaks in the band's play on one of the pianos lurking around the house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all at the party&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257203501000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251894975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HALLOWEEN PARTY AT BRUCE &amp; DEB's Place (special guest Mojo Myles Band)</name><id>11267479</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257030000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11267479/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/2/global_10537362.jpeg</photo_url></item>