<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>239 Woburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.519917</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Unitarian Universalist Church</name><city>Reading</city><id>9738042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116348</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Just a reminder about the Fibromyalgia Recovery Workshop this coming Saturday&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Those that have signed up to attend and have not prepaid please call me for confirmation at 617-943-5570 as soon as possible, thank you. I have to pay the rental for the room at Loring House and need to know how many are really coming.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you know of anyone stuck in their recovery from Fibromyalgia, loved ones or health care practioners wanting to know more about the techniques, treatments and tools that get you to the next level of health and pain reduction this class is for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topics include but not limited to: integrative approaches, Central Nervous System repatterning, essential testing, viral loads, Fibro food planning, supplemention and why it's crucial to recovery, best meds with fewest side effects, why medications are so toxic to the Fibro community, why detoxification and gut health are crucial to recovery, the importance of elevating your pH for pain reduction and general health, exercises and stretches that help not harm, trigger point techqnieus you need and can use on yourself, how to increase your neurotransmitter levels, self-help tools for pain relief and the benefits of medical marijuana over narcotics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a unique class you don't want to miss. 150 minutes (The class is limited to 12 participants, fibromyalgia friendly environment, two scheduled breaks, feel free to get up and stretch anytime during class) &lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;$40, essential handouts included&lt;/span&gt;.  &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Bring notebook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Prepay below to hold your spot as attendance is limited. Call Betsy at 623-251-7547 with any questions on payment or content of class. My direct email is &lt;a href="mailto:btzee6@gmail.com"&gt;btzee6@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Website: east&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;westpainsolutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Due to the small class size no refunds are offered but if you miss a class you can take the next one or have a 20 minute phone consultation in its place&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Betsy is a Certified Bonnie Prudden Myotherapist/Exericse Therapist, Certified Therapeutic Lifestyle Educator (trained in reversing and preventing disease, food plans for your unique situation, the proper supplements for your disease and how to exercise without hurting yourself). Betsy is also certified as a Reiki Master, Advanced Medical Hypnotherapist and Fibromyalgia Educator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Betsy has CEU's in treating Fibromyalgia and related pain syndromes from the National Fibromyalgia Association, University of San Diego Medical School, Omega Institute, Foundation for Care Management and Metagenics Corporation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Betsy teaches Fibromyalgia Recovery and No More Back Pain classes at Paradise Valley Community College and Mesa Community College in Arizona.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Betsy has suffered from Fibromyalgia since childhood.  She teaches her clients how to use a successful, transferable protocol she used to recover her health. This protocol is customized for each individual's symptoms and results in a significant reduction in pain and other Fibromyalgia symptoms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At UU Church of Reading, Loring House (old gray Victorian on church property) technically on Summer Ave.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364067285000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362002403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fibromyalgia Recovery Workshop</name><id>106754412</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364058000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/106754412/</event_url></item>