<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I just realized this upcomming weekend is Seek the Peak on Mt. Washington.  Since it will be very crowded on Big George, I have set up this alternative hike for those who wish to be away from the crowds.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Lonesome Lake parking lot and then shuttling over to the Mt. Kinsman Trailhead.  This will allow us to do a one way thru hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read the below for additional information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the hikers responsibility code and waiver which can be found on this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must at a minimum be able to average 2 miles an hour and to hike two hour stretches without breaks.  Know your abilities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance is 9.98 miles and estimated time is 7:49.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;starting at Mount Kinsman Trailhead 44° 10' 09&amp;quot; 71° 45' 50&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;This trail climbs to the Kinsman Ridge Trail, 0.4 mi. north of North&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman from the east side of NH 116 at the Franconia-Easton&lt;br /&gt;town line, about 4.4 mi. south of NH 18 in Franconia village and&lt;br /&gt;2.0 mi. north of the Easton town hall. There is limited roadside&lt;br /&gt;parking; do not block driveways. There is a sign for the town line a&lt;br /&gt;few yards north of the trail, but most of the time, there has not&lt;br /&gt;been a sign for the trail itself, which follows a logging road closed&lt;br /&gt;by a chain gate between two granite pillars opposite a house.&lt;br /&gt;2.10 mi 1 hr 46 min +1391 ft on Mt Kinsman Trail&lt;br /&gt;2.10 mi 1 hr 46 min +1391 ft This trail climbs to the Kinsman Ridge Trail north of North&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman. There is limited roadside parking; do not block&lt;br /&gt;driveways. There is a sign for the town line a few yards north of&lt;br /&gt;the trail, but most of the time, there has not been a sign for the&lt;br /&gt;trail itself, which follows a logging road closed by a chain gate&lt;br /&gt;between two granite pillars opposite a house. The trail climbs at&lt;br /&gt;moderate grades, is well trodden, and has been recently blazed in&lt;br /&gt;blue, but some care is required to follow it, particularly in the lower&lt;br /&gt;section where there are many intersecting woods roads.&lt;br /&gt;From the gate, the trail follows a sandy logging road that ascends&lt;br /&gt;moderately under tall pines, swinging to the right, always taking&lt;br /&gt;the right at forks where several other roads diverge to the left. It&lt;br /&gt;bears right again at the edge of a grass-grown log yard.&lt;br /&gt;Ascending easily, at times level, it swings left, passes an old&lt;br /&gt;sugarhouse that stands on the left, and swings right again. It&lt;br /&gt;makes a short bypass to the left of a wet section of road, enters&lt;br /&gt;the WMNF and turns right off the road (cairn and arrow), then in&lt;br /&gt;30 yd., turns left onto another road. This road, distinctly older and&lt;br /&gt;steeper, crosses a substantial brook near the site of the former&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman Cabin.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Bald Peak spur 44° 08' 56&amp;quot; 71° 44' 54&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;1.60 mi 1 hr 31 min +1441 ft on Mt Kinsman Trail&lt;br /&gt;3.70 mi 3 hr 17 min +2831 ft Then the trail crosses a small brook that falls over a mossy ledge&lt;br /&gt;to the left of the trail, then crosses Flume Brook. Just over Flume&lt;br /&gt;Brook, a side path on the right descends close to the brook bank&lt;br /&gt;for 150 yd. to small, steep-walled Kinsman Flume, a classic&lt;br /&gt;eroded dike with an overhanging boulder at the top that presents&lt;br /&gt;a reasonable facsimile of a profile. The main trail continues on the&lt;br /&gt;road for another 70 yd., then turns sharp left at the point where&lt;br /&gt;another spur path diverges sharp right, descends briefly, then&lt;br /&gt;makes an easy ascent to Bald Peak, a bare ledgy dome with fine&lt;br /&gt;views that crowns a western spur of Kinsman Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;The ax-blazed trail now joins and follows Flume Brook, winding up&lt;br /&gt;the mountainside at easy to moderate grades, with good footing&lt;br /&gt;except for short, scattered steep pitches with rough footing. It&lt;br /&gt;crosses several small brooks and it swings right and angles&lt;br /&gt;upward, then swings left and climbs straight up to the ridge top,&lt;br /&gt;where it meets the Kinsman Ridge Trail. For North and South&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman, turn right; for Kinsman Pond and Kinsman Junction, turn&lt;br /&gt;left.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Kinsman Ridge Trail 44° 08' 15&amp;quot; 71° 44' 05&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.40 mi 12 min +420 ft on Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;4.10 mi 3 hr 29 min +3251 ft This trail follows the crest of the main ridge from the height-of-land&lt;br /&gt;on NH 112 in Kinsman Notch to the Cannon Mountain Tramway&lt;br /&gt;parking lot just off the Franconia Notch Parkway (look for the trail&lt;br /&gt;sign on a post in the lot and park nearby). From NH 112 to&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman Junction, it is part of the AT. For much of its length, it is&lt;br /&gt;a more difficult route than one might infer from the map—footing&lt;br /&gt;is often rough and there are many minor ups and downs. Hikers&lt;br /&gt;with heavy packs should allow considerable extra time for many&lt;br /&gt;parts of the trail. There is little water on or near several long&lt;br /&gt;sections of the trail, and none that a cautious hiker will drink&lt;br /&gt;without treatment.&lt;br /&gt;From Kinsman Junction, the Kinsman Ridge Trail (now part of the&lt;br /&gt;AT for the rest of its length) turns right and climbs up ledges to the&lt;br /&gt;junction where the Mt. Kinsman Trail enters on the right, then&lt;br /&gt;continues to climb steeply to the summit of North Kinsman.&lt;br /&gt;to North Kinsman 44° 08' 00&amp;quot; 71° 44' 12&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.90 mi 35 min +54 ft on Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;2&lt;br /&gt;Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;5.00 mi 4 hr 4 min +3306 ft Here a side path (sign) leads to the left 25 yd. to a fine outlook to&lt;br /&gt;the Franconias and continues, descending steeply, another 70 yd.&lt;br /&gt;to a ledge that looks directly down on Kinsman Pond. The true&lt;br /&gt;summit of North Kinsman is a pointed boulder on the left (east)&lt;br /&gt;side of the main trail, 30 yd. north of the outlook spur. The main&lt;br /&gt;trail descends steadily to the col between North and South&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman, then ascends relatively easily and passes 15 yd. to the&lt;br /&gt;west of the north knob of South Kinsman’s summit. The Kinsman&lt;br /&gt;Ridge Trail then crosses a scrub-filled sag to the bare south knob&lt;br /&gt;of South Kinsman, which is very exposed to the weather. (Note:&lt;br /&gt;The section of the trail between South Kinsman and Harrington&lt;br /&gt;Pond may require much extra time, particularly for those with&lt;br /&gt;heavy packs, and is also somewhat exposed to weather.)&lt;br /&gt;to South Kinsman 44° 07' 23&amp;quot; 71° 44' 12&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.90 mi 35 min -54 ft on Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;5.90 mi 4 hr 39 min +3251 ft From here the Kinsman Ridge Trail crosses a scrub-filled sag,&lt;br /&gt;passes 15 yd. to the west of the north knob of South Kinsman,&lt;br /&gt;and descends relatively easily to the col between South and North&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman. The trail then climbs steadily to a side path (sign) that&lt;br /&gt;leads to the right; this side path runs 25 yd. to a fine outlook to the&lt;br /&gt;Franconias and continues, descending steeply, another 70 yd. to&lt;br /&gt;a ledge that looks directly down on Kinsman Pond. The true&lt;br /&gt;summit of North Kinsman is a pointed boulder on the right (east)&lt;br /&gt;side of the main trail, 30 yd. north of the outlook spur.&lt;br /&gt;to North Kinsman 44° 08' 00&amp;quot; 71° 44' 12&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.40 mi 12 min -420 ft on Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;6.30 mi 4 hr 51 min +2831 ft The Kinsman Ridge Trail now descends steeply to the junction&lt;br /&gt;with the Mt. Kinsman Trail on the left.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mt Kinsman Trail 44° 08' 15&amp;quot; 71° 44' 05&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.20 mi 6 min -112 ft on Kinsman Ridge Trail&lt;br /&gt;6.50 mi 4 hr 57 min +2719 ft The trail then continues to Kinsman Junction. Here the Fishin’&lt;br /&gt;Jimmy Trail continues the AT to Lonesome Lake, and the&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman Pond Trail bears right, leading to Kinsman Pond and&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman Pond Shelter.&lt;br /&gt;to Kinsman Junction 44° 08' 17&amp;quot; 71° 43' 59&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;1.91 mi 1 hr 32 min -997 ft on Fishin' Jimmy Trail&lt;br /&gt;8.41 mi 6 hr 29 min +1722 ft This trail, a link in the AT, leads from Lonesome Lake to the&lt;br /&gt;Kinsman Ridge Trail at Kinsman Junction, near Kinsman Pond.&lt;br /&gt;Parts of it are steep and rough, with wooden steps on ledges. It&lt;br /&gt;received its peculiar name from a well-known local character&lt;br /&gt;called Fishin’ Jimmy—his real name was James Whitcher—who&lt;br /&gt;lived in the Franconia area and was featured in a story by Annie&lt;br /&gt;Trumbull Slosson, once a popular New England author.&lt;br /&gt;From the Kinsman Ridge Trail, the Fishin’ Jimmy Trail descends&lt;br /&gt;gradually from the ridge to the Kinsman Pond Trail. The Kinsman&lt;br /&gt;Pond Shelter can be reached by traveling south a short distance&lt;br /&gt;on this trail. From this junction, the trail begins a long descent. It&lt;br /&gt;curls around a large boulder on the right, passing through a fairly&lt;br /&gt;flat area and then continues to descend, at times steeply but with&lt;br /&gt;occasional minor ascents as well. It then flattens out, crossing&lt;br /&gt;several small brooks then runs around the lower end of a ridge&lt;br /&gt;coming down from the Middle Cannon Ball, making several&lt;br /&gt;ascents and descents and passing over a ledgy ridge crest.&lt;br /&gt;to AMC Lonesome Lake Hut 44° 08' 18&amp;quot; 71° 42' 12&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.04 mi 2 min -11 ft on Fishin' Jimmy Trail&lt;br /&gt;8.45 mi 6 hr 31 min +1711 ft Then the trail reaches Lonesome Lake Hut then passes the&lt;br /&gt;junction with the Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail near the beach at&lt;br /&gt;the southwest corner of the lake.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail 44° 08' 18&amp;quot; 71° 42' 10&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.05 mi 2 min -4 ft on Fishin' Jimmy Trail&lt;br /&gt;8.50 mi 6 hr 33 min +1707 ft It crosses the outlet brook on a bridge then ends at the Cascade&lt;br /&gt;Brook Trail at the south end of Lonesome Lake.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail, Cascade Brook&lt;br /&gt;Trail&lt;br /&gt;44° 08' 17&amp;quot; 71° 42' 07&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.25 mi 8 min +22 ft on Cascade Brook Trail&lt;br /&gt;3&lt;br /&gt;Distance Time Elev&lt;br /&gt;Change&lt;br /&gt;Trail / Waypoint Latitude Longitude&lt;br /&gt;8.75 mi 6 hr 41 min +1729 ft This relatively easy trail, a link in the AT, leads to Lonesome Lake&lt;br /&gt;from the bike path at the former Whitehouse Bridge site, just&lt;br /&gt;south of the bike path’s bridge over the Pemigewasset (the Liberty&lt;br /&gt;Spring Trail begins just north of the bridge). There is no parking at&lt;br /&gt;the Whitehouse Bridge site.&lt;br /&gt;From this junction, Lonesome Lake Hut is 150 yd. to the left. The&lt;br /&gt;trail continues along the east side of the lake towards a junction&lt;br /&gt;with the Lonesome Lake Trail and the Dodge Cutoff.&lt;br /&gt;to Lonesome Lake 44° 08' 25&amp;quot; 71° 41' 57&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;0.90 mi 52 min -834 ft on Lonesome Lake Trail&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a black four door Echo with Maine plates.  I will also have my yellow baseball cap on.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248705179000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248092807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NORTH &amp; SOUTH KINSMANS</name><id>10914491</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248525000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10914491/</event_url></item>