<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Interstate 93 South</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.289845</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lafayette Place Campground</name><city>Lafayette</city><id>2852131</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.571411</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets get out into the woods of New Hampshire and hike! Cannon Mountain is located in Franconia Notch and provides incredible views in all directions. It is also home to Cannon Ski area, come and see it without all the snow, ice and freezing temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Plan is to meet at the Lafayette Campground parking area located on 93 South in Franconia Notch at 9 AM. To get there, take 93 N out of Boston and take exit 34 B. Take a left at the bottom of the ramp and get back on 93 S. The campground entrance is a pullout off the highway. Driving mileage is about 140 miles from Boston for a driving time of approximately 2-2.5 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we start hiking we will hike up the Lonesome Lake Trail to the Hi-Cannon Trail and finally the kinsman ridge trail to the summit. The hike up will be 2.8 miles with 2,350 feet of elevation gain. We will hike at an easy to moderate pace and should reach the summit in 2-2.5 hours. Based on the elevation gain and pace, this hike should be of MEDIUM intensity. Once we have summited there are two options. We can either head down the way we came or add on a side trip to Lonesome Lake and the Lonesome Lake hut. At the Hut, there will be opportunity to refill water and possibly swim in Lonesome Lake. Total trip time should be in the neighborhood of 5 hours without Lonesome Lake and 6-6.5 with the lake detour.&amp;nbsp; Please note your preference for the Lonesome Lake detour when signing up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please dress appropriately for hiking (Backpack, Sturdy shoes/Hiking boots, at least 2 liters of water, suncreen/bug spray high energy snacks/lunch for the summit, and if possible no cotton) I will have a map and a basic first aid kit with me.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in a Gold/Silver Volvo XC70.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George Fraley</member_name><member_id>10925592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313245735000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312331996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt. Cannon</name><id>28038801</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313240400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/28038801/</event_url></item>