<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEATHER LOOKS GOOD SO FAR.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 80. Calm wind becoming south between 5 and 8 mph.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I AND IM SURE MANY OF YOU HAVE BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME TO SLAP THE WATER real hard WITH THOSE PADDLES and see if the boats don't have holes in them from hungry rats making them homes and /or source of food for the winter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ITS ALSO A GOOD TIME AND PLACE TO MEET FELLOW FUTURE AND PRESENT PADDLERs you will see in this group and maybe other paddling groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am estimating the water temp to be 55*F which is still pretty cool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an event WAS listed weeks in advance with great hopes on good weather conditions, SO check back closer to the WEEKEND.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By then my girlfriend in the picture above will have consumed 60 more buckets of Kentucky Fried Chicken and 50 more pounds of Bon Bon,s  maybe 30 more gallons of High Fructose Coca Cola...and waiting for me and you to help rescue her.&lt;br /&gt;are ya ready ?? A SEXY damsel in distress... HELP !&lt;br /&gt;Are ya ready for mouth to mouth..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be using the both areas of the boat ramp  as our base since not many boaters are even out then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im choosing this day/week combination on the time we were here in the last 3 or 4 years as we arrived for our first group paddle of the year. Seems like a good time to start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its more of a get together than a real paddle event, we / you play in the lake and get a chance to introduce each other, check out boats, etc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some can tour the lake,its pretty small and easy to see everything in 15-40 minutes of paddling..then let another bunch tour the area, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE WEAR SOME FLEECE JACKET AND quick drain POLY STUFF TO KEEP WARM IN CASE SOME WATER SPLASHES ON YOU..NO COTTON OR JEANS..IF THEY GET WET ItS COLD ON YOU, OR simply HAVE SOME CLOTHES READY TO CHANGE INTO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is event is great for everyone, first timers especially.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;IF YOU DONT HAVE A KAYAK....., you are encouraged to JOIN US ANYWAY, you can try mine and im sure others will let you try theirs also, you can ask questions..etc..its not like we are going anyplace on this small lake but more to get you ready for the next events on the list and all summer long at various places from rivers to the shore areas..each area a bit more challenging.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experienced paddlers are welcomed and would inspire the beginners along with gilding them into what and not to get for our type of kayaking. (as i always say &amp;quot;don't buy Junk&amp;quot;, you will be pained by the mistakes in many ways if you do). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can however do well (and very well) with used boats and some inexpensive paddles, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are not an elitist group where ya need the best... i just say if you do get something - get the best you can afford , then ya never need anything else, and you can sell for almost what ya paid in the first place, especially if new.. and not even loose anything if used, in some cases even make profit..&lt;br /&gt;sort of like Kayaking for free and then some.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; i can only help and introduce a few people at a time to the water, equipment, etc..everyone can help each other too so this is also a interesting social event in the water or shore area for all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; All we are going to do is introduce paddling to the beginners, we can demonstrate a few rescue routines, paddle float entry, a T rescue, and maybe something else, depends on temperature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some can paddle around the lake and see whats new on the lake.. a pretty simple event ..a Get in shape thing for the next one. (most likely Eaglevill dam upstream portion  first for a good work out, then downstream to the dam, &amp;quot;just like last year&amp;quot;.)&lt;br /&gt;After this event..the real events start slowly building up to finally hit the ocean till its too cold out again and we return to the rivers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the Boat Launch area:&lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortoPotties (they should be there by then if not , Pee in the water..LOL) . Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit in the sun .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: to the boat launch.&lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 heading East to Bolton Notch &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) ...rte 6 is to the right &lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (South street intersection)&lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE LEAVE THE LAUNCHING CIRCLE OPEN after unloading AND PARK ON THE DESIGNATED SIDE AREAS, the DEP cops show up all the time it seems. They are looking to make some money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need help unloading we will always help you but don't know if you need help all the time so ask anyone to help you, we do this at all events anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU ARE WELCOMED TO JOIN US IF YOU DO NOT HAVE A YAK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ITS A PLAY IN THE WATER THING AND OTHERS WILL MOST LIKELY LET YOU TRY THEIR BOATS TOO AS I DO WITH MINE..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ITS OUR OWN ...&amp;quot;TRY BEFORE YOU BUY&amp;quot;  KIND OF EVENT but with our members yaks we use all the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then its a BARBIE-Q NEARBY AT OAK GROVE NATURE CENTER BY THE COVERED BRIDGE AND WATER FALL, nearby in MANCHESTER, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully, everyone will arrive @ the Covered Bridge &lt;br /&gt;(locally/unofficially referred to as &amp;quot;Childrens Covered Bridge&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;over Porter Brook) smoothly!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS LOCATION CAN handle more cars but still IS nearby. (this is not the same place as last OR PRIOR years).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location is just minutes from Highland Park Market (if you forgot or want something fresh) as a reference and very easy to caravan to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some chairs, food, and your faviourite beverage for here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; GPS apx       200 Oak Grove St,  Manchester&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park at: Oak Grove Nature Center Parking Lot (some may have to doubble park)&lt;br /&gt;I will park out on the roadside abit ways up since the trailer takes up so much room.&lt;br /&gt;There is room here also for about 5 cars more if necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions from Bolton Lake:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leave Bolton Lake boat ramp, take a right onto rte 44 going &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;WEST&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear left onto 384 toward Hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the first exit off of 384  (exit # 4)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left onto Highland St         (if going to Highland Park Market take a right)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go apx 0.5 mile and take a right onto &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;AUTUMN&lt;/span&gt; ST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THEN AN IMMEDIATE RIGHT onto Oak Grove St&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the first parking lot area on the right is the place..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park tightly..use some of the areas off on the sides also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will walk up into the area a bit to a nice secluded spot near the covered bridge and water fall.&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt; Kayaks Available: TO SIMPLY TRY and play around with on this particular event :&lt;br /&gt;NOT ASKING for ANY kayak DONATIONS FOR THIS EVENT..JUST BRING SOME GOOD Tasty FOOD &amp;amp; Bugg Juice FOR the pot luck..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BEGINNER AND STEP INTO THEM VIA THE FLOOR OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a seasoned pro and impress the others who dont know how. Or you may laugh at the ones that fall in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familliar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for you since a GOOD QUALITY PFD should be chosen for your particular body shapes and paddling  style, if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap ones for that.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourtie Yak Pad optional accessory to all yaks..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Riot Tourlite 15, Blue, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wickedwaters.com/riot-tour-lite-15.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://wickedwaters.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;,  transitional kayak, 15'=   &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS KAYAK IS FOR SALE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.....I will have this at the event to try... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cobra Expidition, Yellow, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cobrakayaks.com/expedition.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cobrakayak...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;, Fast Sea kayak, , Sit On Top type, moderate to low initial stability, 18', = (depends on water temp, kind of cold ?)= ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer, Red, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;, highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'= ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro, Red, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;, fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Un Modified), Red and White, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;, stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Modified), Yellow, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;, stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;, stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I HAVE The GRILL &amp;amp; heaters,  already loaded up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case of any rain wind or cool cloudy weather, It might be best to wait till a better weekend.&lt;br /&gt;but i will update the last time at 10 am the day of the event if it looks questionable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be safe and  ALWAYS wear YOUR Personal Flotation Devices ,  a whistle is good to have tied to it and will let  us hear you if ya fall in or have any other problem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayak trailer and Stryped Orange Cones by boat launch area &amp; Orange Hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>32</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274030766000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260141247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>* KAYAK SEASON OPENING EVENT at Bolton Lake* - Barbie-Q @ Oak Grove Ntr CTR Aftr</name><id>12031628</id><headcount>57</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272729600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/12031628/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/a/global_13060842.jpeg</photo_url></item>