<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Time to take it up a notch! This hike takes us to Lake Solitude, White Ledge, and Mount Sunapee. There are great views from both White Ledge and the summit.  And Lake Solitude is a beautifully pristine spot with crystal clear waters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total distance: About 6 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: About 1650 feet (cumulative)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interactive trail map here: &lt;a href="http://www.everytrail.com/view_trip.php?trip_id=56919" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.everytrail...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket, a hat) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:  We will start and end at the Andrew Brook Trailhead, located in Newbury, New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;    * From the junction of Rt. 103 and Rt. 103A in Newbury, head east on Rt. 103 for 0.8 mile.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn right onto Mountain Road.&lt;br /&gt;    * After 1.2 miles, the trailhead will be on the right just before Mountain Road crosses a bridge.&lt;br /&gt;    * There is limited parking here; do not block the woods road (trail). There is a sign for the trailhead but it isn't readily visible from the road.  The trail can be hard to spot!  It is on your right just before going over a small bridge over a brook. If you hit a dirt road you have gone too far. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ETA: Dog friendly, kid friendly (older kids!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Rain cancels! I will keep an eye on the weather!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is cross-posted with &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/New_England_Over_40_Hiking_Group"&gt;New England Over 40 Hiking Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the trailhead by 9:00am.  I have a bright orange backpack and a big smile.  My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289079122000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286030915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (More) Into It - Hike to Lake Solitude and Mt Sunapee!</name><id>14973589</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289049300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14973589/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/f/2/global_18395874.jpeg</photo_url></item>