<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>notloB Folk Concerts is pleased to welcome back two alumna, Julie Dougherty (from the Folk Arts Quartet) and Mariel Vandersteel (from Blue Moose and the Unbuttoned Zippers).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fiddler Julie Metcalf began as a classical violinist in Worcester, MA. Coming from a family of musicians, she was encouraged to make music from an early age; Julie picked up the violin for the first time when she was 4 years old and has been playing ever since. When she was twelve, Julie discovered fiddle music and jazz through PBS and country radio, and began learning Celtic tunes on her own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julie studied classical violin at Boston University's College of Fine Arts. Recently, she has immersed herself in the study of both traditional folk and contemporary styles of music, including Celtic, Appalachian, bluegrass, jazz, and Latin music. She is a graduate of Berklee College of Music with a degree in Violin Performance. Julie plays viola in the Paper Star Trio, formerly the Folk Arts Quartet. The Paper Star Trio is a grooving chamber-folk string ensemble that plays contemporary arrangements of world fiddle music. She can also be spotted playing violin with Mariachi Palenque.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARIEL VANDERSTEEL ~ Inspired by her summers spent studying traditional music in Ireland and across the united states, Mariel decided to study music in norway after graduating from Berklee. She is studying the hardingfele and Norwegian folk music at høgskolen i telemark rauland. While in Norway, she has performed at outdoor festivals and in the local elementary school where she taught children about American folk music.&lt;br /&gt;Mariel has taught at alasdair fraser’s sierra fiddle camp, has been an assistant teacher at fiddlekids, a San Francisco Bay Area fiddle camp for children, and has shared the stage with Alasdair Fraser, Laura Risk, Hanneke Cassel, Natalie Haas, Tristan and Tashina Clarridge, Nic Gareiss, André Brunet, and Philip Bailey of Earth Wind and Fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She currently lives in Norway and will return to Boston in 2010 where she will teach the fiddle and hardingfele and perform with Blue Moose and the Unbuttoned Zippers and the Paper Star Trio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors 7:30, Concert 8:00&lt;br /&gt;Coffee, tea and pastries will be available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested donation $12 at the door; $10 if reservation is made at least 24 hours in advance and to Loring-Greenough museum members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations: notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artist’s websites: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/juliemetcalf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://marielvandersteel.com/Mariel_Vandersteel" target="_blank"&gt;http://marielvanderst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official website: &lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://sites.google.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;notloB Folk Concerts are volunteer run and not for profit. All interested in volunteering are encouraged to send an email to notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website ~ &lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://sites.google.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facebook ~ &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/notloB-Folk-Concerts/118395891509908" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mail list ~ &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291572454000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289146812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Julie Metcalf and Mariel Vandersteel</name><id>15368009</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291510800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/15368009/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/b/global_19447275.jpeg</photo_url></item>