<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>CGIS South Building Tsai Auditorium</address_2><address_1>1730 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375269</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tsai Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>748933</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112774</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Biodiversity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conserving through Knowing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Conversations with E.O. Wilson and Daniel H. Janzen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, October 1, 2010, in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: : :&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6.00pm-7.30pm: Public lecture and discussion session (Tsai Auditorium, 1730&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge St.); open to the public, admission free, donations encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8.00pm: Benefit dinner with Wilson and Janzen supporting conservation in Costa Rica (UpStairs on the Square, Harvard Square). Find out more &lt;a href="http://www.gdfcf.org/fr_cambridge.html" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets available &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/122701" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join E.O. Wilson (Harvard University, Museum of Comparative Zoology)vand Daniel Janzen (University of Pennsylvania; Area de Conservaci?n Guanacaste) for a discussion of how we understand and protect the wild living world, how we can do these things better, and, most of all, why we should care. Dinner will be a delicious 3-course seasonal menu with house wine selections from UpStairs on the Square (vegetarian options available). Eat and share ideas with two of the preeminent biologists and conservationists of our time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All donations are tax-deductible to the extent permitted by US law and benefit the Guanacaste Dry Forest Conservation Fund, a US 501c3 nonprofit funding conservation in the Area de Conservaci?n&lt;br /&gt;Guanacaste, Costa Rica. The price of every ticket is a direct donation to preserving tropical biodiversity in a 400,000 acre conservation area. No part of it is wasted or or used for overhead expenses.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Edward O. Wilson is the Pellegrino University Professor, Emeritus, at Harvard University. A member of the US National Academy of Sciences and a two-time Pulitzer prizewinner, Wilson's pioneering work on evolution, ecology, behavior, and biodiversity have earned him the National Medal of Science, the TED Prize, and the Crafoord Prize from the Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences. Wilson published his first novel, &lt;i&gt;Anthill&lt;/i&gt;, earlier this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Daniel H. Janzen (PhD) is the Thomas G. and Louise E. DiMaura Professor of Conservation Biology at the University of Pennsylvania. A member of the US National Academy of Sciences, he has received the MacArthur Fellowship, the Crafoord Prize, and the Kyoto Prize for his work in tropical biology and conservation. Janzen and his wife Dr. Winnie Hallwachs were instrumental in restoring the Area de Conservacion Guanacaste, and have been working for the last 25 years to expand and endow it in perpetuity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Area de Conservaci?n Guanacaste (ACG) is: 163,000 hectares of stunning tropical forest and marine habitat in northwestern Costa Rica, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, 2% of the country, and 2.6% of the world's biodiversity. It is the product of one of the world's most successful habitat restoration and conservation efforts. The ACG is home to an estimated 230,000 species of plants and animals, and it supports research at the leading edge of ecology, evolutionary biology, biotechnology,&lt;br /&gt;biodevelopment, child education, and conservation. Read more about Janzen's work and ACG in this recent New York Times&lt;br /&gt;article &lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2010/06/15/science/15crea.html" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286031712000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282328682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biodiversity (E.O. Wilson)</name><id>14486648</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285970400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/14486648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/5/global_16178405.jpeg</photo_url></item>