<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a 12.2 mile hike going over Mt. Whiteface and Mt. Passaconaway. Book time is 9 hours but I'd like to keep around a 2mph pace so it should take us less than 9 hours. This is an intermediate hike so you should be experienced with hiking this distance in the Whites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the Blueberry Ledge Trailhead off of Ferncroft Rd, Wonalancet, NH. I plan to start hiking at 8:00 so arrive early so you're ready by 8. I don't always have cell phone reception in the Whites so if you're running late I probably won't get your message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trails:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blueberry Ledge -&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rollins Trail -&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Square Ledge Trail -&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Old Mast Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the weather looks bad I'll cancel the day before the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a headlamp, map, water (3Liters should be good) and other appropriate gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a dog friendly hike but it is up to you to determine if your dog is capable of doing this hike. My dog will be with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy with the yellow Lab dog wearing a blue dog pack.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Garrett</member_name><member_id>6580546</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312245401000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311728220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Passaconaway and Whiteface - Intermediate</name><id>27164771</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312113600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/27164771/</event_url></item>