<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main Street, Hartford, ct</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.763206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>607396</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674088</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/2/8/event_61069192.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;5- 8 pm, $10; Free admission for members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;View the photography of Patti Smith in &lt;em&gt;Patti Smith: Camera Solo&lt;/em&gt; and Claire Beckett in &lt;em&gt;MATRIX 163&lt;/em&gt;! Join Claire Beckett&amp;rsquo;s gallery talk at 6; listen to the bluesy sounds of the XY Eli Band; capture a moment in our photo booth and enjoy food from Peppercorn&amp;rsquo;s Grill and Healthy Source. Be inspired by the HARTT Dances! performance of excerpts from the repertory of Graham, Limon, Balanchine, and contemporary choreographers Katie Stevinson-Nollet and Stephen Pier at 6:45. Stay and win tickets to the CT Forum, or party-hop between here and the Billings Forge Mash-Up event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;Film: &lt;em&gt;Short Short Story Film Festival&lt;/em&gt;, 8 pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exhibition Opening: Claire Beckett / MATRIX 163&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;November 3, 2011 &amp;ndash; March 4, 2012&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;Claire Beckett&amp;rsquo;s large-scale, color photographic series &amp;ldquo;Simulating Iraq&amp;rdquo; investigates the American military training sites where soldiers participate in role-playing exercises in preparation for deployment to Iraq and Afghanistan. In makeshift simulations of Middle Eastern villages, military personnel and hired civilians assume the various &amp;ldquo;parts&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;from Iraqi villagers and medical workers to Taliban fighters&amp;mdash;dressed in approximations of traditional clothing, including head scarves, tunics, and robes. Although the military activities are intended to familiarize troops with a foreign culture and unknown terrain, Beckett&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;documentary&amp;rdquo; photographs present the viewer with a fascinating and false alternate reality&amp;#8213;through a straightforward but problematic account of cultural simulation charged with genuine humanity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;Claire Beckett is certainly in line with the project&amp;rsquo;s goal of presenting challenging, current and occasionally controversial art. Enter Beckett&amp;rsquo;s , &amp;ldquo;Simulating Iraq&amp;rdquo; a collection of photographs replicating the training of military personnel to prepare for integration into the Iraqi culture. Beckett&amp;rsquo;s fabrications present a false, yet believable reality of a culture that is entirely simulated via helpful props and actors. Beckett&amp;rsquo;s photographed lesson in authenticity will leave viewers questioning the ends gained via an invasion of another country&amp;rsquo;s cultural identity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;The year 2011 marks the tenth anniversary of 9/11 and the 150th anniversary of the start of the Civil War. MATRIX 163 offers a contemporary counterpoint to the concurrent Civil War-focused&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Colts &amp;amp; Quilts&lt;/em&gt; exhibition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Short Story Film Festival&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;Now in its fifth year, and being shown at the Wadsworth for the first time, The Short Short Story Film Festival is a competitive international festival of films that each tell a story within five minutes. From mini-documentaries to sentimental melodramas to black comedies to animated horror, the festival features succinct presentations of all kinds of short film stories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #2375a4"&gt;8 pm (Heartstrings Program only)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #bb99e4"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #44305d"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;In addition to parking on the street, (after 6 free), convenient parking available at the Front Street Garage, off Prospect Street, behind the museum. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the lobby at 5:30 or find us having cocktails inside the hall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320425026000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317752289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art After Hours: SNAP!</name><id>36118382</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320355800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/36118382/</event_url></item>