<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Reservation Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01375</zip><lat>42.503792</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Toby State Reservation</name><city>Sunderland</city><id>710040</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.529472</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I love to hike Toby in the Spring and look for wildflowers and other emerging spring plants.  We will begin traveling on the Tower road and may make some side trips, depending or trail conditions.  I expect some mud so choose your footwear accordingly.  Let's enjoy a stroll/romp in the spring air and the tall trees with our dogs and each other.  See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tower Road is closed to vehicles, and most of the way the trail is next to a mountain stream. Please be sure to have your dog on-leash, at least to begin with, until we know how we all get along.  This walk will mostly be off leash.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the junction of Massachusetts Route 63 and 47 (in Sunderland, 4.5 miles south of Millers Falls, 8 miles north of North Amherst center), go south on Route 47 for 1 mile and turn left onto Reservation Road. Find the gated trailhead on the right in 0.5 miles, with parking in another 50 feet next to a small headquarters building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Route 47 and Route 116 intersection in the center of Sunderland, go north on Route 47 for 3.8 miles and turn right onto Reservation Road. Find the gated trailhead on the right in 0.5 miles, with parking in another 50 feet next to a small headquarters building.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The nearest street address is 90 Reservation Road, for those of you with GPS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristi's cell is 413-230-6757 if all else fails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- Kristi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a black lab w/blue leash, &amp; vanilla PT Cruiser</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273945710000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268588701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Day on  Mt. Toby</name><id>12873689</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272736800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/12873689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/8/global_5887576.jpeg</photo_url></item>