<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come see Broadway's most honored play at the Shubert- &amp;quot;Doubt.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set against the backdrop of a Catholic school in 1964, DOUBT is the story of a strong-minded woman faced with a difficult decision.  Should she voice concerns about one of her male collegues...even if she's not entirely certain of the truth  The play examines the line between gossip and truth, discipline and compassion, certainty and doubt.  Hailed as &amp;quot;eloquent and provocative.  A gripping mystery.  Tightly written, elegantly directed and beautifully acted.&amp;quot;  Stars Tony-award winnning actress Cherry Jones who holds many TV, film, and Broadway credits to her name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrive at theater by 7:30 pm, show starts at 8 pm and runs 90 minutes with no intermission.  Meet your organizer in the lobby of the theater for your ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only open to 8 members.  Half-price tickets were already purchased for this night. We have reserved seats in second row front balcony.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total cost per ticket is $25.00; pay your organizer the night of the play.  (The ticket price includes handling fees.)  Other tickets may be purchased at full price by going into the Shubert Theater website which would be on your own.&lt;br /&gt;*******************************************&lt;br /&gt;For those who can make it earlier, we will meet at Hot Tomato's at 6:15 pm on 261 College St. (next door to the theater) for appetizers and drinks. (Dinner is rather pricey.) They have GREAT martinis!&lt;br /&gt;********************************************&lt;br /&gt;PARKING--- either on street, if you can find a spot, or in the parking garage near the theater.&lt;br /&gt;*********************************************&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions:&lt;br /&gt;From the North:&lt;br /&gt;I 91 S to Exit 1 onto Rte 34 connector.&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 1 off Rte 34 &amp;quot;Downtown New Haven&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight to lite and make a RIGHT onto Church St.&lt;br /&gt;At second lite take a LEFT onto Crown St.&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 blocks to parking garage on RIGHT (corner of Crown and College Sts.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. Hopefully on a Weds nite there will be parking on the street, but you might have to drive around the block to find a space.  Caution: many streets are one-ways.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177251174000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171141327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Doubt" a dramatic play at the Shubert Theater</name><id>5470411</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175724900000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5470411/</event_url></item>