<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kaitlyn, our former international service chair, will be joining us to cook up some delicious recipes she picked up on her travels around Central and South America last summer.  Shelby has graciously offered her place for us to have this dinner.  Please RSVP accordingly so that we can purchase enough food.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Join us and bring a friend! This is an open, social event, so feel free to bring anyone along who loves to eat and socialize!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;There will be a minimum $15 donation for our on-going project in Guatemala with Mayan Families. A few members went to Guatemala as part of a service project and we'll be going back this year to help set up water filters, teach hygiene and basic water sanitation.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The fiesta will take place at Shelby and Andrew's apartment in Watertown.  It is accessible by T, take the red line (or a bus line) to Harvard and catch either the 71 (get off at Kimball St in front of the 7/11) or 73 (get off at Marion St across from a gas station), less than 5 minute walk from either stop.  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;See the facebook group or contact Shelby directly for the exact address.  If you have any questions or would like to help with planning/execution, please email Shelby at: internationalservice@bostonrotaract.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ray W</member_name><member_id>2975533</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caitlyn Aerial Clarke</member_name><member_id>55952082</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370828359000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrotaract</urlname><id>1501340</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Rotaract - A Service/Social Club for 18-30 Yr Olds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1370308324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Latin American cultural dinner benefit</name><id>122793362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370804400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrotaract/events/122793362/</event_url></item>