<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Berkshire Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01007</zip><lat>42.277036</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>American Legion</name><city>Belchertown</city><id>1450797</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.400918</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This regional meeting will encompass several topics in which members have expressed an interest.  One of the ideas that some members have discussed is to publish our own newsletter/paper for the Western Mass area. This is a worthy endeavor and we would appreciate input from as many folks as possible. Basically this will be a brainstorming session, so please bring your ideas and suggestions with you. This meeting is open to all members of the 912 groups. Other areas of discussion will include, upcoming campaigns and elections. Getting our conservative infrastructure in place so that we can flip this state in 2012. This may include getting involved with your local RTC's, and most importantly joining the MARA  group in District 1.  Please consider attending this meeting. All are welcome. Updates to the meeting will be posted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note that in the event of a winter storm, the snow date for this meeting will be Thursday, February 3rd, at 7 p.m. at the same venue.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Take the driveway into the Btown Police Station, across from Chestnut Hill School on State Street. Continue straight past the police station, to the American Legion. There will be a sign at the entrance to the police station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Baran</member_name><member_id>9211691</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296177034000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>We Surround Them</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Western-Mass-912-Project</urlname><id>1394602</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6299972534</group_lon><name>The Original WMass 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293572115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Western Mass. 912  Regional Meeting</name><id>15841280</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296172800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Western-Mass-912-Project/events/15841280/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/9/global_7591481.jpeg</photo_url></item>