<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>How about a slightly more rugged hike away from the North Shore for a change? I've wanted to go here for a while. I have a map but we'll be figuring it out together. Here's what the guidebook says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rugged topography, outstanding panoramas, deep woods and an extensive network of trails...the circuit hike provides a good sample of what this MDC reservation has to offer..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located only minutes from the bustle of downtown Boston, the DCR Blue Hills Reservation stretches over 7,000 acres from Quincy to Dedham, Milton to Randolph, providing a green oasis in an urban environment. Rising above the horizon, Great Blue Hill reaches a height of 635 feet, the highest of the 22 hills in the Blue Hills chain. From the rocky summit visitors can see over the entire metropolitan area. With its scenic views, varied terrain and 125 miles of trails, the Blue Hills Reservation offers year-round enjoyment for the outdoor enthusiast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION : The start of the hike is easily located from the jn of MA 28 and I 93 (exit 5). Drive North 1.4 miles on MA 28 to a traffic light for the first cross street. Turn right on to Chickatawbut Rd and park in a small gravel lot on the right. Our hike involves a climb up Chickatawbut Hill - max elevation of 500 feet. The vertical rise is 1370 feet (so we'll be stopping a lot for me to catch breath).  Hiking time is 3 hours so bring water and snacks. 4.1 miles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancels. Call me if necessary. I'll send you my phone number if you sign up.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289216814000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288661733000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Sunday hike - LOCATION IS IN DESCRIPTION! </name><id>15305163</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289145600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15305163/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/5/global_11261669.jpeg</photo_url></item>