<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A thru-hike of 6.5 miles running north to south on a section of the Mattabesett Trail. The hike is anticipated to be of moderate difficulty giventhe length and some steep parts. We'll meet at the end location on Rte. 17 in Durham where roadside parking is more ample and shuttle to the roadside start location on Rte. 68 in Durham. We'll have some potential clifftop views on Fowler Mountain with Ulbrich Reservoir below and on Pistapaug Mountain we'll have Pistapaug Pond below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Weather looks great with 59 F and Mostly cloudy with low 10% chance rain and 11 mph winds***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the roadside parking on Rte. 17 in Durham at 12:45 PM. At 1 PM we'll shuttle to the start in Reed Gap on Rte. 68 to the limited roadside parking. We would finish at about 7 PM. It is not anticipated we'll head out to eat as we usually do at this time given the lateness and the work day following.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring bug spray and/or headnet, at least 1 qt. water, trail may be muddy from rains overnight***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions for meetup location and ending point via MapQuest for roadside parking near intersection of Rte. 17 (New Haven Rd.) and Stagecoach Rd. in Durham CT (address in link is only to get approximate location in MapQuest): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Durham&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=997+New+Haven+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions for starting point we shuttle to with limited roadside parking near intersection of Rte. 68 (Wallingford Rd.) and Rte. 157 (Skeet Club Rd.) in Durham CT (address in link is only to get approximate location in MapQuest):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Durham&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=715+Wallingford+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A rough topographical map of the area from Google Maps (Start marked w/&amp;quot;A&amp;quot;, zoom for more detail):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=715+Wallingford+Rd,+Durham,+CT&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=46.36116,51.416016&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.444785,-72.739449&amp;amp;spn=0.086213,0.100422&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=13" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map at: &lt;br /&gt;(No on-line map known)&lt;br /&gt;See CFPA's &amp;quot;Connecticut Walk Book: West&amp;quot;, maps MB-6a and MB-6b on page 112&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one in Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243618055000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242481775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Mattabesett Trail in Durham &amp; Wallingford CT</name><id>10424379</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242579600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10424379/</event_url></item>