<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>647 Broadway (Rt.1)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.501931</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781)-941-2220</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Saugus </city><id>1064209</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.014707</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>suggested donation</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this talk, we'll define energy as how self-aware a person is to what's going on within &amp;amp; around them. There are two types of approaches to how energy works for us -- it's either destructive or creative. Each moment, we have the conscious choice regarding which type we want more of in our lives  -- and the choice would seen obvious, right? But something gets in the way that blocks us from experiencing the higher, more vibrant type of energy we really want. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This talk is about understanding, re-framing and overcoming what stops us from experiencing the creative energy that allows us to live with less fear and self-doubt. We'll explore the four main reasons we self-sabotage and what to do when those energy blocks pop-up. Overcoming these four destructive habits leads to greater happiness, success and deeper sense of life mastery. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Rachel O'h-Uiginn of Undercurrent Coaching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;is a trained and certified life-coach through the Institute for Professional Excellence in Coaching (iPEC).&lt;/span&gt; Rachel works primarily with Millennial women on self-esteem, career &amp;amp; personal development issues. Through positive psychology &amp;amp; coaching tools, Rachel helps clients capitalize on their strengths and achieve desired outcomes to end the cycle of intimidation, guilt and fear that comes up around making positive life changes. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For more information, please visit www.undercurrentcoaching.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be meeting from &lt;strong&gt;7:00pm-8:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; in the back room of Panera Bread. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Panera is in a plaza of shops, next to Marshalls. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 See you there! &lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif" alt="smile" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Ellen &lt;br /&gt;

 Organizer &lt;br /&gt;

 617-750-4830&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>9941060</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1338128342000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>northofbostonlawofattraction</urlname><id>567480</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The North-of-Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335282908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Channeling Energy: 4 habits that ruin your life - Speaker Rachel O’h-Uiginn, CPC</name><id>dxqcpcyqhbfc</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337814000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/northofbostonlawofattraction/events/61918822/</event_url></item>