<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>What: Annual Harvest Festival &amp;amp; Scarecrow Contest&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: October 19, 2008 12:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: The town of Sturbridge is lovely all seasons of the year, but especially in the fall!  &lt;br /&gt;The Annual Harvest Festival takes place on the town common just across from the Public House. It has always been wonderful  The common is filled with crafters, homemade baked goods,  harvest displays, food, &amp;amp; several activities. Amazing scarecrows of all kinds are all over the grounds of the Public House. You will see many unusual and amazing ones! Cast a vote for your favorite!  Curiosity shops will be open for browsing. The bakery, pub, &amp;amp; restaurant are open also.  In addition to The Public House, there are several eateries a short drive away  to choose from.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festival opens at 11am. Closes at 4pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*******NOTE:*******&lt;/b&gt; I would love for us to meetup right outside The Public House, but it is usually VERY crowded. We will meetup just  next door @ the white picket fence outside of Sadie Green's Curiosity Shop @ 283 Main St. I will provide contact info in a message closer to the date.  RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT. Please check for an update before heading out.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup by the white fence outside of  Sadie Green's -283 Main ***SEE NOTE</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224803614000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222043237000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Harvest Festival &amp; Scarecrow Contest</name><id>8804526</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224432000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/8804526/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/d/global_5597325.jpeg</photo_url></item>