<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>BA member Janid invites us to buy a pie for charity... Pie in the Sky is an annual Thanksgiving bake sale and a major fundraising effort for Community Servings, a local Massachusetts charity, with over 90% of their revenue going towards providing meals for the critically ill, their families and caregivers. Clients live in 16 cities throughout Eastern Massachusetts and battle over 20 kinds of illnesses, including HIV/AIDS, breast and other cancers and kidney diseases. Pies are baked by over 150 of Boston best chefs, and can be pick-up on the November 23rd at over 45 locations across Eastern Massachusetts. Each Pie costs $25, an amount that provides an entire week of nutritious home-delivered meals to a person too sick to shop or cook for themselves. Last year Pie in the Sky raised $503,000 for Community Servings, providing tens of thousands of meals to critically ill clients, this year with your help, the goal is $525,000. Pies can be purchased by visiting &lt;a href="http://www.servings.org/events/pies/seller.cfm?ID=3470" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.servings.o...&lt;/a&gt; before November 19th. Janid assures us, on his honor, that the pies are delicious. At this link, you can click to buy from Janid -- he is a volunteer, and does not in any way benefit from your purchase -- or any other seller. We may be Godless, but that doesn&amp;#146;t mean we have to be Pie-less! I've already sent in a donation. Further, I'll make an additional $3 donation for every additional member that sends me an email receipt of their own purchase. Please, please help me get rid of this extra money of mine. - Zachary&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321744697000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321559310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buy a pie for charity</name><id>41540752</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321740000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/41540752/</event_url></item>