<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Now I know what people are going to say, have a meetup at the mall?&lt;br /&gt;It's actually one of the hottest spots to go right now. Two weeks ago, I went down there on a Saturday night and at 11 o'clockl the line was in to the mall parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;The girls are hot and the guys are pretty easy to push out of a set to get yourself in there.&lt;br /&gt;Plus, people have been complaining that New Haven and Hartford are the same old thing so here's the other option boys and girls... actually only boys. We are going out to GET the girls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be having an open meetup for new and Sr. members of the Wingman group. We do this right, we can tear the place apart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get there around 10. 10:30 at the LATEST. If you are later, you are going to be waiting for a WHILE in that line. Remember any time we pick a time, it's not done at random. There's a reason for it... like avoiding long lines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But like always, we have a plan B. If for some reason the place turns out to be a bust, we can head to downtown Milford which is full of options like SBC, Stonebridge, Daniel Street and Archie Moores.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text JC's Cell - 203 410 6861</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319645515000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237425919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Bear in Milford</name><id>9985077</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237600800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/9985077/</event_url></item>