<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Suck! a Rock'n'Roll Vampire Spoof!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suck is playing a limited engagement at the Regent Theater in Arlington. Please join us! I strongly encourage you to buy your ticket in advance. Not only will you guarantee yourself a seat, but you save $2* by buying ahead. *turns out, with the service fee you only save a buck, but think of the fun you can have with one hundred shiny pennies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showtime is 9:15, so show up around 9. I'm usually easy to find. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the Regent site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The SUCK Story&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A rock’n’roll vampire spoof about a down and out band, The Winners, who will do anything for a record deal. When their disgruntled manager (Dave Foley) tells them that they are getting “long in the tooth”, he doesn’t know that his words are truly prophetic. During a road trip, their humdrum image radically changes when Jennifer (Jessica Paré), the bass player, disappears one night with a hip vampire (Dimitri Coats). She emerges with a sexually charged charisma that drives the audiences wild. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the band members succumb, one by one, to blood lust, their “gimmick” launches them into the limelight. Following an “incident” on a national radio show with “Rock’n Roger” (Henry Rollins), they hit mega-stardom beyond their wildest dreams. Joey (Rob Stefaniuk), the lead singer, is haunted by an eerie bartender (Alice Cooper), who turns out to be much more. Meanwhile, legendary vampire hunter, Eddie Van Helsig (Malcolm McDowell), is tracking them down, despite his fear of the dark. When a veteran music producer (Iggy Pop) calls them on becoming a vampire freak show, they begin to realize that fame is not what it’s cracked up to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suck is a wild ride down a highway to hell, with a killer soundtrack that includes Iggy Pop’s, “TVeye” and “Success”; Alice Cooper’s, “I am a Spider”; Lou Reed’s Velvet Underground’s “Sweet Nuthin”; David Bowie’s, “Here Comes the Night” and The Rolling Stones, “Sympathy for the Devil”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/suck.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;CLICK HERE TO GO TO THE REGENT SITE FOR TICKETS AND THE TRAILER!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KateMcQ</member_name><member_id>6532193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284049689000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283626998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Suck @ the Regent</name><id>14657621</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283994000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14657621/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/d/b/global_17690779.jpeg</photo_url></item>