<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 138 by Route 110</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02881</zip><lat>41.457460</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Great Swamp</name><city>Kingston</city><id>591989</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.528660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>May 4th Great Swamp Trip- Taylors Landing, Kingston, RI. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet at 10:00am for a shuttle&lt;/b&gt;  We will move the cars to the take out downstream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leaders:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mark Roberts Mark Roberts mroberts@cia.com 401-533-1883. &lt;br /&gt;Jim Cole JimCole@hotmail.com 401-377-1033 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring a lunch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Narrow twisty waterways, trip is not suitable for long kayaks. No Kayaks over 15 feet. At this time of year, a wetsuit or drysuit is recommended. &lt;b&gt;At the very minimum, a change of clothes in a waterproof bag is required.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This can be reached from Rt. 95 South in southern RI. Take the exit for Rt. 138 and follow it EAST. Follow this just past the University of RI campus to the intersection with Rt. 110. Right BEFORE this intersection on your RIGHT is the put in. Watch for the sign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Put in:  N41 28 962   W071 33 082&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Great Swamp, located in the southern part of Rhode Island, provides perhaps the most intriguing canoe trip in the state. The trip is an excursion into hidden jungle-like retreats that cannot be reached any other way. Here, you will float into a vast state-owned management are a on one river, paddle across a shallow but wide pond, and then finish your trip on another river that snakes its way through dense vine-draped vegetation. There will be no doubt in your mind why this area is called Great Swamp. &amp;quot;(excerpt from Gorp)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Recent scouting suggest we may need to portage [drag boats while walking] around one beaver dam, but we can run the other [paddle really fast to get up onto the dam, and then hunch forward until you slide off the other side &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt; ]. Last year we also encountered strong winds on Wardon's Pond [really a big lake] in a favorable direction so we could surf  the 2-3' waves most of the way across.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am 5'9" 200 pounds with a shaved head. I expect to be out on work release, so I may have an ankle bracelet.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210215884000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Unbelievably scenic 6-8 mile paddle.</why><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209403995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Swamp (Southern RI)</name><id>7828413</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209909600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/7828413/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/2/global_3956338.jpeg</photo_url></item>