<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for the 14th Annual Walk for Animals at Wampatuck State Park!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets spend next Sunday walking for a great cause - show off our pups and raise a few bucks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MSPCA walk we participated in a few weeks ago was a success!! The pack members who came said they really enjoyed it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or Shine! 10am - 2pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.standishhumanesociety.com/html/events.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.standishhu...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions, details are on the website above.&lt;br /&gt;On the website you can download the registration form so you can get sponsors. Even if you choose not to get sponors, you can make a donation for as little as $10. If you raise $50, you get a free T-shirt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make a donation or do not want to get sponsors, please show up and walk with the pack anyway to support the cause. I will be getting sponsors so I can make a donation in my name, but as the organizer of our group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will linger around the registration table so everyone can find me. Please look for my two French Bulldogs - you can't miss them!!! More likely than not they will be causing a scene :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see a lot of you at the event! Pack member, Susan, mom of Henry and Nestle, will be there as a guest at the event promoting her store, Woof and Whimsy in Weymouth Landing. Stop by her table and say hello!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wait close by the registration table - Look for my French Bulldogs!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223211808000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Dog Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>packwalk</urlname><id>1030709</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dog Lovers Pack Walk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221398652000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Benefit Walk for Animals - Folk and Furfest!</name><id>8754505</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222610400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/packwalk/events/8754505/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/1/global_5035697.jpeg</photo_url></item>