<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Killingly, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><lat>41.831390</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Old Furnace State Park</name><city>Killingly</city><id>12073752</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.850281</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lets meet up with our freinds from &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;active singles&lt;/a&gt;, and hike at Old Furnance State Park in Killingly. This park is located just minutes outside of Foster, and is just off of rt 6.By March 30th all the snow should be gone away and the temps should be headed higher. AYou could just do the hike if you choose, but after we could also head off to a nice but casual restaurant that will allow is in with our muddy shoes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The map for Old &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Furnace&lt;/a&gt; is of not much help, so from the Prov area rt 6 will take you all the way to the park, and as you cross the state line you can start looking for Kikapoo Pizza which will be over on your left, and is located @ 817 Providence Pike,(which is also rt 6),Killingly CT, and you will also see The South Killingly Fire Department which is right next door to Kikapoo. The park is 2.4 miles from Kikapoo and as you approach you will see both a sign for the park which will be on your right, and a yellow blinking light. At that point you will take a sharp left onto South Frontage Road, and this will take you directly to the parks entrance where you will easily see my white &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Chevy Cobalt&lt;/a&gt;. The address for the pizza place will work with a gps, or mapquest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay here are some updates.... After taking that left you will travel 1-2/10 of a mile to the parks entrance. After the hike I am thinking that we could head up to JD Coopers restaurant in Putnam CT. Coopers is a nice place, and very relaxed in regards to things like reservations. If you want, you can just choose to do the hike. I will send out contact info for me, the night before the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also.... Last Friday the trail was still covered with snow and ice, and I know that they are tracking another possible storm for Monday into Tuesday. Should I have to postpone this hike, I will try to give plenty of notice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>11253417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364838143000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362445498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Old Furnace State Park.</name><id>107635592</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364670000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/107635592/</event_url></item>