<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>DON'T MISS OUR LAST MEETUP OF THE YEAR - THE NOVEMBER BIRTHDAY MEETUP!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, it's true, ALL of the Clarke Puggies, Buford, Max, and Miss Millie, celebrate their birthdays in November, Shar Clarke is bringing the birthday cakes (for Puggies AND people), and all the Puggies and their people are invited to the party!   We have a new location, in Bridgewater this time.  Tom and Jess Gove and their Pugs, four year old Buddha and three year old Biggie (Bigfoot), are inviting us all to meet at their place in Bridgewater right off Rte 24.  They have a huge fenced in backyard and plenty of parking, since there is a little ballpark right across the street that won't be in use on Sunday.  Bring your chairs!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that your host provides the soft drinks and paperware for each meetup, but we count on our members to bring the snacks.  If you do bring snacks for the Pugs, try to bring soft snacks so that Clovis can have some too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know. We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR OCTOBER MEETUPS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three dozen Pug lovers and their Pugs got together in Carver on the third Sunday in October for our Howl-o-ween Pug Meetup, and it was a real hit!  I saw skunks, a pony and rider, Batman, Superman, a bumble bee, a Jail Pug, a pirate, a chicken, a pretty pink princess, and a hula dancer at the party, and if I've overlooked some of the costumes, it's because there were just too many to keep track of.  The panel of judges took their jobs very seriously, and the ribbons and prizes they handed out were hotly contested.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, we added a few more contests, and more prizes and toys! - pug races by sex, best trick, cutest pug, best tail wagger, best behaved pug, best smile, oldest pug, youngest pug, and my all time favorite - FATTEST pug.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to all the people who brought the Halloween treats, and especially to Sharon and Ron for being such marvelous hosts.  And for baking the Bow-wow-wownies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once wasn't enough, and we got together AGAIN on the fourth Saturday of the month for an informal get together at your organizer's backyard for the Saturday Second Pug Meetup.  This was our second Saturday meetup, and we were pleased to welcome 16 people and 15 Pugs to our little get together.  Clovis and Cletus were thrilled to be able to host their friends.  Also in attendance were Franky and Sophie, two owner surrendered Pugs, who were more than happy to join in the fun.  They are the two Pugs with bright blue fabric and chain collars in the photos.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the people attending! If you bring treats for the Pugs, please ONLY hand out treats around the central table where everyone can keep an eye on the dogs, DON'T FEED CLOVIS, and PLEASE BE SURE that nothing gets dropped - your organizer has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who has brain damage which makes it very difficult for him to swallow. I don't want Clovis to choke to death on a stolen treat, and I'm sure no one else does either.. Thank you for your consideration!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups and the South of Boston Small Breed Dogs Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend. Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis and Cletus's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227383532000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224443353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug November Meetup</name><id>8990702</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226257200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/8990702/</event_url></item>