<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01850</zip><lat>42.649700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lowell Brewery Exchange</name><city>Lowell</city><id>297863</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.317700</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Dinner reservations have been made for about 40 people under the name &amp;quot;Sandy&amp;quot;...If you replied yes for dinner please try to arrive by 7:30. There is plenty of free parking in the lot across from the entrance. My understanding is they planned extra staff to cover us...The final dinner bills will be written &amp;quot;by table&amp;quot; so it will be easier to determine the correct amount. Please do not forget to include the tip for your server, you may want to try to bring some extra ones for change. If you did not reply for dinner but want to come at the last minute I understand the room holds up to 56....so come on along anyway.   :-)&lt;br /&gt;See you all tomorrow!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has finally all come together.....&lt;br /&gt;On FRIDAY October 19th Four on the Floor will play on the third floor of the Brewery Exchange for our group from 9 PM to 1 AM!!! While this event will be open to the public it has been planned just for US!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please spread the word to all of your friends in other singles meetup groups, everyone is welcome! The third floor is where many of us saw Spreadeagles. There is a bar, dance floor and pool tables along with plenty of tables and chairs. We are of course also welcome to use the second floor if you want to go down and ride the bull, watch the tv... whatever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brewery charges a $5.00 cover charge to go up to the 3rd floor. But if you come earlier for dinner they let you up without the charge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you reply:&lt;br /&gt;Please state yes for dinner and HOW MANY or no for dinner (at 7:30), we will need a reservation if a large crowd.&lt;br /&gt;If just coming for dancing please state how many friends you are bringing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this is a success the promoter may consider doing it with us every month! Yahoo, our own party place! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193053811000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189718461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OUR OWN SUPER EVENT!!!!</name><id>6353748</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192836600000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/6353748/</event_url></item>