<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Would you like to take your business to the next level???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's Time to Move Up!&amp;quot; is bringing in one of the best on May 27th!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DON'T MISS THIS EVENT with the one and only Mark McClure!!!  Mark McClure is the electrifying speaker and author of the hugely popular and effective Ruthless Entrepreneur System. A system of selling and entrepreneurship developed by Mark that has transcended continents and made money for those that are consistently looking to outsell, out-think and outperform their competition with tips, techniques and strategies you will be hard pressed to find anywhere else!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having spoken to SOLD OUT audiences on 4 continents, Mark has shared the stage/speaking docket with such names as Robert Kiyosaki (Rich Dad Poor Dad), Blair Singer, Brian Tracy, Tom Peters to name just a few, as well as consulted to more than two hundred of the FORTUNE 500 and thousands more at his Ruthless Entrepreneur events, Mark McClure brings experience and expertise that have made him one of the Top 5 Speakers in the world on sales and entrepreneurship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about Mark McClure, please check out this video, &lt;a href="http://youroptionsonline.com/mark/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://youroptionsonl...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Network with like minded individuals and professionals and learn something new!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It's Time to Move Up&amp;quot; networking events are designed to be unique by combining business networking, social networking and continuing education.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Agenda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00pm - 7:00pm -&amp;gt; Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;7:00pm - 7:10pm -&amp;gt; Introduction&lt;br /&gt;7:15pm - 8:30pm -&amp;gt; Special presentation with Mark McClure&lt;br /&gt;8:30pm - 9:00pm -&amp;gt; Open Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizers will be served... Check out the venue website at &lt;a href="http://www.fuji1546.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fuji1546.c...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time for a change... It's Time to Move Up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make it a great day,&lt;br /&gt;Ruben&lt;br /&gt;ruben@bostonrealestatesolutions.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the host...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217217689000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Because we have Mark McClure, top marketing and sales coach speaking this month!!!  Check out http://youroptionsonline.com/mark/index.html for more info.</why><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>realestateinvestor</urlname><id>596743</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>InvestorsBeat.com - Massachusetts Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209423861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Time to Move Up! Real Estate Business &amp; Networking w/Mark McClure!!!</name><id>7830785</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211925600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestateinvestor/events/7830785/</event_url></item>