<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Walkers Brook Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.519901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 944-9090</phone><name>IMAX Theater at Jordan's Furniture</name><city>Reading</city><id>715408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090759</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's go check the Verizon IMAX theater in Reading&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;11/4 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; I suggest buying your tickets in advance and to do that follow these directions, if you buy them at the door on Friday it may be sold out, as of tonight they have already sold 251 tickets and the theater holds 500 people!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the directions to order your ticket:&lt;br /&gt;Go to the Imax website: &lt;a href="http://www.jordansimax.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jordansima...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the right side of the screen you will see what’s plating at which location, you want the Reading Theater,&lt;br /&gt;Click on the logo a Christmas Carole,&lt;br /&gt;On the left side see pricing click on that,&lt;br /&gt;In the middle of the page you will see SEE SCHEDULE AND/OR PURCHASE WEBTIX NOW,&lt;br /&gt;When that window opens click on Reading Theater,&lt;br /&gt;Click on “For Future Schedules or to Purchase Tickets for a Future Date” Click on GO&lt;br /&gt;On the next page you will see a Calendar, click select Friday 11/6,&lt;br /&gt;Click on the 8:00 show,&lt;br /&gt;On the next page fill in how many tickets you want to purchase,&lt;br /&gt;Then follow the checking out directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to update your RSVP on the site to say “reserved ticket” so I know that you are coming, and I am looking for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you order your ticket on line it holds a spot for you when you get to the theater you will then get your ticket to enter the theater.  I am told that the place can get nuts and there are tons of people either in line, leaving the theater and or picking up tickets, so be prepared to be in the crowd.  Ordering your ticket in advance holds the ticket for you so if it sells out then you will not get in, but ordering ahead is the best way unless you work/live close and are able to get in to buy your ticket.  All the tickets are pickup you do not have the option to print it.  When you finish the ordering process you will get an email, print that and bring it with you.  You are responsible for ordering your own ticket!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHERE TO MEET:&lt;/b&gt; We will meet in the line/lobby to get your ticket in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME:&lt;/b&gt; I am changing the meetup time to 6:45pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO GET IN THE IMAX THEATER:&lt;/b&gt; When you come in the door look to your left there should be someone standing there ask that person where the Imax theater is and they will direct you.  You will basically walking to the left of the store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEATING:&lt;/b&gt; If we all get there and in line to get in the theater then we may all be able to sit together hopefully, if you are able to meet me in line then that would be great for all of us to sit together.  All together between the 3 groups there are 15+ of us signed up so it may be hard to keep us all together, but we will try! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the film it wiill be digitally re-mastered into the unparalleled image and sound quality of The IMAX Experience through proprietary IMAX DMR technology. With crystal clear images, laser-aligned digital sound and maximized filed of view, IMAX provides the world's most immersive movie experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price For an Adult the ticket is:11.50 + 1.25 handling fee &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all so bring your children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update this with more information as the date gets closer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Donna &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will update this as the date gets closer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257724078000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252768210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Disney's A Christmas Carol---in 3D!</name><id>11353938</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257551100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11353938/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/f/c/global_10653580.jpeg</photo_url></item>