<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will hike a thru-hike of about 6 miles in the southwestern corner of MA. This hike is generally hard given steep ascent and descent of Race Mtn. in typically snow and ice conditions. About half of this hike follows the AT northbound and can be rather scenic if weather cooperates. There is a chance for a fair amount of ice and/or snow. &lt;b&gt;Some experience and equipment for cold weather hiking as well as icy conditions is required.&lt;/b&gt; Any questions about your ability or equipment, talk to the hike organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike will take us gradually down through Sages Ravine (start alt 1832 ft. then down to about 1400 ft.) with an interesting stream that will have several little waterfalls and pools that should have a fair amount of ice formations this time of year. Then we will ascend to clifftop trail and on to Mt. Race (alt 2365 ft.), then down via a steep and poorly blazed (orange) side trail to Plaintain Pond Rd., and roadwalk to the cars. If the weather is clear, we should have an outstanding view of the area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Those who wish to go MUST have:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* Backpack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food, water, gear.  &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed warm hiking boots or comfortable winter boots - There will likely be ice/snow or it could be wet/muddy!  &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;MICROspikes&lt;/span&gt; (or crampons or other traction device) -MUST have! There WILL be ice! &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Snowshoes&lt;/span&gt; - There could be deep snowdrifts on ridge of Mt. Race!&lt;br /&gt;* Hiking poles (or snowshoe poles)&lt;br /&gt;* Gators (or snowpants) -To keep snow out of boots.&lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks - To keep those feet warm even if wet.  &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing - Avoid cotton as it stays wet/cold. Don't forget your legs can get cold too.  &lt;br /&gt;* Gloves - MUST have and warm ones too!  &lt;br /&gt;* Jacket - Warm outer layer. &lt;br /&gt;* Warm hat - You loose 20% of your heat through your head! Protect those ears too.  &lt;br /&gt;* 2 quarts of water - MUST bring!  &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate food/lunch - (e.g. at least G.O.R.P -Good Old Raisins and Peanuts, beef jerky, granola bars, etc.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advised/optional equipment depending on conditions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp - Just in case&lt;br /&gt;* Fanny sled - for those prone to fun on a whim &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The jacket shouldn't be too heavy as other layers of clothing should add to your insulation to keep warm and layers would be added or removed as needed. While hiking you WILL be hot but if you stop you WILL get very cold after about 15 minutes and thus need more dry layers added. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 9 AM at the parking area at the hike endpoint (see location/directions below). We will condense into one or more vehicles and drive to the start location (see location/directions below) and start hiking at about 9:15 AM. We will hike (with rest stops and sightseeing) about 6 hr. but it could be up to 7.5 hrs. depending on conditions and get back to the vehicles at about anywhere from 3 PM to 4:45 PM. Then the plan is to head out to eat at a location to be determined or you can just head home on your own.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor ***leaving*** at a 7 AM for those interested. The drive is about 1.75 hour to the meetup location. Return at about 8 PM at the latest (6 PM at earliest). You must call or e-mail Kevin (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool. If no one signs up for the carpool, the carpool will be canceled and will not go to the Wal-Mart location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/mt-washington.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt. Everett State Reservation:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/western/meve.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to meet at Meetup location, endpoint parking area&lt;/b&gt; (parking lot of small Town Hall behind church, around 120 East St., Mount Washington, MA): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=South+Egremont&amp;amp;state=MA&amp;amp;address=120+East+St&amp;amp;zipcode=01258-9710&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.099551&amp;amp;longitude=-73.453987&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(approx. Lat=42.099551, Long=-73.453987) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location/directions for the carpool meet-up location can be found at:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?searchtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;searchtab=home&amp;amp;formtype=address&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=69+Prospect+Hill+rd.&amp;amp;city=East+Windsor&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions for the hike starting point&lt;/b&gt; (east shoulder of Mt. Washington Rd. just before the MA boarder): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Salisbury&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=390+Mount+Washington+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;(approx. Lat=42.0480, Long=-73.4668) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Can meet in E. Windsor carpool.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295880581000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288188036000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike at Mt. Race in Mount Washington MA</name><id>15246016</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295704800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15246016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/4/global_19116596.jpeg</photo_url></item>