<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>74 Prospect St,</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 576-3530</phone><name>Carberry's</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>408625</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This was a well voted book, so we're finish October with The Memory Keeper's Daughter by Kim Edwards.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments: (copied from powell.com)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Award-winning writer Kim Edwards's The Memory Keeper's Daughter is a brilliantly crafted, completely riveting family drama that explores every mother's silent fear: what would happen if you lost your child, and she grew up without you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On a winter night in 1964, Dr. David Henry is forced by a blizzard to deliver his own twins. His son, born first, is perfectly healthy. Yet when his daughter is born, he sees immediately that she has Down's syndrome. Rationalizing it as a need to protect Norah, his wife, he makes a split second decision that will alter of their lives forever. He asks his nurse to take the baby away to an institution and never to reveal the secret. But Caroline, the nurse, cannot leave the infant. Instead, she disappears into another city to raise the child herself. So begins this beautifully told story that unfolds over a quarter of a century ? in which these two families, ignorant of each other, are yet bound by David Henry's fateful decision that long-ago winter night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rich, compulsively readable, and deeply moving, The Memory Keeper's Daughter captures the way life takes unexpected turns, and how the mysterious ties that hold a family together help us survive the heartache that hold a occurs when long-buried secrets burst into the open. It is an astonishing tale of redemptive love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll try something different this time around, meeting in a coffee house for a cup of joe and dessert.  The joint closes at 8, so try to be on time so we can get lots of discussion in...this is fairly close to central square, so we can change locations if there's still a ton to cover.  &lt;br /&gt;Check out their website: &lt;a href="http://www.carberrys.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.carberrys....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Lisa with any questions.    &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>cathy</member_name><member_id>4263429</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193526069000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187572963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meeting-Memory Keeper's Daughter</name><id>6209615</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193353200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/6209615/</event_url></item>