<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Tang Center (E51)</name><city>Cambridge </city><id>1233340</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;The reception is open to all starting at 6:00 pm, with the lecture starting at 7:00 pm. Let's grab seats at 6:45 pm. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering at MIT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cee.mit.edu/events/freeman-lecture-2010" target="_blank"&gt;http://cee.mit.edu/ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rubbish, Stink and Death&lt;/u&gt;: The Historical Evolution, Present State and Future Direction of Water-Quality Management and Modeling&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker&lt;/b&gt;: Steven C. Chapra, Ph.D.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Professor and Berger Chair, Civil &amp;amp; Environmental Engineering, Tufts University&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Modern environmental and water resources engineering grew out of societal concerns related to aesthetics (rubbish), ecosystem health (stink) and disease (death). The discipline originated in the latter half of the nineteenth century when civil engineers were called upon to design and construct large-scale urban water distribution and sewage collection systems. In the early 20th century, the focus of such &amp;quot;sanitary engineers&amp;quot; moved beyond infrastructure design and construction to address environmental transport and fate. A key element of this broadening involved the development of mathematical water-quality models linking anthropogenic waste discharges to ecosystem impacts. Although these models were initially designed to rationalize the sizing of urban wastewater treatment plants, they evolved over time to address a range of water-quality problems and management contexts. The present talk provides an overview of this evolution followed by an assessment of the current state of water-quality modeling and management. Finally, future directions are discussed with emphasis on my current research involving the modeling of waterborne diseases&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher was thinking of attending the reception, waiting outside the Tang Center starting at 5:50 pm, then heading in at 6:00 pm, seeing what is there. Feel free to drop in as we crash the event. It mentions it is open to all, and doesn't limit it just to students and/ or faculty, so technically we wouldn't be crashing, no? T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, but will be incognito sans nametag. He doesn't want to impersonate any of the organizers who are running this event he is crashing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the The Freeman Lecture:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cee.mit.edu/events/freeman-lecture-2010" target="_blank"&gt;http://cee.mit.edu/ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The John R. Freeman Lecture is co-sponsored by the Environmental and Water Resources Group of the Boston Society of Civil Engineers Section, the ASCE, and the MIT Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering. For more information, go to the Freeman website &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/freeman-bsces/" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/fr...&lt;/a&gt;  &amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering at MIT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://cee.mit.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;http://cee.mit.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The MIT Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering (CEE) is dedicated to balancing the built environment with the natural world. In our research, we seek to understand natural systems, to foster the intelligent use of resources and to design sustainable infrastructure systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We provide leadership in the field by focusing on technological innovations, seeking advances in basic knowledge and taking a systems perspective. We concentrate our efforts on quantitative and analytical approaches, novel experiment-based modeling, and the development and/or use of appropriate tools and technology. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;CEE is an innovative and vibrant place of learning, where undergraduates, graduate students and postdoctoral researchers pursue their educational and research interests in order to lead the next generation in transforming the disciplines of civil and environmental engineering&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Dr. Chapra's faculty page at Tufts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://engineering.tufts.edu/cee/people/chapra/index.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://engineering.tu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Steve Chapra teaches at Tufts University outside Boston, MA, where he holds the Louis Berger Chair in Computing and Engineering. Dr. Chapra received engineering degrees from Manhattan College and the University of Michigan. He has authored five textbooks including Numerical Methods for Engineers, which has been used at over 150 universities since it was first published in 1985. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Before joining the faculty at Tufts, Dr. Chapra worked for EPA, NOAA, Texas A&amp;amp;M and the University of Colorado. He has also served as the Associate Director of the Center for Advanced Decision Support in Water and Environmental Systems (CADSWES), and has been a visiting professor at Duke University, the Imperial College of Science, Technology and Medicine (London), the University of Reading and the University of Washington. His general research interests focus on surface water-quality modeling and advanced computer applications in environmental engineering. His research has been used in a number of decision-making contexts including legislative testimony and the 1978 Great Lakes Water Quality Agreement. In addition, he was the 1993 recipient of the ASCE's Rudolph Hering Medal for the outstanding paper in the field of environmental engineering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Aside from his activities in environmental engineering, he was awarded the 1987 Meriam-Wiley Distinguished Author Award by the American Society for Engineering Education for his texts on computing and engineering. He has taught over 65 workshops on water-quality modeling in the United States, Canada, Mexico, Europe, South America and Oceania. He has also produced several educational videos including &amp;quot;An Introduction to Water-Quality Modeling&amp;quot; for the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. In addition to his research, he is the first recipient of the AEESP Wiley Award for Outstanding Contributions to Environmental Engineering and Science Education, and has been recognized as the outstanding teacher among the engineering faculties at both Texas A&amp;amp;M and the University of Colorado&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Boston Society of Civil Engineers:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bsces.org/about/History/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bsces.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Boston Society of Civil Engineers Section of the American Society of Civil Engineers is a professional organization that excels in its technical programs, enhances the professional growth of its members, advances engineering knowledge and works to improve the standards of practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Established in 1848, BSCES is the oldest engineering society in the United States and currently supports over 2500 members throughout Massachusetts. BSCES formally became a Section of ASCE in 1974 after the merger with ASCE's Massachusetts Section. Ten years later, BSCES was instrumental in the formation of The Engineering Center, already a focal point for our professions throughout New England&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map of the Tang Center:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://ilp-www.mit.edu/display_page.a4d?key=p4h53" target="_blank"&gt;http://ilp-www.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;quot;The nearest paid parking is at the Kendall Marriott Hotel&amp;quot; (and seems to be &amp;quot;On-site parking, fee: 8 USD hourly, 23 USD daily&amp;quot; according to the Marriott site at &lt;a href="http://www.marriott.com/hotels/travel/boscb-boston-marriott-cambridge/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marriott.c...&lt;/a&gt; ). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Flyer (in Adobe Acrobat format):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://cee.mit.edu/sites/default/files/Freeman%20flyer%202010%20Chapra.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://cee.mit.edu/si...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272496375000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270065533000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steven C. Chapra, "Rubbish, Stink and Death: Water-Quality Management"  @ MIT</name><id>13050898</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272322800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13050898/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/e/global_14050030.jpeg</photo_url></item>