<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1230 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372617</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.497.0400</phone><name>Grafton Street Pub &amp;  Grill</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696851</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116138</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.graftonstreetcambridge.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu is posted on a &amp;quot;tab&amp;quot; on the main page of the restaurant's website: www.graftonstreetcambridge.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our reservation is for 11am. If you arrive late, ask for the Brunch Meetup at the front door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll gather at this beloved neighborhood hotspot, named after the spirited cobblestone-lined shopping district in Dublin's famed Temple Bar area. Grafton Street deftly combines a traditional Irish pub's warmth and coziness with a contemporary and comfortable full service restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Executive Chef Dan Pogue serves up contemporary American cuisine for lunch and dinner seven days a week, including a prized Sunday brunch. The bustling bar boasts an extensive selection of beer, wine and liquor, and features several signature cocktails created exclusively by award-winning Grafton Street mixologists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, weather-permitting, we can stroll about and enjoy the last bit of autumn in picturesque Harvard Square. Explore the many shops and boutiques in Harvard Yard, or check out one of the famed cultural attractions: The Harvard Museum of Natural History, the Fogg Art Museum, the Harvard University Museums, the Old Burial Ground, the Cambridge Common, or the historic Brattle movie theater, to name a few. For a post-stroll pick-me-up, we have our choice of coffee and tea purveyors, including Peet's, Starbuck's, and the ubiquitous Dunkin's; ice cream at Ben &amp;amp; Jerry's or Herrell's; or we can pay a visit to the European-style chocolatier, Burdick's, on Brattle Street, for their signature pastries and hot chocolate to die for! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refer to the &amp;quot;Getting Here&amp;quot; section on the &amp;quot;Harvard Square&amp;quot; tab on the restaurant's website. Here's some additional information you might find helpful:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TAKING THE T &lt;br /&gt;From Park Street or Downtown Crossing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grafton Street is a 5-minute walk from the Harvard Square T stop. Take the Red Line outbound to the Harvard Square stop. Exit the platform by following signs for Harvard Square. Head down Massachusetts Avenue towards Central Square. You'll pass Bartley's Burger Cottage and the Harvard Book Store on your right. Grafton street is at 1230 Massachusetts Avenue, on the corner of Bow Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BY CAR &lt;br /&gt;For those of you unfamiliar with driving in Harvard Square, please note that although there are numerous metered parking spaces (which are not in effect on Sundays, by the way), finding a space during the weekend is next to impossible--NO JOKE! I recommend you park in one of the garages mentioned on the restaurant's website, and get your ticket validated. (Nearby lots and garages are listed on the &amp;quot;Getting Here&amp;quot; section on the &amp;quot;Harvard Square&amp;quot; tab on the restaurant's website).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events &lt;br /&gt;run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while &lt;br /&gt;sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving &lt;br /&gt;promptly. &lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and &lt;br /&gt;tax. &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event &lt;br /&gt;and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO- &lt;br /&gt;SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than twenty- &lt;br /&gt;four hours from the the event you are counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if &lt;br /&gt;you've NO-SHOWED. &lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the &lt;br /&gt;group. &lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on &lt;br /&gt;the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who &lt;br /&gt;staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not &lt;br /&gt;able to attend, you must email me (Laura) at DessertAndCoffee@aol.com.  I don't give out my phone number, so you will not be able to reach me at the last minute.  If on that morning you are lost and need directions, call the restaurant (see phone number above).&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than &lt;br /&gt;twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected &lt;br /&gt;courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other &lt;br /&gt;unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO &lt;br /&gt;with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO &lt;br /&gt;with a comment to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and &lt;br /&gt;venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199145055000</updated><rating><average>4.63000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193836232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Late Autumn Brunch in Harvard Square</name><id>6649582</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195401600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6649582/</event_url></item>