<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>73 Weir Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01776</zip><lat>42.402975</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Meadows National Wildlife Refuge </name><city>Sudbury</city><id>808751</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.374657</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet in the parking lot of the refuge headquarters / visitor center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Meadows National Wildlife Refuge lies within a region uniquely rich in natural and cultural resources. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A great diversity of birds have been recorded at the refuge. Several species of waterfowl, including mallards, black ducks, wood ducks, and blue-winged teal nest here. While-tailed deer, muskrats, red fox, raccoons, cottontail rabbits, weasels, beaver, squirrels, and a variety of small mammals are common. Many species of amphibians and reptiles are active during the warmer months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A visitor center, located at refuge headquarters in Sudbury, contains interpretive exhibits and brochures, as well as a small sales outlet, where a variety of books and post cards may be purchased. Interpretive information and general information is posted on kiosks throughout the refuge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wildlife Observation and Photography&lt;br /&gt;Great Meadows National Wildlife Refuge is a popular destination for birders and others who enjoy observing and photographing wildlife. Accessible trails at both the Concord and Sudbury units of the refuge provide visitors with a unique window through which to view and experience the natural world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Refuge Headquarters is located at 73 Weir Hill Road in Sudbury, Massachusetts, and is open from 8 am to 4 pm, Monday through Friday, closed all Federal holidays. To reach the office and visitor center at Weir Hill, follow Route 27 (1.7 miles) from Wayland and turn right onto Water Row Road. Follow Water Row Road (1.2 miles) until it ends and turn right onto Lincoln Road. Travel one half mile, turn left onto Weir Hill Road and follow to the end. All refuge lands are open sunrise to sunset, 365 days a year. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286928348000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285266254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Meadows Nat'l Wildlife Refuge - Sudbury</name><id>14872618</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286634600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/14872618/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/c/global_2171756.jpeg</photo_url></item>