<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Note:  This event requires a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason.  Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The February Restaurant of the month is the Meena's Kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a first generation migrant hailing from Andhra Pradesh, Meena was looking for authentic vegetarian Indian food without any luck. Her penchant for good food made her look for ways to create a good foster environment in their friendly New England area, resulting in the Meena's Kitchen. After years of hard work and with the help of friends, her experience in Indian food from childhood, and a cooking style closer to her heart, she was able to recreate some of that here. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meena says: &amp;quot;Meena's Kitchen will be a trend where I'd like to incorporate a style of cooking closer to people's tastes and provide different cuisines prevelant all over India. Be it south or north  or Gujrathi or Bengali. I thank all my friends who stood by me, my family who believed in me and all the patrons who embraced my food with enthusiasm&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Management&lt;br /&gt;Meena's Kitchen was founded by Meenakshi and family. Meenakshi is the chef-in-charge of the operations and  is the vision behind the concept. It is a family owned and operated business in tune with their motto of bringing the authenic flavors and tastes of India to the people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meenaskitchen.com/Menucard.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meenaskitc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266884011000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259076678000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Restaurant of the Month</name><id>11946762</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266710400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/11946762/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/0/global_13196736.jpeg</photo_url></item>