<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 North Moodus Rd.,</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06469 </zip><lat>41.530704</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 668-7885 </phone><name>HEARTSTONE LABYRINTHS</name><city>Moodus</city><id>1166345</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.456648</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;HeartStone Labyrinths Open House&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at Heartstone's Summer Open House to walk the Forest Labyrinth. Experience its connections to the Earth and to yourself, play with the finger labyrinths, and enjoy a pleasant afternoon of healing and connection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moodus, CT&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1 to 5 p.m. Cost: FREE &lt;br /&gt;(Note: Rain date July 11th) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk into the labyrinth provides an opportunity for us to begin self-observation, contemplation and release. The task is to walk the labyrinth cognizant of a &amp;quot;witness&amp;quot; state—being the observed and the observer at the same time. Simply pay attention to what you are feeling and thinking and then, with a deep breath, release it and let it go, freeing your awareness to be available for the next moment in time. The walk in is a time of preparation, as if you are emptying your mind of thoughts, memories, expectations, and judgments, so that you are open and ready to receive guidance when you reach the center. It is the journey from your head to your heart, from thought to feeling, from logic to intuition, from believing to knowing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The center of the labyrinth, the heart, represents the sacred destination. Whether you receive an answer to a question, a valuable insight about your life or merely a sense of peace, solitude or joy, the center is a quiet space in which you get what you need, if not what you came for. You come to know the stillness of the center—your center—as a sanctuary to which you always have access and can return whenever your soul needs rejuvenation. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278785916000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275955932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HeartStone Labyrinths</name><id>13730621</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278781200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/13730621/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/a/global_11136970.jpeg</photo_url></item>