<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Many people don't realize that its called Plum Island because of the abundance of wild beach plums. Park visitors are allowed to pick a quart each of plums and cranberries after Labour Day, in designated areas. We will try to pick our quota and take a walk on the beach afterwards. Wear long pants to protect your legs while picking fruit. Bring your swimsuit too if you want to get in a final swim of the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park admittance is $5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beach plum (Prunus maritima) is a fruiting shrub native to coastal dunes of the Northeastern United States. Since colonial times, people have collected wild fruit to make preserves and jelly. Today, native stands still support a cottage beach plum product industry in the Northeast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Parker River National Wildlife Refuge is located approximately 32 miles northeast of Boston on Plum Island. Plum Island is a natural barrier island stretching along the Massachusetts Atlantic coast between the mouth of the Merrimack River to the north and the mouth of the Ipswich River to the south. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Refuge occupies the southern three-fourths of the island and is 4,662 acres in size. Included within this space are 6.5 miles of sandy beach, approximately 3,000 acres of salt marsh, three managed fresh water impoundments, and one of the few unspoiled dune-beach complexes still existing in the Northeast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Refuge is accessible by motor vehicle and foot over mostly gentle terrain. Several miles of foot trails meander through dune, shrub/thicket, freshwater marsh, and other Refuge habitats. Observation towers and platforms afford commanding views of the Refuge and surrounding lands and waters. A 6.3 mile (10.1 km) roadway runs the length of the Refuge and provides several pulloffs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the information building at the first parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221690526000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219548746000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>pick wild beach plums and cranberries at Plum Island</name><id>8607760</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221332400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/8607760/</event_url></item>