<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The books for August:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Stoning of Soraya M.: A Story of Injustice in Iran&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;by Freidoune Sahebjam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;A moving look at justice run amok in Iran&amp;mdash;now more timely than ever.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soraya M.&amp;rsquo;s husband, Ghorban-Ali, couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to marry another woman. Rather than returning Soraya&amp;rsquo;s dowry, as custom required before taking a second wife, he plotted with four friends and a counterfeit mullah to dispose of her. Together, they accused Soraya of adultery. Her only crime was cooking for a friend&amp;rsquo;s widowed husband. Exhausted by a lifetime of abuse and hardship, Soraya said nothing, and the makeshift tribunal took her silence as a confession of guilt. They sentenced her to death by stoning: a punishment prohibited by Islam but widely practiced.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Day by day&amp;mdash;sometimes minute by minute&amp;mdash;Sahebjam deftly recounts these horrendous events, tracing Soraya&amp;rsquo;s life with searing immediacy, from her arranged marriage and the births of her children to her husband&amp;rsquo;s increasing cruelty and her horrifying execution, where, by tradition, her father, husband, and sons hurled the first stones. A stark look at the intersection between culture and justice, this is one woman&amp;rsquo;s story, but it stands for the stories of thousands of women who suffered&amp;mdash;and continue to suffer&amp;mdash;the same fate. It is a story that must be told.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Left to Tell: Discovering God Amidst the Rwandan Holocaust&lt;/em&gt; by Immaculee Ilibagiza&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1994, Rwandan native Ilibagiza was 22 years old and home from college to spend Easter with her devout Catholic family, when the death of Rwanda's Hutu president sparked a three-month slaughter of nearly one million ethnic Tutsis in the country. She survived by hiding in a Hutu pastor's tiny bathroom with seven other starving women for 91 cramped, terrifying days. This searing firsthand account of Ilibagiza's experience cuts two ways: her description of the evil that was perpetrated, including the brutal murders of her family members, is soul-numbingly devastating, yet the story of her unquenchable faith and connection to God throughout the ordeal uplifts and inspires. Her account of the miracles that protected her is simple and vivid. Her Catholic faith shines through, but the book will speak on a deep level to any person of faith. Ilibagiza's remarkable path to forgiving the perpetrators and releasing her anger is a beacon to others who have suffered injustice. She brings the battlefield between good and evil out of the genocide around her and into her own heart, mind and soul. This book is a precious addition to the literature that tries to make sense of humankind's seemingly bottomless depravity and counterbalancing hope in an all-powerful, loving God.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sara</member_name><member_id>6494254</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314884866000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311613590000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August book discussion</name><id>26960621</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314829800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/26960621/</event_url></item>