<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.407043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-1499</phone><name>Together in Motion</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.133880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the Wednesday Night Meetup for the Arlington Martial Arts Group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Together In Motion has opened their gym for our group for Wednesday Nights at 8:00 typically to 9:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Donation of $5.00 is recommended which goes to the Not Me! non profit which is a ORGANIZATION DEDICATED TO PROVIDING INSTRUCTION, CONDITIONING, AND TRAINING TO INDIVIDUALS IN AT-RISK POPULATIONS. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit Not-Me.Org if you would like information on the group the donations benefit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This open mat time is open to all levels and backgrounds of martial arts, typically this is a self directed group which allows everyone to work on practice of their choosing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Past meetups have had flow drills, throwing practice, locking practice, punching mitt and kicking targets. This really is an open format which allows members to question what they have been taught, share with others and just practice with no pressure of joining a school or formal system. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've been out of practice for years or months but want to start doing something again this is the place! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us with a friendly spirit, bring whatever equipment you have or just yourself, uniform or running shorts makes no difference to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Together in Motion facility has a large open area with raised spring hard wood floor with dense mats covering, so it is adaptable for just about any type of practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The facility is located at One Broadway in Arlington MA 02474&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Bob or Erik when you get there</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob</member_name><member_id>4202193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290437229000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Martial Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>martial-221</urlname><id>502152</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The Arlington Martial Arts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283101570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Mat time at Together in Motion, Arlington MA</name><id>jbljpynpbwb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290042000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/martial-221/events/15413848/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/d/global_1922077.jpeg</photo_url></item>