<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.762536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-987-6000</phone><name>Bushnell Theater</name><city>Hartford</city><id>890377</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>Group Rate Discount</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Century of Broadway&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, February 20, 2010, 8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mortensen Hall, The Bushnell Center for the Performing Arts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Tyzik, conductor&lt;br /&gt;Christiane Noll and Doug Lebreque, guest artists&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Gilbert &amp;amp; Sullivan and Irving Berlin, to Rodgers &amp;amp; Hammerstein and Andrew Lloyd Weber – we invite you to tour the world of Broadway over the course of a century with three of today’s most accomplished artists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeff Tyzik is principal pops conductor of the Rochester Philharmonic, Vancouver and Oregon Symphony Orchestras. Christiane Noll made her Broadway debut as Emma in Jekyll &amp;amp; Hyde, received an Ovation Award for her role in the national tour of Urinetown, and wowed audiences in the American premieres of The Mambo Kings and The Witches Of Eastwick. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doug LaBrecque has starred as both The Phantom and Raoul in the Broadway production of The Phantom of the Opera, played Ravenal in the Harold Prince revival of Showboat,and toured nationally with Les Misérables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $32.50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUY ONLINE AND GET OUR GROUP DISCOUNT&lt;br /&gt;Only $25 While Tickets Remain &lt;br /&gt;Oct 26 Hartford Symphony Orchestra with The CT Theatre Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on Buy Now and use Credit or Debit Card or call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266886997000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252608957000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Century of Broadway with the Hartford Symphony Orchestra at the Bushnell Theatre</name><id>11339894</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266714000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/11339894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/b/global_10634331.jpeg</photo_url></item>