<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 William T Morrissey Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.309647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Savin Hill Yacht Club</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1527219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The author of The Annapolis Book of Seamanship, Fastnet, Force 10, and many other well-known books, John Rousmaniere will give a presentation on basic sailing safety. He has spoken at or moderated more than 100 seminars on sailing safely at sea. John is a world renown and safety authority.. He sailed in the 1979 Fastnet Yacht Race which was hit by severe storms wreaking havoc on 303 yachts and claiming fifteen lives. He wrote the definitive book about the storm, Fastnet Force 10. Most recently he was part of US SAILING&amp;#146;s independent reviews of two widely publicized fatal sailing accidents &amp;#150; one that killed two sailors on Lake Michigan in the Chicago-Mackinac Race, the other a capsize in a 420 class boat at Annapolis, Md., in which a 14-year-old died. The reports were released in late October and are at www.ussailing.org. John will discuss these accidents and the lessons learned, and answer questions. He is the author of twenty eight books on sailing, history, instruction and safety. Most notably, he is now writing the 4th edition of The Annapolis Book of Seamanship, the standard text used by the ASA and many other sailing schools for sailing education. Pelagic Sailing Club meets at Savin Hill Yacht Club, Dorchester, MA, on the second floor at 6:30pm for social hour and pizza, 7:30pm for meeting, 8:00pm guest speaker. For more information, updated details of speakers, sails, etc, or to join, check out our website at: &lt;a href="http://PelagicSailingClub.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://PelagicSailing...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324427065000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320412521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hear John Rousmaniere Report on Safety At Sea At Pelagic Sailing Club</name><id>39930372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321572600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/39930372/</event_url></item>