<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a hike that our single members might enjoy. Charlie's Active Singles hikes are for active single people in their 30's through 50's and average up to 200 people per event! These events have been found to be fun and well planned!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet-up is at about 8:15 AM at location of the hike. Hikers are usually split up into 3 different hiking skill levels (something like advanced, novice, and social) and the difficulty of the hike corresponds. The hike starts at 8:30 AM and usually lasts about 2 hours. Afterwards, dinner facilities are arranged for refueling and socializing. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (a bit sketchy but best I have): &lt;br /&gt;* Take 84 west &amp;amp; get off exit 10&lt;br /&gt;* End of ramp turn right and proceed up Church Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Go thru two traffic lights then under train tressel&lt;br /&gt;* Take first right after train tressel onto Boulevard Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow Boulevard Rd which turns into Hanover Rd. for 3.5 miles till boat launch on right&lt;br /&gt;* Park in parking lot at the boat launch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles is a 10 year old, non-profit Connecticut organization that brings together singles who enjoy participating in a variety of outdoor activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Charlie (organizer of Active Singles) 860-489-9611&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership is planned to be at this hike. Just mingle with the other Active Singles (you're one!). No trail maps appear to be available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO Children or Dogs, Singles only (this doesn't mean you can't have a boyfriend or girlfriend). Wear Hiking Boots. Bring water. Optional Brunch follows each hike. Non hikers can join us at the restaurant. Call Charlie early to reserve a spot for Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540262000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1148326060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Active Singles Hike to Upper Paugussett SF in Newtown CT</name><id>4946991</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1150028100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4946991/</event_url></item>