<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:40 on Tuesday night, so we'll meet by 7:10 just outside (or just inside, if it's raining buckets) the theater doors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, please keep your RSVP up to date. Feel free to call me with any last-minute changes to your RSVP, if you get lost, if you're running late, etc. 508/308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul (my hubby) and his son, Ryan, saw this movie on Saturday and liked it a lot, so I think we're in for a good show!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, cost: $8/ticket. $3/small popcorn. $3/small soda. All are bargains off the list price at the theater. After the movie, those interested can head to Friday's to chat and eat and drink and be merry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Denzel Washington: Good guy. John Travolta: Bad guy. Exciting stuff! &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/summer-movies/the-taking-of-pelham-1-2-3/1810003158" target="_blank"&gt;The Taking of Pelham 123&lt;/a&gt; promises to deliver a train ride of a thriller/action movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summary:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;It's just another day for New York City subway dispatcher Walter Garber, until Ryder, a bitter ex-con, hijacks one of the trains. Unless the city pays Ryder one million dollars within the hour for each hostage on the train, he and his four armed accomplices will execute them all. The mystery is: Where does Ryder plan to go once he gets the money? Garber finds himself in an unlikely position of power, since he is the only one who knows the subway system well enough to foil Ryder's plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for The Taking of Pelham 123!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246408359000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244003308000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Taking of Pelham 123</name><id>10563160</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245798000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10563160/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>