<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/2/6/event_134778982.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hitman: The Untold Story of Johnny Martorano: Whitey Bulger's Enforcer and the Most Feared Gangster in the Underworld by Howie Carr&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Martin Scorsese's The Departed barely touched on his story. Now radio talk-show sensation, crime reporter, and Boston Herald columnist Howie Carr takes us into the heart of the life of Johnny Martorano. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For two decades, Martorano struck fear into anyone even remotely connected to his world. His partnership with Whitey Bulger and the infamous Winter Hill Gang led to twenty murders... for which Johnny would serve twelve years in prison. Carr also looks at the politicians and FBI agents who aided Johnny and Whitey, and at the flamboyant city of Boston, which Martorano so ruthlessly ruled. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 A plethora of paradoxes, Johnny Martorano was Mr. Mom by day and man-about-town by night. Surrounded by fast-living politicians, sports celebrities, and showbiz entertainers, Johnny was charismatically colorful--as charming as he was frightening. After all, he was, in the end... a hitman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Chosen by: Scott&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defending Jacob by William Landay&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andy Barber has been an assistant district attorney in his suburban Massachusetts county for more than twenty years. He is respected in his community, tenacious in the courtroom, and happy at home with his wife, Laurie, and son, Jacob. But when a shocking crime shatters their New England town, Andy is blindsided by what happens next: His fourteen-year-old son is charged with the murder of a fellow student. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Every parental instinct Andy has rallies to protect his boy. Jacob insists that he is innocent, and Andy believes him. Andy must. He’s his father. But as damning facts and shocking revelations surface, as a marriage threatens to crumble and the trial intensifies, as the crisis reveals how little a father knows about his son, Andy will face a trial of his own—between loyalty and justice, between truth and allegation, between a past he’s tried to bury and a future he cannot conceive. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Award-winning author William Landay has written the consummate novel of an embattled family in crisis—a suspenseful, character-driven mystery that is also a spellbinding tale of guilt, betrayal, and the terrifying speed at which our lives can spin out of control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Mystery Guest&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott </member_name><member_id>5819153</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Turnberg</member_name><member_id>10580891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343955527000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335405289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July's Discussion: Hitman &amp; Defending Jacob</name><id>62172472</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343773800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/62172472/</event_url></item>