<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1271 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-491-6568 </phone><name>East Coast Grill</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669133</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**** Email Confirmation Required ****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've RSVPd YES, you must confirm with Tonya via email before 11am on Saturday, August 25th that you will join us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** If you don't email, It is assumed you're not able to attend and your RSVP will be changed to NO. **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call Tonya at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Shirley, the newest organizer, we will be enjoying brunch at East Coast Grill which the Phantom Gourmet describes as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Claiming the world's largest Bloody Mary bar, East Coast Grill &amp;amp; Raw Bar is a famously fun restaurant with a wacky Sunday brunch. Their specialty barbequed seafood is in full effect, but the Latin flavored eggs are just as good.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join fellow brunch buddies for a fun time on a spicy culinary adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eastcoastgrill.net/menus/brunchmenu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;East Coast Brunch Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may call East Coast for parking details at (617) 491-6568&lt;br /&gt;Check mbta.com for train and bus directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly for events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend an event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO after 11am Saturday August 25th, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call Tonya at (617) 445-7549. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192597655000</updated><rating><average>4.53999996185</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186289680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Coast Brunch With Punch</name><id>6127318</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188140400000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6127318/</event_url></item>