<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,          &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a moment to read the complete update below.... Thank you to all who attended our last Meetup!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a special announcement a &amp;quot;Special Event &amp;quot; will be taking place at Doggie Day Playcenter,  Thursday, March 20, 2008!!!!  &lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring your pet as this is a &amp;quot;mini-meetup&amp;quot; for all the Boston Chi members.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet and Greet with  &lt;br /&gt;Amy Citarell of Harvest Moo&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; Amy is a talented artist who in a whimsical and bright way can  &lt;br /&gt;capture your pet?s most intimate or crazy moments with oil on  &lt;br /&gt;canvas. Each painting is an original that you will have for  &lt;br /&gt;your entire life. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Please join us on Thursday, March 20, 2008 from 6pm-8pm at the  &lt;br /&gt;DoggieDay play center located at 400 Tremont St, Boston, MA for  &lt;br /&gt;a meet and greet with this aspiring artist. You can also bring  &lt;br /&gt;a favorite photo with you to have Amy convert into a timeless  &lt;br /&gt;art piece. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;More information about Amy Citarell and Harvest Moo can be  &lt;br /&gt;found online at www.harvestmoo.com &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you are unable to meet Amy this Thursday, samples of her  &lt;br /&gt;work can be viewed at the DoggieDay Play Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;We will also be meeting again on April 13th at 1PM for our meetup. I am hoping to plan a special event for the spring so please stay tuned.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:      &lt;br /&gt;There is some free parking located behind Doggieday Playcenter (Tremont Street)  and the CVS, for non-residents of the area there are also plenty of metered spots near DoggieDay located on Tremont street as well as &amp;quot;South End visitor parking spots&amp;quot; located on each end of the street in the South end . Although those may be harder to come by.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay well....ST      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;br /&gt;DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER ( 400 Tremont Street, South end, Boston,02116 ...our usual location 1:00PM ONLY!        &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.doggieday.com/playcenter.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doggieday....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208615053000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205086326000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua April Meeting</name><id>7497429</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208106000000</time><rsvp_limit>42</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/7497429/</event_url></item>