<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a local Connecticut vineyard located in Wallingford approximately 30 minutes south from Hartford.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday evenings from 4 pm to 7 pm there is musical entertainment for your wine tasting experience.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relax, and enjoy some conversation with your fellow partners about all the summer activities you want to do, your passions, your dreams, and bring some of your favorite snacks or desserts that accents the wine you like to share with the group.  The winery offers cheese and crackers only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost for the wine tasting is $6.00 which includes a souvenir wine glass to taste all four wines offered here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the following websites for more information:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gouveiavineyards.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gouveiavin...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctwine.com/gouveia.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctwine.com...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:  &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:  &lt;br /&gt;From I-91 South, Take Exit 14, East Center Street. Turn left onto East Center Street. Go approximately 1 mile, the reservoir and Ct Wine Trail sign will be on the right, Turn right onto Whirlwind Hill Road.  &lt;br /&gt;The winery is approximately half a mile on the right.   &lt;br /&gt;Go through the gate up the the first building on the right. &lt;br /&gt;The wine tasting room is the smaller building next to the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not sure how many people tend to be there on these Saturday's, but will do my best to make my and Meetup.com's presence known for those who are new to the group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Al-r is the organizer for this event.  Please contact him with questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174512900000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172611474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gouveia Vineyard, Entertainment and Conversation</name><id>5519653</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173560400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5519653/</event_url></item>