<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2011/SHOWBIZ/Movies/06/01/tree.of.life.goodman/index.html?hpt=hp_c1"&gt;EXCERPT&lt;/a&gt;: "[The Tree of Life] stars Brad Pitt as a stern but ultimately disappointed   father of three boys in 1950s Texas, Jessica Chastain as his  luminescent  wife and Sean Penn as one of their grown-up sons many years  later;  there is little in the way of linear narrative or dialogue  outside of  breathy voiceovers contemplating the existence and  disposition of God;  there are lengthy sequences of volcanoes erupting,  cells dividing and  many other awe-inspiring natural phenomena that  recall both "Nova" and  "2001: A Space Odyssey"; and, yes, there are CGI  dinosaurs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This should be a great movie for BA due to the way this film touches upon the conflict between our want of life and our understanding of it. It seems like it might even capture the relentless "soul searching" everyone goes through on some level, without  the typical appeal to a preferred dogma. Giving credit where deserved, the film deals with concepts of faith, love, and meaning in a poetic way. In any case, it will make for good after-movie discussion at Tommy Doyles over beer and spirit immediately after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will gather outside the theater at 745, and begin seating ourselves at 8pm for the 810pm start. If you watch the movie earlier, feel free to join us at Tommy Doyles just across and down the street from the theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My cell (Evan): 702-280-3583&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be waiting outside the theatre all the way up to 5 minutes prior to the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>4427039</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307841132000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306953245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie night, "The Tree of Life"</name><id>20548051</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307836800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/20548051/</event_url></item>