<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The discussion for November and December will be "Everything is the Way - Ordinary Mind Zen" by Elihu Genmyo Smith (paperback, Shambhala Publications, also available as an e-book).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please read Part One and Part Two.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, when Zen has become a kind of shorthand for anything that's enigmatic or aesthetically spare, it's refreshing to be reminded that Zen is at heart a practice for waking up from the dream we inhabit -- in order to free ourselves from suffering the dream imposes on us. Elihu Genmyo Smith's eminently practical Zen teaching never loses sight of that central concern:  Whether it takes the form of &lt;em&gt;zazen&lt;/em&gt; (meditation), &lt;em&gt;koan&lt;/em&gt; work, or just eating your breakfast, the aim of Zen practice is always nothing other than intimacy with ourselves and everything around us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elihu Genmyo Smith is resident teacher of the Prairie Zen Center in Champaign, Illinois. A cofounder of the Ordinary Mind Zen school, he is a dharma heir of Charlotte Joko Beck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please enter on the Commercial Street side of the building - first door on right after entering.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352848595000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346729045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion of "Everything is the Way - Ordinary Mind Zen" by Elihu Genmyo Smith</name><id>80724882</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352764800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/80724882/</event_url></item>