<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The lazy days of summer are over! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/crying.gif' border='0' alt='crying' /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The family, friends and holiday-oriented events kick off this month with Rosh Hashanah, and last through January. Whew! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great time to pick one clutter area and tackle it once and for all. To learn how, we will call on the friendly folks at &lt;b&gt;The Container Store&lt;/b&gt; - the &lt;i&gt;neatest&lt;/i&gt; place I know! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will show us how to develop a plan to get organized and what tolls will help keep you that way. The right system and plan can totally change your life.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Friday, 8/29, Oprah revisited some of the season's most memorable guests. You may remember the hoarder, who had layers &lt;i&gt;several feet deep&lt;/i&gt; of stuff on every surface. Her house was unbelieveable. It took over 100 people &lt;i&gt;months&lt;/i&gt; to get rid of the clutter. Now, many months later, the Oprah show paid a surprise visit (with cameras) to see how she was doing. The house was immaculate! The former hoarder was now a black belt organizer, thanks to a system she could follow. She radiated joy in showing people around her lovely clean home - down the sock drawer, sorted by color and neatly rolled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I figure if she can do it, so can we. Come listen as the experts share their ideas, systems, tips and tricks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 7 PM on Tuesday, September 23 at the Chestnut Hill location off Route 9. There is plenty of free parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilyn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://declutter.meetup.com/113/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the door greeting people as they arrive</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225238844000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220105777000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Use Organizing Systems and Tools</name><id>8652339</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222210800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/8652339/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/d/global_5119229.jpeg</photo_url></item>