<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>212 Route 101</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03031</zip><lat>42.874680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 672-0500</phone><name>The Black Forest</name><city>Amherst</city><id>820222</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.613480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Note: This event requires a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason. Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The June Brunch of the month is the Black Forest Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Brunch of the Month:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce &amp;amp; Martha Walters first opened the doors of the Black Forest Café &amp;amp; Bakery on November 25, 1988. Early on, the Walters adopted a unique philosophy. All foods made at the Black Forest would be fresh, hand-made everyday from scratch using natural ingredients. No mass production at this shop! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Originally, the café &amp;amp; bakery was located in Salzburg Square, a quaint little shopping plaza located in Amherst, NH. The starting location of the café &amp;amp; bakery helped the owners, Martha and Bruce, determine the name of their restaurant, paying homage to the Square’s German heritage. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 10 years, the Black Forest outgrew its Salzburg Square location and was in dire need of an expansion. In order to accommodate their ever-growing list of customers, Martha and Bruce needed more space for dining and a larger kitchen/bakery to accommodate the production of take-out meals and side dishes. Fortunately, the two found just the right location not too far away in Amherst on Route 101. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the new location came space for a function room located on the top level of the new building. This extra space allowed the Black Forest to open its doors to cater events such as business luncheons, baby showers, holiday lunch parties and bridal showers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, the Black Forest Café &amp;amp; Bakery has more than 40 employees in their hard-working team. All of the hard work and dedication is paying off as the restaurant continues to grow and prosper with each passing year. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.theblackforestcafe.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theblackfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.theblackforestcafe.com/index.php?submenu=menus&amp;amp;src=gendocs&amp;amp;link=SundayBrunchMenu" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theblackfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from Manchester via Interstate 93:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going North on I-93, follow signs for I-293/Rte 101 West. I-293 and I-93 split south of Manchester. Follow   I-293 as it forks to the left. Continue on this road following signs for Rte 101 West until you reach a large 4-way  intersection and traffic lights. At the light, you will take a left to continue on Rte. 101 West. Follow this road through Bedford into Amherst. You will pass a store on the right called the Basket Barn (about 8 miles from the 101 light). The next business on the right will be the Black Forest Cafe (1.5 miles past the Basket Barn). See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from Nashua and Massachusetts via Route 3:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going North on Route 3, take Exit 8. This exit loops around and you go through 3 sets of lights. At the third light, you will take a right onto Route 101A. (At the new Hampton Inn) Go approximately 5 miles into Amherst. When you cross over a set of railroad tracks, look for a sign on your left that says &amp;quot;Amherst-Bedford Route 101 East - Next Left&amp;quot;. Taking that left brings you onto Route 101. At this point, The Black Forest will be about 3 miles on your left. See you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244862860000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239398787000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Brunch of the Month</name><id>10160809</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244388600000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/10160809/</event_url></item>