<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;CT REIA Monthly Meeting with Nyrik &amp;amp; Linda Huuskonen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Build an empire from single family homes that cost less than many new cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 15, 2010. 5:30-9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Crowne Plaza Hotel. 100 Berlin Road. Cromwell, CT&lt;br /&gt;FREE for CTREIA Members, $30 for guests&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=240" target="_blank"&gt;ctreia.com/events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nyrik and Linda Huuskonen started buying real estate 23 years ago. They bought at the height of the market in the late 80's. The painful mistakes they made then caused them to come up with a formula for buying real estate that ensured their long term success. Nyrik was able to retire from his contracting business at age 38 and devote his attention to his passion - real estate. They now own real estate in five states and are proud to have had their daughter join them at the age of 17 in building her own portfolio. She is 20 years old now and manages her five properties as well as working in the family business, located in Peabody MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nyrik and Linda are associated REIA members and have been guest speakers at many New England REIA's. The success shown to members of those REIAs who have participated in their worshops and road trips have earned them several repeat invites as guest speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nyrik and Linda have successfully taught many New England investors how to purchase properties and grow their portfolios. Perhaps YOU will be their next million dollar portfolio owner!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will teach you:&lt;br /&gt;* Buy Real Estate Investments with minimum 20% ROI&lt;br /&gt;* Find and purchase single and multi family homes for less than $20k&lt;br /&gt;* Create long term multi-generational wealth&lt;br /&gt;* Buy at tax sale for less than $1/sq. ft. gross living area&lt;br /&gt;* Grow your portfolio using none of your own money and making money EVERY STEP OF THE WAY. Never wait years to put money in your pocket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - Early Bird Members Workshop&lt;br /&gt;5:40-6:40 - Network with investors, vendors, and professionals&lt;br /&gt;6:40-7:00 - Member Deals and Announcements&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Guest speaker: Andy Heller&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER at: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=240" target="_blank"&gt;ctreia.com/events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268862915000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267023157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CTREIA Monthly Meeting: Build an empire from single family homes</name><id>12694509</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268688600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12694509/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/d/b/global_13304523.jpeg</photo_url></item>