<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Put your turkey in the oven and come join Steve and Mary for this short, fun hike! Over the river and through the woods (and along the cliffs), we’ll hike a combination of trails and cover 3+ miles in 1.5 hours (with the option to add a mile at the end for those with time). Hike in the morning and you can have seconds at Thanksgiving dinner!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;HIKE PLAN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be hiking at Valley Falls Park in Vernon, an easy to get to location between I-84 and I-384. We've planned a hike route that gets to the little used trails and more interesting vistas of the park.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A looping hike of moderate difficulty. We'll start at the pond, go up the hillside to the Hop River Linear Trail then take the Boulder Crest Trail to the top of the ridge (Bolton Schist of the Devonian Littleton Formation to you geologists). From here, we’ll head to the garnet studded cliffs that overlook the park to enjoy the view. It’s a short hike from here back to the parking lot; or stick around for the bonus mile along the babbling Railroad Brook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;During our scouting of the hiking trails we were passed by White-tailed Deer, got within ten feet of roosting Black Vultures, and were entertained by the Downy Woodpeckers, Chickadees, and other winter birds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;I-84 E to exit 66.  Left off ramp onto Frontage Road. First right onto Bolton Road. Right onto Bread and Milk Road. Left onto Valley Falls Road. Parking lot will be on your right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I-384E to end. Bear left onto Route 44 E. At Bolton Notch, turn left onto Quarry Road. Go 2.4 mi. and turn left onto Valley Falls Rd. Parking lot will be on your left.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Address for GPS: &lt;/span&gt;312 Valley Falls Rd, Vernon Rockville, CT 06066&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contact:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;Call Mary at (&lt;/span&gt;860) 712-1008&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Link to Trail Map:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vernon-ct.gov/parks_rec/Vernon_Rails-to-Trails.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.vernon-ct.gov/parks_rec/Vernon_Rails-to-Trails.pdf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary</member_name><member_id>8931904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353612968000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353039980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Valley Falls in Vernon CT</name><id>91634042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353594600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/91634042/</event_url></item>