<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Danforth Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Spontaneous Celebrations</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>230203</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110001</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>dance; $20 inc. dinner</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Are you looking for like-minded progressives to dance with in Boston?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns in a tropic environment? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions while banishing those winter blues?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Socializing for Justice at the Tropical Fiesta at Spontaneous Celebrations on March 3rd @ 8PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out and dance in a beautifully decorated space that gives the feel of being in a jungle.  Spontaneous Celebrations is the type of community center you didn't think existed anymore and the Tropical Fiesta is a fantastic way to get out of the biting cold of Boston's winter and into a space of creativity and love!  Not to mention a great way to support a vibrant social justice organization!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No program. No speaker. Just show up and shake your tailfeather!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP yes, maybe or no.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At SoJust you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that the SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/47/139082095_6654353d6b_m.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tropical Fiesta is a two-part event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first part, from 4pm-8pm includes craft activities, children's performances, and dinner.  The performances will include a puppet show, as well as a drumming dancing, and stilt walking performance by the Spontaneous Celebrations youth performance troupe.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After 8pm, the Tropical dance party begins with youth-led Salsa and Hip-Hop dance lessons.  Music and dancing will continue until midnight.  Beer &amp;amp; wine will be served in addition to non-alcoholic tropical drinks.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JUST CONFIRMED:  Entertainment provided by neo-reggae group Dis-N-Dat Band!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.disndatonline.homestead.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.disndatonl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SoJust members receive discounted prices: $20 entire event, $10 dance party&lt;br /&gt;All proceeds from the event will go to Spontaneous Celebrations youth programs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T and driving directions: &lt;a href="http://www.spontaneouscelebrations.org/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spontaneou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173143274000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171413776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dancing for Justice - TROPICAL FIESTA</name><id>5479187</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1172970000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/5479187/</event_url></item>