<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mount Major is a mountain located in Alton, New Hampshire, south of Lake Winnipesaukeeand northeast of Straightback Mountain of the Belknap Range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scenic, rocky summit is a popular hiking destination, accessible by multiple trails including the Mount Major Trail, the Brook Trail, and the Boulder Loop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The north, east and south faces of Mount Major drain into Lake Winnipesaukee, thence via the Winnipesaukee River into the Merrimack River and finally into the Gulf of Maine inMassachusetts. The west ridge of Mount Major rises only 186 feet (57 m) feet above the colwith the higher Straightback Mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a loop hike up to Mount Major where there are fantastic views of Lake Winnipesaukee. The hike ascends via Boulder Loop Trail and descends on Major-Straightback Link, Brook Trail, and Mount Major Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cross posted with the New England Hiking Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[img]&lt;a href="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/0/0a/Mtmajorsummitbig-2007-1022a.jpg/280px-Mtmajorsummitbig-2007-1022a.jpg[/img" class="linkified"&gt;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/0/0a/Mtmajorsummitbig-2007-1022a.jpg/280px-Mtmajorsummitbig-2007-1022a.jpg[/img&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike and hit up a eatery after the hike. most likely Patricks Pub and Eatery &lt;a href="http://www.patrickspub.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.patrickspub.com/&lt;/a&gt; about 3 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18 Weirs Rd &lt;br /&gt;

Gilford, NH 03249-6303&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patrick's (603) 293-0841&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;info&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt. Major via Boulder Loop and Brook Trails&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain: Mt. Major (1786') Trails: Boulder Loop Trail, Major-Straightback Link, Brook Trail, Mount Major Trail Region: NH - Central East &lt;br /&gt;

Lakes Region, Belknap Range Location: Alton, NH Rating: Moderate Features: Summit, views, brook, ledges, loop hike Distance: 4.0 miles Elevation Gain: 1150 feet (cumulative) Hiking Time: Actual: 2:30 Typical: 2:40&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

carpooling is advised! suggest location in your RSVP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map: &lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/images/MajorGeneral-Map.gif" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikenewengland.com/images/MajorGeneral-Map.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351535704000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349221420000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Major  Hike and Brew</name><id>85200682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351432800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/85200682/</event_url></item>