<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 20 - 146 and Pike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01604</zip><lat>42.250000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Park and Ride</name><city>Worcester</city><id>256761</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.769997</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You Asked for it! You got it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A click and Shoot in Boston- Anyone want to join in the fun?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Boston's Big Dig project plunged previously elevated roadways underground, the city found itself rich in prime urban land. Community and political leaders seized the opportunity to enhance Boston's city life by providing additional parks and gardens to connect some of its oldest, most diverse and vibrant neighborhoods. One of the most important public projects in Boston?s history, the Greenway challenged designers to balance natural beauty and landscaped grace with the vitality and dynamism of a 21st Century city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who would be interested in taking a nice photo walk along some of the parks this spring/ summer and maybe grab a bite to eat afterwards?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a lot of interesting things to shoot. Check out the website for the Rose Kennedy Greenway. &lt;a href="http://www.rosekennedygreenway.org/about-the-greenway/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rosekenned...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My Suggestion is we car pool to Boston: Meet at the Park and Ride at 146 and Rt 20 at 9AM Sat Morning. Then take the Pike into the City and park either at the&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North End Garage - 588 Commercial Street, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;br /&gt;or the South Station Bus Terminal Parking, it has its own exit off the highway Entrance on Kneeland Street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt; I heard a rumor it's only 10.00 to park there on Sat....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leave the garage by 10AM. Folks should bring 5.00-10.00 cash to help pay for parking and gas if we share rides. We can then walk around the Park together, meet up for Lunch in the North End and wander about some more....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Does anyone have experience with this area of Boston and want to make some suggestions for food etc?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update: We decided that Quincy Market would be the best place to get food! Then we can chill there and eat together...say 11:30-12.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otherwise we will just go with the flow of the day! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click and shoots happen rain or shine!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274724577000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266775239000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Click and Shoot at the Rose Fitzgerald Kennedy Greenway</name><id>12663882</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274533200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12663882/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/a/global_13234042.jpeg</photo_url></item>