<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our January pick is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Poisonwood Bible&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; by Barbara Kingsolver.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the synopsis of &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Poisonwood Bible&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Poisonwood Bible is a story told by the wife and four daughters of Nathan Price, a fierce evangelical Baptist who takes his family and mission to the Belgian Congo in 1959. They carry with them all they believe they will need from home, but soon find that all of it - from garden seeds to Scripture - is calamitously transformed on African soil.  This tale of one family's tragic undoing and remarkable reconstruction, over the course of three decades in postcolonial Africa, is set against history's most dramatic political parables.  The Poisonwood Bible dances between the darkly comic human failings and inspiring poetic justices of our times. In a compelling exploration of religion, conscience, imperialist arrogance, and the many paths to redemption, Barbara Kingsolver has brought forth her most ambitious work ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in January and I hope you enjoy the book!  I just want to send a big THANK YOU to all who showed up this evening even with the holidays looming.  I can not believe how many people showed, I was astonished! (being the time that it is)  And so happy...  So I wanted to thank my fellow book lovers for attending, I had a fabulous time as usual.  You guys are the greatest!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234309777000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228871372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club January Meetup - Poisonwood Bible</name><id>9311253</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231891200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/9311253/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/3/8/global_6575176.jpeg</photo_url></item>