<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 19 , 2009 - Monthly Meeting &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wendy Patton&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Soft Markets are Great Markets! &amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“Investing in real estate has changed in many markets in our country.  If you are like me, you live in a real estate market that has gone soft.  There are still some areas in the country where homes are appreciating nicely, but nothing like it was just a year or two ago.  There were a lot of self-proclaimed real estate gurus that popped up during the boom times telling you how to make HUGE PROFITS in real estate.  Back then, during the up cycle, investing in real estate was so easy.  You could throw money at almost any piece of real estate and be practically guaranteed to make a profit.  It seemed like anyone who had flipped a couple of houses and made a profit was an “expert” investor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Times are different now.  Investing in real estate takes a little more effort.  Investors that haven’t weathered down cycles before are struggling because all they know are massively appreciating markets.  All too many of those self-proclaimed gurus lost their shirts when the markets changed.  Those ads that go “I made $256 Million in real estate in 4 weeks with no money down” are a whole lot less believable.  Okay, $256 Million is an exaggeration, but you know what I mean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the question is, “How do we still go about investing in real estate and make profits?”  Can it be done in these soft markets?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The answer to that question is quite simple.  I can say without question, without hesitation, the answer is:  YES!  ABSOLUTELY!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Veteran investor Wendy Patton as she discusses why&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soft Markets are Great Markets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Patton is widely recognized as one of the most inspiring speakers on &amp;quot;Little or No Money Down&amp;quot; real estate investing.  Her real estate savvy, great depth of experience and viable knowledge has helped her in orchestrating the most complete and easy to follow Lease Option &amp;amp; Subject To Program in the country. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After graduating from the University of Colorado, Wendy went to work for EDS, (Electronic Data Systems).  Soon after, she had an enlightening experience in real estate (lease/option) and walked away from her corporate job to focus her efforts on real estate investing full-time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wendy is a licensed Real Estate Broker in 3 states and licensed Builder in Michigan. She is the former President and a current Board Member of D.O.L.L.A.R.S., a Detroit based organization comprised of real estate strategists.  Wendy has extensive experience in lease options, subject to’s, land development, property management, rehabs, foreclosures, new construction and pre-construction with lease options and new construction being her favorites.  With over 22 successful years in general real estate and hundreds of transactions using Lease Options, she is the country’s leading expert on lease options and working with Realtors to acquire lease option deals.  Wendy loves to teach others and assist them to achieve the same level of success that she has personally experienced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Patton is a published author and well known public speaker. She also recently appeared on HGTV’s, My House IS Worth What?   &lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;5:30 - Power Hour - Members only &lt;br /&gt;6:00 - Orientation - Members and Visitors - get more out of your visit and your membership &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;NOTE LOCATION CHANGE!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237671771000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>102</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235086746000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association March Meetup</name><id>9779199</id><headcount>129</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237498200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/9779199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>