<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Carter Dome and Mt. Hight&lt;br /&gt;by Bog Brook, Wildcat River, Carter-Moriah, Rainbow, and Wild River Trails&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 13.16 miles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: 3867 ft &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 8 hours and 35 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most hikes to these summits start from rt 16 and the 19 Mile Brook Trail. I am choosing the path less travelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike starts out following the Wildcat River to Carter Notch hut. It is a moderate climb of 1669 ft over 4.3 miles and passes a boulder field known as the Rampart. At the Hut we can fill up on water and take in the views of the lakes as we prepare for the steep ascent out of Carter Notch to Carter Dome. This section will climb 1547 ft in 1.26 mi. Carter Dome counts as a 4000 footer at 4832 feet but does not have the best views. For that we continue to Mt. Hight, 8/10ths of a mile away. Hight is shorter at 4675 ft but has a bare summit and the best views in the range. From there we return to Carter Dome where we pick up the Rainbow Trail which descends across a ridge with views and through a birch forest. We will lose 2308 ft of elevation in 2.5 miles. Then it is a gentle descent of 914 ft over 3.5 miles back to our starting point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be approximately 13 water crossings, some of which can be tricky at high water levels, but that should not be a concern this time of year. You should bring extra socks in case you should slip in. Poles can be helpful for water crossings also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost. Please update any Maybe RSVPs by 6 PM the day before the hike. After that time they will be considered as No RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216470512000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215878234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dark Side of the Dome</name><id>8326891</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216127700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8326891/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/5/global_4754725.jpeg</photo_url></item>