<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Since we had such a great response from our last overpass banner wave, let's try and get in at least one more before it gets too dark and cold.  Friday is supposed to be 61 and partly sunny, so it's our best chance to get one in for rush hour traffic.  Last time we had 9 people cover 4 overpasses on Everett and 293 and on one overpass alone, I estimated that we had about 12,000-15,000 cars pass in just over two hours.  You can't get much better FREE mass marketing than that.  To pull this off take coordination, so please email me as soon as you can at phoebaca@yahoo.com (don't reply to entire message board) with some information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) What time can you start?  (Even if you can't start until 5:30pm, that's ok - I'll pair you up with someone with a similar schedule)&lt;br /&gt;2) What highway (Everett, 293, 93) and Exit # is the easiest for you to get to at that time?&lt;br /&gt;3) Do you have a large Google Ron Paul or Ron Paul Revolution banner? &lt;br /&gt;4) Best way to contact you? (email / phone)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll gather all the info, team people up, tell you where to meet, and get you a banner if you need one.  All you have to do is answer the four questions and show up.  I'll send out the &amp;quot;assignments&amp;quot; Thursday, but I'll probably communicate with you before then.  Sunset is around 6:15, but even if you can only do 5:30 to 6:15, that's still a big help.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193603640000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193119488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Overpass Banner Wave</name><id>6600353</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193430600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/6600353/</event_url></item>