<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Exit 12 off Mass Pike,</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.320000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Framingham Park and Ride</name><city>Framingham</city><id>363021</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.430000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's time to hit the Midway at New England's largest state fair!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Big 'E' in Springfield, Mass runs from Sept 14th-30th.  Check out the offerings at their official website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.thebige.com/fair/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thebige.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've sworn I'd attend year after year but this year it's finally gonna happen!  Join me on opening day, Sept 14th.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can buy tix in advance for 10 bucks, otherwise they are $12 at the door.  Just be sure to bring plenty of cash for yummy carnival food and those slightly daunting Midway rides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(FYI, any military personnel and veterans get in free that day with military i.d.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heh, if we stick around till 8 pm, we can catch the mother of all state fair performers, Joan Jett, for free!&lt;br /&gt;She does love rock and roll, ya know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the Framingham Park and Ride off exit 12 of the Mass Pike at 8:30 am and organize carpooling.  We can leave cars there during the day and through the evening.   It's a little over an hour to the fair from Framingham.  Return times to be determined by members of said carpools.  The site for day parking is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonmpo.org/bostonmpo/info/pnr/fram1.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonmpo....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on the &amp;quot;print&amp;quot; button and you'll get driving directions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those staying for the concert or till closing at 10 pm, we'll chat Friday morning about whether to leave cars there or in a gated, lit lot that offers overnight safety.  If desired, we'll organize from the Park and Ride and hop over to the Logan Express lot near shopper's world off Exit 13, where the cars will be safe overnight/after dark.  There is an $11.00 charge per day, but no risk of towing etc.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Logan express site for Framingham with link for map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.massport.com/logan/getti_logan_frami.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.massport.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Save room for the fried dough!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, contact  Lisa (vetchick)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beantown and Beyond</member_name><member_id>4494456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192122652000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184690070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's the Big 'E'</name><id>6036372</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189773000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/6036372/</event_url></item>