<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ever since I finished reading 
&lt;em&gt;Moby Dick&lt;/em&gt; about a year ago, I have been yearning to see whales up close. So here's my chance to see these beautiful creatures. If we're lucky, we may see dolphins and other wildlife, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/em&gt; I have set this up for 8:00 a.m. because we should pick up our tickets a half hour before the boat's departure time, which is 8:30 a.m. on Saturday, August 13, 2011. 
&lt;strong&gt;I plan to arrive even earlier: by 7:45 a.m. Look for me and my bright red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;You must purchase a ticket through 7 Seas to attend this event. See "Tickets" below. Please mention in your RSVP that you have purchased your ticket.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;*****************************************&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From various pages at the 7 Seas website (&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;a href="http://www.7seas-whalewatch.com/"&gt;http://www.7seas-whalewatch.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;What to Bring&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Appropriate clothing and a camera (lots of film or lots of space left on your memory card, of course). But remember that a 7 Seas Whale Watch is a nature trip out into the North Atlantic to see animals in the wild. [[And the trip lasts about 5&amp;nbsp; hours.]] We do have a heated cabin; however, you will want to be out on deck while we are watching the whales. During late June through September, a jacket or sweatshirt is usually sufficient. Even gloves are a good idea. You can always take off clothing if you are too warm. Rubber-soled shoes or sneakers will provide good deck traction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Directions to 7 Seas Whale Watch&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take route 128 north into Gloucester to the first rotary. Take the first right off the rotary (Route 127, Washington Street, Exit 11). Follow 8/10 mile to the Joan of Arc Statue (a woman on a horse). Bear right at the statue, then take your first left onto Angle Street. Come to a stop sign, then go straight across the intersection toward the harbor. About 100 yards ahead and downhill, you'll turn left onto Rogers Street (Route 127). The Gloucester House Restaurant and 7 Seas Whale Watch are on the right, 200 yards ahead. [[7 Seas has its own free parking lot; I checked via phone!]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;NOTE: MapQuest directions may not be accurate! MapQuest does not direct you to the correct location. Please use Google Maps instead.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think that you may be late for your trip, please call us (7 Seas) at 978-283-1776.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Tickets&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $45.00 for adults ($5.00 off for AAA members). See the 7 Seas website or call 1-888-283-1776 for complete information about ticket pricing. 
&lt;strong&gt;[[Purchase your ticket for the 8:30 a.m. trip on Saturday, August 13, 2011. You must purchase a ticket&amp;nbsp; from 7 Seas to attend this event. And there is a possibility that tickets will sell out.]]&lt;/strong&gt; A valid credit card is necessary to hold your online reservation; however, your card will not be charged until you arrive to pick up your tickets. You may choose an alternate method of payment at that time. Any applicable discounts to your ticket price will be credited when you pick up your ticket on the day of your trip. There is no additional charge for booking online. Please arrive to pick up your tickets 30 minutes prior to your trip's scheduled departure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;******************************************&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;A Note&amp;nbsp;about Seasickness/Motion Sickness&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sometimes, without any warning whatsoever, on buses, planes, and boats and in cars, can succumb to the landlubber's worst fears. So I have researched the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. If you know you will need something to tide you over (pun alert!), consult your primary-care physician about the best options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Bring your own thermos of water. You should keep hydrated in the sun anyway, but if you are taking any over-the-counter (OTC) remedies for seasickness, they may add to your need for hydration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Bring carbohydrates to nibble on (for me, this means a couple of plain bagels). When I called the information line at 7 Seas, the operator suggested crackers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need to plan ahead for seasickness/motion sickness. Even OTC remedies require that you start using them before you get on the boat for maximum effectiveness. And the folks at 7 Seas aren't responsible for your queasy stomach once you are on board their boat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my bright red backpack at the ticket booth by 8:00 a.m. See the event description for complete details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313282455000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312676508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whale Watching in Gloucester!</name><id>28525771</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313236800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/28525771/</event_url></item>