<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>167 Thayer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.826103</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MacMillan Hall 117 (Starr Auditorium), Brown University</name><city>Providence</city><id>1549075</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400093</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Like last month, this is a little different then our usual Monday Night Meetup, but hey, something different is good. The lecture sounds good, as does the tasting afterward and if we don't have enough, we'll head over to Kartabar afterward:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uncorking the Past:  The Quest for Wine, Beer, and Extreme Fermented Beverages &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public, but you must be 21+ to attend the tasting &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The University of Pennsylvania's Biomolecular Archaeology Laboratory for Cuisine, Fermented Beverages and Health is documenting the antiquity of alcoholic beverages. Its director, Patrick McGovern, will discuss new approaches to discovering the history and tastes of ancient beers and&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; wine. One of the lab's recent findings-a cacao-based beverage brewed more than 3000 years ago in Honduras-also documents the earliest known use of chocolate. Like grape and rice wine, chocolate "wine" eventually became a prerogative of royalty and religious consumption. Was this ancient beverage the incentive for domesticating the cacao tree? Following the talk, the Graduate Center Bar will offer tastes of ancient beers, created by Dogfish Head brewery in conjunction with Professor McGovern's work, providing a unique way to travel through time. Copies of his book, Uncorking the Past will be available for purchase. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is the third in a series of four programs in this year's Barbara Greenwald Memorial Arts program, entitled Tastes of the Americas. Each program features a presentation about the featured food followed by a tasting at the reception. Each event is sponsored by the Brown University Department of Anthropology, the Center for Environmental Studies at Brown, donors to the Barbara Greenwald Memorial Arts Fund, and the Friends of the Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf and sneaking in the back of the auditorium as usual........</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300399256000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We can learn something AND do a tasting - what's not to like!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299371250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Uncorking the Past Lecture and Beer Tasting</name><id>16812525</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300138200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16812525/</event_url></item>