<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>695 Hillside Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.213108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-698-1802</phone><name>Blue Hills Reservation</name><city>Milton</city><id>908716</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We already had a great hike in the Blue Hills a couple of weeks ago and we only covered a very small part of it so I thought we could explore a different area. Most people do the skyline trail through the eastern part of the reservation to Great Blue Hill (which we did last time) so we'll try the central part this time. We will meet at the headquarters parking lot again (right across the street from park headquarters). This time we'll take the skyline (blue blaze) trail east over Tucker, North Boyce, Buck, and Chickatawbut hills. Then we'll veer off onto the red dot trail and loop back around, briefly retrace our steps on the skyline trail and finish on the white triangle trail. Total hike between 5 and 6 miles with definite elevation gains. Its starting to get chilly out so bring warm clothes (including pants...yes you know who I'm talking to), plenty of water and snacks....and your sense of direction because as those of you who have been on previous hikes with me know, I always need help finding the path! See you out there and feel free to message me with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;          &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the bright yellow escape or call my cell 508 414 8544.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259684221000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259029666000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Part 2</name><id>11943944</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259510400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11943944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/3/global_11965331.jpeg</photo_url></item>