<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>An after work and Autumnal Equinox hike starting at 5:30 PM on Tuesday, Sept. 22.  We will be enjoying Tolland breezes and the sounds of tinkling streams and cricket violins. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a guest hike leader for this event, June M (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/members/9270463/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; ). She is an excellent photographer and hiker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A moderate 2-3 mile hike at Stoppleworth Conservation Area and Campbell's Peaceful Valley Conservation Area in Tolland, CT.  This approximate 1.5 hour long hike is not for the faint hearted.  There is a number of scrambles up rocky trails, a crossing over of a log bridge hanging off the side of a cliff, and a view of Shenipsit Lake and a beautiful sunset from the steep ascent up the overlook trail.  We will also be heading out to the meadow trail, through ancient fences, to see late butterflies and perhaps a fisher or two.  This is a local town trail that you won't find on any map.  It is a very pretty area that isn't easy, but beginners are certainly capable of taking on the short but steep elevation gains.  We will also be viewing 400,000 year old geology in action with a decent critter cave on the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at Stoppleworth parking off of Hunter Rd. in Tolland.  Parking is limited but the road is pretty visible if you have to park out on the edge of it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids and leashed dogs are welcome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; to meet at Stoppleworth parking area (entrance on west side of road, 359 Hunter Rd., Tolland, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Tolland&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=359+Hunter+Rd"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brief textual directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* Exit 67 off I-84 and follow Route 31 briefly toward Rockville.&lt;br /&gt;* Take a right on Route 30.&lt;br /&gt;* Route 30 takes a sharp left, keep following (known as Crystal Lake Rd. here).&lt;br /&gt;* Take 3rd right onto Hunter Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* The parcel is directly across from 376 Hunter Road (on left, west).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map for Stoppleworth Conservation Area&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.conservingtollandct.org/stoppleworth_flyer10-08.pdf"&gt;http://www.conserving...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map for Campbell's Peaceful Valley Conservation Area&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.conservingtollandct.org/campbell_flyer10-08.pdf"&gt;http://www.conserving...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on Conserving Tolland&lt;/b&gt; (land trust) &amp;amp; related properties:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.conservingtollandct.org/"&gt;http://www.conserving...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information on the Autumnal Equinox&lt;/b&gt; (i.e. Fall Equinox):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Equinox"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254573177000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252868841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Stoppleworth &amp; Campbell's Peaceful Valley Conservation Areas, Tolland CT</name><id>11361510</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253655000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11361510/</event_url></item>