<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>361 Middlesex Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01879</zip><lat>42.689282</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978 649 8312</phone><name>Angela's Coal Fired Pizza</name><city>Tyngsborough</city><id>843181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.432641</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There's a new pizza place where Matthews Strip Club used to be called Angela's Coal Fired Pizza, that I want to try.  I understand the wings are also supposed to be good.  So we are going to Angela's to try out the pizza.  Afterward we are going to Maximiilians, to work off the pizza with a couple of games of pool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Angela's does not take reservations, so please be there on time.  I will be there early to try to get a table or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Angela's Coal Fired Pizza:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ve found our old friend Coal. We’ve cleaned him up a bit, put him in a new shirt and sent him out to show just how good he can be.At Angela’s, we have taken this old, difficult, often messy method of cooking and are delivering it to you in a comfortable friendly atmosphere.The intense 900 degree heat generated in each of our two coal ovens, create flavor profiles to our pizza and wings that simply cannot be replicated by any other conventional cooking method. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reviews:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Angela's Coal Fired Pizza, your straw barely hits the soda before you get your pie. That's how fast pizzas ($13.50-$18.50, above, right) come out of the coal ovens here. They're heated to 900 degrees and were custom built in the Abruzzi region of Italy, designed less for speed than for the clean, crisp quality they impart to everything that goes in them. Soft, fluffy dough is lightly blackened on the outside, which owner Eric Sideri says he worked long and hard to perfect. Angela's other house specialty is buffalo wings ($8.50-$14.95, above, left), also cooked in the ovens. Sideri loves chicken but hates greasy wings, so he dresses them up as his Italian family does, with olive oil, lemon, garlic, and rosemary, and serves them with caramelized onions. They have a thin, crisp, golden skin. Bring your appetite. Angela's Coal Fired Pizza, 880 Broadway, Route 1 North, Saugus; 781-941- 2625. - DARRY MADDEN&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/lifestyle/food/articles/2007/11/28/fire_it_up/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I was home for Christmas vacation, my parents wanted to try this new pizza place right near the New Hampshire-Massachusetts border since they heard good things about it. We went to Angela's for lunch while there was still a considerable amount of snow on the ground. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was easy to get to from the highway and had plenty of parking.  Angela's is just a few minutes away from the Pheasant Lane Mall in Nashua, NH. I was expecting your average pizza and sub joint but experienced something ten times better. It has a nice modern interior with big plain windows that gives the restaurant an open feel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was blown away by the chicken wings and the pizza. These weren't your usual buffalo-style chicken wings but instead were cooked in an unique sauce that contained what I thought was lemon, thyme and some other ingredients I couldn't identify. Very tasty. The pizza itself was excellent. It was thin-crust with fresh mozarella and pepperoni and not alot of sauce. Nothing tasted processed or frozen, which I appreciated. A great place to go for lunch or on a date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/angelas-coal-fired-pizza-tyngsboro" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.angelascfp.com/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.angelascfp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Maximillians:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9000 sq. ft. billiard parlor/lounge with full service bar and dining. Maxamillians is the perfect location for your next event. Enjoy a game of pocket billiards on our Connelly Ultimate billiard tables. Watch the game in front of our wide screen televisions. Sip brandy beside the fireplace. Win money playing Keno. We have something for everyone. We can accomodate parties from 10 to 175 people. We offer something special you will not find in a standard function facility. The atmosphere is warm and inviting. The service is exceptional. This is simply the place to be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours of operation; 4pm to 1am. Will open early for events with 75+ attendees. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;315 Middlesex Rd&lt;br /&gt;Tyngsboro, MA 01879&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234045252000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231098376000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night 3-P : People, Pizza and Pool</name><id>9441816</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232757000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9441816/</event_url></item>