<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fortin Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06234</zip><lat>41.791862</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>My House</name><city>Killingly</city><id>13101372</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.898209</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to add a description of the hike. The red trail is the shorter trail at the Wolf Den, and it is a lot of fun to do, but it is semi challengeing. You can expect a one half mile area in particular that can be a little hilly and rocky, with one hill that will be a bit steep. However, we will move along at a pace that will allow everyone to keep up. We can start by going to my house first so people can leave things at the house, and then from there we can head off to the Den.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the pot luck/cookout/byob if people choose to bring something, it would be a big help if they can post it here, so we will have a general idea of what we will have. Of course, the most important thing to bring, is to make sure that you bring yourself. I will provide the burgers, and others can bring something either as a potluck, or something for the grille, or adult beverage, or just a soft drink. It will be a big help if people can bring one &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;folding chair&lt;/a&gt; for themselves, but I can help out the people who are not able to do that. Keep in mind that we also have ten people from &lt;a style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;active singles&lt;/a&gt; that are going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of days  before the meet up I will send out all the contact info that will be needed in order to get to my house, which is very easy to get to with a gps or mapquest.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>11253417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367720116000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364952779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Wolf Den followed by a pot luck/cookout/byob at Tims.</name><id>112378022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367677800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/112378022/</event_url></item>