<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are in unprecedented turmoil in the financial markets.  Solutions that are untested are being put forward.  The proposals being made are changing daily.  By the time October 6 and our meetup rolls around, we may have something in place.  Or it may be that we will still be having ideas just bandied about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is the prognosis for us as investors from the bailouts being proposed?  Will a bailout stop the freefall in credit tightening?  Will it stop foreclosures?  Will the real estate market begin to bottom out?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What kind of investments make sense in this market?  What are the best money-making strategies right now?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an open discussion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan before all this hoopla was to have a presentation on bankruptcy law, and we can still talk about how bankruptcy works today, and how it can even be a tool for us in our investing.  A part of the bailout plans being proposed is to change the bankruptcy law to add loan modifications to the mix.  It seems logical to me to come at bankruptcy from this possible new perspective, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be present and let's learn from one another!  See you on the 6th at 7!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come through the lobby, down the hall and down to the lower level theater</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225756948000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New Normal RE Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>GreaterBostonREIClub</urlname><id>320990</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Real Estate Investing Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218111220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bailouts and R E Investment</name><id>8495899</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223334000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/GreaterBostonREIClub/events/8495899/</event_url></item>