<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Jewett Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04548</zip><lat>43.864052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Knubble Bay Cottage</name><city>Georgetown</city><id>1545863</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.734047</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>76.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/e/event_22021662.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Bring your kayaks for 2 gorgeous nights in a cottage on the waters of Knubble Bay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knubble Bay Cottage&lt;/strong&gt; is&amp;nbsp;located right on the water at Georgetown Island, Maine, where there&amp;nbsp;are endless miles of kayaking right from our door.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is a beautiful post-and-beam building that operates almost completely&amp;nbsp;off the grid. There is an indoor&amp;nbsp;composting toilet (&amp;amp; 2 outdoor ones), hand-pumped water, and wind- &amp;amp; solar-powered lighting but no other electricity.&amp;nbsp; It does have a propane refrigerator and range, and&amp;nbsp;a wood stove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cottage has its own private dock.&amp;nbsp; We can kayak in the bays and coves with seals and ospreys to keep us company. Explore local shops and beaches, and eat lobster fresh from the boat at one of Georgetown Island&amp;rsquo;s picturesque fishing hamlets. Paddling destinations include Robinhood Cove (with a genuine shipwreck), Goose Rock Passage, Five Islands and Reid State Park.&amp;nbsp; Several nearby islands are on the Maine Island Trail and are maintained by the &lt;a href="http://www.mita.org/"&gt;Maine Island Trail Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: $76 per person&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;includes 2 nights, Friday &amp;amp; Saturday, Sept.9-10&amp;nbsp;with a mix of shared sleeping arrangements;&amp;nbsp;beds, bunks, futons, etc.&amp;nbsp;- please be flexible.&amp;nbsp; Payment is due via credit card&amp;nbsp;when you RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;What to Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; flashlights, sheets/pillows/blankets or a sleeping bag, ear plugs, towels,&amp;nbsp;soap/dish soap, paper towels, toilet paper, matches, extra D-cell batteries for the lamps, all food including spices, condiments, etc., extra drinking water (in case of issues with the pump), &lt;strong&gt;a sun shower (you can buy one at any camping dept. AKA solar shower, camp shower&lt;/strong&gt;),&amp;nbsp;your cell phone car charger. Oh, and your KAYAKS -&amp;nbsp;and a bicycle if you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What NOT to Bring:&lt;/strong&gt; Pets, flammable lanterns, candles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Provided:&lt;/strong&gt; all kitchen utensils, firewood, mattresses,&amp;nbsp;books, games, a great view, ospreys, seals, and miles of paddling!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are indoor toilets but no shower. Bring a sun shower (you can buy one cheaply at any camping&amp;nbsp;store or dept.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swimming&lt;/strong&gt;: Reid State Park is a 15-min drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seaspraykayaking.com/index.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3987cb"&gt;Seaspray Kayaking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;- rents sea kayaks for $35/day and will deliver to&amp;nbsp;the cottage for FREE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;I-95 North to exit 44 for I-295 North/Portland. I-295 to exit 28 for Route 1/coastal route. Follow US Rt.1 through Bath across the Kennebec River Bridge. Just beyond the bridge, turn right onto Rt. 127 (towards Reid State Park). Proceed 5.8 miles to Robinhood Road. Take a left onto Robinhood Road, proceed 1 mile, turn left onto Webber Road. If you have passed Robinhood Meeting House Restaurant, you have gone too far. Follow Webber Road 1.2 miles and turn right onto Jewett Road. Follow Jewett Road, turning right at each fork, approximately 0.6 miles turn left at the KBC sign.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The cottage is&amp;nbsp;less than&amp;nbsp;2 hrs from Portsmouth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/strong&gt; hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs,&amp;nbsp;and all members&amp;nbsp;and participants&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group&amp;nbsp;from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage&amp;nbsp;including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience&amp;nbsp;and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;As organizer I make no claims regarding any expertise for this outing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; -Larry Pilla&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1315784581000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299180599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knubble Bay Cottage Kayak Weekend</name><id>16785258</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315594800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/16785258/</event_url></item>