<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>your share of gas</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>more or less</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>OK, here's the plan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's summertime, and Rumney beckons!  This will be my first trip of the season, and I cannot wait to get up there again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who aren't familiar with Rumney:  It's a lot like the gym, in that there are a large number of high-quality climbs in very close proximity to each other.  I plan on hitting 5.8s to 5.11s myself, and there will be some 5.6s and 5.7s available too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's going to be sunny and warm, but the warmest weather isn't starting until 11 or noon, so I suggest we meet up near Davis square at 9am sharp and head out from there.    The drive is under two hours, and I'd like to stay up there until it gets too cold or dark to climb, or until we're just spent, whichever comes first.  We'll probably get back to Boston between 6 and 8pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transportation: We need a car!  If you have a car, please let me know when you RSVP!  Otherwise, we can rent a car for the day (I'll probably just grab a zipcar)  Either way, we'll split the cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What I'm offering:  I have two ropes, and enough other gear for four people who are climbing near each other.  If you don't know how to sport lead yet, I can teach you!  There's a nice little 5.2 right near the parking lot that's great for learning the mechanics of sport leading.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you should bring:  Your personal climbing gear: harness, shoes, belay device, food and water for a day trip, appropriate clothing, including long pants and warm top (we may be in the shade for a while) and sunscreen (we may not!).  The approach trails are short, but can be steep, so feel free to wear hiking boots if you think you'll need them.  I'll be wearing trail runners.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we split a zipcar four ways, we'll each be in for about $25.  If we split gas on your car, it might be cheaper.  Either way, please bring cash!  We might also stop for dinner on the way home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?  Drop me a line!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm limiting this to four people right now, because I'm assuming we'll have that much space in the car.  If we get a larger car...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: I've reserved a zipcar.  It's on!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one with the ropes</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208783365000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Rumney is hands down the best sport climbing area east of the Mississippi.  Most of the cliffs are schist: hard rock, with crisp edges.  There are dozens of crags, and hundreds of routes.  Come find out just how awesome it is!</why><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208529449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rumney!</name><id>7763749</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208610000000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/7763749/</event_url></item>