<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A member had e mailed me recently and asked if we can have an evening of &amp;quot;showing off&amp;quot; our talents whether it is music, dance, singing, comedy acting, etc.... &lt;br /&gt;Another meet up group I belong to is  having a Talent Show night. I talked with the organizer and he said our Cambridge Singles group is more than welcome to join them. &lt;br /&gt;I am sure there are many talented people in this Cambridge Singles group too including artists, actors and singers. This will be an opportunitey to share and listen to our talents. I understand a member in the other group is already preparing a comedy act for us!!!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;Please bring what ever material you may need (ie: music stand, book box for a tape if doing a dance), etc....  &lt;br /&gt;Please note a voluntary donation of 5.00 is suggested to help cover the rent cost of the room. There is a stage available for the evening and also please feel free to bring some light snacks/drinks for us to share.&lt;br /&gt;I personally am looking foward to this event as I know there will be some fun laughs and great entertainment!!!!&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see all of you there and please look for myself, Krista with the balloons as a landmark as this is a joint event with another group. Then we can find a table or two for us to sit together. &lt;br /&gt;Perhaps this may be a good location for our possible casino night in the works???&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a red meet up t shirt on as well as balloons, which seem to work</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246807703000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243802495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Talent Night </name><id>10537562</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244847600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/10537562/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>