<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Bring your problems, puzzles, questions, epiphanies, solutions, triumphs and tribulations. It's Hack Night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This months (STILL very loose) agenda is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Welcome to new people.&lt;br /&gt;2) Open Code Reviews - a fast way to understand Ruby idioms. Bring a class or method and the group can tear it apart and build it up again (if needed...maybe *you'll* be teaching us a thing or two.)&lt;br /&gt;3) Open problem solving, help with dev environments for new users, open discussion.&lt;br /&gt;4) Lightning talks (If anyone has one they want to present.)&lt;br /&gt;5) Hack Night Demo's...(I saw something called instaCalc...while not totally Ruby...very cool!)&lt;br /&gt;6) Dinner? This is up in the air. Post to the list what your desire is. We'll can break around 8:30 - 9:00 and go out for food on Rt-9 or we can plan on having food at the location. What do you think?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The point of this night is to solve your problems, share nifty hacks, and get feedback on your code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are completely new and want help setting up a Ruby development environment, bring your machine and you'll probably leave with a working development environment. I said probably. :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You can't miss me. I'm bald, bearded and loud.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204330100000</updated><rating><average>4.63000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Ruby noobies can bring any problem/question and get ideas for solutions, or just downright solve it. Ruby experts have lots of opportunities to share their expertise, gain a fan-base, and move forward with their plans of world domination! Huzzah!</why><group><who>Rubyists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>route9rubygroup</urlname><id>389347</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Route 9 Ruby Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201145243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup For February. Hack Night!</name><id>7183453</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204156800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/route9rubygroup/events/7183453/</event_url></item>