<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Francis St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.830235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 919-5050</phone><name>Temple Downtown</name><city>Providence </city><id>823545</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416389</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Temple Downtown restaurant &amp;amp; Lounge on Francis Street (underneath the Renaissance Providence Hotel across from the State House).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've been here for dinner during Restaurant Week a few years ago (which was great) and a couple times for drinks and trivia. Last year they changed the decor and went to an "Inspired Mediterranean" theme. They also offer various events during the week, most notably for the thrifty-at-heart, a BYOB on Tuesday nights. The bar area is huge so there's LOT's o' room, and there's a lounge area to hang out in the back. I remember when this was an abandoned, boarded up building - even then it looked like a great space, and look at it now! Its history is pretty interesting too, so let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wear some kind of scarf, but you can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321460310000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320230128000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Temple!</name><id>39621432</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321311600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/39621432/</event_url></item>