<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 21 Congress Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076801</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name> The Thirsty Moose </name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>9882902</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.758583</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/1/e/event_170535902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hi Trailblazers join us for a pre Halloween Party on Wednesday, October 24th, 5:30pm at The Thirsty Moose (downstairs), 21 Congress Street, Portsmouth&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s right, we have a new location!The Thirsty Moose. For those who are not familiar- it was formerly known as Foobar and also Muddy River Smokehouse.  The fun starts from 5:30 to 8pm. 50 beers are on tap (cash bar), plus tasty appetizers provided by Thirsty Moose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a fundraiser! This month we are supporting the &lt;a href="http://www.spookyportsmouth.com/"&gt;Portsmouth Halloween Parade&lt;/a&gt;, and we couldn’t be more excited. All proceeds at the door will be going to support the parade and their amazingly creative works. $5 gets you in, $10 or more gets you in plus a t-shirt (while supplies last). What a deal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because this party is just a week before Halloween we thought you may want to &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;try out your new costumes&lt;/span&gt;. So we are also going to have a costume contest. You don’t have to come in costume, but if at least 10 of you do, a minion from the Halloween Parade will judge you appropriately and the &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;winner will get $100 cash&lt;/span&gt;. Yup, cash. The kind you can spend on things and stuff. We will also have a few very cool, very creepy indie video games to play on a big screen (Limbo, Slender).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After our event The Thirsty Moose has a fun night planned with 4 local bands starting around 9pm. The bands are: The Orange Umbrellas, Sneeze, The Erotic City Electric Blues, and Black Norse. You’re welcome to stick around and enjoy the tunes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351274423000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350610783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Party</name><id>87626042</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351116000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/87626042/</event_url></item>