<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You've probably seen the famous scene from 
&lt;em&gt;Steamboat Bill, Jr.&lt;/em&gt; many times: it's the one in which Buster Keaton stands in front of one wall of a house that is left standing after a storm. The audience watches in horror as the wall falls down over Keaton, but he remains unscathed thanks to a window without any glass left in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keaton filmed this famous scene in one take. He relied on his own skills and the expertise of his film crew to place him in the exact spot where the windowless window would be. And it worked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Somerville Theater ( 
&lt;a href="http://somervilletheatreonline.com/"&gt;http://somervilletheatreonline.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;) is presenting this Buster Keaton silent classic with original live music (by Jeff Rapsis), the way audiences&amp;nbsp;would have seen it in 1928. Jeff Rapsis is&amp;nbsp;a New Hampshire-based musician who specializes in creating live musical scores for silent film screenings. We'll also see two Buster Keaton shorts: 
&lt;em&gt;The High Sign&lt;/em&gt; (1921) and 
&lt;em&gt;Cops&lt;/em&gt; (1922).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that the admission for this combined movie/live music performance is $12.00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have already purchased&amp;nbsp;my ticket. I'll&amp;nbsp;wait in the theater lobby for 15 to 20 minutes, from about 6:20 to 6:40. Look for me and my bright red backpack. I'll head into the theater auditorium about 6:40. 
&lt;strong&gt;The presentation starts at 7:00 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt; If you are late, look for me and the bright red backpack in the auditorium. After the presentation, I'll wait for everyone in the theater lobby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;****From the Somerville Theater's website:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Steamboat Bill, Jr.&lt;/em&gt; (1928). Buster's last independent silent feature finds him as the bumbling son of a rundown riverboat's rough captain. When a rival brings a newer boat to town, the family is forced to face competition, just as Buster is forced to face down a cyclone that blows through town. One of Buster's best. Shown with Keaton shorts: 
  &lt;em&gt;The High Sign&lt;/em&gt; (1921) and 
  &lt;em&gt;Cops&lt;/em&gt; (1922). Live music by Jeff Rapsis.*****&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you Sunday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my bright red backpack. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312866350000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311126631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buster Keaton's "Steamboat Bill, Jr." (with live musical accompaniment)</name><id>26357701</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312756200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/26357701/</event_url></item>