<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.363068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>5488072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083893</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Java and Content Management: Introduction to the Open Source Hippo CMS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're already a quarter into the year. Have you learned something new this year? We'd like to introduce you the challenges that Content Management Systems face today. How do you manage multiple websites across the globe? We’ll show you how Hippo addresses these problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hippo CMS is a solution based on Java and open standards. It allows you to broadcast your content in many different channels (websites, REST, mobile) and is used by enterprises in high traffic, high volume websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll give you a quick overview on how end users work with the system to manage content in multiple websites and channels, all without any coding involved. Then we'll expose the technologies and architecture that are driving the main functionalities. After that we'll start coding. You'll build your own project and learn how to use our APIs. We usually see amazing stuff happening during meetups, so we expect to see even more from this group of Java all-stars!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started quickly, please make sure you have installed the following on your laptop: Java 6, Maven 3 and your favorite IDE. We'll hand out a couple of free manuals for those that got Hippotized. Can't wait? Follow the trail on the community website: &lt;a href="http://www.onehippo.org/"&gt;http://www.onehippo.org/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #3b74a4 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mickaël Tricot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mickaël is a passionate Software Engineer at Hippo and is an advocate and speaker on Java EE and Web technologies, with an affinity for open source software. He had the opportunity to work in different countries (Netherlands, USA, France, New Caledonia) and environments. More about him at &lt;a href="http://gimmick.fr/"&gt;http://gimmick.fr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://gimmick.fr/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #3b74a4 ; font-size : medium"&gt;About Mathijs Brand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mathijs has been helping Burc out with organizing the Boston Java Meetups this year. He is the delivery manager for Hippo USA. His educational background is a mixture of usability studies, organizational management, Java/PHP web programming and mathematics, all starting at the University of Amsterdam. Mathijs has been actively involved the past few years in the development of versions of Hippo CMS, combined with consulting and implementation experience as a project leader in many large scale projects. More about him on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/mathijsbrand" class="linkified"&gt;http://twitter.com/#!/mathijsbrand&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://mathijsbrand.blogspot.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://mathijsbrand.blogspot.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Burc Oral</member_name><member_id>4238999</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mathijs Brand</member_name><member_id>12111377</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337876163000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>85</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334934748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Java and Content Management</name><id>61401352</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337812200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/61401352/</event_url></item>