<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NEW ENGLAND UNITED&lt;br /&gt;General Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY, APRIL 17, 1-5 PM&lt;br /&gt;Round Top Center at Beneficent Church&lt;br /&gt;300 Weybosset Street, Downtown Providence RI&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;a href="http://beneficentchurch.org/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://beneficentchur...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OPENING DISCUSSION ON&lt;br /&gt;Pirates of the Caribbean: A Brief History of US Intervention in the Region&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free &amp;amp; Open to the Public | Light Refreshments Will Be Served&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NEU Regional Committee has prepared the following proposed agenda for the NEU meeting in Providence on April 17:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Program 1:00-2:30:  Pirates of the Caribbean: A Brief History of US Intervention in the Region, presented by Shaun Joseph&lt;br /&gt;* Refreshments 2:30-2:50&lt;br /&gt;* NEU Structure proposal (below) 2:50-3:20&lt;br /&gt;* March 20 evaluation 3:20-3:50&lt;br /&gt;* UNAC conference 3:50-4:15 (Marilyn Levin reporting)&lt;br /&gt;* Treasurers report 4:15-4:20 (Ann Glick reporting)&lt;br /&gt;* Next meeting 4:20-4:25&lt;br /&gt;* Announcements 4:25-4:30&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following NEU structure proposal has been approved by the Regional Committee and will be presented to the NEU meeting on April 17 for a discussion and vote:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEU structure proposal from the Regional Committee:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 1:  The New England United Antiwar Network (NEU) is a network of progressive groups in New England committed to ending unjust wars and foreign occupations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 2:  Affiliation with NEU is open to all progressive groups in New England that support the following principles of unity:&lt;br /&gt;* Immediate withdrawal of all occupying forces from the Middle East and Central Asia.&lt;br /&gt;* An end to US support for the Israeli occupation of Palestine.&lt;br /&gt;* Opposition to US intervention in the affairs of other countries.&lt;br /&gt;* Support Our Communities, Fund Human Needs.&lt;br /&gt;* Stop the Attacks on Civil Liberties, Defend Human Rights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 3:  NEU supports the National Assembly and will request affiliation with that body. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 4:  NEU supports multiple strategies, including mass action as a central strategy for the antiwar movement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 5: New England progressive groups with at least six active members, some who participate in building NEU events and programs, may have one member approved by majority vote of the RC to serve on the NEU Regional Committee (RC).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 6:  The NEU Regional Committee (RC) is an administrative committee with the following responsibilities:  1) Preparing for the general meetings; 2) Overseeing the NEU website, listservs, and treasury; 3) Reviewing requests for NEU affiliation and applications for the RC; 4) Acting in emergency situations when necessary; 5) Promoting regional unity in the antiwar movement.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 7:  Minutes for all conference calls of the RC will be posted on the NEU general listserv, and all RC decisions are subject to review by the next general meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 8:  NEU treasurers, and the NEU representative on the National Assembly, will be ex officio members of the Regional Committee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 9:  To assist in maintaining regional unity, the NEU general meeting is the senior authority in NEU, and all substantive decisions at the general meetings, and on RC conference calls, will be made by a super-majority of two-thirds of those present and voting.   Votes on procedural motions will be by a simple majority of those voting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 10:  NEU will have on-site general meetings once each quarter, or more frequently as needed.  Meetings will be rotated in various areas around the region.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Section 11:  NEU will sponsor a regional antiwar conference once per year.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Harris</member_name><member_id>5188497</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suren Moodliar</member_name><member_id>5714882</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271697598000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People for Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>stopthewars</urlname><id>708558</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Antiwar</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269347869000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Regional Antiwar Meeting</name><id>12966340</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271523600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/stopthewars/events/12966340/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/global_2184137.jpeg</photo_url></item>