<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>366 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01566</zip><lat>42.112167</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sturbridge Host Hotel</name><city>Sturbridge</city><id>322018</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.088600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>2008 Natural Living Expo:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expo has a door fee of $8 (gives access to both days of the expo)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the site for the expo: &lt;a href="http://www.spiritofchange.org/expo-2008/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.spiritofch...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Out-of-Body Experience (OBE, astral projection, astral travel) is a phenomenon that offers profound benefits. Through OBEs we can visit non-physical dimensions or realms, and obtain direct personal knowledge of what happens when we die. This allows us to overcome our fear of death so that we can take more advantage of life, becoming concerned less about ourselves and more about helping others. And through experiencing OBEs and carrying the perspective they offer over into our daily life, the 'real us' gradually emerges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this seminar you will learn the difference between dreams, lucid dreams, and OBEs. You will learn about the subtle non-physical bodies that we use when we have an OBE. You will learn about the relationship between those bodies, our personal attributes, and reincarnation. And you will learn how the OBE can be used to visit non-physical realms, allowing us to interact directly with spirit guides, and to apprehend the whole interactive mechanism of physical and non-physical life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Offering a profoundly new integrated view on a phenomenon known since antiquity, this seminar takes a scientific approach based on decades of extensive academic and experiential research, encouraging you to replace belief with knowledge.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>IAC  </member_name><member_id>1977812</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222718731000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Researchers of Consciousness</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-OBE</urlname><id>1258624</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Out-of-Body Experience Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219971692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intro to Out-of-Body Experiences</name><id>8643943</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222545600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-OBE/events/8643943/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/9/global_5325001.jpeg</photo_url></item>