<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A restored version of a great film.  &amp;quot;The Third Man&amp;quot; returns to the big screen. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(UK, 1949) Produced and Directed by Carol Reed. Screenplay by Graham Greene. Cinematography by Robert Krasker Cast: Joseph Cotten, Alida Valli, Orson Welles, Trevor Howard. The second of two films written by Graham Greene on the Cinestudio flyer (see Brighton Rock!) quite deserves its #1 standing on the British Film Institute’s List of Best 100 Films. A mystery that excites both the senses &amp;amp; the brain, The Third Man also works as a parable of a naïve America sucked into the complexity and corruption of post World War Europe. Writer Joseph Cotten arrives in Vienna looking for his best friend, Harry Lime. But what he finds along the way – including his rendez-vous with a never-better Orson Welles - is much more than he ever imagined. “QUITE SIMPLY, ONE OF THE FINEST FILMS EVER MADE! The joy this film provides is so magnified when it’s projected in a movie theater that seeing it on the big screen is like watching it for the first time.” – Elvis Mitchell, The New York Times. 104 min. www.rialtopictures.com.com, &lt;a href="http://www.filmforum.org/films/3rdman.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmforum....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270250361000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269004228000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Third Man</name><id>12931673</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270077300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12931673/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>