<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Can't resist Woody Allen movies - if only to watch him change or not change throughout the years.&amp;nbsp; The other thing I like about his movies is that they're short - 90 minutes is perfect.&amp;nbsp; So at 8:00 we'll go to one of the usual suspects for a meal and a discussion, depending on the weather - it would be lovely to sit outside - but not if we need down coats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the info about the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/em&gt;, a new romantic comedy from writer/director Woody Allen &lt;em&gt;(Vicky Cristina Barcelona, You Will Meet a Tall Dark Stranger)&lt;/em&gt;,  tells the story of a family that travels to the picturesque French  capital on business. The party includes two young people (Owen Wilson,  Rachel McAdams) who are engaged to be married in the fall and have  experiences there that change their lives forever. It's about a young  man's great love for a great city, Paris, and the illusion people have  that a life different from theirs would be much better. Marion  Cotillard, Kathy Bates, Adrien Brody, Michael Sheen and Carla Bruni also  star. Official Selection (Opening Night Film) at the Cannes  International Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be inside after the snack bar and before the ticket taker from 6:10 to 6:20.  If you want me to save you a seat, let me know.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315252919000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306239167000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Midnight in Paris with Woody Allen</name><id>19515881</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306708200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/19515881/</event_url></item>