<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Mandarin-Cantonese PlayDate will alternate in exposing our children to the Mandarin and Cantonese Languages.  It is co-hosted by MJ who is a native and fluent speaker (reader and writer) in both Mandarin and Cantonese.  I help provide the informal educational components in the form of a short group activity appropriate for all ages to promote the learning and use of the languages.  We strive to make Mandarin and Cantonese accessible to all levels!  So don't be shy!  We can all learn together with our kids.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Anyone wanting to volunteer as a co-host or if you want to be the story-time reader or have a great group activity idea, please message me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week, we will have story-time in Mandarin.&lt;/strong&gt; We will start this around 10:45am.  The activity this week will be learning a Chinese New Year Song in Mandarin&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt; Very easy to do for tots and even easier for Moms of infants!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids can always free-play as desired.  If you have DVDs to share or information on links to videos in Chinese that are appropriate for babies and young toddlers to view, please bring them to share!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a breastfeeding-friendly environment!  Bring your baby's bottle/fomula or your tots lunch if you want to stay for lunch together. (And your own lunch too.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check back often before we meet!  I will update the activity once it's been decided. And I may change our location from time to time either for variety, a field-trip or just because another member would like a chance to co-host at their home!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also download and print the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston/files/"&gt;parking permit&lt;/a&gt; for parking on my street.  It is posted on my street and all the neighboring streets that there is no parking.  However, residents may temporarily grant parking to friends/family -- with a parking badge or permit that will distinguish you from just anyone!  Please place on dash, easily seen, to avoid a parking ticket.  And fit into my driveway first!  (We have the FSU/Framingham Police supporting this temporary parking permit on ONLY my street.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP, I assume you're coming with your child!  If you have 2 kids or more, please add them to your RSVP so I know how many kids will be participating.  Thanks!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;***Last minute RSVPers... Please request to be added in the comments if the RSVP closes before you got your RSVP in. There is no&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;guarantee that I will have enough materials for each child when you RSVP late.  But we will do our best.  Please RSVP early to ensure I do have enough materials for all kids!  Thank you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>SMS/Call: 508-202-0097 or Comment Here on your status.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elsie Smits</member_name><member_id>17363801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mei Jie Li Chiu</member_name><member_id>62766022</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366392713000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Parents &amp; Kiddies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>1371768</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Asian-American Families of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361475752000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mandarin-Cantonese PlayDate</name><id>dgmmlfyrgbzb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366381800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston/events/114159562/</event_url></item>