<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>47 Palmer St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373848</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-492-7679</phone><name>Club Passim</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>842822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119921</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/events/passim-story-slam-2" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; Our special guest, Tony Kahn, began collecting stories as the host of WGBH's Morning Stories in 2004. His latest project, Sunday Stories, can be found on youtube. Admisson $10 or $5 for students and Passim members. Passim, a nonprofit arts organization, creates an interactive and inspiring music experience for all, building a vibrant community for artists, students and audience members through its legendary listening venue and school of music. &amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#150; Directions: Via the T Take Red Line to Harvard Square T stop. &amp;#149; Exit via Church Street entrance Walk one block down Church Street past Harvard Square Theater to Palmer Street on left. We are in the basement just around the corner on the left. &amp;#149;Exit via Harvard Square main entrance Cross Massachusetts Ave. to Harvard Coop building. Stay left by newsstand on Brattle Street to first right (Palmer Street) which is 200 feet from the corner. Turn right and walk one block. We are on the right in the basement just before you reach Church St. Parking Effective immediately Club Passim patrons &amp;amp; school of music students can now park in Harvard Square for only $6.00! University Place Garage, 124 Mt. Auburn St. Cambridge. This is a special rate that you will not find anywhere else and is for Club Passim patrons ONLY! (rate begins daily @ 5pm 7 nights a week) &amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#151;&amp;#150; Listen to our podcasts at iTunes and podcast webpage. And check out our video archive to get an idea about 5 minute stories &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/video" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; OMING SOON: see eventbrite to reserve tix. On April 11, 2012, 7-9PM All the finalists will gather at Coolidge Corner, main Theater to compete for a week in a medeival townhouse in Tuscany and other prizes. &amp;quot;Because have a life, you have a story. Bring it!&amp;quot; Listen to our podcasts at iTunes and podcast webpage. And check out our video archive to get an idea about 5 minute stories &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/video" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/story-slam-rules-pr-what-is" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://massmouth.ning.com/forum/topics/way-to-be-sure-to-tell-at-a" target="_blank"&gt;http://massmouth.ning...&lt;/a&gt; &amp;#8232;Other massmouth slams this season: Mondays: Club Passim in Cambridge, MA and Semi finals in March 2012 Tuesdays: Somerville, Cambridge and other venues Semi-finals in March 2012 Semi Finals: in March 11th for JP events Finals: WED APRIL 11th the Finals will be at Coolidge Corner Theater main theater Brookline, 7-9PM Grand Prize for Slam Season 2012&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326814332000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326171891000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Story slam - genesis at ClubPassim</name><id>47456502</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326758400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/47456502/</event_url></item>