<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;(from the publisher:)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its long history, the English language has had many lawmakers&amp;mdash;those who have tried to regulate, or otherwise organize, the way we speak. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Lexicographer&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma: The Evolution of Proper English from Shakespeare to South Park&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; offers the first narrative history of these endeavors, showing clearly that what we now regard as the only &amp;ldquo;correct&amp;rdquo; way to speak emerged out of specific historical and social conditions over the course of centuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As literary historian Jack Lynch has discovered, every rule has a human history, and the characters peopling his narrative are as interesting for their obsession as for their erudition. The struggle between prescriptivists, who prescribe a correct approach, and descriptivists, who analyze how language works, is at the heart of Lynch&amp;rsquo;s story. From the sharp-tongued satirist Jonathan Swift, who called for a government-sponsored academy to issue rulings on the language, and the polymath Samuel Johnson, who put dictionaries on a new footing, to John Horne Tooke, the crackpot linguist whose bizarre theories continue to baffle scholars; Joseph Priestley, whose political radicalism prompted riots; and the ever-crotchety Noah Webster, whose goal was to Americanize the English language&amp;mdash;Lynch brings to life a varied cast as illuminating as it is entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grammatical &amp;ldquo;rules&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;laws&amp;rdquo; are not like the law of gravity, or laws against theft or murder&amp;mdash;they&amp;rsquo;re more like rules of etiquette, made by fallible people and subject to change. Charting the evolution of English, Jack Lynch puts today&amp;rsquo;s debates&amp;mdash;whether about Ebonics in the schools or split infinitives in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&amp;mdash;in a rich historical context, and makes us appreciate anew the hard-won standards we now enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the bottom floor with a copy of the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334198753000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1481208</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331867160000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lexicographer's Dilemma: The Evolution of 'Proper' English by Jack Lynch</name><id>56563732</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334183400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group/events/56563732/</event_url></item>