<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>420 Totten Pond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-0100</phone><name>Hilton Garden Inn Hotel</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669398</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.254820</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly meetings will be held on the third Thursday of every month.  Monthly meetings are free to members, $25.00 for visitors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd, Waltham, Ma  781-890-0100&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors, when you decide to join that night, we will credit your $25.00 to the cost of the yearly membership.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steps for Success Trainings and other weekly session locations are to be determined.  Costs for these will vary depending on the event.  Members will be offered a discount on all educational opportunities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upcoming Meetings&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;August 16, 2007 - Meet the Players and Board of Advisors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30PM     Networking and Meet the Vendors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 - 9:00PM     Meet the Players and Board of Advisors, enjoy some refreshments, learn about the group and take advantage of networking with Investors, Financiers, Real estate Brokers, Mortgage Brokers, Real Estate Service Professionals and many others.  Build your power team.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***We will have an update from Attorney Alan Segal on Attorney General Martha Coakley's &amp;quot;Emergency Foreclosure Rescue Scheme Regulations&amp;quot; .  Don't miss this critical information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***We will also have National REIA Representative and Lobbyist Barry Lefkowitz, President and Founder of Management and Government Resources, Inc. will speak briefly on what investors can do to address the &amp;quot;Emergency Foreclosure Rescue Scheme Regulations&amp;quot; and how to have a profound effect on local legislation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Lefkowitz is a nationally distinguished trainer in the areas of grassroots organizing, coalition building, lobbying and grantsmanship. Early in his career, Barry refined his writing, speaking and organizational skills as a television host, part-time newscaster and newspaper editorial columnist. He has authored many books, including Lobbying and Influence: A Legislative Reference. He has also published numerous magazine and newspaper articles in the fields of politics, government and law-related education. Congress has recognized Barry for his innovative training approaches and exemplary educational materials. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187472890000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183570978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association July Meetup</name><id>5974599</id><headcount>170</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187299800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/5974599/</event_url></item>