<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Park and Beacon Streets</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.346428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>6331532</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105408</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/4/c/event_187842572.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the holiday season for a majority of Americans, and public spaces are full of signs of celebration: menorahs, candles, twinkle lights, Christmas trees. The local Christian community, for example, has a long-standing tradition of erecting a nativity crèche on Boston Common; and of course, this is problematic if the Christian theist perspective is the only one that enjoys this privileged position in the public space at this time of year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As secular citizens, we're alert to the possibility that municipal leaders, in their enthusiasm to embrace the season, may overstep the Establishment Clause boundary by allowing sectarian displays on public property. That is why the Boston Atheists have teamed up with the Secular Coalition of Massachusetts in supporting the Freedom From Religion Foundation's effort to install a banner with the secular point of view on the Common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The banner's arrived, and we have the permit in hand, so we'll be installing the banner this coming Monday, December 17th, at 2 PM. (The exact location will be announced following a discussion with the Parks &amp;amp; Rec department Monday morning.) Please plan to stop by; you can enjoy free coffee and doughnuts, hammer in a stake, and act as a friendly representative of our thriving secular community.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355782258000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355523719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Secular Banner Installation on Boston Common</name><id>95387872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355770800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/95387872/</event_url></item>