<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Interested in going but dont have a ride or are you offering a ride? Call me to work out the details as the date approaches. 
- mark (617) 65-2012-1
A new film by Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz
PHARMAWHORES:
The Showtime Sting of Penn &amp; Teller
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
Special Presentation and Q&amp;A With
Leonard Horowitz and Sherri Kane
Thursday, July 1, 2010, beginning 6:00 PM
Frances Crowe community meeting space
60 Masonic St., Northampton, MA - PDF - Flyer
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
National Tour Press Release:
PharmaWhores:
Are They Manipulating Your Mind?
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -

PHARMAWHORES: The Showtime Sting of Penn &amp; Teller is set to launch nationally on June 5th, and is bound to raise awareness about Big Pharma's ties to the Mainstream Media. The film also includes compelling evidence that ties Big Pharma to 911 Terrorists.

On June 6th PharmaWhores will be screened at the Conspiracy Conference in Santa Rosa, CA, and on June 12th will be held at the Bal Theatre in San Leandro, CA,

On July 1st, the East Coast premiere screening will be held at the Frances Crowe Community Meeting space in Northampton, MA. It is sponsored by FlybyNews.com and Valley 9/11 Truth. There will be no admission charge at the Northampton screening, however, donations to cover costs will be appreciated.

All screenings will include a Q &amp; A by the filmmakers, Dr. Leonard Horowitz and Sherri Kane, who both star in the film.

This whimsical tongue-in-cheek documentary, produced by Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz exposes BigPharma's media connections. It is filled with ironic humor, centering around the Las Vegas comedy team of Penn &amp; Teller and their SHOWTIME TV show called, "Bullshit!" Originally, the program planned on debunking Horowitz for his natural healing product endorsements. However, the doctor, a YouTube favorite, along with FOX News defector Sherri Kane, armed with documents, props, and a professional film crew, exposed SHOWTIME's network executives in partnerships with the most powerful drug industrialists. The "counter-sting" proves Penn &amp; Teller are more than celebrity magicians. They serve BigPharma as media propagandists--PHARMAWHORES! Plus, the film provides compelling evidence that ties 'Big Pharma' to '9/11 Terrorism' and profiteering.

Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz, the award-winning author and producer of In Lies We Trust: The CIA, Hollywood &amp; Bioterrorism .is an internationally known authority in the overlapping fields of public health, behavioral science, natural healing, and a Harvard trained expert on emerging diseases, and. Horowitz has written 16 books, and three national bestsellers. During the Obama 2008 Presidential campaign, Horowitz was referenced by Obama’s pastor, Rev. Jeremiah Wright about his book, "Emerging Viruses: AIDS &amp; Ebola--Nature, Accident or Intentional?"

Following their film screening, Dr. Horowitz and Ms. Kane will update us on their efforts to help people stay healthy in this deceptive world, as well as a way to finance grassroots organizations and campaigns including 911-Truth. There are no obligations, financial investments, or purchases necessary to join "Healthy World Affiliates" and all company profits go to humanitarian projects.

The first documentary film by Dr. Horowitz. "In Lies We Trust: The CIA, Hollywood &amp; Bioterrorism" was shown by Valley 9/11 Truth on May 13, 2008.

For more on this film, go to:, PharmaWhores .com.



Contact Information:
Sherri Kane
Healthy World Organization/ 528 Records.com
Los Angeles, CA
Phone: 1-888-399-3639
Email: info@healthyWorldAffiliates.com

Jonathan Mark
Publisher - FlybyNews.com
Founder - www.valley911truth.org
Email - flyby{AT]mtdata(DOT}com



News fit to transmit in the post Cassini flyby era
&lt;&gt;~&lt;&gt;~&lt;&gt;~ FlybyNews.com ~&lt;&gt;~&lt;&gt;~&lt;&gt;
for life's survival in the 21st Century</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280098223000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275438728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>7/1 Film by Dr. Leonard G. Horowitz PHARMAWHORES and Q+A with the filmmakers</name><id>13664899</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/13664899/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/global_12798054.jpeg</photo_url></item>