<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 141</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1346807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It could be a clinic in rural Mexico, a personal trainer in Beverly Hills, or a hospital in Dallas — all face a universal care-giving challenge — how to bring better health to more people using fewer resources. One strategy showing real success — for patients, physicians, technologists, and investors — brings together biometric sensing and mobile platforms. Tonight’s panel brings together four of this emerging industry’s leading innovators for a discussion — led by one of its leading market researchers — on what is happening now, what is about to happen and, most importantly, why.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Monday, September 13th 6:00 p.m. -- 9:00 p.m. (Light buffet dinner 6:00 - 6:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free for SIG members -- please RSVP on this Meetup page&lt;br /&gt;$10 for other MIT Enterprise Forum members -- &lt;a href="https://alum.mit.edu/smarTrans/public/Register.dyn?eventID=46881&amp;amp;groupID=298" target="_blank"&gt;please register at MIT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 if not a member of the MIT Enterprise Forum -- &lt;a href="https://alum.mit.edu/smarTrans/public/Register.dyn?eventID=46881&amp;amp;groupID=298" target="_blank"&gt;please register at MIT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Panelists:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; Adorian N. Ignat&lt;/b&gt; — Director Integrated Business Solutions - Healthcare for Sprint. With primary involvement in hospitals and accute healthcare, Mr. Ignat’s role is to develop a unified go-to-market strategy for Sprint’s heatlhcare business encompassing all relevant Sprint technologies, industry solutions and products.  Prior to joining Sprint he was the Director of Information Technology for North Bronx Healthcare Network (NBHN), a network of two teaching hospitals for the Albert Einstein College of Medicine, several medical practices and a Level One Trauma Center, with a total combined workforce of over 5000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; Robert W. Campbell &lt;/b&gt; — Vice President of Clinical Services and Research for Bedford, Massachusetts-based Insulet Corporation. Insulet is the maker of OmniPod, the world’s first tubing-free insulin management system that employs a handheld PDM (personal diabetes manager) to wirelessly program the user’s personalized insulin delivery, calculate suggested doses, and monitor patient glucose level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leo Anthony Celi, MD, MPH, MS&lt;/b&gt; — Co-founder of Sana, an MIT-based organization dedicated to revolutionizing healthcare delivery to underserved populations in remote areas. Sana’s end-to-end system seamlessly connects patients to medical specialists for faster, high quality, and more cost effective diagnosis and intervention. The challenges include poor cellular coverage, intermittent connectivity, multiple standards, incompatible networks and cultural differences. The solution employs packetization, a synchronization model, and multi-modal data transport in a mobile-centric system that also supports alternatives like WiFi and tethered uploads for bandwidth-constrained situations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Doug McClure&lt;/b&gt; — Chief Technology Officer and Vice President of Operations for Healthrageous, Inc., a connected personalized health company leveraging biometric sensors, smart phones and inspirational support to help people shed unhealthy habits, embrace healthy lifestyles and achieve health and wellness goals. Mr. McClure developed the technologies on which Healthrageous is based while chief technology officer at the Center for Connected Health at Partners HealthCare, whose founders are Massachusetts General Hospital and Brigham and Women’s Hospital. He is also a past chair of the American Telemedicine Association’s RFID Special Interest Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steve Hilton&lt;/b&gt; (panel moderator) — lead analyst for the Enterprise Research Program of Analysy Mason, a UK-based global IT consultancy. Areas of specialization include M2M, mobile enterprise solutions, cloud services, IT and communications products and sales channels. Mr. Hilton has 17 years' experience in technology and communications marketing. Prior to joining Analysys Mason, he managed the Enterprise and SMB team at Yankee Group. He has also held senior positions at Lucent Technologies, TDS and Cambridge Strategic Management Group (CSMG). A frequent speaker at industry and client forums, Mr. Hilton publishes monthly articles in several respected trade journals for the enterprise and channel partner community. He holds a degree in economics from the University of Chicago and a Master's degree in marketing from Northwestern University’s Kellogg School of Management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Cronk</member_name><member_id>465168</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284476126000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279902636000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sensing Opportunities in Mobile Health</name><id>14191421</id><headcount>90</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284415200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/14191421/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/2/4/global_16814852.jpeg</photo_url></item>