<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 George P. Hassett Drive </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.418622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-395-0402</phone><name>Springstep</name><city>Medford,</city><id>1119289</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Shadows of Bali&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First New England performance interpreting one of the world's most ancient theatre experiences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN.  Saturday Jan 30.  Performance @ 8:00 pm, Arts and Community Reception @ 7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT.  On Saturday, January 30, 2010, Springstep, rapidly emerging as the area’s leading multicultural arts center, will host Shadows of Bali, a rare  performance of one of the most ancient world theatre traditions. This event marks a first-time collaboration between LA-based dalang Maria Bodmann (Bali &amp;amp; Beyond) and Boston University’s Brita Heimarck and her Gender Wayang Ensemble, Amrita.  &lt;br /&gt;A free Arts and Community Reception, offering a chance to deepen appreciation for Bali and Wayang Kulit will be held at Springstep from 7-8 p.m.  &lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $16-$22 in advance; $25 at the door.  Youth under 16: $10.  Group rates available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OVERVIEW. Long considered the world’s #1 island, Bali is a mystical oasis where every living thing is sacred; where there is no word for art because life itself is art.   Shadows of Bali brings the island to life through an intimate, interactive and improvised performance of the ancient art of Wayang Kulit (Balinese Shadow Play).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dating back to at least 930 AD, Wayang Kulit is one of world theatre’s oldest and most exciting events. The performance revolves around intricately designed puppets that enact myths bridging illusion and awareness.  The instruments that make up the Balinese Gamelan specific to this form (Gender Wayang) create a rich musical tapestry.  And the dalang, who serves as puppeteer, comedian and, in this case, bilingual narrator, weaves a tale that blurs the lines between myth and reality, sacred and mundane, current events and ancient legend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shadows of Bali weaves themes from the Mahabharata, a sacred Sanskrit text that examines how individual lives relate to the world at large. At once mystical, silly, and educational, this expert and yet innovative performance is a multifaceted experience rarely available in New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The UN has designated the Wayang Kulit A Masterpiece of Oral and Intangible Humanity.  There are only a handful of performers in the US who practice this ancient art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The atmosphere will be informal and welcoming and, as in the traditional Balinese shadow play, the audience is invited to wander behind the screen to watch the magic as it is made. Food and wine will be available, all ages are welcome, and all are guaranteed to enjoy this feast for the senses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artists:  Dalang:  Maria Bodmann        Music:  Amrita:  Gender Wayang Ensemble of Boston with Brita Heimarck and Erin McCoy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional information:    Bali and Beyond    Bali&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE PERFORMANCE SERIES. Springstep’s acclaimed Performance Series  offers Greater Boston audiences a chance to travel the globe, experiencing music and dance traditions that uniquely define cultures while reaffirming the common bonds that unite all global citizens. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT SPRINGSTEP. With over 20,000 annual visitors, Springstep is rapidly emerging as the region’s leading destination for multicultural dance, music and art.  Connecting arts, culture and community through performances, exhibitions, classes, workshops and social dances, Springstep spotlights cultural rooted artists locally and from around the globe!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.springstep.org&lt;br /&gt;Springstep&lt;br /&gt;98 George P. Hassett Drive&lt;br /&gt;Medford, MA 02155&lt;br /&gt;781.395.0402&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;============================== ==================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;High Resolution Press Photos:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.springstep.org/sites/default/files/ShadowofBali1.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.springstep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three Hero Brothers (the Pandawas) - Prince Yudistera, Prince Bima, and Prince Arjuna meet with their teacher, Drono.  &lt;br /&gt;This is from a Shadows of Bali Performance - during the end Shadow Demonstration Section.&lt;br /&gt;Photographer Michael Burr&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.springstep.org/sites/default/files/ShadowsofBali2.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.springstep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lord Kreshna riding a chariot &lt;br /&gt;Photographer Cliff DeArment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.springstep.org/sites/default/files/ShadowsofBali3.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.springstep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prince Bima, strong one, third born Pandawa son.  This puppet was made by dalang Maria Bodmann.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.springstep.org/sites/default/files/ShadowsofBali4.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.springstep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the Garuda (on right) Naga (on left) from a short segment of their interaction in Shadows of Bali Demonstration.  &lt;br /&gt;Photographer Michael Burr&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison</member_name><member_id>10846307</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265073145000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263910456000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shadows of Bali</name><id>12361192</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264899600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/12361192/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/f/global_12704111.jpeg</photo_url></item>