<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1678 Asylum Avenue</address_2><address_1>St Joseph University</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.779681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>646 688 6038</phone><name>Hoffman Auditorium in The Bruyette Athenaeum</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>872424</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.731273</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Carolyn Autorino Center for the Arts and Humanities at Saint Joseph College, in partnership with the department of Theatre at Easter Connecticut State University and the department of Film Studies at Wesleyan University, and in collaboration with the Jack Lemmon family, presents a tribute to one of the most promient film actors fo the 20th Century.  Three movies will be screened, and include an introduction by a member of faculy from one of the schools.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you missed the Cine Classics showing, here's another chance to see &amp;quot;Some Like It Hot,&amp;quot; the 1959 film that many people consider one of the great comedies of all time.  Briefly summarized as &amp;quot;when two musicians witness a mob hit, they flee the state in an all female band disguised as women, but further complications set in&amp;quot; on IMDB, this is one of the films that someone can see time and again and still catch new bits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Billy Wilder, starring Tony Curtis and Marilyn Monroe in addition to Jack Lemmon.  Running time 120 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST:  $15&lt;br /&gt;($10 for senior citizens)&lt;br /&gt;Screenings are at 7:00pm, general seating, so arrive a bit early to pick a choice seat.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295917077000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288102293000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Craft of Jack Lemmon:  "Some Like It Hot"</name><id>15232971</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295912700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/15232971/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>