<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01453</zip><lat>42.527428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978.840.2253</phone><name>The Dessert Bar</name><city>Leominster</city><id>966992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.759102</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In March we&amp;rsquo;re reading&lt;em&gt; Chocolat&lt;/em&gt;, followed by &lt;em&gt;eating &lt;/em&gt;chocolate at Dessert Bar in Leominster. Dessert Bar serves a bevy of specialty coffees, desserts, martinis, and *dessert martinis*! Relax on their comfy couches and plush armchairs and enjoy gelato or a slice of rich chocolate cake (yum!) while we discuss the book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the description of &lt;em&gt;Chocolat&lt;/em&gt; from the front cover of the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In tiny Lansquenet, where nothing much has changed in a hundred years, beautiful, unmarried newcomer Vianne Rocher and her young daughter sweep into the pinched little town on a wave of gossip. On the heels of the carnival, Vianne promptly opens a chocolate shop right across the square from the church, and thus begins to wreak havoc with the town&amp;rsquo;s Lenten vows. Vianne finds herself embroiled in a battle for the town&amp;rsquo;s souls with the local priest, Father Raynaud, who tries to cast Vianne &amp;ndash; with her unconventional, gypsy-like ways &amp;ndash; as the village Jezebel. Soon she has effected a civil war in the little country town between those who prefer the cold comforts of the church and those who revel in the warm delights of chocolate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But each box of chocolates she sells comes with a free gift: Vianne&amp;rsquo;s uncanny perception of its buyer&amp;rsquo;s private discontents and a clever, caring cure for them. Is she a witch? Soon the parish no longer cares, as it abandons itself to temptation, happiness, and a dramatic confrontation between Easter solemnity and the pagan gaiety of a chocolate festival.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A literary confection that has already become an international sensation, Chocolat lingers in the memory like the taste of a splendidly aged Burgundy. It is an enchanting and timeless story about temptation, pleasure, and what a complete waste of time it is to deny yourself anything. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservations will be under Book Club or Heather. We'll be sitting in a circle of comfy couches and chairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301671007000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299181816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Chocolat by Joanne Harris</name><id>16785594</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301612400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/16785594/</event_url></item>