<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2nd floor Suite 6B - (take elevator)</address_2><address_1>201 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-240-3671</phone><name>A Higher Balance </name><city>Salem</city><id>848691</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895309</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear meditators...some of you may want to learn to read Angel cards...it's simple and fun! Learn from the best! Elizabeth Foley is THE angel lady of New Engliand and I'm happy to have her back to teach at A Higher Balance! &lt;br /&gt;

An Angel Reading is an easy way to connect and talk with your Angels. In this class you will learn how to give accurate and healing angel readings, using psychic means and angel oracle cards through skill-building and experiential practice. The curriculum includes giving angel readings during the practicum period and interpreting the angelic messages. You will learn how to interpret the meaning behind the cards and how to present the information given to you by the Angels for helping to heal yourself and others. If you have angel cards, please bring them.  I've been reading angel cards for years, and was taught by Elizabeth! Come join us if you feel called. Just rsvp to this Meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As an international Angelologist and spokesperson for the celestial hierarchy, Elizabeth Foley conducts private angel readings and sessions, and facilitates unique spiritual workshops and programs about angels, psychic development and soul therapy. She is a teacher and author of several books about angels.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy Copp</member_name><member_id>8642061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360289564000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Salem-MA-Meditation-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1362498</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem MA Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359940527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn to read Angel Cards! with Elizabeth Foley</name><id>102870222</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360279800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Salem-MA-Meditation-Meetup-Group/events/102870222/</event_url></item>