<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>With Gene Hackman, Fernando Rey, Roy Scheider&lt;br /&gt;US 1971, video, color, 104 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hcl.harvard.edu/hfa/films/2009janfeb/friedkin.html#french" target="_blank"&gt;HFA Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A garrulous and engaging speaker, &lt;b&gt;William Friedkin&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;will be present to discuss his work at the Harvard Film Archive on February 20th and 21st.  The Harvard Film Archive is reserving ten reduced tickets to our meetup group in order for us to attend Friday's showing of &lt;u&gt;The French Connection&lt;/u&gt; and the Q&amp;amp;A with the director.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A consummate master of studio filmmaking, Friedkin has thrived as the rare empiricist within the dream factory, an artist driven by a curiosity to capture those dark, unseen mysteries that define the material world, without destroying their spell.  Friedkin returned to his documentary roots in the early 1970s, with &lt;u&gt;The French Connection&lt;/u&gt; a riveting film whose power lies in its extraordinarily gripping realism, an uncanny verisimilitude of detail and character based largely on Friedkin's own meticulous research and close consultation with the veteran New York police detectives who were the real life models for his protagonists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserved tickets are $8 and must be paid in advance.  In addition, we must submit everyone's full name to be put on the list at the HFA.  Not only will we have reduced admission, but also will avoid getting shut out of what should be a sold out event. I have provided a link to paypal to assist with pre-payment and I reserve the right to cancel anyone's RSVP who does not pre-pay as I will be fronting the full amount to the HFA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those familiar with these events at the HFA know that they tend to run late, as the time with the director is unpredictable.  For this reason, we will not schedule a post-film discussion. I will be standing at the ticket counter as early as 6:15 in order to meetup with folks and attempt to get seats close together.  Doors will probably open at 6:30, and your ticket will be held for you at the counter as long as you arrive before 6:45.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be standing at the ticket counter as early as 6:15</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234195838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The French Connection with William Friedkin in Attendance</name><id>9705343</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235174400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9705343/</event_url></item>