<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wallingford</address_2><address_1>1339 Whirlwind Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.436100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Goeveia Vineyards</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>345258</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.764336</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's meet for a wine tasting, picnic and entertainment at Gouveia Vineyards. The winery is  located at 1339 Whirlwind Hill Road in Wallingford, CT. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gouveia Vineyards is located on 140 acres of which 15 acres are cultivated with over 16,000 vines. The winery offers Stone House White, Whirlwind Rose, Chardonnay, Merlot and Stone House Red wines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gouveia Vineyards is the joyful realization of a dream long cherished by the proprietor ~ to bring in some measure of remembrances of his village in Portugal and his grandfather's beautiful vineyards here to America. Located high on 140 sun kissed acres, this jewel of a winery, built of stone and old timbers, commands a spectacular 360 degree view of lush woodlands, open fields, pristine hundred year old farms and, of course, the vineyard itself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here, where the days are warm and the nights are cool, eight different varieties of grape thrive: Seyval Blanc, Vignoles, Chardonnay, Pinot Noir, Cabernet Franc, Merlot, Cayuga and St. Croix. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors to the vineyard for a wine tasting can bring their own picnic lunches or savories to enjoy ~ beside the pond in the summer, before a roaring fire in the winter, or from the delightful stone patio any time of the year. Visitors are not allowed to bring any other beverages onto to the premises. Bottled water and soda are also available for sale. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come! Savor the truly charming surroundings and the genuine hospitality of Joe and Lucy Gouveia! Settle back, relax with a great glass of wine and dream your own dreams! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Events: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members will meet at the vineyard to enjoy a picnic dinner and entertainment. Please indicate on the RSVP what you will be bringing to avoid duplication. Finger foods that would go well with wines would be desirable. Also needed would be paper plates and plastic utensils. The vineyard does not allow visitors to bring wine or bottled beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a 5 dollar fee payable to the vineyard for the wine tasting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entertainment on Saturdays from 4:00 PM to 7:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the first of a possible series of tours of CT Vineyards. There are 20 located all over the state. We can sample the wine and see what CT has to offer!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lynn</member_name><member_id>4669226</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189455048000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187030818000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wines Tasting and Picnic at Gouveia Vineyards in Wallingford, CT</name><id>6173541</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189281600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/6173541/</event_url></item>