<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Star Island</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03870</zip><lat>42.976505</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Star Island</name><city>Rye</city><id>6336762</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.612999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join members of the New Hampshire Society of Photographs Artists for this annual four-day (September 8th-11th) immersion in fine art photography. This unique program offers fine art photographers the opportunity to meet and share their work with others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year the NHSPA retreat will feature &amp;nbsp;guest artist Todd Gipstein, who has 40 years experience as a photographer, Director of Multi-Image, and ExecutiveProducer for the National Geographic Society. His work for National Geographicincluded writing and producing shows about geography, nature, and culture,including Geography of the Human Spirit.&amp;#157; He also worked with Vice-PresidentAl Gore on media related to environmental issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd will work with us over the four days to shoot and edit our own multi-mediapresentation, which he will ultimately assemble (and show us how and why). Participants should bring their gear, including a laptop if possible, and somework to show. &amp;nbsp;As any of you know who have been to Star, there are always surprises on the island (and in our group).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Friday evening Todd will make a presentation of his own work for both ourgroup and the Isles of Shoals Research Association (ISHRA), which is on theisland for the weekend. &amp;nbsp;Followed by an ice cream social!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a bonus, Star Island star photographer Alexandra de Steiguer will be on-island with ISHRA, and we can look forward to spending some time with her. Alex was our guest at the retreat several years ago, and as the wintercaretaker of the island she has &amp;nbsp;a truly unique perspective on its geography! &lt;br /&gt;

Come explore one of the great landscapes of New England with some greatphotographers and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need to register with the &lt;a href="http://www.nhspa.org"&gt;NHSPA&lt;/a&gt; in order to take part in this retreat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details to be made available soon</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347127935000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332527349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>15th Annual NHSPA Star Island Photo Retreat</name><id>57577602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347116400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/57577602/</event_url></item>