<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Our next meeting is Thursday, July 24th from 7:00pm to 9:00pm at the Prudential Mall food court.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to talk about a variety of topics as well as do an exercise or two to help strengthen our communication.  Here's the agenda for the meeting: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introductions and icebreakers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Field reports and news from our members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lesson:&lt;/b&gt; How to keep the conversation going after the approach&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exercise:&lt;/b&gt; Personality feedback&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Munchies:&lt;/b&gt; I always go to Legal Seafoods after the meeting.  Anyone who wants to come along is welcome.  The last time 15 of us went and had a great time.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you want to learn some simple methods for keeping a conversation going with a person after you approach them, then you're going to love this month's meeting.  You'll not only learn what to do to keep the conversation going with strangers, but this will also help you in your day to day conversations with family, friends, loved ones, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll learn:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to smoothly transition from the approach to the next conversation topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What to actually talk with her about (and which topics people generally interesting).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use the &amp;quot;oh shit button&amp;quot; to bail yourself out of awkward silences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Then we'll break up into smaller groups, and each person will have an opportunity to receive direct, honest (and extremely rare) feedback on how you can improve the way you come across.  Be prepared for a fun, interactive meeting.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;It's important that I get an accurate head count, so please RSVP if you plan on coming. I'm looking forward to meeting you in person.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Jason King&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - The cost of the meeting is only $10 cash.  This will include the cost of the meeting and any take home materials I provide you with.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the table with the large Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329108727000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215511945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Social Skills Meeting - How To Keep A Conversation Going After The Approach</name><id>8297673</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216940400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/8297673/</event_url></item>