<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>November Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just how many of these bank-owned foreclosures are out there?  According to realtytrac.com, what we are seeing today is unprecedented as… &lt;b&gt;40% OF PROPERTIES SOLD IN THE LAST THREE MONTHS WERE BANK-OWNED FORECLOSURES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, November 11, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM Best Western Executive Court, Manchester, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free for members; $20 for non-members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THEN . . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 14, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 AM - 5:00 PM Southern NH University, 25 Pelham Road, Salem, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$29 for members; $59 for non-members; $99 day of the event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attend the most important workshop on getting RICH in today’s market, and thanks to NHREIA it is pretty much FREE!!!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This full day workshop “costs” $29 for members and $59 for nonmembers….BUT &lt;b&gt;it really costs nothing because&lt;/b&gt;….&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         You get lunch for free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Andy Heller’s book Buy Even Lower was rated within the top 3 real estate books of the year, and it costs over $20 in bookstores today.   All those who pre-register for this workshop get this book at the end of the workshop for FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this event!  YOU may be the one to win the an Asus netbook, to be given away at the end of the day!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy Heller is our speaker and he’s the nation’s #1 expert on this topic!  He’s going to share his secrets of buying Bank-Owned properties for just pennies on the dollar.  Wondering about Andy’s credibility?  Check this out … Andy’s entire investment strategy has been recommended by Fortune Magazine as one of the TOP 5 Wealth Building Strategies for Real Estate Investors.  So you will not only learn how to find the deals, but how to rent your properties in days or weeks and sell WITHOUT DISCOUNTING.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just &lt;a href="http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/EventDisplayNew.cfm?clubID=1914&amp;amp;EventID=103089&amp;amp;mo=11&amp;amp;tDate=%7Bd%20%272009%2D11%2D20%27%7D" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to register now, and get your FREE copy of &amp;quot;Buy Even Lower&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday Andy will cover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Why Fortune Magazine recommended the Buy Low, Rent Smart, Sell High program&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Why today’s COOLING market is a RED HOT opportunity for investors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Buying Low:  Learn about the untapped fortunes with bank-owned real estate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Why especially today bank owned properties offer investors of all means unlimited deals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         WHY ESPECIALLY TODAY AN INVESTOR CAN MAKE ENORMOUS PROFITS BUYING BANK-OWNED FORECLOSURES!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Why bank-owned properties may be the best SOURCE for investors who have limited cash and/or credit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         How to calculate the EXACT price you need to buy properties at in order to maximize your profits&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         What types of properties can you buy from banks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Why a MOTIVATED tenant is the key to landlording fortunes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         How the “typical” lease options minimize, not maximize, an investor’s profits&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         How to make a fortune in real estate AND help your tenants at the same time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         How to sell for top dollar WITHOUT paying real estate commissions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;·         Achieve your REGULAR RICHES:  Real estate fortunes for regular people…without the hassles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You’ll also hear about Andy’s students:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hans van der Kolk.  Hans bought a business with the money he made from Andy’s system, then returned to real estate investing four months ago and has already made $168,000 on three deals!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following Andy’s step-by-step system, Richard Lamberi bought 2 bank-owned foreclosures in his first 30 days and 7 in his first 8 months!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wally Fetrow and his son, with no experience, flipped their first REO and made $28,000.  Their next two REOS they have Lease Optioned with Andy’s “Rent Smart System.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Adams was building a new home, and could not sell his primary residence in 10 months.  In less than two months John and his family were looking at the frightening thought of having two mortgages to cover.  Two weeks after implementing Andy’s Rent Smart program, he lease/purchased his home (that he could not sell in 10 months) at a positive cash flow.  John has done two more lease/purchases since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LEARN what these students KNOW and you can enjoy the same results!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258155238000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-756</urlname><id>633261</id><group_lat>42.9399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>NH Entrepreneurs Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255563346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The New Hampshire Real Estate Investors Association November Meetup</name><id>cffzfympbpb</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257982200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-756/events/11629058/</event_url></item>