<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>16 Ella Grasso Turnpike </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06096</zip><lat>41.917051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 236-3343</phone><name>DOUBLETREE HOTEL</name><city>Windsor Locks</city><id>1176579</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.673491</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;When was the last time you got a chance to meet and talk with &lt;br /&gt;15 – 25 Single Guys or Girls in one evening?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating works on nature’s laws of chemistry and attraction – when you meet someone new – you know instantly whether there is a romantic potential, and friendship potential, or a possible business relationship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have a 7-minute discussion with each SPEED Match Dater, and them YOU decide who is a great match for you. If both SPEED Match Daters pick each other as a potential match, we will send you the email address of your matches so you can contact each other to make arrangements for dinner, drinks, movie, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This provides you an unique opportunity to meet and talk to people that you otherwise would not meet – to dig deeper and discover what is inside each person for a happy relationship and a compatible match!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because all your info is confidential, other SPEED Match Daters know only the information that you choose to provide them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No personal info such as phone numbers or email addresses are exchanged at the event, so SPEED Match Dating is a very safe and fun way to meet new people with feeling uncomfortable, embarrassed, bored, or nervous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your SPEED Match Dating matches will be emailed to you soon after the event, and you can then contact your matches by email if you wish for the next step for meeting and dating arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting that special compatible person can be a difficult and lengthy process, and SPEED Match Dating can help SPEED up that process by providing you with 15 – 25 Instant Mini-Dates in one fun and exciting evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not tried SPEED Match Dating, then you are missing out on the best way to meet Local Compatible Singles, New Friends, and Business Opportunities that otherwise would pass you by.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the next SPEED Match Dating Party, &lt;br /&gt;and purchase your ticket in advance at a discounted price!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEXT EVENT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday FEB 18 at 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;DOUBLETREE HOTEL &lt;br /&gt;16 Ella Grasso Turnpike &lt;br /&gt;Windsor Locks, CT 06096&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACROSS FROM BRADLEY AIRPORT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;15 minutes from Hartford * 15 minutes from Springfield &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes Appetizers * FREE CHAMPAGNE FOR THE LADIES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 236-3343&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the Singles CT signs </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Singles CT .com  -Join The Party</member_name><member_id>5188478</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266710980000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264807013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPEED Match Dating with SinglesCT.com Instant 15 - 25 Mini-Dates in one Evening</name><id>12462612</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266537600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/12462612/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/b/7/global_12418279.jpeg</photo_url></item>