<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Through Our Eyes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Personal Stories of the 2011 Japan Earthquake &amp;amp; Tsunami, and Ongoing Efforts to Help Those Affected&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's been over a year since the devastating 3.11 earthquake and tsunami heavily damaged Tohoku and many other regions of Japan.  Although numerous individuals both inside and outside of Japan were deeply affected, many still continue to do their best to encourage, aid, and reconstruct communities across Japan. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 On July 5th, the Boston Japanese &amp;amp; English Language Club will be hosting three speakers at Harvard University that will introduce their own personal stories related to last year's events, as well as their own continuing aid efforts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 A bit about our speakers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Karen Gibbons&lt;/strong&gt; is the aunt of Taylor Anderson, a JET Program teacher in Ishinomaki, Japan, and the first known American victim of last year's tsunami.  Karen will speak about Taylor's life and memories in Japan, as well as the St. Catherine's School Fund Taylor's family has established in Taylor's memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 More about the St. Catherine's School Fund:  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.st.catherines.org/tayloranderson"&gt;http://www.st.catherines.org/tayloranderson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Regge Life&lt;/strong&gt; is a successful documentary filmmaker and the producer of 'Live Your Dream: The Taylor Anderson Story.' He will be joining us to speak about his work on the documentary, as well as his own experiences in interviewing those close to Taylor in Ishinomaki and surrounding towns, and those close to Monty Dickson, another JET who was lost in Rikuzentaka. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Regge's Kickstart Project Page:  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/675402675/live-your-dream-the-taylor-anderson-story"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/675402675/live-your-dream-the-taylor-anderson-story&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Mihoko Terada&lt;/strong&gt; will be joining us from Sendai, Japan, and will be talking about her own earthquake and tsunami experiences, as well as her work with The Fund for the Future of Children affected by the Great East Japan Earthquake.  She will also share a bit about the heroes of the Red Cross hospital in Ishinomaki. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The Fund for the Future of Children affected by the Great East Japan Earthquake: &lt;a href="http://www.mirai-kikin.com/en/index.html"&gt;http://www.mirai-kikin.com/en/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;石巻赤十字病院の100日間: &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/409388207X"&gt;http://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/409388207X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no cost for attendance, but a donation to any of the aid funds discussed during the evening is greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Seating is limited.&lt;/strong&gt; We will be opening up 20 seats to Boston Japanese &amp;amp; English Language Club Members, and RSVP is required.  If for some reason you need to cancel, please let us know as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Harvard Center for Government and International Studies (CGIS) South, Room S250 &lt;br /&gt;

 Address: 1730 Cambridge St, Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: 7 - 9:30 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Map: &lt;a href="http://map.harvard.edu/?ctrx=760767&amp;amp;ctry=2961814.5&amp;amp;level=9&amp;amp;layers=Campus%20Base%20and%20Buildings,Map%20Text"&gt;http://map.harvard.edu/?ctrx=760767&amp;amp;ctry=2961814.5&amp;amp;level=9&amp;amp;layers=Campus%20Base%20and%20Buildings,Map%20Text&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341541100000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340371560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Through Our Eyes: Personal Stories of the 2011 Japan Earthquake &amp; Tsunami</name><id>70263172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341529200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/70263172/</event_url></item>