<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/1/2/event_185393522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hi Everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well when the Hyde Park on the Hudson movie was canceled, I started searching for another film for Saturday Night.  I found this Hitchcock movie that looks interesting.   Unfortunately the times at the downtown Lowes are rather inconvenient.   Luckily the Kendall Square Theater is running it as well.   This way we can all have a bit of a change in venue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showtime is at 6:40.  I will be in the lobby by 6 and we can head in for seats around 6:25.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can go to Tommy Doyles or the CBC after the movie they are across the street from the theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get to the theater by taking the red line to Kendall Square and walking (about 1/2 mile to the theater) or there is street parking and a garage next to the theater.  I know they validate garage parking for $3 off the total cost.    &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information about getting to the theater go to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheatres.com/market/Boston/KendallSquareCinema.htm"&gt;http://www.landmarktheatres.com/market/Boston/KendallSquareCinema.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Please note:  this theater does not use Fandango.  For Tickets go to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Ticketing.aspx?TheatreID=231&amp;amp;MovieID=14166&amp;amp;ShowDate=12/8/2012&amp;amp;ScheduleID=112722"&gt;https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Ticketing.aspx?TheatreID=231&amp;amp;MovieID=14166&amp;amp;ShowDate=12/8/2012&amp;amp;ScheduleID=112722&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lurking behind Alfred Hitchcock (Anthony Hopkins)—cinema's "master of suspense" and the extraordinary film icon known for orchestrating some of the most intense experiences of menace and intrigue audiences have ever seen—was a hidden side: his creatively explosive romance with his steadfast wife and filmmaking collaborator, Alma Reville (Helen Mirren). Now, for the first time, director Sacha Gervasi's &lt;em&gt;Hitchcock&lt;/em&gt;lays bare their captivating and complex love story. It does so through the sly, shadowy lens of their most daring filmmaking adventure: the making of the spine-tingling 1960 thriller &lt;em&gt;Psycho&lt;/em&gt;, which would become the director's most controversial and legendary film. When the tumultuous, against-the-odds production was over, nothing about movies would ever be the same, but few realized that it took two to pull it off. Co-starring Scarlett Johansson, Toni Collette, Danny Huston and Jessica Biel. Co-written by John J. McLaughlin, co-screenwriter of &lt;em&gt;Black Swan&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;a href="http://www.foxsearchlight.com/hitchcock/" target="_blank"&gt;Official Web Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Director:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sacha Gervasi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cast:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony Hopkins, Helen Mirren, Scarlett Johansson, Toni Collette, Danny Huston, Jessica Biel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the Lobby sporting my stylin Meetup Pin</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355192791000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354735605000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hitchcock</name><id>94202662</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355007600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/94202662/</event_url></item>