<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>181 Boston Post Road West</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.337498</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Best Western Royal Plaza Hotel &amp; Trade Center</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>4189582</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.592583</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This year the 22nd Annual Evening of Giving to benefit Roland&amp;rsquo;s House for the Marlboro-Hudson Homeless Shelter will be held on Thursday, December 8th at the Royal Plaza Hotel. The event features&amp;nbsp;music, dancing, cash bar, and the ever&amp;nbsp;popular raw bar&amp;nbsp;with oysters, clams, and shrimp. Tickets prices are $30.00 each or you may purchase&amp;nbsp;a table of 10 for $300.00. Please let me know if you are interested in attending this important event to help the homeless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the original&amp;nbsp;Evening of Giving Event which was established in Marlborough during the 1980's. In 1986, a homeless man froze to death in Hudson because he had no place to sleep at night. This prompted a meeting between then-Marlborough City Counselor Roland Simoneau and the local Interfaith Clergy Association. Together they vowed to do something to ensure that no one else would suffer the same fate, so they created a shelter in the basement of a Marlborough municipal building. The space they occupied was not large. It had no showers, no paid staff, and the shelter only operated during the evening and overnight hours. Working with a small group of volunteers, the group held a fundraiser in the basement of St. Matthias Church in Marlborough. This fundraising event continued for a few years and in 1990, the event was officially named The Evening of Giving. After several years as the event's popularity increased, the crowd grew and The Evening of Giving was moved to the Best Western Royal Plaza Hotel in Marlborough. Today the event features over 30 restaurants, a popular raw bar featuring oysters, clams, shrimp, music, dancing and a cash bar. The Evening of Giving draws over 1,200 people. Through Roland's efforts, he and the committee have raised approximately half a million dollars. Over the years, those proceeds have helped improve the shelter through the addition of a new heating system, new windows, new floors, and kitchen and bathroom remodeling. The funds have also paid 100% of the food costs and have helped us to maintain the staffing levels necessary to operate the shelter. With Roland&amp;rsquo;s passing in 2005, the shelter was rededicated as &amp;ldquo;Roland&amp;rsquo;s House&amp;rdquo; in honor of a man who made a difference in the lives of so many. Your ticket purchase will help support the Roland&amp;rsquo;s House shelter. Please consider purchasing an individual ticket or sponsoring a table of ten in your name or your organization&amp;rsquo;s name. Thank you for your anticipated support, Nicole Carey, Committee Member e-mail nikkcar@aol.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323874041000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319829212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Attend Benefit for The 22nd Evening of Giving, Royal Plaza Hotel, Marlborough</name><id>39084392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323388800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/39084392/</event_url></item>