<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 1, 2nd Floor</address_2><address_1>2000 Massachusetts Avenue </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.390246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-864-5720</phone><name>Acropolis Boston</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>796377</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121506</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In celebration of &lt;b&gt;World Philosophy Day and the U.N Day of Tolerance&lt;/b&gt;, Acropolis Boston is proud to present a tribute to three free-thinkers who gave their lives in the pursuit of the freedom and dignity of the human spirit.   &lt;br /&gt;Friday, November 20th at 7:30 pm   Reserve Now!  &lt;a href="http://acropolisboston.org/events.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://acropolisbosto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Martin Luther King Jr.: During the civil rights movement, he captured the attention of the nation with his philosophy of nonviolent resistance. According to Dr. King, this was the only solution that could cure society’s evil and create a just society. As King emerged as a leader in the civil rights movement, he put his belief into action and proved that this was an effective method to combat racial segregation. King was shot on April 4, 1968 while he was standing on the Lorraine Motel second floor balcony. After emergency chest surgery, King was pronounced dead at St. Joseph's Hospital at 7:05 p.m. ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- * Giordano Bruno: Bruno's world view integrated both scientific and philosophical thought into a humanistic approach that provided a vision of the modern Man. As a symbol of the freedom of thought, Bruno and his ideal of religious and philosophical tolerance has influenced free thinkers ever since. On February 17, 1600 in the Campo de' Fiori, a central Roman market square, Bruno was burned at the stake. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------ *Hypatia of Alexandria: Daughter of the philosopher Theon, Hypathia was so accomplished in literature and science, as to far surpass all the philosophers of her own time. Well versed in the schools of Plato and Plotinus, she explained the principles of philosophy to her disciples, many of whom came from a distance to receive her instructions. She never felt abashed in going to an assembly of men. For all men on account of her extraordinary dignity and virtue admired her the more. One day in March 415, Hypathia was beaten by a zealous mob who, tearing her body in pieces, took her mangled limbs to a place called Cinaron, and there burnt them. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rita Kraner</member_name><member_id>3033713</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephanie</member_name><member_id>10475843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258936992000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Practical-Philosophy-Application-of-Timeless-Wisdom</urlname><id>1304986</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Practical Philosophy -- Application of Timeless Wisdom</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258493490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Freedom and the Power of Philosophy</name><id>11897760</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258763400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Practical-Philosophy-Application-of-Timeless-Wisdom/events/11897760/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/9/2/global_11869426.jpeg</photo_url></item>