<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.370484</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-354-4144</phone><name>Au Bon Pain</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>777305</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113436</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Talk about democracy in action, our next book has been chosen by Sept 8th's enthusiastic members (give me a couple &amp;quot;i want to read that's and Kate's enthusiastic endorsement and I'm sold! :-).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;American Gods by Neil Gaiman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publishers comments copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?isbn=0380789035" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A master of inventive fiction, Neil Gaiman delves into the murky depths where reality and imagination meet. Now in American Gods, he works his literary magic to extraordinary results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shadow dreamed of nothing but leaving prison and starting a new life. But the day before his release, his wife and best friend are killed in an accident. On the plane home to the funeral, he meets Mr. Wednesday — a beguiling stranger who seems to know everything about him. A trickster and rogue, Mr. Wednesday offers Shadow a job as his bodyguard. With nowhere left to go, Shadow accepts, and soon learns that his role in Mr. Wednesday's schemes will be far more dangerous and dark than he could have ever imagined. For beneath the placid surface of everyday life a war is being fought — and the prize is the very soul of America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the suggestion of our wise participants, we'll be meeting at Au Bon Pain on Mass Ave in Harvard Sq.  Look for us at the outside tables if it's nice, inside if not.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225150522000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220957232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meetup: American Gods by Neil Gaiman</name><id>8720361</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223334000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/8720361/</event_url></item>