<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>[617] 621-1200 </phone><name>Friendly Toast</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>915453</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be meeting for a delicious brunch at the Friendly Toast in Kendall.  It's near Kendall Cinema, so that means a 10 minute walk from the actual T stop.  Know thyself-- plan to come early if you're chronically late ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We only say this because it's impossible to delay ordering food!  Once you've taken a look at the menu, you won't be able to resist.  Don't say we didn't warn you.  Omg Belgian waffles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;menu : &lt;a href="http://thefriendlytoast.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://thefriendlytoa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julie and Olivia will be there at 11 sharp to welcome all hungry heathens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;T: If you come out on the side with flags down the middle of main street, look for Legal Sea Foods (behind the bus stops) and walk past, taking a right when you get to Galileo Galilei Way, then a left on Broadway.  Follow the diagonal sidewalk onto Hampshire Street, you'll bump right into the Friendly Toast.&lt;br /&gt;If you leave the T from the other side, take a left down Broadway and continue until you get to that diagonal sidewalk for Hampshire Street.&lt;br /&gt;[For future reference, that's the same way you get to Flattop Johnny's, Tommy Doyle's, The Blue Room, and a bunch of other cool meetup places.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving: From Boston take the Longfellow Bridge off of Storrow Dr. which becomes Broadway St. and turn rt. onto Hampshire St. The Friendly Toast is immediately on the right at 1 Hampshire St.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you can't find us right away, ask for the Boston Atheists!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>5612245</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olivia</member_name><member_id>7737049</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1250435575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249051389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Brunch @ The Friendly Toast</name><id>11001076</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249830000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/11001076/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>