<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>253 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3983</phone><name>Bruegger's Bagels</name><city>Brookline</city><id>972928</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This month we'll be reading 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Immortal Life of
Henrietta Lacks&lt;/span&gt;, which is the true&amp;nbsp;story of a woman
whose cancer cells were extensively cultured without her permission
in 1951. &amp;nbsp;It has gotten raved reviews and has been on the
NYTimes best sellers list for 13 weeks. &amp;nbsp;Hope you enjoy it!
&amp;nbsp;(The full Publishers Weekly review is below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. There is a decent size waiting list for library copies.
&amp;nbsp;So, if you get your books from the library, please put your
name on the waiting list now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Science journalist Skloot makes a remarkable debut with this
  multilayered story about faith, science, journalism, and grace.
  It is also a tale of medical wonders and medical arrogance,
  racism, poverty and the bond that grows, sometimes painfully,
  between two very different women&amp;mdash;Skloot and Deborah
  Lacks&amp;mdash;sharing an obsession to learn about Deborah's mother,
  Henrietta, and her magical, immortal cells. Henrietta Lacks was a
  31-year-old black mother of five in Baltimore when she died of
  cervical cancer in 1951. Without her knowledge, doctors treating
  her at Johns Hopkins took tissue samples from her cervix for
  research. They spawned the first viable, indeed miraculously
  productive, cell line&amp;mdash;known as HeLa. These cells have aided
  in medical discoveries from the polio vaccine to AIDS treatments.
  What Skloot so poignantly portrays is the devastating impact
  Henrietta's death and the eventual importance of her cells had on
  her husband and children. Skloot's portraits of Deborah, her
  father and brothers are so vibrant and immediate they recall
  Adrian Nicole LeBlanc's&amp;nbsp;Random Family.&amp;nbsp;Writing in
  plain, clear prose, Skloot avoids melodrama and makes no
  judgments. Letting people and events speak for themselves, Skloot
  tells a rich, resonant tale of modern science, the wonders it can
  perform and how easily it can exploit society's most vulnerable
  people.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the big table up front</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel Greene</member_name><member_id>11862196</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1312200376000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307798502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Book Club</name><id>21809861</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312142400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/21809861/</event_url></item>