<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Kayak Rental Doughnation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per kayak rented</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This looks like the last padddle of the year, (unless there is some real good weather in the next few weeks)...so get them boats out one more time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU DONT LIKE TO KAYAK&amp;gt;&amp;gt;NO PROBLEM..&lt;br /&gt;JOIN US FOR THE POT LUCK MEAL AFTERWARD&lt;br /&gt;ITS A GOOD SOCIALIZING EVENT TOO...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When will we get to the picanick..when we get there..good answere right ???...its most likely &lt;br /&gt;around 2-3pm  time frame//&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the shortened trip from the ones we have done in the past on this river. &lt;br /&gt;It allows for an easy in and out location, along with a fast car transport between locations (most of you know the drill on this one..its not difficult) allowing for plenty of time for our food and relaxing time afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is the same trip, put in and take out as Tuan did on Saturday, but much later in the morning, i know most of you dont get up early...LOL &lt;br /&gt;He has a lot more kayaks and canoes than i do so check out his listing at the newest and largest, i think its the Hartford Area Adventures listing if you cant go sunday or i dont have a suitable boat for you..I only have one recreational boat, the rest are ocean boats at 18 feet long..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The put in location, THE PLACE WE MEET FIRST, unload etc..... &lt;br /&gt;is at the Giant Sickomoore tree in Simsbury CT,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use 20 Hartford Road (rte 185) Simsbury for a GPS, mapquest location &lt;br /&gt;The tree is at the traffic lighted intersection of Nod Road and rte 185 by taking a north entry into a small driveway that leads down to the river.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be going to Curtis Park as out take out point and picknic, rest, conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon towing the Kayak Trailer..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;End of the trip location and Picknick location: IF YOU ARE GOING TO THE PICKANICK DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;from hartford direction: &lt;br /&gt;91 north to exit 36, &lt;br /&gt;Take left (west direction) on to 178 (park ave) toward bloomfield for 1.6 miles. &lt;br /&gt;At intersection take right onto 187 (north direction) (blue hills ave) for about 5 miles heading toward tariffville direction. &lt;br /&gt;You will meet rte 187/189, &lt;br /&gt;Stay on 189 to Tarriffville..at the end you will end up in tariffville, take a left at the light onto rte 315 (elm st) follow it to the end at the stop sign take the left into Tarrifville road (the street sign says Withrop, thats the raod to the right though)..continue on 315 for about 1.2 miles, take a right into Curtis Park (right side) and go to the river via the dirt road..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok if you use Mapquest, GPs or other..there is 2 Tariffville roads in the town and the numbers dont match right.... &lt;br /&gt;so just look at your map for Curtis Park..based the decriptors given above.. &lt;br /&gt;its near rte 315 and 202 intersection for a secondary land mark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks already reserved..&lt;br /&gt;Pungo 12 by Kathy G&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer by Lisa J.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Left is &lt;br /&gt;Tourlite 15..not for beginners, rolls very easy&lt;br /&gt;Cobra expidition 18, Fast SOT&lt;br /&gt;Greenlander Pro 18, fast but stable, 12.5 inch butt max..&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193152147000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192816667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Last Fall Paddle of the year on the Farmington River and Pot Luck Meal</name><id>6580566</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192978800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6580566/</event_url></item>