<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be meeting again this month, having enjoyed ourselves so much on the first. The meeting place is yet to be determined, but we are aiming for the Coolidge Corner area. The Starbucks listed below will be our default meeting place, but I will send out an email with confirmation of the meeting place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On December first we met (6 of us) at the Trident, and had a wonderful first gathering. We have decided to do some homework for our next meeting (details below) but feel free to come even if you don't get a chance to read up. We would love to have more of you join in. At the last meeting we determined that Tuesdays and Thursdays are other possible meeting days for us, so again, if you want to attend but have a strong preference regarding day/time, please do let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am also trying to compile a list of everyone's email and phone number. If you wish to be included (it will be shared information) please send me your data.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to the evolution of this group, and can't wait to meet again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s. if you have a digital camera, think about brining it to our next meting, so we can get some pictures of the group up on our website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please rsvp even if you are not going to make it...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Homework: the essay in Eye of Spirit on literary criticism (2 chapters)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole Trudel Churchill</member_name><member_id>3348175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1101955855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Ken Wilber Group December Meetup</name><id>3796302</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1103155200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/3796302/</event_url></item>