<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Memorial Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.364303</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Esplanade</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>701442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116057</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want some FREE ZUMBA&lt;/strong&gt;® &lt;strong&gt;with Zumba with Jess?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join her at Fiedler's Field on the Esplanade on JUNE 17TH (FATHER'S DAY) -- class starts at 3:30 PM -- below are details on all the activities available. If you can't make it for this Sunday, save the date for the next Sunday Fun in the Park on September 9th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday Fun in the Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday is a day of rest, but it doesn’t mean you have to. Have a little fun! Sunday Fun in the Park is a community day promoting healthy living and sense of place. Though geared towards youth and families, there are a variety of activities for all ages, from music and fishing to yoga and arts &amp;amp; crafts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All Sunday Fun in the Park activities are free and open to the public. Activities run from 2:00–4:00pm and are located at the Fiedler Field, near the Hatch Shell and the Fiedler Footbridge. &lt;a href="http://www.esplanadeassociation.org/about-the-park/getting-there/"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for directions. We hope you come out to soak up the sun and enjoy a free community day on us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are two Sunday Fun in the Park days this summer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 17th (Father’s Day)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 9th&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Schedule June 17th&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:00-4:00pm -&lt;/strong&gt; Parkland Games with &lt;a href="http://knucklebones.us"&gt;Knucklebones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;We’re here to have fun so let’s play some games! Knucklebones, a recreational programming company dedicated to inspiring athletics for all ages for the love of play, will be providing a variety of games geared towards every age group. Whether you want to try hoola hooping, playing volleyball, bouncing on blow-up animals, or winning at corn hole, Knucklebones has games for all ages and welcomes you to get out there and have some fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:00-4:00pm -&lt;/strong&gt; Fishing off the Docks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;Reel ‘em in! As a part of our Sunday Fun in the Park program TEA offers kids a chance to catch as many as they can off of the River Dock. Grab a rod and try your hand at nabbing a big one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:00-4:00pm -&lt;/strong&gt; Arts &amp;amp; Crafts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;Offering fun arts activities to youth of all ages. Make some thing for Dad for Father’s Day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:00-3:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; – Family Fun Yoga with &lt;a href="http://barebonesyoga.com/"&gt;Bare Bones Yoga&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;Kids and parents alike can participate in this great program that includes yoga-inspired games and poses to encourage a healthy and active lifestyle. Karen Fabian, founder of Bare Bones Yoga, incorporates different techniques to ensure that all can take part and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:30-4:00pm&lt;/strong&gt; – &lt;a href="http://www.shapeuppersonaltraining.com/page.asp?ID=37"&gt;Zumba with Jess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;Zumba® combines high energy and motivating music with unique moves and combinations that allow you to dance away your stress while you get fit. Zumba ® is based on the principle that &lt;em&gt;exercise should be FUN and EASY to do&lt;/em&gt;. Anyone can Zumba!  It’s a “feel happy” workout that is great for your body and mind.  Join Zumba with Jess at Sunday Fun in the Park as she holds a class geared to both adults &amp;amp; kids alike — it will give you a nice sampling of what to expect at a Zumba® class.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria</member_name><member_id>10004360</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340030266000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Zumba Dudes and Divas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>zumba-cambridge-com</urlname><id>1476579</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Zumba® with Jess in Union Square</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339069324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ZwJ on the Esplanade - FREE ZUMBA</name><id>68139632</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>1800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339961400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/zumba-cambridge-com/events/68139632/</event_url></item>