<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>337 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.560995</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-343-8850</phone><name>Public Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Middletown</city><id>930443</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.650093</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As for our first April meeting, I was thinking about the topic being &amp;quot;Finding the Light.&amp;quot; We will focus our discussion and techniques around ideas of finding great quality lighting and how it affects your photographs.   We will do a mini safari around town, (probably in smaller groups lead by professionals) searching out great spots of lighting wherever we turn. Hopefully we can answer some questions like, What is good light vs bad light and how does it affect your photos?  What do you do if the light is bad?  How can work around that.  Where can I find the best light?  We will probably walk a few blocks after our discussion at Public, and apply some of the techniques and tricks we learn.  Since there are some great opportunities in and around Main Street in Middletown, we will keep the group centered around there.  We won't really be able to use Wesleyan for anything this time around as they are having an &amp;quot;event&amp;quot; this weekend and lots of security, and people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As of today, (April 13th)  I confirmed a new meeting space due to the size of this group.  Initially we thought of having a quick gathering outside on the grass on the town green, but our size now requires a permit and we can't get one for this day, due to Wesleyan's &amp;quot;event&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So our new agenda is to have a &amp;quot;Professionals Only&amp;quot; pre-meeting at 1pm at &lt;a href="http://www.harbor-park.com/directions.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;Harbor Park.&lt;/a&gt;  (The grass park next to the restaurant)) then head over to our &lt;b&gt;official meeting at 2pm&lt;/b&gt; at &lt;a href="http://publicct.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Public Restaurant and Bar&lt;/a&gt;.   377 Main Street, Middletown, CT 06457.   Our discussion will probably be about an hour or so then we will spend another hour walking around Main Street practicing our techniques.   At 4pm we will be headed back to Public for drinks and food as a &amp;quot;thank you&amp;quot; for them letting us use their space.   All are encouraged to patronize Public for their generous use of their side room for this meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the official meeting/discussion there won't be any food or beverage service in the restaurant as they aren't open at that time.  The open at 4pm, for when we return. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone!  Bring your cameras!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for all the people with cameras...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerome Braga</member_name><member_id>8713251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>27</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248477744000</updated><rating><average>4.65000009537</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>shootout</urlname><id>1362724</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Connecticut Photography Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232742895000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Inaugural Meetup and Shootout</name><id>9587380</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240164000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/shootout/events/9587380/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/1/6/global_7013142.jpeg</photo_url></item>