<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 East Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01585</zip><lat>42.236007</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 867-3409</phone><name>The Holistic Center, Inc.</name><city>West Brookfield</city><id>820419</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.136570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us for a spiritual afternoon at The Holistic Health Center in West Brookfield withKeith. &lt;br /&gt;He will be giving us a tour of his wonderful center, and people will have an opportunity to purchase various items he has for sale, and learn about the services he offers. He will then give us a talk on auras, the chakras, and energy, and then lead us through a guided chakra meditation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People can then have their aura photographed and receive a reading. with two packages offered:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A (4) page reading, and full body aura photo for $20.00&lt;br /&gt;or &lt;br /&gt;a (22) page reading and  (2) aura photos, one of the head, and one of the entire body &lt;br /&gt;for $35.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meet up will run for (6) hours, from 10:30- 5:00, and sign ups will be in 2- hour intervals, &lt;br /&gt;with a tour, talk and meditation at the beginning of each session. While people are waiting for their readings, we will be having an open pagan-spiritual chat upstairs in the center, with tea and cookiesavailable. We will also be running the Celestine Prophecy Movie, and a movie on Indigo Children and other spiritual &amp;quot;shorts&amp;quot; Times to be posted soon. Please note that there is only room for about&lt;br /&gt;(12) people at a time upstairs, which is why we are doing it in 2 hour intervals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People who are there during lunchtime and would like to go for a bite to eat will be going to &lt;br /&gt;the Clambox, down the street,  which serves a wide variety of seafood, hamburgers, hot dogs, and sandwiches of all kinds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A sign up sheet will be posted on the list a couple of weeks prior to the meet up.&lt;br /&gt;Please note, that once you sign up for a time, you are making a commitment to show up for the meet-up, as this is an appointment just as any other appointment you would make for a psychic reading. There are only (23) openings, so if you rsvp &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; please plan on attending! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please continue to check email list for updated information, and if the meet up is cancelled due to snow- The snow date will be the following Sunday, January 25th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please park out front on the main road, and walk around the back, and come up the back stairway.&lt;br /&gt;Please remove your shoes before entering, as the upstairs is sacred space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out The Holistic Center's website at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.TheHolisticCenter.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.TheHolisti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park in front on the road, go around to the back &amp; come up back stairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232815556000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227474394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Aura Photo/ Reading Party</name><id>9218361</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232204400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/9218361/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/f/global_3694063.jpeg</photo_url></item>