<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you missed our event at the Gallery last week and last month, you have another chance to eat/drink/dance at this Singles Party!  Here you can mingle in the crowd (much larger than Gallery), but yet feel safe with familiar faces (we'll have a reserved table to hide out at).  Going to a singles dance with your friends is a bonus and much appreciated by our last group in January.  Not so threatening for those of you who are on the shy side! Our group is very friendly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;U.S.S. Chowder Pot IV&lt;br /&gt;165 Brainard Rd&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Nite, February 23, 2007&lt;br /&gt;Time:  8 pm - 12:30 am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner Buffet 8 - 9:30 pm, coffee/dessert at 11:30 pm, dancing to DJ's Top 40/Soft Rock, dress to impress/no jeans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$17, pay at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have a reserved table(s) with champagne.  Look for our table with the Meetup sign.  Meet me there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP no later than Feb 21st.  You can bring guests.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Springfield and Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;I 91 S to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd).  Left off exit onto Airport Rd.  Go to end of road and turn right at lite onto Brainard Rd.  Go thru one traffic lite.  Chowder Pot is on right.  Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Manchester/Vernon/Sturbridge, MA:&lt;br /&gt;I 84 W to Charter Oak Bridge exit.  Go over bridge and take second exit (exit 87, Brainard Rd).  Go right off exit.  Chowder Pot is on right.  Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Danbury and Points West:&lt;br /&gt;I 84 E to I 91 S to exit 27 (Brainard Rd).  Turn left off exit onto Airport Rd.  Go to end of road and turn right at lite onto Brainard Rd.   Go through one taffic lite.  Chowder Pot in on right.  Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from New Haven:  I 91 N to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd)  Turn right off exit.  Chowder Pot is on right.  Please use ballroom entrance.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1172452147000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169555625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Eat/Drink/Dance Night- Chowder Pot</name><id>5417531</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1172278800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5417531/</event_url></item>