<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Paris-Boston Link: Building the Future in Life Sciences Reception&lt;br /&gt;When:              Thursday, October 21, from 6:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             One Broadway, 4th Floor&lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge, MA 02142&lt;br /&gt;RSVP to:         cafe@hubtech21.com &lt;br /&gt;In the last year, the Paris region has engaged in an unprecedented initiative to foster innovation and growth for small companies who want to tap into the no. 1 life sciences market in Europe. Come and meet with future business partners, learn about a wealth of opportunities available to you to help you succeed in one of the largest life sciences markets in the world. The organizations to be represented include the following:&lt;br /&gt;-Medicen, as the premier European cluster dedicated to therapeutic innovation, is ideally positioned to support companies engaged in translational medicine, biologics and bio IT.  Medicen is composed of over 180 companies and research institutes. Its mission is to boost, federate, promote and enhance networking locally and internationally. &lt;br /&gt;-ARD (Paris Region Economic Development Agency), is a non-profit organization dedicated to international companies that plan to expand their business activities on the Paris Region market. ARD mission is to drive economic growth in the Paris Region as well as to promote Paris and the Paris Region internationally as a prime European business location.&lt;br /&gt;-AEE (Essonne Development Agency), is gateway for investment and international development projects. AEE assists companies to expand in south Paris. It supports companies with business location, partnerships and growth. It is pro-active especially in companies in the biotechnology sector, optics/optronics, research and development.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287702943000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287449741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paris-Boston Link: Building the Future in Life Sciences Reception</name><id>15153494</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287698400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15153494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>