<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello PP2012 People!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So-- I'm part of a group in Boston called the Boston Artists Group, it's run by an old meetup member named Jeff Haynes. He was approached by Google recently and they have offered to give his group some special training on all the new google offerings. Including Google Plus and Google Hangouts. In exchange for learning all that google has to offer they are hoping artists will find creative ways to use these tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I am part of this group, we have meet with google already, and I am pleased with what they have said so far. I am also very open to learning any new ways I can to promote myself as a photographer so I am very interested in attending this training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the rub. It's Monday Night, May 21st from 6pm to 9pm. So I have decided to cancel this months goal group and invite you all to come to Cambridge and attend this Google meeting with us. There is space for about 20 people at the moment. So if you are interested, you should immediately got to this link and sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/redirect?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs%2Egoogle%2Ecom%2Fa%2Fgoogle%2Ecom%2Fspreadsheet%2Fviewform%3Fformkey%3DdDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRmc6MQ&amp;amp;urlhash=iaZa&amp;amp;_t=tracking_anet" target="_blank"&gt;https://docs.google.com/a/google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/redirect?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs%2Egoogle%2Ecom%2Fa%2Fgoogle%2Ecom%2Fspreadsheet%2Fviewform%3Fformkey%3DdDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRmc6MQ&amp;amp;urlhash=iaZa&amp;amp;_t=tracking_anet" target="_blank"&gt;c6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/redirect?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs%2Egoogle%2Ecom%2Fa%2Fgoogle%2Ecom%2Fspreadsheet%2Fviewform%3Fformkey%3DdDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRmc6MQ&amp;amp;urlhash=iaZa&amp;amp;_t=tracking_anet" target="_blank"&gt;MQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can not attend or have no interest in attending- I am planning on having a "sub meeting" to this next weeks meetup on Thursday May 31st to do a check in with all Goal Meeting Members. So we will still get a full 12 months of meetings. If you can please attend this meeting instead of Monday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Free, fun seminar - Boston Artists &amp;amp; Google+ 
&lt;p&gt;Google is inviting you -- us, the Boston Artists group -- to come over to their Cambridge campus for a free seminar on using their Google+ tools and learn how to increase our exposure.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I don't send many direct emails to the BA members, but when a company, positioned as Google is, offers a hand in helping increase our exposure... well, that strikes me as something most artists would be interested in.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

But take note, even though there are 450+ people in this group, the attendance is capped at 75. So please click through on the link to register if you want to go. (Again, this is all free) Depending on the response, they may do another program later.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/redirect?url=https%3A%2F%2Fdocs%2Egoogle%2Ecom%2Fa%2Fgoogle%2Ecom%2Fspreadsheet%2Fviewform%3Fformkey%3DdDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRmc6MQ&amp;amp;urlhash=iaZa&amp;amp;_t=tracking_anet"&gt;https://docs.google.com/a/google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dDhDMl9aamNGajdCaE02ay1NVXBmRmc6MQ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The program is Monday evening, May 21 from 6-8 at 5 Cambridge Center, which is right off the Red Line's Kendall/MIT stop. Google will have someone there to greet people as they come in. Light snacks are planned.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I encourage you to take advantage of this; bring along your laptop if you want. Having seen what they're doing now, and what they're planning, I clearly see the value in this for the local creative community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Jeff Haynes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk in the room to the right as you enter from the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337698140000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329242683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meeting Change!! for Photography Projects for 2012</name><id>dpglncyqhbcc</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337636700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/52322152/</event_url></item>