<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Daniel Shays Highway (Rt 202)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01355</zip><lat>42.556288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 29</name><city>New Salem</city><id>887032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.289561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for this approximately 8 mile moderate loop hike with a diversion to the summit of Rattlesnake Hill. AMC Hike Leader Dan Bolton will be co-leading this hike with me. He has been to Rattlesnake Hill Summit and I have done the gorgeous loop hike where the ledges are. &lt;strong&gt;Parking is limited and we don't want to take up all of it so we will also be parking directly across from rt 202 on a side street called Elm Street.&lt;/strong&gt; We chose this gate to hike in from because of the good parking situation and good central easy to find location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Please read the details of this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Micro-spikes or other stabilizers are required for this hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please dress in layers (no cotton) and bring adequate food and water for this hike. Approximate time: 3-4 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northquabbinwoods.org/entries/205" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northquabb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photo: Quabbin Gate 29 Photo: Quabbin Gate 29&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Gates 28-30 Petersham Road (Rte. 122), New Salem, MA Biking on paved trails. Hiking loop trails to other gates. Historical sites, birdwatching, and views of the Quabbin. No pets, please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description: Gates 29 and 30 both end up on the same paved road, but Gate 30 also crosses the lovely, stone-arched Keystone Bridge, built by hand in 1866 to span the Middle Branch of the Swift River. From the bridge a fisherman&amp;rsquo;s trail leads east along the river to the Quabbin Reservoir. Along the approximately 2&amp;amp;frac12;-mile main trail are many cellar holes, echoes of the lost section of New Salem, and varied habitats&amp;mdash;woodland, edge, and open field&amp;mdash;leading to the shores of the Quabbin. One side trails allows a loop hike that exits at Gate 28, with the last leg along Rte. 122; another connects with Gate 27 near New Salem center; and a third makes a steep climb up Rattlesnake Hill to a magnificent view of the reservoir. Consult a map or guidebook for details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: From Rte. 2, take Exit 16 and go south on Rte. 202. You'll pass the intersection of Rte. 122 &lt;strong&gt;Gate 29 is a short way further south on Rte. 202, on the left. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Bolton</member_name><member_id>11623335</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330280452000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329339872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Gate 29 Hike/ Rattlesnake Hill Summit</name><id>52493432</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330182000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/52493432/</event_url></item>