<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>62 Harvard Street (rear)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.332803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-232-7440</phone><name>Benefitness Health Club for Women</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1186489</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/4/4/event_209116452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Two Brookline Businesses Team Up For an Evening of Poses and Sips &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Benefitness Health Club and the Wine Gallery are inviting members and the public to Yoga * Wine * Cheese event on Friday, March 15th, 2013. Starting at 730pm, an all-levels yoga class will be taught by certified yoga instructors Laura Newbold and George Rhoades at Benefitness Health Club, located at 62 Harvard Street, Brookline MA 02445. The hour class will be done to music in the main studio. At 830pm, participants will enjoy wine and cheese presented by the Wine Gallery of Brookline. Rene Little, Fine Wine Consultant of the Wine Gallery will conduct the wine tasting, explaining the grapes and regions of each wine.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Relax with Yoga * Wine * Cheese. Invite your friends, loved ones (guys are welcomed) for an evening of yoga poses followed by sipping and noshing of wines and cheeses. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

$10 per person. Advanced purchase by 3.12.13. Space is limited. Please call Benefitness Health Club at 617-232-7440 to reserve your spot and for additional information. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

About Benefitness Health Club: Benefitness is an all women's health club located in Brookline Village. The club has been serving Brookline women for over three decades. Since 1980 the club has attracted a loyal membership – women of all ages with a variety of fitness goals and health needs. Just the right size, the club is large enough to provide all the equipment and facilities needed, yet intimate enough to provide personalized services and attention. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

About The Wine Gallery: The Wine Gallery is a boutique store offering wines, beers and exotic spirits. Located at 3 Cypress Street in Brookline, MA 02445, the wine gallery offers educational classes and wine tastings. 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>MBTA: Take the Green Line D Train to Brookline Village stop or Green Line C Train to Coolidge Corner stop.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol O'Connor</member_name><member_id>9130755</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363645758000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361928093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening of Sips and Poses</name><id>106599472</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363390200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/106599472/</event_url></item>