<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate but hilly, 4 miles estimated. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Meet time:&lt;/strong&gt; 10:45am (Will leave before 11, to lead you to Gate 15. Please do not park directly in front of Gate, but pull to the side.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Hike time:&lt;/strong&gt; 11am&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/3/0/event_79166672.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralph has done this hike before, and there are some long, lovely views down the West Branch of the Reservoir! This is one of those hikes with two locations where old roads go into the Quabbin. The second is on a nice bump-out affording us those long views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be cold, so dress warmly. Bring a drink, maybe a snack. (Not sure if we'll want to stop for lunch, depends on weather, and the hike isn't long.) Bug repellant is highly recommended...if there is some cool spot where you are tempted to detour off-road through the brush, ticks are still out in full force. Where there's deer, there's ticks! (The roads themselves aren't a problem, as they are well-used by park vehicles.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is on old dirt roads through the woods. As for the reservoir, to quote an earlier description, "Quabbin Reservoir is, in surface area, the second-largest man-made body of water in the world. It provides drinking water for the Boston area, and is home to bald eagles, moose, bears, foxes, deer, wild turkeys, and more. It is spectacular, with old roads, natural beaches, and crystal-clear water!" (We did see a bald eagle flying overhead on the Dana Common hike last week!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from North-Central or Northwest Mass:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Northeast or Northwest, take Route 2 or 122 to New Salem. Turn South on Route 202. The Pelham Historical Society is about 10 miles on the southbound side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the East or West:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 to Belchertown, and turn North on Route 202. The Pelham Historical Society is about 7.5 miles on the southbound side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from the South:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the nearest road North to Route 9 and follow directions "from the East or West."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Walking is on old roads (mostly dirt), no special equipment needed. It will be chilly Monday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No pets, swimming, or wading. (Quabbin Reservoir is a drinking water supply.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry in, carry out." Take your trash home with you. (Same reason.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll lead the group to Gate 15 from here! Historical Society is in the old white church on the corner of Amherst Rd and Rt 202 (Daniel Shays Hwy).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323954019000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323387069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Hike: Quabbin Reservoir Gate 15</name><id>43875622</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323877500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/43875622/</event_url></item>