<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event has been cancelled by the author.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REBECCA M. JORDAN-YOUNG &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;discusses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brain Storm&lt;br /&gt;The Flaws in the Science of Sex Differences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;:::&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is delighted to welcome sociomedical scientist REBECCA M. JORDAN-YOUNG, an expert in the biological components of sex, gender, and sexuality, for a conversation about her new book, Brain Storm: The Flaws in the Sciences of Sex Differences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Female and male brains are different, thanks to hormones coursing through the brain before birth. That’s taught as fact in psychology textbooks, academic journals, and bestselling books. And these hardwired differences explain everything from sexual orientation to gender identity, to why there aren’t more women physicists or more stay-at-home dads. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this new book, Jordan-Young takes on the evidence that sex differences are hardwired into the brain. Analyzing virtually all published research that supports the claims of “human brain organization theory,” Jordan-Young reveals how often these studies fail the standards of science. Even if careful researchers point out the limits of their own studies, other researchers and journalists can easily ignore them because brain organization theory just sounds so right. But if a series of methodological weaknesses, questionable assumptions, inconsistent definitions, and enormous gaps between ambiguous findings and grand conclusions have accumulated through the years, then science isn’t scientific at all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, September 24th, 3:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285359598000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281643441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science of Sex Differences - Cancelled.</name><id>14404911</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285354800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/14404911/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/3/global_15836403.jpeg</photo_url></item>