<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Talbot Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.404760</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tufts University Granoff Music Center</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1421722</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"NBC Nightly News" anchor and managing editor Brian Williams will discuss political and election news coverage at the seventh annual Edward R. Murrow Forum on Issues in Journalism at Tufts University on Monday, April 23, at 12 p.m. The forum, which is free and open to the public, will take place in the Distler Performance Hall at the Granoff Music Center on Tufts University's Medford/Somerville campus. Members of the news media who would like to reserve a seat and media credentials should contact Katie Cinnamond at 617-627-4703. Williams has become the most highly decorated evening news anchor of the modern era and is seen by more U.S. television viewers on a daily basis than any other individual. In addition to serving over seven years as anchor of the "NBC Nightly News," Williams recently launched "Rock Center with Brian Williams," NBC's first new primetime newsmagazine in nearly two decades. He has received 11 Edward R. Murrow Awards, 12 Emmy Awards, the DuPont-Columbia University Award, the Water Cronkite Award for Excellence in Journalism and the industry's highest honor, the George Foster Peabody Award. In 2007, TIME named him one of the 100 most influential people in the world. Williams will be interviewed by Jonathan Tisch, co-chair of the board of Loews Corporation and chairman of Loews Hotels. Tisch is a graduate of Tufts and host of the Emmy-nominated and Gracie-award winning one-on-one interview show "Beyond the Boardroom with Jonathan Tisch." The Edward R. Murrow Forum on Issues in Journalism at Tufts is inspired by legendary broadcaster Edward. R. Murrow for his many contributions to journalism and public diplomacy. The forum brings together interdisciplinary panels to reflect on Murrow&amp;rsquo;s legacy and relate it to contemporary issues in journalism. The forum is sponsored by Tufts University's Communications and Media Studies Program at the School of Arts and Sciences, the Edward R. Murrow Center of Public Diplomacy at The Fletcher School, and the Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service. Previous featured speakers at the Murrow Forum include Katie Couric, Ted Koppel, Tom Brokaw, Dan Rather and Chris Matthews.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335202140000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329969675000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edward R. Murrow Forum: Brian Williams, Anchor NBC Nightly News</name><id>53442582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335196800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/53442582/</event_url></item>