<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>~~&gt;Pull way in on grass, almost to water</address_2><address_1>50 River Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.902190</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Strawberry"s  Park (Kayak Put In)</name><city>Windsor</city><id>626791</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.678420</lon></venue><fee><label>Kayak Rental Donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per Kayak Rented</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok i had a few options on my list and goal for paddling,&lt;br /&gt;again everything is weather Dependant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This section of river was planned for a future event and Mansfield hollow was to be the next location,&lt;br /&gt;in seeing the weather report:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 76. West wind between 5 and 13 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;it almost could be a good Mansfield hollow event except for the possible wind, i promised and didnt ever want to bring you on open water where the surface over a long distance was subjected to wind above 10 mph.. it looks like is not that bad but last year this portion of water was actually wavy and cold even in the center of summer...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I have decided to stay local and do a short paddle this Sunday,&lt;br /&gt;next weekend, I dont know yet..ya just have to wait and see..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok getting to Strawberry Park, the put in and meeting place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;take I 91 North to exit # 38,&lt;br /&gt;This is the exit for rte 75.&lt;br /&gt;Take a right off of the exit and go North on rte 75 toward Bradley Airport Direction,&lt;br /&gt;go 2.25 miles, cross the river bridge and the first right is RIVER STREET, go apx 1,000 feet and the Park entrance is on the right..go into the drive way around the little circle, we will be unloading in the grass a bit further into the park nearer the river..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A FEW OF US WILL BE GOING UPSTREAM TO ANOTHER PUT IN ON NILES ROAD ( jOHN wELCH pARK)... MAYBE ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our take out point is behind BARTS Drive In restaurant in the boat ramp area.&lt;br /&gt;This is where we can do a simple Barbie-Q and also get stuff to eat from BARTS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok getting from Strawberry Park to Barts, &lt;br /&gt;Leave the park, take a left onto River Street, a left onto rte 75, head toward 91, go under 91 stay on 75 for another 1.25 miles and take a left onto Pleasant Street,  (Barts is on the corner of Pleasant and Palisado)&lt;br /&gt;Barts is on the left a short ways after you go under the rail bridge underpass, pull into the boat ramp lot and we will go back to Strawberry and Welch Parks with just a few cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember these directions....LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok bring some food, and other stuff for a short boat trip and get together after..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;available Kayaks are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;x&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub= Pungo 12'= Kim's Guest&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-r&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', includes Paddle Pants= ALex&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= Manny or Guest&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenland= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= ? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Hotub= Canoe 18' this one can hold 3 people pretty easily..maybe more..= Denna and Mom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa J will have her kayak loaded on trailer too...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have enough safety equipment and paddles for the above boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK if you know which kayak fits your paddling style and know its characteristics say so in your comments..&lt;br /&gt;I can only rent kayaks to full yes RSVP's..(limited carry capacity and none can be left on the trailer)..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok see you there if you can make it..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BACK UP PLAN ~~&amp;gt;IF THERE IS NO DAM RELEASE WE GO TO RAINBOW RES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;extra stuff..&lt;br /&gt;PUT-IN : Access Point 30, River Street Boat Launch, Windsor, CT&lt;br /&gt;Directions : From Rt. 20, take Rt. 75 to the Poquonock section of Windsor. In the center of Poquonock at the traffic light, turn left onto River Street. Follow River Street for approximately .3 mile. Turn right into Strawberry Hills Park. During periods of low water, this area can be &amp;quot;scratchy.&amp;quot; Better launching times may be around 12:00 p.m. when water is typically released from the reservoir. NOTE: If you wish to run the rapids: In Poquonock, turn right onto Niles Road and continue to Welch Park. At the back of this town park there is a difficult carry to access the river and no formal boat launch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INTERMITTENT ACCESS POINTS&lt;br /&gt;Access Point 31, Pleasant Street Park, Windsor, CT This asphalt launch ramp is behind Bart?s on Rt. 159, located one mile north from jct. Rt. 75/305/159 in the center of Windsor. Note: Put in here only after 12:00 p.m. Due to the release from the hydro facility upstream, there typically is not enough water to boat here before noon.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have the Blue Toyota Avalon with kayak trailer and look for the Traffic ORANGE CONES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212509287000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><why>You need the excersize.</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212161076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayak The Farmington River, Strawberry Park to BARTS</name><id>8042489</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212336000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/8042489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/global_474104.jpeg</photo_url></item>