<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.azoreanrestaurant.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.azoreanrestaurant.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

There's parking across the street from the restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;

When owner Deo Braga opened the Azorean Restaurant &amp;amp; Bar, he was determined to bring the distinctive cuisine and warm ambience of his native Azores to New England's Cape Ann.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He began by recreating the look and feel of these beautiful Portuguese islands. The decor features exquisitely hand-crafted tiles and artwork specially selected and imported from Portugal. Interior colors capture the rich gold of the Azorean sun and the cool blues of the surrounding Atlantic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The atmosphere is casual and conducive to conversation, with the dining room offering both tables and booths, and a full bar that welcomes you with creatively mixed cocktails, wine, bottled beer, beer on tap, bar menu including tapas, and convenient patio access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An impressive wine cellar stores an amazing collection of Portuguese and American wines, and makes available several selections by the glass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, Head Chef and General Manager Manny Lapa, also a Portuguese native, ensures that the food is authentic, high-quality and Azorean-style generous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conveniently located, surprisingly affordable, always comfortable, the Azorean is suitable for special occasions or simply an impromptu meal out.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Donna!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna</member_name><member_id>8804826</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338315822000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>travel-575</urlname><id>418980</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Old and Not so Old Ladies Travel</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334591238000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lunch at Azorean Restaurant, Gloucester</name><id>60789282</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338053400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/travel-575/events/60789282/</event_url></item>