<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>FYI:&lt;br /&gt;i just copy and paste this stuff it is up to you and me to tailor a message for this event.  i suggest leafleting, banners and your input.  &lt;br /&gt;-mark&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Tuesday, November 11, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop Suppression of Free Speech/End the Wars and Occupation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Veterans Day 2007, 15 veterans and 3 supporters were arrested on City Hall Plaza for protesting the silencing of their messages of peace by the American Legion, who runs the Veterans Day events. The charges were later dismissed. The American Legion does not allow members of Veterans For Peace to speak, but only allows pro-war and pro-Bush speeches. We want to march as we please and have a speaker for peace on City Hall Plaza, where hundreds of inner city JROTC students assemble. The City of Boston refuses to run the parade fairly themselves but outsources it to the American Legion, so they are complicit with the Legion in denying us a voice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will march behind the street sweepers once again, with our signs and chants. And we invite you to join us and march behind us on Veterans Day, supporting our messages of peace, ending endless wars and occupations, and stopping the suppression of our free speech by the America Legion and the City of Bsoton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12PM (Parade kicks off at 1PM)&lt;br /&gt;Boston Common at Beacon and Charles St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, call 781-643-3307 or email info@smedleyvfp.org or visit htty://smedleyvfp.org.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226620019000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225000151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11 Truth @ Veterans Day Parade</name><id>9032844</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226422800000</time><rsvp_limit>53</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/9032844/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>