<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Atlantic Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.356689</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston South Station</name><city>Boston</city><id>7048912</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;New England Patriots&lt;/span&gt; vs. &lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;Arizona Cardinal’s&lt;/span&gt; 1:00 game at Gillette Stadium.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Have you ever wanted to go check out Patriot's Place?  Well let's head on down and be AT the game when the Patriot’s play against the Cardinal’s…. There are plenty of places to watch the game, either on the HUGE TV or at any of the restaurants or if you don't want to watch the game, there is soooooo much to do there, so let’s go join in and watch the game on the HUGE TV,  shop, dine, people watch.  We can stay together or separate and explore on our own, just make sure you are back in time for the train, see all the information below!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This will be a long day and there is a lot of info below about the day, make sure you read it all so you are prepared for what the day.  If you are NOT leaving from South Station, make sure you take the Meetup phone with you so that I can tell you which car we are in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see what time the train departs your location: &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/riding_the_t/patriots/"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/riding_the_t/patriots/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never been you will see that it is an awesome place to go, it’s a football stadium with an outside mall, movie theater, 5Wits adventure, The Hall which is an innovative and interactive, modern museum experience for all ages.  Stores such as Bass, Christmas Tree Shop, Bed Bath &amp;amp; Beyond, Old Navy, and now Trader Joe’s etc…...  Restaurant’s such as CBS Scene, Bar Louie, 5 Guys, Toby Keith’s, Dunkin Donuts etc….  Check out the link for a list of things to do at the stadium: &lt;span style="color : #00ccff"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.patriot-place.com/about.aspx"&gt;http://www.patriot-place.com/about.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also make sure you notice that there is a shuttle that can take you to the lower level stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TICKET for the train:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YOU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are responsible for getting your own ticket to get on the train, when you do come back to the site and let me know that you have yours so I know to be looking for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The good news:&lt;/strong&gt; The MBTA is pleased to once again offer Football Trains to Gillette Stadium in Foxboro for all New England Patriots home games. These special event trains will depart from South Station in Boston and from Providence Station in Providence, RI. Trains will depart 30 minutes after the completion of the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost round trip tickets: $15.00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regular Commuter Rail tickets, Monthly Passes, Employee Passes or any other fare media are not valid on these trains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changes in operation for the “Football Trains” will be in effect for the 2011/2012 season as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boston Train:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ticket Sales - Due to the continued popularity and increased ridership on the Boston to Foxboro train, the MBTA has increased the size of the train to provide maximum seating capacity.    This train will now be all “Reserved” seating ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South Station &amp;amp; Back Bay&lt;/strong&gt; - Tickets for the train will be available at South Station and Back Bay Station two weeks in advance of each game.  These tickets will be available until they are Sold Out or up to 15 minutes before the train′s scheduled departure from South Station and Back Bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;North Station&lt;/strong&gt; - Tickets will be available two weeks in advance of each game until the close of business on the day before the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dedham Corp&lt;/strong&gt; - Tickets to board the train at Dedham Corp may be purchased in advance at South Station, North Station and Back Bay.  Tickets will be available for purchase from the Ticket Van in the Dedham Corp parking lot on the day of a game. Ticket sales begin 1 hour prior to the scheduled departure time from Dedham Corp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capacity - For all Regular Season games there will be a capacity of 1,800 seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Norwood Central Trains WILL NOT STOP at Norwood Central.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;** BOSTON TRAIN PASSENGERS MUST PRESENT THEIR ROUND TRIP TICKET PRIOR TO BOARDING THE TRAIN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fans are reminded &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;NO personal items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; may be left on the trains during the game. As a security precaution, all trains will be subject to a search after arrival at Gillette Stadium. All personal items left on the train will be collected and discarded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.  Also don’t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to see you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you are taking the Newburyport train in I will meet you on the platform, if you are meeting at South Station I will be at the doors.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347817444000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347083787000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriot's Place to watch the game, shop, explore......</name><id>81429162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347805800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/81429162/</event_url></item>