<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Union Pl</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hot Tomato's</name><city>Hartford</city><id>5389332</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.681511</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The New Hot Tomato’s, located within the historic Union Station and in walking distance to all of Hartford’s major venues reopened in August 2010. And with a new name came a new look. An inviting and intimate feeling created by comfortable leather booths and walls accented with rich wood and natural stone. A delicately carved wrought iron rail gracefully highlights an open air kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple dining areas offer diverse dining experiences ranging from the casual, open air bar atmosphere to the cozy feel of the upper level dining areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two private rooms are available for special events and parties. The intimate Wine Room with its wall of wine and hundreds of tiny starlight’s accommodates up to 60 guests and the Great Room located in the historic Union Station easily hosts up to 500 guests for a fête in the style of The Great Gatsby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our sunny patio overlooking the wide sweeping grounds from the Capital and the Memorial Arch is the perfect place to “shred your stress” with a glass of wine or cocktail and good friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our contemporary menu features renditions of favorites (old and new) made from only the highest quality, freshest ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add a selection from our extensive global wine cellar with over 65 varieties of only the finest, carefully selected wines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The perfect wine, the perfect meal, the perfect place. The New Hot Tomato’s, come in and escape life for a while.....check the menu....&lt;a href="http://www.hottomatos.net/images/dinner%20menu%20web.pdf"&gt;http://www.hottomatos.net/images/dinner%20menu%20web.pdf&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>a warm welcome by chuck 860-729-4504  my email chuckles125@att.net</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chuck</member_name><member_id>11483387</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1359315242000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Smiling Happy Faces</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford</urlname><id>1498492</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Eat, Laugh, and Be Merry in West Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357152664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HOT TOMATO'S   JAN 26 2013 6:00 pm</name><id>97507922</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359241200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Eat-Laugh-and-Be-Merry-in-West-Hartford/events/97507922/</event_url></item>