<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Mill Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.132530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Waysmeet Center</name><city>Durham</city><id>1792391</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.928139</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Film &amp;amp; Food Night: "How to Boil a Frog"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Print ticket &lt;br /&gt;

 Export &lt;br /&gt;

 Share&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, February 10, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Waysmeet Center&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15 Mill Road, Durham, NH (map)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOW TO BOIL A FROG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to Boil a Frog is an eco-comedy that gives an overview of the Big Mess We're In - environment, energy, economic - and lays out a set of personal solutions that will make your life better and save civilization as a by-product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HTBAF chronicles Jon Cooksey's personal, three-year adventure as a filmmaker, activist and, above all, a father driven to make sure his daughter would have a future beyond living on a raft with the last polar bear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With its Everyman approach in the style of "Supersize Me", interviews with scientists, journalists and energy experts across North America, HTBAF takes the kind of information that makes most people want to jump off a bridge and makes it into entertainment that just might save your life, and everybody else's too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start with the film (starting on time - feel free to come early to get settled!), then have a potluck. Please bring a "potluck kit" - dish, bowl, cup, silverware, napkin - as well as your potluck contribution. We will be able to plug in crockpots, heat some items up, make hot water for tea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking on Sunday is easy there - go to UNH's C Lot, across Mill Rd from Waysmeet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be taking donations to cover costs for the event as all our films this year have required a screening license cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by the Greater Seacoast Permaculture Meetup Group &amp;amp; The United Campus Ministry to UNH&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boiester</member_name><member_id>8570902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360545296000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359910209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOVIE night in Durham NH </name><id>102798862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360533600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/102798862/</event_url></item>