<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday is looking very fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHVN&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 79. North wind around 6 mph becoming east. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sat...N winds 5 to 10 kt...becoming SE in the afternoon. Seas 1 ft or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip Details given out this time since its not the regular trip but one with more options for many.&lt;br /&gt;Its about &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;11 -12 miles total &lt;/span&gt;l  if you want to do the whole thing, so be prepared if you are going to J cove with us (water, self rescue..etc..).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smaller boats can stop around the closer islands and return..(Just like last time we were at CIP) etc or play in the river areas nearby or go to the Love Shack..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This trip includes Inner White Top, Lobster Rock, Outer White Top Big Indian and Goose Rocks islands if you have enough stamina on the return trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we pass the ancient Human Sacrifice site we will look for the floating head of Sachem in the water and drag it to Joshua cove (someone may want to pull it aboard, but legend says it will bite a hole right through your boat), we can put it on the end of a paddle thats stuck in the mud to help guard us as we have our lunch snack (I think it may like Brownies too) and get some energy for the return trip. Usually the wind will help push us back ??.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then its hearing the sizzle of fine food and the aroma of  the cooking with wine (or our famously known Bugg Juice) by a small fire before we head out for home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;11:30 am is chosen as a plan to avoid Middletown traffic. (so far its been NO traffic)&lt;br /&gt;Would like to start paddling by 12:00 Noon...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;List of available kayaks and who reserved is below near the bottom of the page, indicate which one fits you.&lt;br /&gt;First reserved , first choice....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POT LUCK BARBIE-Q AFTER THE EVENT ..specific time unknown..Obviously when we are done paddling- so bring your food, chairs, bug spray and BUGG JUICE..whatever. Pot Luck Barbie-q will be right at CIP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a gallon or so of fresh water to rinse off the salt water if it bothers you..&lt;br /&gt;if i have time i will make a solar heated 3 gallon shower, if not, its a 5 gallon solar water bottle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fire side time? defiantly the Gas Fired Fire Pit.. Pop up shelter too if too sunny..etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Tides for: Tides for Guilford Harbor: &lt;br /&gt;Sort of dosen't really matter this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Getting There Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford, take I- 91 south to exit 22s toward Middletown.&lt;br /&gt;Take exit #13 for rte 17 south.&lt;br /&gt;At end of exit take a left and head toward Durham.&lt;br /&gt;Once in Durham bear right at the 79 and 17 split then left onto &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;rte 77&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; at the 17 split,&lt;br /&gt;(You are taking the center route of the 3 way splits)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travel south on Route 77 for approximately 13 miles to the center of Guilford. &lt;br /&gt;Cross rte 1, go strait.&lt;br /&gt;Turn right onto Broad Street and then take a quick left onto Whitfield Street driving around the Guilford Town Green. &lt;br /&gt;Continue south on Whitfield Street for approximately 0.2 miles. &lt;br /&gt;Turn right onto Route 146 (Water Street) and travel approximately 1 mile. &lt;br /&gt;Turn a slight left onto Mulberry Point Road.  LOOK for BROWNS Boat Yard Signs at the bridge, follow them..&lt;br /&gt;Travel on Mulberry Point Road for approximately 0.5 miles. &lt;br /&gt;Turn LEFT onto Chaffinch Island Road.  (be careful since the sign is small etc). again look for Browns boat yard sign.&lt;br /&gt;Travel approximately 0.7 miles to the END of Chaffinch Island Road passing Browns where CIP will be located at the circle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS 400 Chaffinch Island Rd, Guilford, CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POOP HOUSE on site. AKA a place to get SH-T Faced if you look in the bottom. Bring sanitizing wipes if ya have em..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;xxxxxxx&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle &amp;amp; Leash,   Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dougnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any wide yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only bring the yaks that are confirmed by a yes and by persons i have some familiarity with..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybee's obviously can't reserve any yaks and if ya reserve one and don't show up ya won't ever get a second chance to again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry i don't like to leave un-attended yaks on the trailer. They get stolen too easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF USING MY YAKS YOU CANT LOOK LIKE A BONEHEADED BEGINNER AND STEP INTO THEM VIA THE FLOOR OR DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. Only Novices in cheap plastic boats do that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way and you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro and impress the others who don't know how. Or you may laugh at the ones that fall in who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: always get out parallel to shore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes and paddling  style, and tight fit adjusted...if you have your own please bring it..&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths and types of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some cheap ones for that.)-&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourtie Yak Pad optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer, Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with Novice and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR JILL's Guest ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro, Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;--RESERVED for AL-R---.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest and smallest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR MARY---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light (Modified), Yellow, Skeg Version.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR HELENA --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and larger cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED FOR JILL ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guillemot Night Heron&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with beginner/intermediate and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (45 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-------&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR KATE- --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see ya all there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for ORANGE STRIPED TRAFFIC CONES @ parking lot and ORANGE Hunting HAT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281046006000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280411685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAKING Saturday @ CIP &amp; looking for Sachems Head on water &amp; PotLuck Barbie-Q.</name><id>14251405</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280590200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14251405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/1/global_13936689.jpeg</photo_url></item>