<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AGENDA for JUNE 5th BostonLOA Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clearing the Way:  Allowing Allowing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're not manifesting what you want.  Or maybe you're scoring big on some desires and not others.  You think you're very clear of what you want and have paved the way for it, &lt;br /&gt;but why isn't it showing up?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 4 simple steps you can take to clarify your heart's desires and uncover hidden beliefs and intentions that block your fulfillment of them.  Deliberately clearing the way allows allowing what you want to come into your life more naturally. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clarityworker and Boston LOA member Kathryn Deputat presents these 4 steps, and guides us in using writing, inquiry and deep listening to untangle our thoughts, clear our obstacles, and access the focus, insight, and clear guidance within us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guided by the power of intention, we reveal the solutions that await beneath the dust of confusion, restoring enthusiasm and life direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us, plan on being actively engaged in learning and using these 4 steps with Kathryn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you very much, Kathryn, for your gift of time and facilitation at our June meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have amazingly abundant days!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chew-Hoong and Dave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Kathryn Deputat:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn is a writer, coach, and clarity consultant who has been reuniting people with their inspiration, passion, and authentic expressions?in their lives and/or in their writing?for more than 15 years. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A distinguished alumna of Wellesley College and a member of Phi Beta Kappa, Kathryn is founding owner of Claritywork.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She draws on highly attuned listening and intuitive gifts, and her techniques, rooted in the Goldberg writing method, combine her interest and training in psychology, Zen Buddhism, metaphysics, Emotional-Kinesthetic Psychotherapy, and vocal and visual improvisation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kathryn's poetry and articles have appeared in various publications, and she publishes regularly on LovesFreeway.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181342180000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>69</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178064528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction June Meetup</name><id>5730791</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181084400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/5730791/</event_url></item>