<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>South Boston</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.336075</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Island</name><city>Boston</city><id>252075</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.035835</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We&amp;quot;ll meet at Sullivan's food stand right next to the parking lot.  AFter the walk  we'll have lunch either at Sullivan's or head into South Boston to a restaurant.    Light rain is predicted so we will still meet unless there is a torrential downpour.  Call me with any questions  617-775-0045.  Castle Island, Pleasure Bay, M Street Beach &lt;br /&gt;and Carson Beach&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Castle Island  &lt;br /&gt;Day Boulevard, South Boston &lt;br /&gt;617-727-5290&lt;br /&gt;Open year-round&lt;br /&gt;Fort Independence, a pentagonal five-bastioned, granite fort built between 1834 and 1851, is the dominating feature of Castle Island. This 22-acre urban park is connected to the mainland by both pedestrian and vehicular causeways. Pleasure Bay, the M Street Beach and Carson Beach form a three mile segment of parkland and beach along the South Boston shoreline of Dorchester Bay. Carson Beach offers some beautiful views and great public amenities: a rehabilitated Mothers' Rest, public restrooms, exhibit space, first aid and lifeguard functions, while the outdoor courtyards allow space for passive recreation. Carson Beach also features a walkway which allows one to walk, bike, or run along the water's edge from Castle Island to the Kennedy Library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fort Independence and Castle Island are on the State and National Registers of Historic Places, and the fort is a National Historic Landmark. Fort Independence is open from Memorial Day to Columbus Day, hours vary. Fort tours are conducted by the Castle Island Association in the summer months and there is interpretive signage for self-guided tours. The principal program theme, the History of Castle Island, stresses the role of the fort in harbor defense. Please call the Harbor Region Office at (617) 727-5290 for information and school programming. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253980407000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250893458000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CASTLE ISLAND STROLL - CHESTNUT HILL WALKNG GROUP</name><id>11168378</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251036000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/11168378/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>