<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362095</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kendall Press</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1523815</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079887</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Here's your chance to learn first hand how the BIMM TUESDAY GROUP took the 30 day challenge and created a forum in which we can now hold panel discussions and talk TV live with a world wide audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Believe us - it scared the heck out of us the first time we tried it. Particularly with viewers dropping in from anywhere in the ineternet world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our October meeting will give you our takeaways and learning experiences. For those of you who watch the Oct 2nd broadcast- you'll have a chance to get a live-and-in-person debrief and answers to any questions we couldn't get to on air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also we will look to the group for best practice sharing for those of you who have implemented video and broadcast marketing and sales programs and lastly, we will save some time for people to choose up small working groups if you want to experiment with this in a guided format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always - we welcome newcomers and regulars and will provide one good takeaway that you can implement immediately in your own internet marketing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>12427891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351543752000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348780723000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn some fast tips in overcoming your fear of live broadcasting</name><id>84417682</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350511200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/84417682/</event_url></item>