<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>74 Main Street</address_2><address_1>Route 133</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01929</zip><lat>42.630001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 768-6320</phone><name>Periwinkle's Restaurant</name><city>Essex</city><id>367940</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.779999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>UPDATE - Essex River Cruise is sending a boat to pick us up. We will depart from Periwinkle's - UPDATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lettie's invited us to the North Shore for another loooooong meal with excursions.&lt;br /&gt;Lettie's put a lot of time and energy into arranging this amazing adventure, so please be certain you can join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lettie says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey ya'll, you are all cordially invited on another North Shore Adventure...&lt;br /&gt;I thought it would be wonderful to explore historic, beautiful, and quaint Essex.&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive by 11:15 AM for our 11:30 AM seating for lunch at Periwinkle's Restaurant, a place for GREAT waterside food...fresh native seafood specialties, fine wines and locally microbrewed beers. Since there will still be nice outdoorsy weather I thought we could sit out on the heated wrap-around deck which is right by the Essex River, so I suggest you dress in layers and have rain gear. Even if we sit inside there are still BEAUTIFUL views from every table. There is also a piano for anyone willing to delight us with their talent :-D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.periwinklesrestaurant.com/peri_menus_pg6.html" target="_blank"&gt;Periwinkle's Lunch Menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions from Boston S &amp;amp; W:&lt;br /&gt;Rt. 128 North take exit 15 Manchester/Essex, LEFT 3.2 miles to stop sign LEFT on to Rt. 133/Main St.  go about 0.4 mile and Periwinkles Restaurant is on the right hand side, parking available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All commuter rail riders will be chauffered at 11:15 AM from the Manchester-by-the-Sea station to Periwinkle's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA Link&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/uploadedFiles/Documents/Schedules_and_Maps/Commuter_Rail/newburyport_web.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Commuter Rail Schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a yum, yum delicious lunch we have a couple of options:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Essex River Cruise is sending the boat to us. We will board from Periwinkle's at 3:15 PM &amp;amp; set sail at 3:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $23 for adults $10 for children&lt;br /&gt;Experience up close the Choate Island film site of &amp;quot;The Crucible&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Witches of Eastwick&amp;quot; on a nearly two hour narrated cruise. Enjoy the spectacular beauty of New England's famous fall foliage at its peak.&lt;a href="http://www.essexcruises.com/narrated.html" target="_blank"&gt;Essex River Cruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Stroll along the streets of Essex from 5:30 PM until 6:00 PM visiting antique shops, and historical sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.essexshipbuildingmuseum.org/collections&amp;amp;research.html" target="_blank"&gt;Essex History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal.&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax as well as the appropriate cruise fee.  &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;***If you RSVP YES you MUSt add a comment whether you'll arrive via car or train with train number as well as if you'll join for the post meal cruise and or stroll .***&lt;br /&gt;If you choose to travel on the commuter rail from North Station on Sunday the trains are 2101 which leaves at 8:30 AM and arrives in Manchester-by-the-Sea at 9:19 AM and 2105 which leaves at 10:15 AM and arrives in Manchester-by-the-Sea at 11:05 AM.&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO after 11:30am Saturday October 20th, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.  &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me (Tonya) at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                   If do not contact me it will be counted as if you NO-SHOWED 3 times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.&lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed.&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199221767000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189741800000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Periwinkle's Lunch - Another North Shore Adventure With Lettie</name><id>6356586</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192980600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6356586/</event_url></item>