<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Mill St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.399824</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rock Meadow conservation area</name><city>Belmont</city><id>923083</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/5/3/2/event_200190002.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 2 hour walk through field and forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Owned by the town since 1969, Rock Meadow Conservation Area is located less than two minutes from Beaver Brook Reservation on Mill Street. The land is comprised of 70 acres of undulating meadows, wetlands, streams and woods. The state has designated the area as an important grassland and a natural habitat for plants and animals that have been forced from former farmland. Rock Meadow offers hiking, birding, biking, picnicking and wandering opportunities. The area is also the home of Belmont's community gardens. It resembles the meadows in the south of England.&lt;/span&gt; It is the home of Belmont's community gardens (Victory Gardens). Originally owned by McLean Hospital in 1895, a farm was created to provide food during WWII.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/c/f/4/event_201067412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;This is a picture of the sign for the Rock Meadow parking lot. On the other side of the street, about 150 feet away, is a similar sign for the Lone Tree parking lot. The Rock Meadow parking lot will get full, so some people will have to use the Lone Tree lot and walk over to Rock Meadow. The walk will begin from the Rock Meadow parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for the turn-off heading downhill to a small parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360521249000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359509617000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rock Meadow - Belmont</name><id>102060042</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359905400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/102060042/</event_url></item>