<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>TURBO-CHARGING THE LAW OF ATTRACTION WITH NLP &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are very delighted to have Marilou Seavey from North Carolina, an international facilitator of personal &amp;amp; professional change and a Master Trainer of NLP, as our special guest.  Marilou was introduced to us by Tom Maloney, a BostonLOA Meetup member. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Go to end of Agenda to read how working with Marilou has transformed Tom's life.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suppose you had an opportunity to redesign your life, from the deepest levels of your experience &amp;amp; reaching out to every aspect of day-to-day living what would stop you from doing so?   Isn't this what attracts you to the Law of Attraction?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP (NeuroLinguistic Programming) is the science of studying success, &amp;amp; then &amp;quot;reprogramming&amp;quot; the software of your mind to produce immediate &amp;amp; positive change in all areas of your life. Combining the thinking of LOA with NLP skills offers you the most powerful &amp;amp; practical tools available for changing limiting beliefs, behaviors, &amp;amp; for achieving rapid results in your personal, professional &amp;amp; spiritual development.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's an important question.  If you could literally transform your life (&amp;amp; the lives of others) with the skills you acquire from combining NLP with the LOA principles, is there any reason you wouldn't start immediately?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would there be any reason to postpone the improved relationships you would enjoy with your partner, family &amp;amp; friends?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would you dare hang on to the fears &amp;amp; concerns that currently limit you, for 1 day longer than you had to?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you could enjoy more success than you have ever known in your business or career, would you start today or in a few years from now?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the inevitable conclusion that the students of NLP have come to realize -- &amp;quot;Why Didn't I Do This Sooner&amp;quot;? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This evening offers students of LOA the opportunity to incorporate incredibly powerful NLP tools to their philosophy.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Marilou Seavey&lt;br /&gt;www.mindbridge.ccm&lt;br /&gt;1-800-307-9026 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilou Seavey facilitates personal &amp;amp; professional change worldwide. She assists people from all walks of life with the interior design of their lives -- redefining who they are &amp;amp; getting them on track and &amp;quot;on purpose.&amp;quot;  Her clients include Fortune 500 executives, small business owners, senior political advisors, entertainers &amp;amp; educators.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has a special ability to create an ideal atmosphere for growth whether she is working with individuals, seminar groups, company teams, or large audiences.  Marilou's passionate belief that she can help people free up something inside themselves - &amp;amp; that it is easier than they think - creates a personal connection with her audience.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Her work in the field of human potential, metaphysics &amp;amp; her study of NLP for over 25 years has formed the basis of her life's work.  For Marilou, NLP is partially the art of personal genius, part science &amp;amp; elegance based on the efficiency with which it can create change at any level. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Marilou is giving 2 different workshops on October 6,7 &amp;amp; 8 in Burlington, MA. For details, go to www.mindbridgetrainings.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston LOA Meetup members get a further 10% discount.  Thanks-a-lot, Marilou! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;============================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Maloney shares this with us..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilou's ability to elicit positive change in people is an asset that I aspire to have.       She has taught me the skills that support LOA. My life &amp;amp; those of others around me have been profoundly transformed since working with Marilou.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's some examples that have put me back in balance &amp;amp; given me the gift of emotional perspective.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-There was a family situation that was causing me great anger with one of my children. Through Marilou's knowledge of  how important my family is to me, she worked with me using NeuroShift to neutralize the emotions I had about the situation &amp;amp; continue to have a healthy relationship with my son. The NeuroShift process did not change what happened, but did change how I emotionally responded to the situation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-After endless attempts to stop smoking, the powerful process of NeuroShift finally set me free!  I have been a non- smoker for one year as of October 2nd!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-My daughter was undertaking new goals &amp;amp; dreams.  She was planning to request different investment amounts from different people for her projects.  I explained that I believe the Universe will grant her through LOA what she asks for, so don't limit the amount that people are going to invest.  She willingly placed no limits &amp;amp; the next day 2 people invested more than 10 times what she expected them to invest.  What you ask for... you can receive that quickly!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of knowledge I had gained from the study of NLP I realized that I had tools, through the use of language, to impact my daughter's life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilou Seavey is one of the few people whom you come across in life that will leave you more empowered than you were before you met. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192018338000</updated><rating><average>4.57999992371</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189555865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AGENDA for October 2nd BostonLOA Meetup</name><id>6340197</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191366000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/6340197/</event_url></item>