<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>176 Water St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.543907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>9787741983</phone><name>Andy's Sunnyside Bowladrome</name><city>Danvers</city><id>522415</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.919700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for something fun to do?&amp;nbsp; Want to go candlepin bowling? Well come on down to Sunnyside Bowl and have some fun with friends, this isn't glow bowling (see that later this month) and in this location all scores are posted electronically, hmmmm something different.&amp;nbsp; So come out and join us for a night of laughter and fun!!&amp;nbsp; Can't bowl?&amp;nbsp; Come cheer us on!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After we get our work out bowling let's satisfy our sweet tooth and go on over to the Cheesecake Factory and check out their menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;----------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can't come bowling, but your sweet tooth is saying let's go!&amp;nbsp; It's hard to tell right now what time we will be done so take the Meetup phone # with you and call and see if we know when we will be going.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE&lt;/strong&gt; put in your rsvp if you are ONLY coming for dessert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?&amp;nbsp; Please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo; You can give your dues to either Donna or Janet at any event.&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329061377000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328741471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bowling and.....</name><id>51618762</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329004800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/51618762/</event_url></item>