<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We're Done with Dodd, round 2&lt;br /&gt;DUMP CHRIS DODD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host: Connecticut Tea Party Patriots &lt;br /&gt;Type: Causes - Rally&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Oct&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;23&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fri 4:30 PM Description&lt;br /&gt;Event: We're Done with Dodd, round 2 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;DUMP CHRIS DODD&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;What: Obama and Dodd in Stamford!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: October 23, 2009 4:30PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: &lt;br /&gt;Hilton Stamford &lt;br /&gt;One First Stamford Place &lt;br /&gt;Stamford, CT 06905&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President Obama will be at a dinner fundraiser for Chris Dodd on Friday, October 23. Details are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: 430 PM Friday October 23rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Hilton Stamford Plaza&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;#1 First Stamford Place ( 240 Fairfield Ave , between Greenwich and Fairfield Aves.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I block west of the Stamford train station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We figured we'd have to wait until next summer to see President Obama campaigning for Dodd in Connecticut. And here he is Friday. My man Friday! &lt;br /&gt;Dump Dodders have been following Mr, Dodd all over the state, bringing attention to all who care to look, that there is a very vocal minority, soon to be majority, of disgruntled Nutmeggers ready, willing and able to give our senior senator the boot next year. &lt;br /&gt;On Friday, the two most visible icons for bad government are going to be on our turf. &amp;quot;Let's show them a good time&amp;quot;. And as people arrive to fork-over their cash to help Dodd weather our winter of discontent, let's show them what a Dump Dodd rally looks like. &lt;br /&gt;The Hartford Tea Party Patriots are supplying stage and sound. Let's be as helpful as we can be. Let's police the grounds and make Stamford look better than before we arrived. The Rat Pack Motorcycle Club will be arriving shortly after 5 PM. They are our friends. If any disturbances are attempted by Dodd or Obama supporters, our friends will deal with it. &lt;br /&gt;Friday, Oct. 23, 2009 – “Shine A Light On Corruption” Sen. Dodd and Pres. Obama Stamford CT Protest. Hilton Stamford Hotel 240 Fairfield Ave. Stamford CT. We will be located at the corner of Greenwich Ave and First Stamford Place. 4pm – 6:30pm (Official time is 4:30pm – 6:30pm, note return train times, if you are coming by that route). We will have a staging area set up for entertainment, music, and speakers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We ask everyone to bring a flashlight, along with your voices, signs, family and friends…let’s have a HUGE turn out to this event! The media will be there, also, so let’s let them see that we have not gone away!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If using a GPS system the hotel suggest you use the following address:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;151 Greenwich Avenue, Stamford, CT 06902.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking – The best spot would most likely be the Stamford Train Station, which also will most likely have the nearest restrooms. You will not be able to park at the hotel. There is on street parking, but I wouldn’t count on anything close to the area. The Stamford Train Station is a short walk to the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is the train schedule from New Haven to Stamford and back. This might be a better route to take, as we don’t know how many people are coming, nor do we know what the traffic situation will be for the arrival of Pres. Obama. Roundtrip tickets: $12.50, Seniors - $6.00, child - $6.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We urge you all to drive carefully. Park as far away as you are able. Daylight will make it easier to find parking. You may view this video to become familiar with the surroundings in Stamford. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;We will not be allowed to assemble on that long sidewalk. Our place is visible at 1:50 to 2:00 on the video. &lt;br /&gt;For people coming from the east, we suggest to take the train into Stamford. Make sure of the schedule so you know when to return. The train station is a short distance to the east of our rally point. &lt;br /&gt;There is parking in the 4-tiered lot south of the station. It is not inexpensive. South of the train tracks a few streets offer parking not too distant. We don't know if these streets will be blocked because of the President's motorcade. If he comes in the back way, you might catch a glimpse at the corner of Fairfield Avenue and Selleck Street, across from the Lumber yard. &lt;br /&gt;We hope to have a large supply of Dump Dodd signs for sale, so bring cash. We will not be able to have bumper stickers and other stuff.....you need to see the web site for those. &lt;br /&gt;We will send an amended and revised email Thursday night with all the final details. &lt;br /&gt;We honestly don't know how many people to expect, but I would estimate a crowd close to what we saw in Hartford on September 11. &lt;br /&gt;Look at this map to see a bird's eye view of the location. You may see side streets where parking is available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bing.com/m.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bing.com/m...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The police presence will be intense. Rest rooms are not too far away at the Train Station. Go in groups to use the rest rooms if needed or when needed. &lt;br /&gt;We probably will not see the President's arrival. I suspect they will bring him in through the back door. But you never know. But for sure, the people arriving to attend the dinner will be talking about us on the inside. &lt;br /&gt;Many politicians, including our Congressmen will be there. Movie stars and media moguls. &lt;br /&gt;Our rally is scheduled to last from 4:30 to 6:30, but you are welcome to come early and stay late.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Signs, signs, and more signs. Flags, flags and more flags!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna R.</member_name><member_id>8973743</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256503063000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Constitutional-Tea-Party-Patriots</urlname><id>1491323</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Constitutional Tea Party Patriots</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253223105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dump Dodd Round 2 -Hilton Stamford</name><id>11399913</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256329800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Constitutional-Tea-Party-Patriots/events/11399913/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/4/global_10345540.jpeg</photo_url></item>