<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Green Park Path</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02180</zip><lat>42.462362</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greenwood Park</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>5873672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090292</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I downloaded 91 photos of the trails we will be hiking on from a hike I took there on 2-25-12 with another hiking group in the photo album for this hike as a preview. &amp;nbsp;Due to the way the photos downloaded and upload they aren't always in the correct order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a crosswalk in between the Stone Zoo parking lot and the Greenwood Park parking lot. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;The address for the zoo is 149 Pond Street, Stoneham, MA 02180&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;The zoo parking lot is just past this address on Pond Street. &amp;nbsp;The roadway at this point is a divided roadway so if you are on the Stone Zoo side of the road and want to park at the Greenwood Park you will have to drive past the park and then turn around at the first intersection a little further down the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Middlesex Fells Reservation is an 2575 acre recreation and conservation area run by the Massachusetts Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) and is a state park. It is located in the towns of Malden, Medford, Stoneham, Melrose, and Winchester and has over 100 miles of trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The Middlesex Fells Reservation's 2,575 acres offer a welcome retreat for city dwellers and a suitable terrain for hikers, mountain bikers, horseback riders, rock climbers, cross-country skiers and picnickers as well as natural and cultural history buffs. "Fells" is the Saxon word for rocky, hilly tracts of land - an apt name for this scenic area which is rich in local history. This picturesque area was once favored for timber, granite quarrying, ice industry, and water power for the many mills including one that manufactured some of the first vulcanized rubber products. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will hike a bunch of trails I hiked with the 4 Seasons Hiking Group. It took us 3 hours to do this so the length of the hike is likely between 5-6 miles as this group tends to hike a faster pace than our group does. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 It is hilly terrain and some of the trails are rougher than others. The highest hill on this hike is Cairn Hill which is only 303' in elevation above sea level so most of the trail sections aren't all that steep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my house in Manchester the drive one way was 44.5 miles and took a little under an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;A trail map:&lt;a href="http://fells.org/Fells_Reservation_Trail_Map.pdf"&gt;http://fells.org/Fells_Reservation_Trail_Map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Department of Conservation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/fells.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/fells.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will simply meet in the parking lot of Greenwood Park which is a playground.  Parking is also available across the street at the Stone Zoo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333323202000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330208547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middlesex Fells Reservation</name><id>53807582</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333288800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/53807582/</event_url></item>