<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>  302 Ball Pond Road  </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06812</zip><lat>41.463327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>    Company A Event Hall     </name><city>New Fairfield</city><id>1136087</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.492520</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>49.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;DIRECTIONS TO THE PARTY AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS POSTING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO FAR OVER 120 HAVE SIGNED UP FROM OTHER GROUPS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hey Gang,&lt;br /&gt;Bruce and Deb are doing it again!!!  They throw some of the best parties going!!!:&lt;br /&gt;*** You must sign up on their site and arrange payment...You can sign up here to let our members know that you're going...but you won't be given one of the limited spots unless you RSVP at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/AMAZINGSINGLES/calendar/11773806/"&gt;Amazing Singles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;THE GRAND ANNOUNCEMENT OF OUR AMAZING NEW YEARS PARTY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;The short version&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $49 PP&lt;br /&gt;Includes: lots of hors d'oeuvres and dinner food, all drinks, favors, Band, DJ, 2000' ft dance floor, lots of parking, big screen TV for ball drop, bar tenders, &lt;br /&gt;10 PM BACHELOR AUCTION &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Have-Fun-Will-Travel/calendar/11945980/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress: Dressy Casual, Formal Optional&lt;br /&gt;Max No. of guests, 190&lt;br /&gt;Payment: Go to the AMAZING SITE LISTED ABOVE or Check by mail to Deb See their site also (but do it now to make sure you get in)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PLEASE READ ALL THE WAY TO THE BOTTOM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK, so you say you liked the Halloween party? Well this will be Giagantonormous! This is at an event hall right around the corner from where the Halloween party was held.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you didn't make it to the Halloween party, here's what you missed: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/AMAZINGSINGLES/photos/754018/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Years Eve will run from 8:00pm to 1:00am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost per person is only $49.00. YOU MUST CLICK ON THE LINK HERE OR AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PAGE TO PAY AND SECURE YOUR RSVP! &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/AMAZINGSINGLES/calendar/11773806/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dress is &amp;quot;Dressy Casual&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Formal Optional.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Everything will be supplied by &amp;quot;Amazing Singles.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space will be limited as we can only accommodate 190 people for this event. Sorry. At present they've opened 150 slots to allow us and other groups to join in and we'll adjust that number as RSVPs come in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many groups will be joining us so sign up early. You must pay with your RSVP. It's first come first served.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Amazing Evening will include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;hors d'oeuvres from 8 PM till the start of Dinner with at least 3 wonderful entree' selections&lt;br /&gt;Dessert&lt;br /&gt;Champagne toast at midnight&lt;br /&gt;Full Service &amp;quot;Open&amp;quot; Bar until 12:30am - Alcoholic &amp;amp; Non Alcoholic&lt;br /&gt;Big screen TV to see the ball drop&lt;br /&gt;Party Favors&lt;br /&gt;10 PM BENEFIT BACHELOR AUCTION &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Have-Fun-Will-Travel/calendar/11945980/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The great Mojo Myles Band and a DJ all night long. (please say what songs you'd like to hear when you sign up)&lt;br /&gt;2000 feet of dance floor for those &amp;quot;Twitching Toes&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Plenty of good on site parking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bruce and Deb will make room for about 10 to 12 overnight guests in their home. Anyone local in the area who can provide overnight accommodations in their homes for members so they don't have to spend money on a hotel in these tough times would be appreciated. If you are able to do this, PLEASE POST IT IN THE COMMENTS SECTION both here and at the Amazing site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have done everything we can to keep the cost low considering the cost of a hall on New Years Eve, food, band, other music, tables and chairs, decorations, alcohol, insurance, bartenders, set up and clean up labor and all the little things that many people forget costs money to make an event like this run smoothly and be enjoyable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are in a financial position to pay more than the $49 price posted, we have some members who have suffered with this economy and we will be happy to help you sponsor all or part of their cost anonymously. We are all friends enjoying friends and if possible, we'd like to make sure that as many who want to attend can attend regardless of their financial situation. But remember, we only have 190 spaces available. Book and pay early to be guaranteed a spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers of other groups, contact Bruce and Deb if you want to be part of this great occasion. Your members will have to pay through one of their sites so they can maintain control of RSVP and funds. Other group's members can join and then remove themselves from our sites after New Years if they wish. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;An RSVP on your this site does not guarantee anyone a spot unless they have paid on one of our sites or arranged another payment method&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazing Singles will be accepting checks by mail but those wishing to do so, should do it as soon as possible to make sure you do get on the guest list. You will not be guaranteed a spot until your check/cash is in hand so keep in mind that the RSVPs can still close while they are waiting on your money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members who wish to RSVP and pay by means other then the RSVP section at the top of the of the Amazing site posting, call Bruce or Deb at 203 746 2240 to arrange payment. Remember, there are only a limited number of RSVPs available and we can only reserve a spot for someone that is fully paid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVPs must be through the following sites since and we must collect the money directly to pay the expenses in advance for the New Years Eve party. Click on the link below to pay or call 203 746 2240 and ask for Bruce or Deb&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SIGNE UP AT Amazing Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/AMAZINGSINGLES/calendar/11773806/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From NY:&lt;br /&gt;From 684 east&lt;br /&gt;Get off at exit 5 for Danbury. Go straight ahead 5 miles to the light at the Mobil Station in &amp;quot;New Fairfield&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Make a left &lt;br /&gt;You are now on Brush Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile and make a right on Rte 39&lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile again and the next driveway just past the police station is the Company A Fire Dept event hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU GET LOST CALL 203 746 2240 BRUCE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short cut from NY but a little more complicated:&lt;br /&gt;From 684&lt;br /&gt;Go to the end of 684, go 1 mile to first light (Milltown Road) and make a right&lt;br /&gt;Go 5 miles till Milltown road ends at a &amp;quot;T&amp;quot; (that is Rout 39 Ball Pond Road)&lt;br /&gt;Make a left and go around the pond about 3 miles and the Fire Dept is on the right, &lt;br /&gt;Turn in there (the next driveway is the police dept) If you're in the police dept, you've gone to far. Put you hands on the top of the car, spread you feet apart and do not resist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU GET LOST CALL 203 746 2240 BRUCE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM Norwalk CT&lt;br /&gt;Take Rte 7 north to 84 going east&lt;br /&gt;get on 84 east and get off about 2 miles up at exit 5 for Danbury. &lt;br /&gt;Go straight ahead 5 miles to the light at the Mobil Station in &amp;quot;New Fairfield&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Make a left &lt;br /&gt;You are now on Brush Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile and make a right on Rte 39&lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile again and the next driveway just past the police station is the Company A Fired Dept event hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU GET LOST CALL 203 746 2240 BRUCE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford&lt;br /&gt;Take 84 West&lt;br /&gt;Get off at exit 6 for Danbury.&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the ramp (at light) make a right on to Rte 37 &lt;br /&gt;Go straight ahead 4 miles to the light at the Mobil Station in &amp;quot;New Fairfield&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Make a left &lt;br /&gt;You are now on Brush Hill Rd. &lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile and make a right on Rte 39&lt;br /&gt;Go about 1/4 of a mile again and the next driveway just past the police station is the Company A Fire Dept event hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU GET LOST CALL 203 746 2240 BRUCE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From England&lt;br /&gt;Take the QE 2 to NY Harbor&lt;br /&gt;Follow directions from NY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU GET LOST have the captain blow the fog horn 4 times, We'll find you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From&lt;br /&gt;LA&lt;br /&gt;Dude! Just beam yourself here man... It's all good&lt;br /&gt;YOU ARE ALREADY LOST, Don't call us, we'll do lunch next week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be everywhere. You can't miss us</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262480775000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>119</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258587244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bruce &amp; Deb's Danbury Area MULTI GROUP New Years Eve Party &amp; BACHELOR AUCTION </name><id>11907095</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262307600000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11907095/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/6/global_11881750.jpeg</photo_url></item>