<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Harvard Yard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Memorial Church</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>899800</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TICKETS ON SALE IN SEPTEMBER! A ceremony to present the 2011 Harvard Humanist of the Year award to Seth MacFarlane: writer, director, and creator of hit TV shows Family Guy and American Dad! While it is rare for someone his age to receive this honor, his extensive body of work, his active, passionate commitment to Humanist values, and his fearless support of equal marriage rights and other social justice issues compel the award program organizers to recognize his contributions now. This event is a program of The Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard, &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/harvardhumanist" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;. Their Facebook event page, where you may also RSVP, is online at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=197034433690802" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;. ABOUT THE AWARD For 20 years, the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard has presented the Humanist of the Year award to an individual whose life's work and personal commitment most exemplified the application of Humanist values in the public arena. Past recipients have included the first openly nontheistic sitting U.S. congressman Pete Stark (2007); renowned scientists Steven Pinker and E.O. Wilson; and human rights hero General Romeo Dallaire.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318724015000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312573115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seth MacFarlane, Harvard Humanist of the Year 2011!</name><id>28406071</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318719600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/28406071/</event_url></item>