<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you have any free time on the weekend and have at least 3 limbs (real or artificial), OR live somewhere with a roof over your head, OR have access to a business or unusual location, you potentially could have a great time being an integral part of the film project I'm on...by either offering-up your location as a potential shooting location, or volunteering as crew, or even being on camera (possibly as speaking or non-speaking)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The group I'm in is entered into the 48 Hour Film Contest (&lt;a href="http://www.48hourfilm.com" target="_blank"&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;) and we're assembling a team, we need more help, and you don't need to have any experience or skill to help out and have fun (&amp;amp; get your name in the credits).  I will be there all 3 days as one of the main actors, and helping-out in general.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've got a great director (who's gotten great reviews from Phil Hall at filmthreat.com) and have some other some great people together for the 48 Hour Contest...Fri. 7/18 at 7pm we're assigned a single line of dialog and given a genre.  We then have 48 hours to write, create, and turn-in a movie that fits the requirements.  The film then gets into the contest, gets shown, and judged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of the work will happen in the New Haven-ish area, and most of the shooting will probably happen Sat., and maybe some Sun., but there's no way to know for sure until the weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CREW:&lt;/b&gt; We need crew!  Even just general unskilled people to be production assistants, who can help fetch things, hold things, move things, etc.  You may be taught something about lighting or sound and given a job.  All you need is a willing attitude.  Of course, if you have skills with cameras, sound, lights, writing, editing, music, makeup, costumes, carpentry, etc we'd love to know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAST (EXTRAS):&lt;/b&gt; We might need extra people to appear in a scene.  Most likely non-speaking, and you can specify if you only want non-speaking background/extra work.  Since we don't know who/what we'd need, we'd take your number then we'd probably call you Friday night or sometime on Sat. to see if you're interested in doing whatever scene in which we'd like to use you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OFFERING LOCATION(S):&lt;/b&gt; Do you have a fancy, spacious, organized, well-decorated apartment?  A cramped, cluttered, plain one?  Do you have an &amp;quot;in&amp;quot; somewhere and could convince a business owner somewhere to let us use their business location (free PR!), or can let us into Yale or some other interesting locations?  If so we'd like to hear from you.  If the space is cool we might decide to lock it in and definitely use it.  Or, since we don't know what we'd need, we'd take your number then possibly we might wait until Friday night or sometime on Sat. to call to see if we can get the space you're offering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GETTING INVOLVED:&lt;/b&gt; If you have questions you can contact me, Jason (&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/message/?recipientId=2254163"&gt;email&lt;/a&gt;, or call 203-901-4957), but the way to get involved is to email the production team, or you can call one of them (Kelly 203-654-6575) to ask questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To email, write to Joel Vetsch (spooly_montana@yahoo.com) and Kelly Barrett (kelly_barrett2002@yahoo.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your subject line &amp;quot;48 Hour Film&amp;quot; and add in &amp;quot;crew&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;extras&amp;quot;, and/or &amp;quot;location&amp;quot;, depending on which of those (or all 3!) you wish to get involved with.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the message, include your phone number, what you'd like to offer (crew, extra, location, or any combination), any relevant skills, training, or experience you have (or just say you're volunteering to be an unskilled production assistant) and your availability on Fri 7/18 - Sun. 7/20.  If you're someone I've met, mention you're a friend of Jason's.  If you want to be an extra it would help to attach any ole' snapshot (pull it off your Meetup profile?), and if you're offering location(s), a sentence or 3 describing a little about the location(s) you have to offer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216767790000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215989526000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fri/Sat/Sun 7/18-20 - On your mark, get set...shoot!  Day 3</name><id>8334483</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216594800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8334483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>