<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For the July meetup, all the little (and big) Puggies are eagerly trooping over to Riley's grandparents' house in Abington to visit with them and their twelve year old Pug, Oscar.  We hope you all can come!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LAST MONTH'S MEETUP...&lt;br /&gt;It was a beautiful day for the South of Boston June Meetup at Buford's house in Carver.  After a week of rain, the sun broke through, and puffy clouds kept it cool enough for the Pugs to run and play.  Buford does indeed have a HUGE yard - securely fenced - and Buford's mom and dad thoughtfully provided chairs and edibles so that everyone could be comfortable while watching the Pugs race around.  Everyone had a great time.  Stoney loved the dip and the carrots.  I loved the Pug throw hanging over the fence!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS...&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby.  Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool.  There will be biscuits for the dogs and coffee, soft drinks, and something to snack on for the adults!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs.  If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him.  We want everyone to have fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you and your Puggie(s) at our next meetup!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1152640973000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1150052449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug July Meetup</name><id>4974684</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1152468000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/4974684/</event_url></item>