<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our book for January and February 2013 is “The Best Buddhist Writing 2012,” edited by Melvin McLeod and the editors of Shambhala Sun magazine (Shambhala Publications, paperback). This is a treasury of the most notable, profound, and thought-provoking Buddhist-inspired writing published in the last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please read up to page 167 for the January discussion, and the remainder of the book for the February meeting (Read up to and including "To Uphold the World" by Bruce Rich.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Practical wisdom from Pema Chödrön and Thich Nhat Hanh share space in this anthology with fresh insight on the Occupy Wall Street movement, the art and practice of contemplative photography, the story of five courageous monks who take on the disastrous forces of a wildfire, and other highly personal accounts.”—Yoga International&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Best Buddhist Writing 2012 includes:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- His Holiness the Dalai Lama on cultivating a universal ethic of kindness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Sharon Salzberg on getting your meditation practice started&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Pema Chödrön on how to smile at fear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- The Venerable Bhikkhu Bodhi on analyzing global problems through the lens of traditional Buddhist teachings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Bruce Rich on the enlightened model of government of the Buddhist monarch King Ashoka&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Thich Nhat Hanh on fidelity in loving relationships&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Michael A. Stusser’s determined—and hilarious—effort to speak—and tweet—no evil&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Norman Fischer on a new and more open understanding of language&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Barry Boyce’s fascinating survey of the life and teachings of the late Chögyam Trungpa Rinpoche&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Michael Stone and David Loy on the basic questions raised by the Occupy Wall Street movement&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Khenchen Thrangu Rinpoche’s explanation of the meditation practice of kusulu, the pinnacle of simplicity and relaxation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Nancy Baker on the powerful and useful energy behind anger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Diane Ackerman on living with her beloved husband’s Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-- Yangzom Brauen’s moving account of her grandmother and mother’s escape from Tibet following the Chinese invasion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;... And much more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358221582000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355060258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discussion of "The Best Buddhist Writing 2012"</name><id>ttkxpyrcbsb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358208000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/94664552/</event_url></item>