<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Jacob Wirth Restaurant has been a Boston favorite since 1868.&lt;br /&gt;Conveniently located in the heart of the city?s theater district, Jake Wirth?s is a ?Best of Boston? award winner, a classic European dining room with a contemporary American flair. Its menu ranges from traditional German specialties to current American favorites, with highlights that include award-winning New England Clam Chowder.&lt;br /&gt;Jake Wirth?s historic bar is a popular destination in itself, with dozens of imported beers on draft and a rich wine list. And Friday nights are extra special, with fun-filled piano sing-alongs that have become a festive weekend tradition in the bar area.&lt;br /&gt;Eat, drink and be merry as you sing along to your favorites. No problem if you don't know the words. You'll get a free songbook with lyrics to more than 500 songs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available next door, with two hours free for restaurant patrons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also, please be sure to bring cash to make it easy on settling the bill with the group.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to the website. Check it out! The history of the restaurant is very interesting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jacobwirth.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jacobwirth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be out front of the restaurant just before 7:30pm with a meet up sign. If you come later, look for a meet up sign on the tables.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212427799000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Good friends, good food, good music!</why><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208462577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner &amp; Friday Night Sing-a-Long at Jacob Wirth German Restaurant</name><id>7758971</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212190200000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/7758971/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/8/global_3827048.jpeg</photo_url></item>