<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 112 in Passaconaway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.993515</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Champney Falls Parking Lot</name><city>Conway</city><id>452208</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.329460</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most popular peaks in the White Mountains, Mount Chocorua,  elevation of 3,490 feet ascends along ledge and stone steps with views to the north, east, and south. Chocorua's summit is a picturesque rocky cone, and the mountain is purported to be one of the most photographed in the world. Once atop the summit you’ll be at the site where Sokosis Chief Chocorua—distraught over the death of his son—supposedly cursed the surrounding area and its settlers. Many strange and tragic happenings have been attributed to the curse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/c/8/event_11428872.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Meet at Champney Falls parking lot on Route 112 in Passaconaway (I-93 to exit 32 in Lincoln).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking area is about 1.5 miles east of Bear Notch Road and about a half hour from downtown Lincoln.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is 7.6 miles with a 2250' of elevation gain. It should take us about 7 hours round trip. Stronger hikers may want to add the three sister peaks to their trip for more great views&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #0000ff"&gt;BYO tailgate after the hike. I'll bring a gas stove so we can roast some sausages or what ever you bring.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This hike has spectacular autumn 360&lt;/strong&gt; degree views with two waterfalls on the descent!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/5/2/event_11443346.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Dress for fall weather hiking with an exposed summit. 40% rain cancels. This hike is not recommended for wet weather. Dogs may find the summit cone challenging. The rest of the trail is dog friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is believed that Chocorua was a real Indian, although no authentic records of his life exist. About 1720 Chocorua was on friendly terms with settlers and, in particular, the Campbell family that had a home in the valley now called Tamworth. Chocorua was called away and left his son in the care of the Campbell family. The boy found and drank a poison that Mr. Campbell had made to eliminate troublesome foxes, and Chocorua returned to find his son had died. Chocorua, distraught with grief, pledged revenge on the family. Shortly thereafter, Mr. Campbell returned home one afternoon to find his wife and children had been slain. Campbell suspected Chocorua and pursued him up the mountain that today bears his name. Chocorua was wounded by a shot from Campbell's rifle. Before Campbell could reach Chocorua, he uttered a curse upon the white settlers and their homes, livestock, and crops, and leapt from the summit to his death. There are at least three other versions of the legend of Chocorua. One is that Chocorua simply fell from a high rock on the mountain while hunting. A second is the white men pursued Chocorua up the mountain after an Indian massacre, and he was not shot at all but simply leapt to his death. The third is that all the white men pursued him with guns, pitchforks, and torches. They collapsed of exhaustion as Chocorua reached the top, and the white men decided to torch the remaining trees up to the summit, and in doing so they burned and exposed the topsoil of the last 1270 feet. As the flames drew closer and closer to Chocorua, he cursed the white men and leapt to his death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The east face of Mount Chocorua from Carter Ledge Although no one can know the exact words of Chocorua's curse (or even if there was a curse), it has been reported to be as follows. "May the Great Spirit curse you when he speaks in the clouds and his words are fire! Lightning blast your crops! Wind and fire destroy your homes! The Evil One breathe death on your cattle! Panthers howl and wolves fatten on your bones!" Another version of Chocorua's curse appears in the story 'Chocorua's Curse' (by the author of another famous Indian work, 'Hobomok'), contained in 'The Token' (1830): 'A curse upon ye, white men! May the Great Spirit curse ye when he speaks in the clouds, and his words are fire! Chocorua had a son — and ye killed him while the sky looked bright! Lightning, blast your crops! Wind and fire destroy your dwellings! The Evil Spirit breathe death upon your cattle! Your graves lie in the war path of the Indian! Panthers howl, and wolves fatten over your bones! Chocorua goes to the Great Spirit — his curse stays with the white men!'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;For those of us that are less fit, hiking is fantastic conditioning, but that stress level is hit much faster so replacement drinks are advised. Nuun, Powerade Zero, and Gatorade all make a good sugar free version for those who are controlling their sugar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The Trail map can be found &lt;a href="http://www.reptiliandesigns.com/files/chocorua.pdf"&gt;***HERE***&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The directions from the MA/NH border on rt 93 can be found &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/lXEx0"&gt;***HERE***&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-align : center ; font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com" style="font-size : 12px"&gt;Click for weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/d/4/event_128896852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the trailhead or better yet, carpool- Expect more tourists in the area to see the fall foliage, so carpool!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351081509000</updated><rating><average>3.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348876313000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Chocorua via Champney Falls Hike &amp; Tailgate: Casual Pace</name><id>84598612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350824400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/84598612/</event_url></item>