<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beach street</address_1><state>ME</state><lat>43.249901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ogunquit Beach</name><city>Ogunquit</city><id>3623262</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.596962</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful Ogunquit, Maine!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/2/2/event_97508482.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The picturesque village of &lt;strong&gt;Ogunquit&lt;/strong&gt; rests peacefully during the winter behind rocky headlands, sandy beaches, and crashing surf. It is filled with quaint shops and warm bistros. And there's a beautiful walkway along the coast that's open to the public. &lt;strong&gt;Marginal Way&lt;/strong&gt; is a scenic 3-mile roundtrip trail along the ocean's edge. And we can meander further along the beach to make a longer hike if we wish. There's lots to see so bring your cameras!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There will be time to browse the shops for gifts and...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/1/b/a/event_98141402.jpeg" width="321" height="205" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;...afterward&lt;/strong&gt;, we'll head to &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thefrontporch.net/index.htm"&gt;The Front Porch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; @ for food and drinks! Taste some of their specialty flatbread pizzas in front of a stone fireplace after a great walk along the coast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/8/e/event_98141102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Front Porch&lt;/strong&gt; also has an upstairs &lt;strong&gt;Piano Bar&lt;/strong&gt;. After we eat, we can walk around town or head straight upstairs for another drink and sing along with old favorites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portsmouth Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;12:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href="http://www.ridecj.com/new-hampshire/portsmouth.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Portsmouth Park &amp;amp; Ride Lot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; - 185 Grafton Ave. There are two parking lots. Meet in the back of the &lt;span&gt;park &amp;amp; ride&lt;/span&gt; lot - the one farthest from the main bus terminal building - at the very back of the lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/8/0/event_97507552.jpeg" width="289" height="243" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Newburyport Carpool&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;Noon.&lt;/strong&gt; C&amp;amp;J Bus lot, 90 Storey Ave/Rt 113 at I-95. (Post a comment if you want to meet here so others can see it.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Don't forget to share driving expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;: Go to the main parking area at the end of Beach Street. We'll meet at the far end of the lot. No parking fee is in effect in the winter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microspikes/Poles:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Bring 'em&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;if you have 'em. It WILL be slippery&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;No Pets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/d/0/event_97507632.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In 1925, the magnificent Marginal Way&lt;/strong&gt; was given as a gift to the Town of Ogunquit by Josiah Chase of York and is now a paved footpath beginning (or ending) in a corner of Oarweed Cove near the harbor, then running for 1.5 miles to the marvelous expanse of Ogunquit Beach. Once called "the margin" because of its patterned development along the rocky edge of the cliff, the origin and preservation of this truly precious piece of natural beauty was not the result of far-sighted conservation planning, but of the dealings of a shrewd businessman and some stubborn, persuasive "locals."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/4/8/event_97507752.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This delightful, exhilarating walk&lt;/strong&gt; meanders by tangled bayberry and bittersweet bushes, gnarled shrubs of fragrant pink and white sea roses, shaded alcoves formed by wind-twisted trees jutting out onto high granite outcroppings, and humbling views of the mighty Atlantic with its varying seasonal moods. Although the bends and inclines along the way are rather ge&lt;/span&gt;ntle, most walkers will choose one of the thirty memorial benches dotting the path to sit and rest, to contemplate and sometimes to paint the panorama of sea, surf and sky which daily unfolds amid noisy protests from the roiling ocean and screeching gulls. After a freak storm damaged the path in 1991, the Committee to Restore the Marginal Way and a capital fund were established to ensure its continued preservation and maintenance. Each year more than 100,000 people take this scenic path along the rugged cliff line, and, while Maine has several similar ocean walkways, Ogunquit's Marginal Way is undoubtedly the most unique, the most popular, the most painted and the most beloved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/a/a/event_98141642.jpeg" width="300" height="223" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356302501000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355842424000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk This (Marginal) Way!</name><id>95776422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356199200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/95776422/</event_url></item>