<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Ed Moffitt Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02563</zip><lat>41.769750</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-833-9678</phone><name>Cape Cod Canal visitor center</name><city>Sandwich</city><id>329185</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.503930</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet in the parking lot of the Cape Cod Canal visitor center at 11:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will ride south on the east side of the canal and then cross over to Buzzards Bay where we will stop for lunch before continuing back on the west side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This bikeway follows the Cape Cod Canal through sections of Bourne and Sagamore, respectively. Partially maintained by the Army Corps of Engineers, it offers fantastic views of the canal's various boat traffic, along with the area's quaint shoreline scenery of unique homes and natural beauty.&lt;br /&gt;The path is actually the canal access road, a paved route designated for government vehicles, foot traffic and non-motorized vehicles only. It runs for approximately 7 - 8 miles (each side) between the Bourne and Sagamore Bridges. Featuring a wide road with minimal grades, it is ideal for beginner to casual cyclists, especially families with younger children.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO THE CAPE COD CANAL VISITOR CENTER&lt;br /&gt;We are located on along the Cape-side of the Canal at 60 Ed Moffitt Drive in Sandwich, MA near the Sandwich Marina and the US Coast Guard Station. 508-833-9678.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Off-Cape&lt;br /&gt;? Travel over the Sagamore Bridge onto Cape Cod. Take the first exit ? Exit 1C&lt;br /&gt;? The off-ramp will lead you to a set of lights. Turn RIGHT at the lights taking Rte 6A towards Sandwich.&lt;br /&gt;? Drive under the Sagamore Bridge and continue for 1.1 miles.&lt;br /&gt;? You will pass the ?Entering Sandwich? sign&lt;br /&gt;? Continue .2 miles. Turn LEFT onto Tupper Road (you will see Rte 130 on your right)&lt;br /&gt;? Continue for .8 mile and turn left onto Freezer Road. (There will be a large brown Cape Cod Canal sign and a dive shop on the corner)&lt;br /&gt;? Continue for .1 mile and take your first RIGHT onto Ed. Moffitt Drive. ? Follow Ed Moffitt Drive for .4 mile around the Marina. Continue on Ed Moffitt by turning RIGHT after the Coast Guard Station (when you see the ?Bulkhead Recreation Area? sign.)&lt;br /&gt;? Take Ed Moffitt Drive to the end. You will see a parking lot and the Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;? We are located next to Joe?s Lobster Mart and across from Seafood Sam?s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189648911000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185212325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Cod Canal bike ride</name><id>6065118</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189350000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/6065118/</event_url></item>