<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>167 Columbus Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.870308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Temple Games</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>1686641</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.365456</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This campaign is being put together specifically for TempleCon 2011. We would need at least 4 regular players.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;House Carrith has recently come into possession of rich caches of dragon shards. These caches contain so many dragonshards, that House Tharashk has fallen on troubled times. With dragonshard prospecting no longer being as profitable as it once was, the Triumvirate has ruled that all of Tharashk's resources be used to strengthen it's last major economic stronghold, it's bounty hunters. House Deneith has heard whispers that Tharashk is hiring all the bounty hunters it can and sending them to all parts of Khorvaire. House Deneith has the best bounty hunters in all of Eberron and they intend to keep it that way. Whatever House Tharashk is up to, House Deneith intends to find out and beat them at their own game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Eberron campaign will meet once a month for roughly 4 hours at The Temple in Pawtucket, culminating in the final episode at TempleCon 2011. This campaign will be episodic with an over arcing story heavy on story, continuity and role playing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Characters are to start at level 5. You are allowed one lvl 6 magic item, one level 5 magic item, and one level 4 magic item from the allowed books. You will also be given level appropriate gold.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-the ONLY source material allowed to be used are the PHB, PHB 2, PHB 3, the Eberron Players Guide and Adventurer's Vault 1, be sure to check the errata for all books &lt;a href="http://wizards.com/dnd/Article.aspx?x=dnd/updates" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. You must take all races, classes, feats, and magic item choices from those books ONLY. This campaign will be cheddar-light. If you looking for a min/max meat grinder, look elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Regular attendance ensures you a spot at the final episode, which will be a two episode long adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Players will treat everyone with respect and remember that the object of the game is for everyone to have fun, not just one person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Capping the group at 6 players, will run a second group if needed.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Seated at a gaming table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>11219434</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1284966411000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282317083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D&amp;D 4th Edition 5th level Eberron Campaign leading to TempleCon</name><id>14484794</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284829200000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/14484794/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/4/7/global_17321703.jpeg</photo_url></item>