<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Bar Mills (Buxton), Maine&lt;/i&gt; 9:00 am to 1:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Please join &lt;b&gt;Carolyn Baker&lt;/b&gt; for an exclusive half-day session drawing on her most recent book:  &lt;i&gt;Sacred Demise, Walking the Spiritual Path of Industrial Civilization's Collapse.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carolyn Baker gives us an honest look at the &lt;b&gt;magnitude of the transition&lt;/b&gt; we’re facing and suggests that we allow it to be a grand teaching to deepen our understanding of life and our place in it.  While the reality of what we are dealing with may be overwhelming when seen with such stark honesty, isn't that what we yearn for?  Isn't the failure to connect with ourselves and each other in this way what unsettles us most? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this half-day workshop, Carolyn will share her personal experiences and some of the wisdom, poetry, questions and activities that will help us navigate both the inner and outer landscapes of systemic change in our society.  She draws upon herself to help us understand and grow from our circumstances by infusing them with compassion.  We will learn some strategies for venturing safely into the tender, vulnerable places that often become exposed during times of upheaval and change.  (Carolyn requests that you read her book before attending this workshop if you are able.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Course fee includes coffee/tea/snacks (please bring your own potluck kit of plate/bowl/utensils/mug/napkin).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://carolynbaker.net/site/component/option,com_frontpage/Itemid,1/" target="_blank"&gt;Carolyn Baker&lt;/a&gt;, Ph.D is an adjunct professor of history, an author, and former psychotherapist. Her latest book is Sacred Demise: Walking the Spiritual Path of Industrial Civilization’s Collapse. She has also written three other books: Coming Out from Christian fundamentalism: Affirming Sensuality, Social Justice, and the Sacred, US History Uncensored: What Your High School Textbook Didn’t Tell You, and The Journey of Forgiveness.&lt;/i&gt;  She lives in Vermont.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>winter</member_name><member_id>5389512</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245539925000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240421732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sacred Demise: A Half-Day Workshop with Carolyn Baker</name><id>10243517</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244898000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/10243517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/c/global_8289212.jpeg</photo_url></item>