<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Eliot St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372083</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 868-1900 </phone><name>Tanjore</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>725098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121367</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot; 'Heat and Dust' contains wonderful sights and sounds and textures. It is seductive, treating both of its love stories with seriousness; these are not romances, but decisions to dissent. It is fully at home in its times and places (the director, James Ivory, and the producer, Ismail Merchant, have spent 20 years making films about the British in India). And when it is over, we're a little surprised to find that it is angry, too. Angry that women of every class and every system, women British and Indian, Women of the 1920s and of the 1980s, are always just not quite the same caste as men.&amp;quot; -- Roger Ebert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Directed with Ivory's customary charm, the film boasts fine performances (Christie and Scacchi in particular), and switches periods with effortless ease, striking up a fine network of ironies along the way. Passion, never one of Ivory's strong points, does get rather submerged beneath a welter of local colour; a delight none the less.&amp;quot; -- Time Out Film Guide &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heat and Dust is a 1983 film directed by James Ivory (Howard's End, Room with A View, Jefferson in Paris, Le Divorce) and produced by Ivory's long-time co-collaborator Ismail Merchant. It is based on the 1975 booker prize winning novel of the same name, written by Ruth Prawer Jhabvala, a two-time Academy Award winning screenwriter and frequent Merchant Ivory collaborator. According to the Museum of Broadcast Communications there was &amp;quot;a cycle of film and television productions which emerged during the first half of the 1980s, which seemed to indicate Britain's growing preoccupation with India, Empire and a particular aspect of British cultural history&amp;quot;.  In addition to Heat and Dust, this cycle also included The Jewel in the Crown (1984) and A Passage to India (1984).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heat and dust is a tale of two Indian love stories which take place during different time periods: the period of the British Raj in the 1920s and the present day of the film (1982). Anne (Julie Christie) is a young English woman searching for the truth about Olivia (Greta Scacchi), her grandfather's first wife. Anne discovers that Olivia fell in love with a Muslim noble and became pregnant with his child.  In the process of finding out about Olivia, Anne finds that she is falling in love with an Indian man as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director James Ivory will be speaking either before or after the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is screening at the Harvard Film Archive at 7 pm, but we will be meeting at Tanjore since the film probably won't get out until after ten. We will leave the restaurant at 6:15 in order to secure good seats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because this event will sell out quickly and advanced ticketing is only open for HFA members and groups, I will have to pre-order groups tickets from the Harvard Film Archive and pay for them out of my own pocket. The tickets cost $8 a piece and only twelve of them will be available. Priority will be given based on how long you have been attending events with the group. Please RSVP only if you plan to attend and pay me back. In order to order tickets, I will need for you to email me with your last name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info on Heat and Dust:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.merchantivory.com/heatanddust.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.merchantiv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rogerebert.suntimes.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/19831020/REVIEWS/310200301/1023" target="_blank"&gt;http://rogerebert.sun...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tcm.com/movienews/index/?cid=63844&amp;amp;rss=mrqe" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tcm.com/mo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will hold a meetup sign at the front of the restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206997408000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205631227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Event: Heat and Dust/James Ivory Appears at HFA</name><id>7541556</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206824400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7541556/</event_url></item>