<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.373015</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weeks Pedestrian Bridge</name><city>Boston</city><id>696287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062754</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>RAIN OR SHINE (Bring rain gear, dress for cold weather, binoculars, lawn chair)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2009 REUNION VILLAGE&lt;br /&gt;Located on the  Boston side of the Charles River which is &amp;quot;best view at the half way spot for the races&amp;quot; between Week's and Anderson Bridges&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's Meet at the Week's Foot Bridge (&lt;b&gt;Cambridge side&lt;/b&gt;) In front of the Chicago UNOs Pizza and Chipotle Food Booths at 1PM. At 1:30 we walk over to the Boston side and walk along the river to &amp;quot;REUNION VILLAGE&amp;quot;(Center Tent). The center tent sells beer and wine (cash only, plus $3 admission ;2 persons for $5...so let's go inside in pairs...for all day access). You can bring your own food into the tent.  &lt;br /&gt;Note: No alcohol beyond the village is allowed.....however, I am sure you will see a flask or two at this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fitness Expo: Try out the rowing machines and see what the fitness pros have to say about rowing as a sport. This is the second of two places to get food at booths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO PARKING: Fuh get about it! Parking will be impossible and Memorial Drive..both JFK and Anderson Bridges will be closed...so Take the Red Line to Harvard Square and walk down JFK street toward the river and turn left on Memorial Street. Food booths will be at the foot of the Week's Footbridge Bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING ONLY FOR THOSE COMING FROM NEW HAMPSHIRE:  Parking is unrestricted in Cambridge on Sunday but very difficult to find. The key is to get to Cambridge EARLY before noon. When you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;..alert me by making a comment about needing help to find parking so that I my assist you. Please remember that your GPS will not tell you about the bridge and road closures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1965, the Charles River has welcomed a breadth of athletes from near and far to participate in the world's largest two day regatta. But the fun isn't limited to competitors - there are many opportunities for spectators to share in the weekend's racing and festivities.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2009 Reunion Village Hours:&lt;br /&gt;The Village offers a fun and relaxed atmosphere located at the halfway point in the race on the Boston side of the Charles River.&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: 8AM - 4PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome at the Village. Clubs, schools, alumni groups, parents, boosters and travel groups are all urged to visit! Admission is $3/person (or 2 for $5) for unlimited day access. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.hocr.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will disclose my cell number  after you rsvp "yes"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256059127000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254675658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHARLES RIVER REGATTA: REUNION VILLAGE</name><id>11543609</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255885200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/11543609/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/e/global_10607966.jpeg</photo_url></item>