<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I and my hiking friend, Darryl, will be peakbagging PATN (Peak Above The Nubble) in WHITES, NH on 9/26(Sun).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is cross posted hiking event from &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-490/"&gt;my own hiking meetup group (Hike / Snowshoe Vermont).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PATN is NE HH (New England 100 Highest) listed peak and there is no maintained trail.  Therefore, bushwhacking is required.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/shock.gif' border='0' alt='shock' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the trailhead of North Twin Trail on Haystack Road, Twin Mountain, NH at 9AM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is &lt;a href="http://www.wikiloc.com/wikiloc/view.do?id=943428"&gt;the example of bushwhacking route. &lt;/a&gt;   There are several different ways to bushwhack around PATN and I'll study a little bit more to choose better (or the best) route for us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is approx 4 miles hiking/bushwhacking.  I estimate we'll complete this event within 5-6 hours or so. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is strenuous hike/bushwhacking.  I've heard there are some sections where spruce is very thick.  If you never hiked any 4K footers, this is not for your hike.  Also, if you haven't hiked several months to high elevation mountains, this is not for your hike either.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My Car is Honda CR-V (Blue)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285593163000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284870903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PATN (Peak Above The Nubble, 3813 ft) Bushwhacking in WHITES - NE 100 Highest.</name><id>14819032</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285506000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14819032/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>