<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Walkers Brook Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.518658</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-944-9090</phone><name>Comcast IMAX Theatre at Jordan's Furniture - Reading</name><city>Reading</city><id>437919</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Runtime: 1 hr. 53 min. | PG-13 - intense sequences of violence including disturbing images, some sexual material and nudity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Ray Winstone, Anthony Hopkins, Angelina Jolie &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director: Robert Zemeckis &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Genres: Action/Adventure, Animated, Sci-Fi/Fantasy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/ae/movies/articles/2007/11/16/behold_beowulf/?page=full" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/beowulf/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.apple.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beowulf_%282007_film%29" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Little known fact: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Beowulf: the Monsters and the Critics is an important 1936 lecture given by J. R. R. Tolkien on the subject of Beowulf criticism. It was first published in that year in Proceedings of the British Academy, 22 (1936), pp. 245?95. It has since been reprinted in many collections, most prominently the 1983 collection of Tolkien's academic papers, The Monsters and the Critics and Other Essays, ed. by Christopher Tolkien (London: Allen &amp;amp; Unwin, 1983, pp. 5.48.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This paper is widely regarded as a formative work in early 20th century Beowulf studies. In this talk, Tolkien speaks against critics who play down the fantastic elements of the poem (namely Grendel and the dragon) in favour of using Beowulf solely as a source for Anglo-Saxon history. Tolkien argues that rather than being merely extraneous, these elements are key to the narrative and should be the focus of study. In doing so he drew attention to the previously neglected &amp;quot;literary&amp;quot; qualities of the poem and argued that it should be studied as a work of art, not just as an historical document. Later critics who disagreed with Tolkien on this point have routinely had to cite him and systematically defend their arguments. The paper remains the first port of call for students of the Anglo-Saxon epic and has been quoted admiringly by Nobel-laureate Seamus Heaney in the introduction to his best-selling translation of the poem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apart from its importance as a field-defining paper in Beowulf studies, the paper also sheds light on many of Tolkien's ideas about literature and is an indispensable source for those seeking to understand his own writing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture is based on a longer lecture series which exists in two manuscript versions, published together in 2002 as Beowulf and the Critics by J. R. R. Tolkien, edited by Michael D. C. Drout, Medieval and Renaissance Texts and Studies 248 (Arizona Medieval and Renaissance Texts and Studies), ISBN 0-8669-8290-6.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;from: &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beowulf:_The_Monsters_and_the_Critics" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what your going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please try to buy your tix AHEAD of time, especially this showtime because it is so early! To buy tix online, go here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nz01.2day.terabyte.co.nz/jordansimax/JORDANSpurchaseReading.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nz01.2day....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I bought mine already!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 2 vehicles going up that is giving rides, 3.5 passenger in Fred Hill's vehicle in Somerville. Fred will be picking up@ Sullivan Square station at 5:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JediFonger's coupe (sorry tight space) can fit roughly 2.5 people, or 3. Please send them a message by clicking on their name and then click contact to get more details. If you want to drive other people, please contact me directly and I will add you to the list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last night to notify drivers is Thursday. After that, Friday messages will pretty much be ignored and these descriptions will reflect that. DON'T WAIT UNTIL THE LAST MINUTE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be there around 6:15PM in the lobby of the IMAX Cinema where you buy popcorn and tickets. This is NOT the same place as the entrance of Jordan's Furniture. DO NOT WAIT @Jordan's Furniture. Go inside and find the cinema, go up the escalator and find the lobby, that is where we will be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I&amp;quot;ll be wearing my green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front. near the entrance of the line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie showtime is 6:45PM (after which, the next showing is 9PM, thus 2late). I'll be there @6:15PM. Our group will head into the cinema @6:35PM sharp (my cell is synced to GMT)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film ends, I'll be waiting right in front of the big screen w/my green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger. Come find me, the group often goes out afterwards and socialize. I won't exit the cinema itself until EVERYONE has filed out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-JediFonger&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198203510000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195974265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beowulf IMAX 3D!</name><id>6798518</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196464500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6798518/</event_url></item>