<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you sometimes wish you could be that person who lights up a room when you walk in?  Do you find yourself admiring other people who seem to have that special magic that endears people to them?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you've ever wanted to have the kind of personality that people find magnetic and enjoyable to be around, then you're going to love this month's meeting.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;4 big mistakes people make that cause others want to avoid them, and how to easily correct each one of them (I guarantee you're making at least one of these).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple technique for remembering people's names. Learn this technique once, use it forever. Also, what to do when you forget someone's name, but are too embarrassed to bring it up.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 simple ways to start conversations with people that work almost every time. I've used hundreds of times in the real world, and they absolutely work.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 simple secrets for keeping a conversation going and getting people to open up to you. You won't have to worry about awkward silences again once you know these two techniques.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 ways to end a conversation that will leave people feeling good about you. If you've ever wanted to end a conversation with someone, but were worried about offending or upsetting them, then this is perfect for you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;PERSONALITY FEEDBACK&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's just the first part of the seminar.  Then we will go into one of the most popular activities that we do in this social skills group... personality feedback!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;You will have an opportunity to participate in small group evaluations of other members, and you'll also get to experience what it's like to receive both positive encouragement and constructive feedback about how you come across to others.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This is often the most revealing part of the workshop, because it's so personalized.  Some members became away of things they were doing for years that were turning people off, and some learned that they come across much better than they realized (which dramatically boosted their confidence in all social situations).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/u&gt;  I want you to know that exercise is done very gently, kindly, and in the spirit of personal growth.  We are all there to help each other.  So if this section makes you a little nervous, don't let it.  I promise that you will find this to be one of the most educational and &lt;u&gt;enjoyable&lt;/u&gt; parts of the seminar.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:00pm.  The first 30 minutes is used for personal networking and socializing, and then we start the seminar promptly at 3:30.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, July 19th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:00pm for registration and personal networking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259592782000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247534272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Develop Confidence And Charisma + Personality Feedback</name><id>10870045</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248030000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/10870045/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/global_9660154.jpeg</photo_url></item>