<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/devilish.gif' border='0' alt='devilish' /&gt;Experience the glow of thousands of pumpkins, set in a magical display of artistry during this night-time Spectacular. A team of over 30 professional pumpkin carvers will spend six weeks creating the trail, resulting in a truly breathtaking display. Feast your eyes on thousands of carved and illuminated pumpkins, with hundreds of them depicting people, places and scenes from popular culture to old-time favorites and everything in between – all with painstaking detail and amazing intricacy!  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/devilish.gif' border='0' alt='devilish' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$12 adults, $10 seniors - No individual advance tickets will be sold.  During its previous run at the Zoo from 2000 to 2004, the Jack-O-Lantern Spectacular drew over 80,000 visitors annually, from all over New England and beyond. Don't miss out this year, as the Spectacular returns to the Zoo, bigger and better than ever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Located just 50 minutes from Boston and 90 minutes from Hartford with well marked, easy access off Interstate 95. From 95 South take exit 17 and from 95 North take exit 16. The zoo is ¼ mile off the exit on Elmwood Avenue. GPS users: enter the address &amp;quot;1000 Elmwood Ave., Providence RI&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;FREE parking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of the Admissions Booth under the Canopy, look for meetup sign and me!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255390889000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251643762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jack-O-Lantern Spectacular</name><id>11237469</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255217400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/11237469/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/f/global_10454191.jpeg</photo_url></item>