<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Railroad Ave &amp; 1A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.725187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-921-2272</phone><name>American BBQ</name><city>Rowley</city><id>1144374</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.865423</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Update 1/14/10:We have discovered that American BBQ closes early so we have pushed the time to an earlier time.  We have been promised the private room at American BBQ which will make discussions a little more private to the group without disturbing other patrons.  American BBQ closes at 9pm but if we feel that we want to continue our discussions we can find a local coffee shop.  I thought we would have a different topic this month but have received numerous requests to have the subject remain the same, with that said we will continue the discussions on Dating &amp;amp; Relationship issues.  Hope to see y'all down at the BBQ &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok so last month's conversation night was a huge success.  The topic of the night was &amp;quot;Dating&amp;quot;, everyone felt very comfortable discussing what was on their minds about dating and relationships.  Topics included, internet dating, sexual relationships, meeting that person and other topics related to dating all while dining on some really good Italian food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month lets bring our memories back to the Summertime and go out to American BBQ in Rowley.  American BBQ has a back room that we are trying to setup so that everyone can hear the conversations around the table. Donna &amp;amp; I are in the process of trying to get this private room from the venue and will keep everyone posted on our progress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although a theme has not been decided upon at this time, we will be organizing this event similiar to last months where we will go around the table and discuss one thing at a time, this way you won't miss any conversations that may be happening at the other end of the table.  If the venue works out we will be able to set the tables in a more conversation friendly environment.  I will be opening a conversation link up on the message board for suggestions on themes for this month, although we could probably continue the conversation of dating from last month and have a night full of conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So go ahead and put your suggestion on the message board or if you want to keep it private you can email me thru this site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on down and have some BBQ and a night of conversation....hope to see ya all at the BBQ.....YEEEHAWWWWWWW&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264460934000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261337985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conversation night at American BBQ</name><id>12121113</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264287600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/12121113/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/3/global_12327475.jpeg</photo_url></item>