<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Wall Street  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.485766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 229-0100</phone><name>Papa Razzi</name><city>Burlington</city><id>899960</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.189434</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Is anyone interested in attending this ACONE event? Seems pretty interesting for a cold February night. Indicate your interest on meetup and on the ACONE site listed below. Note Cocktails start at 6PM, with the event starting at 7PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, February 20, 2013, The Aero Club of New England (ACONE) will host its annual “Ice Breaker” Event at the Papa Razzi in Burlington, MA. Current members are strongly encouraged to bring a prospective new member with them to this year's Ice Breaker event. Garry Kozak, a world renowned salvage expert, will give his presentation on the last flying Sikorsky S-39 Amphibian. This 1930 aircraft was lost some 55 years ago in a very remote lake in Alaska. Garry will take us on a journey of the S-39 history, the story of its tragic loss, and the many futile searches spanning over 40 years. It is a story of frustration, failure, and success; all played out in one of the world’s most scenic places. Garry’s experience will give you an opportunity to live the fantasy, at least vicariously. This will be of great interest to aviation buffs and treasure hunters or anyone who has a little Indiana Jones in them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gathering is at the Papa Razzi (2 Wall St., Burlington, MA 01803). Starting at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00 PM – Open for cocktails (cash bar) &amp;amp; Heavy Hors d’oeuvres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 PM – 7:15 PM – Opening remarks and Introduction (ACONE President) &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 PM – 8:15 - Feature Presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 PM – Closing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Costs: $25 per person, Deadline for a reservation is Sunday, 2/17/13&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register on-line at: www.acone.org/events or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact Deirdre O’Connor – (781) 962-4445 (cell) or (781) 729-0664 (Home)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Estabrook</member_name><member_id>6710962</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra Schweitzer</member_name><member_id>12255001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361454343000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359591670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>“Somewhere in Time: The hunt for the frozen Sikorsky S-39”</name><id>102229542</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361404800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/102229542/</event_url></item>