<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Corner of Route 83 &amp; 25A</address_2><address_1>633 Mt Sinai Coram Rd</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>11766</zip><lat>40.936356</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Heritage Park</name><city>Mount Sinai</city><id>182029</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.013092</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>75.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Psychic Lecture &amp;amp; Buffet Dinner&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;With Free Readings &amp;amp; Healings&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 22nd 5 pm - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Sinai Heritage Trust&lt;br /&gt;(Intersection of Mt. Sinai - Coram Rd. &amp;amp; Rt. 83* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;William &amp;amp; Judith will lecture on:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have you ever wondered what is on the other side? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are you curious to know how psychics and mediums get their information? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;* Would you like to know what kind of messages the spirit world is holding&lt;br /&gt;   for you in 2009?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a fascinating introduction into another dimension. The evening will begin with a 90 minute lecture on the continuation of the soul; insights into how psychics receive their information,  and how readings can be an important healing modality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be followed by a buffet dinner. Also, our certified An-Ra Readers &amp;amp; Healers  will give each participant a private reading and An-Ra Energy Healing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of lecture &amp;amp; dinner is $75. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bonus: Free Individual Reading &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;An-Ra Energy Healing for attendees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Register by Feb. 18th,&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Call Ellen @ 631-513-8183; Seating is Limited.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Judith Grant&lt;/b&gt; is Co director of Pathways To Health,  a Certified Adult Nurse Practitioner, a Clinical Hypnotherapist, and co-creator of The An-Ra Energy Healing System. Over the last 18 years, she has developed her intuitive skills, and has become a full trance channel, and Spiritual Medium. She channels Mary Magdalene, and two master teachers from the Pleiades Star System, Balistar and the Light One. From these guides, she has been receiving valuable information about energy healing, and the chakra medicine.  She is also the author of the book, “Timeless Testaments”, Rolling Away The Stone, which are some of the most powerful transcripts of the Magdalene’s Channeled Sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;William Bezmen, Ph.D. RN., CS&lt;/b&gt; Is co director of Pathways To Health.  For over 30 years he has been working with the deeper mind to assist people to develop their inner senses, so that they can reach their fullest potential. He has been working with many of the Spiritual Guides, and Master Teachers of the Light, to bring the most powerful forms of healing to the planet. He is the founder of the HypnoSynergistic Healing Paradigm, and co-creator of the An-Ra Energy Healing System.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>William &amp; Judith with meet you there</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235783573000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Holistic health &amp; Spiritualist</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Pathways-to-Health</urlname><id>1369837</id><group_lat>40.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-73.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pathways To Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233627174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Lecture, Readings &amp; Dinner</name><id>9659199</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235340000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Pathways-to-Health/events/9659199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/8/global_7174024.jpeg</photo_url></item>