<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/1/a/5/event_28601381.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;Show time is 7:15.&amp;nbsp; I will be at the theater by 6:15, we will go in for seats at 6:45.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Not sure why but the tickets for this one are on sale already, maybe the star studded cast has something to do with it.&amp;nbsp; :)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;It is showing upstairs, so I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.&amp;nbsp; If you get there before me, please snag a table.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;The title of this flick alone made me chuckle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I only hope that it is a really fun B grade action film....love those!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, we will gather in the hallway after the movie is over to discuss the movie a bit, allow for restroom breaks and get a head count for all those who would like to go out to get a drink and a bite to eat after.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Movie details:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; July 29, 2011
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Universal Pictures
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Jon Favreau
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Roberto Orci, Alex Kurtzman, Damon Lindelof, Mark Fergus, Hawk Ostby
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Daniel Craig, Harrison Ford, Olivia Wilde, Sam Rockwell, Adam Beach, Paul Dano, Noah Ringer, Keith Carradine, Clancy Brown, 
&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=21185"&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Ana&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;de&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;la&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;Reguera&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;img src="http://images.intellitxt.com/ast/adTypes/mag-glass_10x10.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; , Abigail Spencer
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Thriller
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;a href="http://cowboysandaliensmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;CowboysandAliensmovie.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; Blockbuster filmmaker Jon Favreau directs Daniel Craig and Harrison Ford in an event film for summer 2011 that crosses the classic Western with the alien-invasion movie in a blazingly original way: " 
&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=21185"&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Cowboys&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;img src="http://images.intellitxt.com/ast/adTypes/mag-glass_10x10.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Aliens." Joined by an arsenal of top moviemakers&amp;mdash;Steven Spielberg, Ron Howard, Brian Grazer, Alex Kurtzman and Roberto Orci&amp;mdash;he brings an all-new action thriller that will take audiences into the Old West, where a lone cowboy leads an uprising against a terror from beyond our world.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;1873. Arizona Territory. A stranger (Craig) with no memory of his past stumbles into the hard desert town of Absolution. The only hint to his history is a mysterious shackle that encircles one wrist. What he discovers is that the people of Absolution don't welcome strangers, and nobody makes a move on its streets unless ordered to do so by the iron-fisted Colonel Dolarhyde (Ford). It's a town that lives in fear.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;But Absolution is about to experience fear it can scarcely comprehend as the desolate city is attacked by marauders from the sky. Screaming down with breathtaking velocity and blinding lights to abduct the helpless one by one, these monsters challenge everything the residents have ever known.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Now, the stranger they rejected is their only hope for salvation. As this gunslinger slowly starts to remember who he is and where he's been, he realizes he holds a secret that could give the town a fighting chance against the alien force. With the help of the elusive traveler Ella (Olivia Wilde), he pulls together a posse comprised of former opponents&amp;mdash;townsfolk, Dolarhyde and his boys, outlaws and Apache warriors&amp;mdash;all in danger of annihilation. United against a common enemy, they will prepare for an epic showdown for survival.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is upstairs I will snag a table by the windows at the top of the escalator, if it is downstairs I will be by the rope near the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312164633000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306857295000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cowboys and Aliens</name><id>20363511</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311977700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/20363511/</event_url></item>