<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

I now know the movie time - the movie is at 7!

I will be at the movie theater at 6:30, 30 minutes before showtime. I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie's upstairs, I'll be at the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand.  We'll head in to the theater at 6:50 or so.

After the movie, we gather just outside the theater doors (the theater wear the movie is showing that is, not outside.) and talk about where we're going for food and drinks. Sometimes I lose people at that point - and I'm not sure if it's because I just lost someone or they didn't want to come to dinner. So, if you are coming to dinner, please find me after the show. I will be wearing that red hat. 'Cause that's my job - to wear the hat!


[b]Synopsis[/b]

Oscar® winners George Clooney and Renée Zellweger match wits in Leatherheads, a quick-witted romantic comedy set against the backdrop of America's nascent pro-football league in 1925.

Clooney plays Dodge Connolly, a charming, brash football hero who is determined to guide his team from bar brawls to packed stadiums. But after the players lose their sponsor and the entire league faces certain collapse, Dodge convinces a college football star to join his ragtag ranks. The captain hopes his latest move will help the struggling sport finally capture the country's attention.

Welcome to the team Carter Rutherford (John Krasinski), America's favorite son. A golden-boy war hero who single-handedly forced multiple German soldiers to surrender in WWI, Carter has dashing good looks and unparalleled speed on the field. This new champ is almost too good to be true, and Lexie Littleton (Zellweger) aims to prove that's the case.

A cub journalist playing in the big leagues, Lexie is a spitfire newswoman who suspects there are holes in Carter's war story. But while she digs, the two teammates start to become serious off-field rivals for her fickle affections.

As the new game of pro-football becomes less like the freewheeling sport he knew and loved, Dodge must both fight to keep his guys together and to get the girl of his dreams. Finding that love and football have a surprisingly similar playbook, however, he has one maneuver he will save just for the fourth quarter...

[b]Website[/b]

&lt;a href="http://www.leatherheadsmovie.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.leatherheadsmovie.com/&lt;/a&gt;

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/Ik68CWaTx78&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie's upstairs, I'll be at the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207535209000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203588892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Leatherheads</name><id>7377033</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207348200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7377033/</event_url></item>