<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 10 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting south of Falls Village, CT off of Rte. 7 at an AT parking area and heading northbound along the Housatonic River, gradually up over Mount Prospect, then over Wetauwanchu Mountain, finally a steep decent to the ending point (about 400 ft. down) on the Rte. 44 AT parking area. I've done this one before in April, 2008 so I know what to expect. It isn't too difficult and it has some varied views. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 9 AM at the Rte. 44 AT parking area on shoulder of road (see below) and shuttle to the hike starting location south of Falls Village, CT off of Rte. 7 on the shoulder of the road. We'll hike at times along the Housatonic River with possibly stunning views of large waterfalls (Great Falls, flow depends very much on water levels and hydro plant operation).  A lunch possibly at the Limestone Spring Lean-to for shelter and to replenish our water. The trip down to the shelter is steep on the short cliff by the small stream. There is a great view called Rand's View of Race Mtn. and Mt. Everette to the north-west. Finally, we end at the Rte. 44 AT parking area where we started and most vehicles are located. I figure we will end the hike no later than 4:30 PM. Some of us will shuttle back to the other end to get our vehicles. We will likely stop for dinner at a local establishment.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If more than 7 people go, we will need assistance in driving people between the meeting location and starting point. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we should come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== &lt;b&gt;ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES&lt;/b&gt; == &lt;br /&gt;* Daypack &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in  &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Hat &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold morning &amp;amp; 53 F afternoon, avoid cotton as it stays wet. &lt;br /&gt;* 2 quart water &lt;br /&gt;* Trail lunch. High energy meal should be planned, no cooking &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp/flashlight -Just in case since we may hike near dark&lt;br /&gt;== &lt;b&gt;OPTIONAL GEAR&lt;/b&gt; == &lt;br /&gt;* Camera and extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the meetup location &amp;amp; AT ending point on Rte. 44&lt;/b&gt; (around 50 Canaan Rd.) north of Salisbury, CT (park on east side of road):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Salisbury&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=50+Canaan+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06068-1600&amp;amp;country=US" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT hike trailhead dirt parking area, intersection of Rte. 7&lt;/b&gt; (Lime Rock Rd.) &lt;b&gt;and Rte. 112&lt;/b&gt; (Lime Rock Rd.) south of Falls Village, CT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/l=41.9327;g=-73.3634" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=41.9327, Long.=-73.3634]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the parking area on the shoulder of the road on Rte. 44 (see event description). A dark BLUE Grand Caravan Sport (mine) and a silver Jeep Liberty will be there (our member Janice's).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258985591000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258602598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT over Mt. Prospect &amp; Wetauwanchu Mtn. near Falls Village CT</name><id>11909536</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258812000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11909536/</event_url></item>