<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;The Sound of Music&amp;quot; 45th Anniversary Celebration, a Sing-a-Long Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of your favorite things returned to the big screen at selected theatres on October 19th and there is one more screening this Tuesday October 26 6:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Don’t miss the opportunity to sing along with Julie Andrews (The Tooth Fairy) and Christopher Plummer (Up) in the extraordinary, Academy Award-winning classic back in theatres in true HD! &lt;br /&gt;This exclusive event will entail the sing-along version of the fully restored feature with timeless hits like &amp;quot;The Sound of Music&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Edelweiss&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;My Favorite Things&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Climb Ev’ry Mountain&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Do-Re-Mi.”&lt;br /&gt;Plus, see I’ll Sing Once More: The Sound of Music Today, an exclusive piece that pays tribute to this timeless classic by looking at The Sound of Music effects on popular culture. Audiences will get a unique look at the brilliant restoration The Sound of Music, be whisked back to Salzburg for a travelogue where the movie was filmed, and be treated to contemporary and surprising tributes ranging from modern dance and rock band salutes to an all-marionette version. All brought to you by NCM Fathom in partnership with Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment in celebration of the release of The Sound of Music on Blu-Ray™ and DVD Combo Packs available November 2.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My all time favorite movie, lets meet Tuesday October 26th at the Lowell Showcase Cinemas, &lt;br /&gt;showtime 6:30pm, 3 hrs. 30 min&lt;br /&gt;tickets $12.50, Available at the theatre &lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;you can purchase your tickets online at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fathomevents.com/upcoming/locations/03060/10/26/2010/Premiere/event/soundofmusic10_26.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fathomeven...&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>6pm at ticket counter</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra S</member_name><member_id>4793319</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288188659000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287949451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Sing-Along Event</name><id>15212862</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288130400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15212862/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/0/global_15205072.jpeg</photo_url></item>