<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1555 Asylum Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06105</zip><lat>41.776393</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-722-6543</phone><name>Elizabeth Park</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>892965</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.718337</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What a great combination: A day celebrating roses at gorgeous Elizabeth Park and a chance to hear a live reading of &lt;u&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wallace Stevens&lt;/b&gt; Poetry&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/u&gt; at 1 p.m. in the Pond House!  Bring a picnic or have lunch at the Pond House.  Feed the ducks! Smell the roses!  I plan to get there at 12:30 to get seats, but come anytime.  If you do not come to the poetry reading, it may be hard to find each other, but we can make arrangements and exchange phone numbers.  The festival goes from 11 a.m.-4 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.elizabethpark.org/calendar-2010.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.elizabethp...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://attractions.uptake.com/blog/elizabeth-park-rose-garden-hartford-connecticut-4627.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://attractions.up...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sailairtravel.com/articles/rose-festivals-and-gardens.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sailairtra...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;(**at this site I learned that the Elizabeth Park Rose Garden dates back to 1904!)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The poetry reading is sponsored by&lt;u&gt; the Friends &amp;amp; Enemies of Wallace Stevens&lt;/u&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.stevenspoetry.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.stevenspoe...&lt;/a&gt; who say on their website listing: &amp;quot; this annual event is held in memory of our former board member, poet Hugh Odgen, who organized the event for many years.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Poems will be read by Benjamin Grossberg and Margot Schilpp.  From the website event posting: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benjamin S. Grossberg teaches poetry and creative writing at the University of Hartford. His books are Sweet Core Orchard, winner of the 2008 Tampa Review Prize (U. of Tampa, 2009), and Underwater Lengths in a Single Breath, winter of the 2005 Snyder Prize (Ashland Poetry Press, 2007). A chapbook, The Auctioneer Bangs his Gavel, was published by Kent State in 2006. His poems have appeared in Paris Review, Southwest Review, and The Pushcart Book of Poetry: The Best Poems from Thirty years of the Pushcart Prize. New poems have appeared or are forthcoming in New England Review, North American Review, and The Missouri Review, among other journals.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Margot Schilpp's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Schilpp's books of poems are The World's Last Night (2001), Laws of My Nature (2005), and Civil Twilight (forthcoming in 2012), all published by Carnegie Mellon University Press. Her poems have been published widely in literary journals, including American Poetry Review, The Southern Review, Cincinnati Review, Denver Quarterly, Green Mountains Review, Hotel Amerika, and New England Review.  &lt;br /&gt;  --- &lt;br /&gt;A Wallace Stevens link: &lt;a href="http://kirjasto.sci.fi/wsteven.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://kirjasto.sci.f...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277332611000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275076368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rose Weekend with Wallace Stevens Poetry Reading</name><id>13626502</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276965000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13626502/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/4/global_15345236.jpeg</photo_url></item>