<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Murphy Dr</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03062</zip><lat>42.739288</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)883-1490 </phone><name>The Holistic Self Care Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>230214</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.487503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new organization called &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Spiritual Enlightenment Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has recently been developed. This group was put together to begin raising funds for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Enlightenment Education Scholarship Fund.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;All proceeds go toward providing scholarships to deserving students with financial need that are ready to go further with their spiritual growth.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On October 20th there will be an open house from 11-4 for visitors to find out more information, take tours and make donations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 6-9 there will be an open house and a LIVE Auction at 7:30. There will prozes and Appetizers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a bake sale throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donors will receive donation gifts in relation to the amount that are donated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some prizes being offered for auction; A Lake house retreat for 1 week, 1 hour Photo Shoot by George, (check out the display!) 2 hours of yard work, 2 hours of handy man services, 2 hours of house cleaning, dinner for 6-8 people catered and served by Doug and Barb Tremlett, massages, Reiki sessions, many other services. It will be a great evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please come to the center and celebrate the new scholarship, the creative fundraising and the personal and professional growth of our sister and friend Barb Tremlett as she beings her journey to Nepal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to thank some of our sponsors, Sue Watson Lake House, InterActive Synergy, LLC, Best Fitness, Vitamin Shoppe, Herner Chiropractic, The Skin and Body Spa,&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And a large group of business owners from the center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A letter from Barb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Dear Friends,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people are called to do great things. I was called to open a wellness center to provide answers to help people to help themselves. Whether it is mental, emotional, physical or spiritual we are all on a path of improvement. Providing this center has changed many peoples live and given many people their lives back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As my life has traveled down this road of understanding I realize more and more I still have so much more to do. I have felt, like many other people feel, something is missing. In my search to find the missing piece I have received a call to go on to deeper spiritual journey. I have accepted a calling to go to the next level in my studies on where we come from and how to share it with the world. As my spirit and soul calls me to this next level of work I have decided to share this calling with my friends and the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the next level on spiritual enlightenment I am traveling to Nepal with a large group of other spiritual seeking individuals from all over the world. We are traveling to learn more about healing, enlightenment and how to spread the love that we all have within us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The calling came to me in my heart and I never addressed the things that could hold me back. I only looked forward to how this can effect change in me and how I can then effect change in those that are also on their journey of soul searching. As with many things in life, a journey to Nepal is costly. A key group of people related to &amp;ldquo;Awaken~The Divine You&amp;rdquo; and The Holistic Self Care Center have come together support me in my expansion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your love and support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Namaste my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>www.thehsccenter.com see Spirit of Nepal Event!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319247139000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318713528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spirit of Nepal Scholarship Fundraiser</name><id>37518372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319148000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/37518372/</event_url></item>