<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Medford Ma</address_2><address_1>Mystic River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.420162</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 718-9600</phone><name>Tennis Courts</name><city>Medford</city><id>239202</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110382</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://WWW.SPORTSDEPOTBOSTON.COM" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;HELLO AGAIN,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I HAVE NARROW THE LOCATION TO ALLSTON.  ( I WAS LEANING TOWARD SOHO BUT THE PARKING MAY BE DIFFICULT) SINCE THE EVENT IS SPORTS RELATED LETS MEET AT THE SPORTS DEPOT IN ALLSTON!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOPE ALL CAN MAKE IT ANYTIME AFTER 6PM I'LL BE THERE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THERE IS PARKING AND ITS LOCATED NOT FAR FROM THE T&lt;br /&gt;WEB SITE WWW.SPORTSDEPOTBOSTON.COM&lt;br /&gt;HOPE TO ADD LINKS FOR DIRECTIONS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CASUAL GATHERING AFTERWORK FOR APPETIZERS/DRINKS/DINNER AND HOPEFULLY LOTS TO  DISCUSS REGARDING TENNIS PLANS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING ALL MEMBERS IF ANY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS PLEASE FEEL FREE TO CONTACT ME ( LAF620@RCN.COM )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE YOU THERE&lt;br /&gt;TAKE CARE&lt;br /&gt;LARA / LAURA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello everyone ! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WOW what a response !!  THANKS to all for replying   Can't wait to meet everyone and  start playing tennis !! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the large response and several members unable to attend Wednesday I am Looking into changing the scheduled date to meet up to  Tuesday MARCH 20TH ANYTIME AFTER 6:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;Casual afterwork gathering on the first day of Spring ? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any input please feel free to contact me I want to allow everyone to meet and have the opportunity to discuss tennis plans! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also I am trying to find a location central to all the replies.  ( Allston Arlington Bedford Boston Cambridge Medford Malden Somerville etc) that will accommodate all of us and hopefully plenty of parking!!  Of course accessible to the T as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am leaning toward Cambridge / Brighten ( restaurant) location to meet up with everyone and discuss tennis teams and convenient times for players to schedule court time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will Post a specific location within the next week . &lt;br /&gt;If anyone has any suggestions or additional input please again feel free to contact me  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOOK forward to meeting everyone real soon &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Kenger</member_name><member_id>4819069</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174602691000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Tennis Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tennis-240</urlname><id>432728</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Somerville Tennis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1171911951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Somerville Tennis March Meetup</name><id>5494582</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174429800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tennis-240/events/5494582/</event_url></item>