<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***Meetup Canceled this month - Brett Zaccardi, the speaker, had a change in schedule and is unable to attend***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between MySpace, YouTube, the exploding blogosphere, Web 2.0, and the undeniable fascination with social media, marketing/advertising agencies and design firms with an understanding of online viral and word of mouth marketing are in high demand. More than ever, marketers and brands need to find ways to reach their audiences and spread their messages on the basis of just one of the five senses:  sight.  This means that graphic, web, and video designers hold a powerful position within the current online climate.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Brett Zaccardi of Boston-based alternative marketing agency Street Attack will be speaking about the ways in which brands and ideas spread through online grassroots communities through viral and word of mouth messaging.  He will utilize real world examples and case studies to demonstrate how designers can fine-tune their skills to visually woo the social media landscape.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540678000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162229989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Social Media Explosion:  It's All About the Visuals</name><id>5232452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168470000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/5232452/</event_url></item>