<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Faneuil Hall Sq, Boston</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Faneuil Hall</name><id>442262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Second Annual Boston Tea Party and Conference for 9/11 Truth! - Scientists &amp;amp; Citizens Speak Out!&lt;br /&gt;December 15 &amp;amp;16, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building on the success of last year?s inaugural event, Boston 9/11 Truth is proud to present two days of 911 truth activism at this year?s Boston Tea Party and Conference for 9/11 Truth, to be held Saturday and Sunday, December 15 and 16, 2007. This year?s theme, ?Scientists and Citizens Speak Out,? reinforces our commitment to the broadest exposure possible of the scientific, criminal and political issues being covered-up and/or ignored by our government and the media concerning the events of September 11, 2001.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCIENTISTS &amp;amp; CITIZENS SPEAK OUT!&lt;br /&gt;December 15 &amp;amp;16, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray McGovern CIA veteran and founder of ?Veteran Intelligence Professionals for Sanity? will present speakers Richard Gage, AIA Architect, Steven Jones, PhD Former Professor of Physics at Brigham Young University, UL Laboratories whistleblower Kevin Ryan, and Joel S. Hirshhorn, PhD Former Professor, Metallurgical Engineering University of Wisconsin, Former Senior Staff Member - Congressional Office of Technology.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a growing concern within the international scientific community that the official explanations put forth by the US government vis-à-vis The 9/11 Commission Report and the NIST and FEMA reports concerning the collapse of World Trade Center Towers 1,2 and often ignored Building 7, contain not only scientifically unsubstantiated theories, but, in many cases, either defy or ignore the laws of physics, metallurgy and a host of other applied sciences in their calculations and conclusions. The cross-section of disciplines represented by each of the symposium participants provides applicable scholarly and professional viewpoints concerning the one theory the government and media refuses to entertain ? controlled demolition. It is their hope, along with the sponsors of the symposium, that the world-renowned community of scientists, architects and engineers in the Boston area test for themselves the veracity of the claims made by government agencies, as well as those of their opponents, with the understanding that the laws governing the sciences must not be manipulated or ignored for political ends on either side of the controversy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more details on this event, see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston911conference.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Boston Tea Party and Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or &lt;a href="http://boston911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston911Truth.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?The Destruction of World Trade Center Towers 1, 2 and 7: A Case for Controlled Demolition.?&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 15, 2007 9:30 am ET - 6:30 pm ET&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542693000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196373042000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Tea Party and Conference</name><id>6826964</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197727200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/6826964/</event_url></item>