<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You want abundance. How do you get out of your own way and tap into your Abundance Spirit everyday?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll &lt;i&gt;listen**&lt;/i&gt; to &lt;b&gt;Sonia Choquette, world-renowned revolutionary intuitive, vibrational healer, and teacher,&lt;/b&gt; share many wonderful ways for you to connect with the Spirit within you, and let Spirit direct and fill your life with abundance.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll discover:&lt;br /&gt;- Where we tend to get stuck in obtaining &amp;amp; then maintaining the abundance &amp;quot;attraction&amp;quot; factor&lt;br /&gt;- The one fundamental thing that needs to change before you take action&lt;br /&gt;- What you can do to easily connect and start the flow of abundance&lt;br /&gt;  ....when you wake up and when showering &lt;br /&gt;- The other Power you want to tap into to receive abundance (besides the Power of Intention).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of cos, the best part, as a community, we provide each other the Power of Believing Eyes.  So, join us to mastermind, support and inspire each other to connect with our Abundance Spirit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**We'll be listening to a recording of a Q&amp;amp;A with Sonia Choquette re: The Abundance Spirit.  Together, we'll practice some of her suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Sonia Choquette:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.soniachoqutte.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sonia is an internationally acclaimed spiritual teacher, intuitive guide and masterful catalyst whose special gift is to energetically activate the highest vibration and free the authentic Spirit in everyone she meets. She releases people from the restriction and fear of the ego and guides them through the portals to joy, wholeness, and personal empowerment in every area of their life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has also been a personal Intuitive advisor to such New Age Leaders as Louise Hay, Julia Cameron, Caroline Myss, Dr. Wayne Dyer, pop icon Billy Corgan of the Smashing Pumpkins rock band, and professional consultant to international business leaders such as Charlotte Beers, Fortune 500 Company CEO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up. Many of you have been wonderful with this and we very much appreciate your understanding and support!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For parking and directions (via T or driving) info to Dave's loft :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) Go here: &lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/about/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/files/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Sign in&lt;br /&gt;(3) Scroll down and open file &amp;quot;Directions &amp;amp; Parking_BostonLOA Meetup&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267571396000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263344732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Connect with Your Abundance Spirit Everyday</name><id>hjcjdyndbdb</id><headcount>44</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265155200000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/12303627/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/6/global_12820918.jpeg</photo_url></item>