<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>184 Dudley Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02119</zip><lat>42.328632</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hibernian Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>5254352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082077</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**This is an invitation, not strictly a meetup. This is a great, informative event and you don't have to attend the whole time to get value out of it ** FACING LOVE is a TV talk show- style symposium exploring the intricacies and dynamics of the Black/Latino Male-Black/Latino Female relationship. The THEME of Facing Love V is : HOW DOES EDUCATION/MISEDUCATION CONTRIBUTE TO THE DYSFUNCTION IN BLACK/LATINO FAMILIES AND COMMUNITIES? &amp;#147;How you behave is dependent upon what you THINK of yourself...... What you think of yourself is dependent upon what you KNOW of yourself... What you know of yourself is dependent upon what you have been TOLD...&amp;#148; -Prof. Runoko Rashidi This fundamental principle speaks to EDUCATION and to what degree it has affected/is affecting Black/Latino people's existence. Facing Love V will explore not only current perceptions of the educational process in America...but will also delve into the pitfalls of MIS-EDUCATION and how it has shaped Black/Latino perceptions of ourselves as a people and inter-genderally. Facing Love V will be anchored by a presentation from the dynamic, and renowned UMAR ABDULLAH JOHNSON who is a PSYCHOLOGIST, ORATOR, POLITICAL SCIENTIST, EDUCATOR out of Philadelphia. More guests and performances to be announced! *Free buffet! *Free Giveaways! *Dollar raffle for KEITH SWEAT concert tickets! *Facing Love tees, I Love Black People tees and Facing Love V CDs will be on hand and available.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cabral Thomas</member_name><member_id>9824758</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330803993000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330649357000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FACING LOVE V</name><id>54586882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330799400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/54586882/</event_url></item>