<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>First off, sorry about the long delay, everyone. I've had a hectic late November - early December, then holidays, then working on getting us meeting space at Microsoft NERD. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaking of, it's all set! Our next meetup will occur on Wednesday, January 13th, 2010 at the Microsoft NERD building. Two of our members, Matt Chisholm and Ed Bielawa, will each present a Grails plugin they've worked on. This should certainly be helpful for anyone looking into how plugins are created and integrate with Grails, as well as give you ideas for future plugins. The two we'll see are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Red 5, Matt - &amp;quot;Demo will include a walk through of the plugin internals and integration approach. Demo of the video recording features, video streaming features as well as a small demo using AMF/Flash Remoting with the plugin.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-gSPT - the Grails Scrum Planning Too, Ed - &amp;quot;It allows you to create a scrum team, size stories, assign stories to a sprint, create tasks, generate burndowns, and approve stories.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should be interesting; hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: I have to let NERD know who's coming 2 days in advance, as you all will have to check in at security on the way in. So, RSVP before that!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Abigail Adams meeting room, located on the first floor of the conference center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Pember</member_name><member_id>9587085</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263709376000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Grails-Boston</urlname><id>1458975</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Grails Users' Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262115037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presentation of Member created Plugins</name><id>12169583</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263429000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Grails-Boston/events/12169583/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/global_9810037.jpeg</photo_url></item>