<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.207620</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>NH State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>671402</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.536620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday, January 19, 2013, starting at noon, in front of the NH State House in Concord: "Guns Across America" rally. "Bring a pro-gun, pro-2A sign." &lt;a href="http://www.examiner.com/article/guns-across-america-rallies-being-organized-for-saturday-jan-19th-2013/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.examiner.com/article/guns-across-america-rallies-being-organized-for-saturday-jan-19th-2013/&lt;/a&gt; (Started by Eric Reed, an airline captain in Texas.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WARNING: NH State law, RSA 111:15, suggests that if you openly display firearms in a group gathering, you are at risk of arrest and of having your firearms confiscated. Here is the statute in its entirety: &lt;br /&gt;

111:15 Armed Civilian Groups. – No organization, society, club, post, order, league or other combination of persons, or civil group, or any members thereof, are authorized to assume any semblance of military organization or character by bearing or possessing rifles, pistols, sabres, clubs, or military weapons of any kind, or wearing a military uniform of any kind. Any person violating any of the provisions of this section or taking part in such military organization shall be guilty of a misdemeanor if a natural person, or guilty of a felony if any other person; and any rifles, pistols, sabres, clubs or other military weapons used in violation hereof shall be forfeited. This section shall not apply to regularly constituted military units under state or federal laws; and nothing in this section shall be construed as forbidding the possession and use of rifles for color guards or firing squad purposes, or the wearing of uniforms of a military character, by an organization composed wholly of veteran soldiers who participated in any war of the United States, or by any other recognized fraternal group of long-standing in the community which uses rifles or sabres merely as a part of its ritualistic exercises and which is not specifically disapproved by the President of the United States, the Department of Defense, or the governor. &lt;br /&gt;

Source. 1941, 46:15. RL 144:15. RSA 111:15. 1973, 528:42. 1981, 327:7, eff. Aug. 16, 1981&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it a stretch to say that there's a risk of arrest and confiscation? How might an anti-gun state government official interpret "or other combination of persons, or civil group, or any members thereof"? How about “by bearing or possessing rifles, pistols, sabres, [or] clubs”?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…and before one argues that “…or other military weapons” should be interpreted to make an exception for non-military weapons (whatever they are), we point out that “clubs” aren’t ordinarily considered military weapons, but if they’re included in the statute, how could revolvers, for example, be considered excluded? No, the statute is drafted (in the "bearing or possessing" clause) so that rifles, pistols, sabres, AND clubs are considered "military weapons."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fair or not, unconstitutional or not, do you want to have your guns thrown into a bucket for years while your case works its way up to the Supreme Court? Sure, it's a gamble... but gamble means risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pgnh.org/upcoming_local_2a_events_and_a_warning" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.pgnh.org/upcoming_local_2a_events_and_a_warning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358876223000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358343715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Guns Across America" rally in Concord</name><id>99870342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358614800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/99870342/</event_url></item>