<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's Have a Meetup and  get our intermediate and moderate rated hikers together and hike this great trail.  Lonesome Lake was one of my very first White Mountain hikes- a beautiful site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/5/2/event_1273138.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our intermediate/easy paced team&lt;/b&gt; will have the Lonesome Lake hut as a destination and depending on how the group feels, continue or enjoy the hut and return back to the trailhead.  This is a good hike for those just starting with winter hiking- I hike at an easy pace and want everyone to feel comfortable.   If the hike is too slow- take some pictures.  We will test your gear, make sure you're wearing your snowshoes right and get you ready for the longer hikes.  This shorter destination is a very nice hike for kids. if its seems too short, there is lots of trail to keep hiking on. Our turn around time is 1pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/5/3/event_1273139.jpegThe" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos2.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; 4K team will plan on summiting both peaks. The pace will be moderate and all hikers should have experience in mountain winter hiking. The leader will set a turn around time that all hikers will adhere to so that you can finish at a reasonable time and get home safely.  Know the weather forecast and turn early if it doesn't look possible to summit safely- That mountain will be here another day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All hikers are expected to hike in a group and stay in your group. No one should need to worry about where the next hiker is. If you cant see each other you will never hear them either!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the AMC hut. It's winter so self service. This is a four season hut so the bunkhouses are available.  Pack snacks/ drinks, you can get hot water here and warm up.  Restrooms.  Dogs are not allowed in AMC huts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AMC Guide information  Copywritten-   for your personal use only- do not distribute&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; starting at Lonesome Lake Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 0.03 mi/1 min/0 ft on the Lonesome Lake Trail&lt;/b&gt; The trail leaves the parking lot at a large trail sign, crosses the Pemigewasset River on a footbridge and then crosses the Pemi Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Pemi Trail&lt;/b&gt;  hike 0.30 mi/15 min/+170 ft on the Lonesome Lake Trail &lt;br /&gt; It follows a yellow-blazed path through the campground, climbing at a moderate grade. Then a bridge crosses a small brook at a sharp left turn in the trail, and the Hi-Cannon Trail leaves right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;to the junction of Hi-Cannon Trail&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.90 mi/52 min/+834 ft on the Lonesome Lake Trail &lt;br /&gt; From this point, the trail ascends by three long switchbacks, then descends slightly to a junction near the shore of Lonesome Lake, where the old bridle path ends; here the Cascade Brook Trail enters left and the Dodge Cutoff diverges right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; to Lonesome Lake&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.25 mi/8 min/-22 ft on the Cascade Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the junction with the Lonesome Lake Trail and the Dodge Cutoff, the trail continues along the east edge of the lake. It soon reaches a junction with the Fishin' Jimmy Trail, which leads west to Lonesome Lake Hut. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;to the junction of Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail and Fishin' Jimmy Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.05 mi/2 min/+4 ft on the Fishin' Jimmy Trail Diverging from the Cascade Brook Trail at the south end of Lonesome Lake, this trail crosses the outlet brook on a bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.04 mi/2 min/+11 ft on the Fishin' Jimmy Trail &lt;br /&gt; Then the trail passes the junction with the Around-Lonesome-Lake Trail near the beach at the southwest corner of the lake, and reaches Lonesome Lake Hut. &lt;br /&gt; to AMC Lonesome Lake Hut &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.91 mi/1 hr 32 min/+997 ft on the Fishin' Jimmy Trail &lt;br /&gt; It runs around the lower end of a ridge coming down from the Middle Cannon Ball, making several ascents and descents and passing over a ledgy ridge crest. It then crosses several small brooks, with the last reliable water source in a small mossy, ledgy brook, and soon begins to climb, at times steeply but with occasional minor descents as well. Then it curls around a large boulder on the left and passes through a fairly flat area. It reaches the top of the serious climbing and ascends gradually to Kinsman Junction and the Kinsman Ridge Trail, north of Kinsman Pond Shelter on the Kinsman Pond Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;to Kinsman Junction&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.20 mi/6 min/+112 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; Here the Fishin’ Jimmy Trail (a part of the AT) enters on the left from Lonesome Lake, and the Kinsman Pond Trail runs straight ahead, leading to Kinsman Pond and Kinsman Pond Shelter. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.40 mi/12 min/+420 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; From Kinsman Junction, the Kinsman Ridge Trail (now part of the AT for the rest of its length) turns right and climbs up ledges to the junction where the Mt. Kinsman Trail enters on the right, then continues to climb steeply to the summit of North Kinsman. &lt;br /&gt; to North Kinsman &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.90 mi/35 min/+54 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; Here a side path (sign) leads to the left 25 yd. to a fine outlook to the Franconias and continues, descending steeply, another 70 yd. to a ledge that looks directly down on Kinsman Pond. The true summit of North Kinsman is a pointed boulder on the left (east) side of the main trail, 30 yd. north of the outlook spur. The main trail descends steadily to the col between North and South Kinsman, then ascends relatively easily and passes 15 yd. to the west of the north knob of South Kinsman’s summit. The Kinsman Ridge Trail then crosses a scrub-filled sag to the bare south knob of South Kinsman, which is very exposed to the weather. (Note: The section of the trail between South Kinsman and Harrington Pond may require much extra time, particularly for those with heavy packs, and is also somewhat exposed to weather.) &lt;br /&gt; to South Kinsman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Retrace back to lafayette place parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Disclaimer&lt;br /&gt; You acknowledge that (i) hiking, climbing and camping and related outdoor activities entail inherent risks and hazards, (ii) that conditions are variable and the content does not purport to be error-free&lt;br /&gt;or up to date, (iii) the presence of some warnings does not mean that all dangerous situations or changes in conditions will result in warnings on the AMC Site (and, thus, in this report), and (iv) ratings are very general, assume good weather and trail conditions and good physical fitness and constitute only one factor of many in a decision to hike a trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Important Phone Numbers   Emergency 911&lt;br /&gt;Appalachian Mountain Club Pinkham Notch Visitor Center 603-466-2721&lt;br /&gt;U.S. Forest Service 603-528-8721&lt;br /&gt;National Weather Service 603-225-5191&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional WMNF Information  Camping is allowed anywhere in the WMNF, but is prohibited or restricted in Forest Protection Areas (FPAs). Generally,  in Forest Protection Areas no camping is permitted above treeline (where trees are less than 8 feet tall), within ¼ mile of a  trailhead or road, within 200 feet of a trail.&lt;br /&gt;Wilderness Areas  In accordance with USFS Wilderness policy, trails in designated Wilderness areas are generally maintained to a lower  standard than trails outside Wilderness. They may be rough, overgrown or essentially unmarked with minimal signage, and considerable care may be required to follow them. Hiking and camping group size must be no larger than 10 people.&lt;br /&gt;Camping and fires are also prohibited above treeline (where trees are less than 8 feet tall) except in winter, when camping  is permitted above treeline in places where snow cover is at least 2 feet, but not on any frozen body of water.&lt;br /&gt;Alpine Zone  Hikers are encouraged to be particularly careful in their activities above treeline because the plants that grow there already  have to cope with the severity of the environment. No plants should ever be picked or otherwise damaged. Hikers are urged to stay on trails or walk very carefully on rocks so as not to kill fragile alpine vegetation. AMC urges hikers to  become citizen-scientists and help AMC in alpine plant monitoring – see www.outdoors.org/mountainwatch for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Safety Tips from the Appalachian Mountain Club&lt;br /&gt;Here's the essential clothing and gear you need — even for a day hike — in the Northeast's mountains in the spring, summer, or fall. Always check the weather and prepare for the worst  conditions; make plans with your group's abilities in mind; and plan an alternate route in  case of bad weather, injury, illness, or slower than expected travel time.&lt;br /&gt;Avoiding Hypothermia: Hypothermia can occur when your core body temperature falls below&lt;br /&gt;normal. This can easily happen when you are exposed to cold winds or wetness. You can avoid hypothermia if you guard against dehydration, fatigue, cold winds, and wet clothes. Be sure to:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Dress warmly, in layers.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Stay dry.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Protect yourself from wind, rain, and snow. (This can be done most effectively by wearing clothes that block wind&lt;br /&gt;and moisture.)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Eat high-energy snacks and drink plenty of water.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Do not over-exert.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#1048707; Pack essential gear, even on day hikes.&lt;br /&gt;Essential Gear: Be sure to wear or bring the following:&lt;br /&gt;Wool sweater or synthetic pile jacket * Hat * Gloves or mittens&lt;br /&gt;Bandanna or handkerchief * Long pants (avoid cotton)&lt;br /&gt;Wind and rain gear (jacket and pants)&lt;br /&gt;5  Extra socks * Sturdy boots * Polypropylene or wool underwear&lt;br /&gt;First-aid kit * Waterproof matches. * Whistle * Knife.&lt;br /&gt;Guidebook, trail map, and compass. * High-energy snacks.&lt;br /&gt;Two to four quarts of water, per person. * Flashlight or headlamp with fresh batteries.&lt;br /&gt;Sunscreen. * Insect repellent. * Plastic trash bags&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consider carrying a sleeping bag in case you are forced to sleep out overnight. If you're traveling in a group, carry at least one sleeping bag. It is an emergency tool that can keep an injured hiker warm until help arrives.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my Gold Honda CRV  There are 2 lots- we will meet in the north lot, not the lot where the Information center is, though you may need to park there is its full.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295967356000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294748831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Two Level Hike:  Lonesome Lake  4 mi and the Kinsmans  4K  10 mi</name><id>16005885</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295789400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/16005885/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/3/global_1273139.jpeg</photo_url></item>