<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Centre St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MacKenzie Center</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>317184</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190002</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The 1-hour dance lesson begins at 7:30, so please be on-time if you'd like to join in. Once again, no partner is necessary - you'll get to meet a lot of new people as partners are rotated throughout the lesson time. :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Swing Dancing from 8:30 pm to 12:00 am Dress is casual to vintage. No partner is necessary Beginners &amp;amp; beyond are welcome! The Boston/Providence Single Parents meetup and The Concord/Metrowest Singles Meet Up will also be there to share in the fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE LOVE DOGS&lt;br /&gt;Based out of Boston, this party on wheels has spent the last decade wowing audiences and critics alike with their combination of great musicianship and relentless energy. The Dogs combine elements of jump blues, New Orleans R&amp;amp;B and early rock?n?roll into their own powerhouse sound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston ~ Take Rt.9 West to CENTRE STREET exit about 2.5 miles past Chestnut Hill Mall. At the end of the exit go right. Follow Centre St. (.8) tenth of a mile to the MacKenzie Center on left After MacKenzie Center, take Crescent Ave. left to parking and entrance in the rear&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 128 / 95 ~ Take Rt. 9 exit # 20A East toward Boston about 1 mile. At the first traffic light, there will be a small shopping plaza on the right. Just after that will be a Dunkin Donuts, take the next exit on right-Centre St. Exit does a 180 degree turn and you dead end onto Centre St (which may say Winchester St. but becomes Centre St.). Take a right onto Winchester St. (which becomes Center St.) and follow it for (0.8) tenth of a mile to the MacKenzie Center on left (red brick building). After MacKenzie Center building, take left onto Crescent Ave (a church will be on your right). and then another left to parking and entrance in the rear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Mass Pike ~ Take exit 17 to Centre Street toward Newton Centre. Go through Newton Centre 1 Block past Beacon St. Holly Cleaners on the left, Sacred Heart Church on right. MacKenzie Center is on the next right hand corner. Take Crescent Ave. right BEFORE the building to park in the rear and entrance &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wannadance.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wannadance...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185147103000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183743701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swing Dance to Love Dogs</name><id>5983683</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184974200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/5983683/</event_url></item>