<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our event will additionally coincide with National Preparedness Month (Department of Homeland Security - Federal Emergency Management Agency). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will you be safer now than you were four years ago? Defining the cutting edge for &lt;b&gt;Terrorism and Technology&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though our memory of the events of 9/11 begins to fade, the lessons learned that day and afterward, are still with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suitcase nuclear weapons, wide-scale chemical attacks, human-engineered pandemics, and debilitating cyber attacks were once the subject of spy movies and techno-thriller novels.  Today they are all too real.  What steps are being taken to detect, monitor, protect, and mitigate these threats?  Are we safer now than eight years ago?  What about four years ago?  In the battle against terrorism, are our defensive technologies up to the task of countering such weapons?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On September 15th a panel of experts will answer these questions and provide useful insight into the business opportunities associated with combating terrorism with technology.  Starting with an update on current government and international initiatives, we will quickly move to a discussion of some of the innovative technologie4s being deployed in the battle against domestic and  international terrorism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in learning about evolving national and international standards, what can and is being done to protect the public and business community against terrorist attacks, and the direction of technology, you should attend this conference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator/Keynote: &lt;br /&gt;Don Byrne, North River Solutions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panel: &lt;br /&gt;John Bagley, Raytheon &lt;br /&gt;W. Russ Webster, DHS &lt;br /&gt;Rich Pietravalle, Mitre Corp &lt;br /&gt;Special Agent Jim Burrell, FBI&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Georgia</member_name><member_id>6917121</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 7170621</member_name><member_id>7170621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256079527000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245249716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Terrorism and Technology</name><id>10671912</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253053800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/10671912/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>