<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 Embankment Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.361889</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charlesbank/Lederman Park at Teddy Ebersol's Red Sox Fields</name><city>Boston</city><id>1650261</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072601</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You know &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Esplanade"&gt;the Esplanade&lt;/a&gt; as Boston's park along the Charles River. This walking tour tells the story of how it got there while walking among incredible views along the Charles River Basin.&amp;nbsp;As many of you already know, much of what we see in Boston is the product of land-making and development. The Charles River and the Esplanade that we see today is also the result of a series of engineering projects building up to this urban oasis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tour begins with Frederick Law Olmsted's Charlesbank, the first outdoor "gymnasium" in the country, precursor to today's 17-mile Charles River Reservation, and now home to Teddy Ebersol's Red Sox Fields. Working our way upriver, we'll take a look at some of the well-known and, of course, the lesser known artifacts that reveal the the history of the Esplanade and the champions who fought to convert a smelly embankment between an exclusive neighborhood and polluted waterway into a recreational water park open to all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a debut tour on the June Boston By Foot Tour of the Month.&amp;nbsp;The tour is $15 but only $5 for Boston By Foot card holders. See www.bostonbyfoot.org for information about becoming a &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/"&gt;Boston By Foot member&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the Esplanade under the Longfellow Bridge and look for a group on the MGH side. Short walk from Charles/MGH T Station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coppeto</member_name><member_id>7594176</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309205363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>you get to squeeze Arthur Fielder's nose</why><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304943959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Esplanade</name><id>17688021</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309111200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/17688021/</event_url></item>