<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi, Everyone -   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for all of your responses to my idea!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know that some people prefer Saturday and others prefer Sunday, so why don’t we schedule two hikes / socials for now - one for Saturday March 6th at 1:00 - and the other for Sunday March 14th at 11:00.  Since I live up here, I’ll be happy to schedule more hikes and socials beyond that point as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll head up the Ring Trail on Mount Agamenticus, which isn’t really a mountain at all, but rather a hill.  Nonetheless, at an elevation of 692 feet it is still the highest point for miles around and offers great views!  The hike up the mountain is short - a half hour or less - and from there, we’ll head across the street for more easy to moderate level hiking over wooded terrain.   We’ll time the hike to last about 2 ½ hours or so, and from there we’ll head to Mike’s Clam Shack (which is not a clam shack at all) but rather a very popular moderately-priced family restaurant located in Wells (www.mikesclamshack.com) for a great meal and coffee!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on trail conditions as they stand now, I would recommend boots or hiking shoes with sturdy grips - and if you have them, micro-spikes and a hiking pole are always good to have on hand.  As with all New England wilderness areas at this time of year, expect typical springtime trail conditions.  Hopefully, with any luck, we’ll have a snowstorm between now and then - it’s really beautiful with snow cover!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’ll look forward to meeting all of you then!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The directions are easy: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 north over the big bridge to Exit 7 just before the toll booths.  Go to the end of the ramp - stop sign - take left - and then next immediate right (the road ends at that point, so you have to turn right), and go approximately 6.3 miles (the name of this road is Chases Pond Road which becomes Mountain Road - same road; just keep going straight).  You will come to a small parking lot at the base of Mount Agamenticus (the paved road ends at this point) - and you can park either in the lot, or if it is full like it often is, on either side of the road. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting near a Silver Subaru Forester in the general vicinity of the above referenced meeting spot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1268071631000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267293508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Lunch in York Area</name><id>12725383</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267898400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/12725383/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/3/global_7735123.jpeg</photo_url></item>