<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>210 Howe Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.755830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 683-7771</phone><name>BOXWOOD GRILL </name><city>Methuen</city><id>1017422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.173902</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Moments to Mind:  Moving from Chaos to Clarity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is your plate frequently overflowing? Feel like a “duty drone” (work, rinse, repeat)?  You can feel in control of your day, rather than controlled by events and circumstances.  Open up to new ways of thinking and gain a sense of control while improving your well-being. Leave with a new perspective and helpful action tips to re-engage and recharge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Christy Matta, M.A.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christy provides customized workshops, consultation and personal coaching in Dialectical Behavior Therapy (DBT), Mindfulness and Stress Reduction.  Her Work Effectiveness Program trains leaders, entrepreneurs and workers in stress reduction and the clarity of thinking that leads to innovation.  She is intensively trained in DBT and has designed and provided clinical supervision to treatment programs, including a winner of the American Psychiatric Association Gold Award. She currently writes for Mentalhelp.net and Psychcentral.com.  For more on her consultation and trainings visit her web site www.dbtmind.com. For mindfulness tips and strategies visit her blog www.christymatta.wordpress.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Chris Vasiliadis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris is a Certified Wellness Coach who happens to be living well with Multiple Sclerosis. Through her coaching and training firm, Priority Wellness &lt;a href="http://www.prioritywellness.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.prioritywe...&lt;/a&gt;, she helps individuals in a life or work transition navigate the process to achieve the best possible outcome. She also works with stressed out and depleted executives, business owners and employees who are ready to increase their energy and decrease their stress, so they can perform better and be more relaxed at work and the things they love. Chris can be heard twice a month on her internet radio show, Energizing You, on blogtalkradio.com. She is currently co-authoring a book on women business owners who have experienced a personal crisis while running their business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Menu for this event:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a scrumptious Grilled Chicken, Pineapple and Mango Salad. If you require a different meal please let me know at least 2 days prior to the event.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maureen Campaiola</member_name><member_id>6037081</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284211928000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Daring Women!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup</urlname><id>1412014</id><group_lat>42.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Dare To Be Phenomenal's Success Minded Women's Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273867976000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DARE Networking Luncheon</name><id>dqzfpynmblb</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283959800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dare-To-Be-Phenomenal-North-of-Boston-Chapter-Meetup/events/13485896/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/0/global_12349600.jpeg</photo_url></item>