<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have to say this first; Plato’s The Myth of the Cave was one of the most rewarding experiences I had when I first read the Republic. The dialogue in The Republic is some of the most intriguing and interesting because of Socrates’ nature and the ideals involved. Plato sets up The Myth of the Cave as a metaphor for everyday life and how he saw certain behavior. He uses the imagery to explain his rationale for how the Ideal State should be. Being that Plato’s Myth of the Cave entails so much thought about how we live our lives and how we view the world the messages are ones that dies hard. The primary function of this event will be for discussion on The Myth of the Cave and all the tangents it entails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A) The Purpose- what was Plato trying to say/explain/do with his metaphor.&lt;br /&gt;B) The Analysis- what are the underlying meanings, representations, strengths, and weaknesses of the metaphor.&lt;br /&gt;C) The Discussion- the part where we discuss and debate Plato’s above premises and conclusion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The have posted a synopsis of the Myth of the Cave on the message board. Please try to the text before the event but it isn’t necessary, just really helpful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also I have posted a series of questions associated with the Myth of the Cave that I feel are helpful in understanding and discussing this subject. Try to answer them privately first because when the event takes place these are going to be questions I brin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis and questions posted on message board. Sorry about the delay!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1115296413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Myth of the Cave!</name><id>4688611</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1118610000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/4688611/</event_url></item>