<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11.8 miles north on Route 16 from Route 302 in Bartlett, NH</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.257275</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Pinkham Notch Visitor's Center</name><city>Gorham</city><id>5638432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.253060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;March is the month that signals the end of another ice climbing season. &amp;nbsp;Warming temperatures are melting the ice in Kinsman, Franconia, and Crawford Notches. Fortunately, old man winter hasn't completely left: ice still lives on Mount Washington. &amp;nbsp;Let's end this season with an easy multi-pitch snow and ice climb in Odell's Gully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;This climb is in Huntington Ravine. &amp;nbsp;It has everything you'd expect: great views, easy snow and ice (WI2), an alpine climb of&amp;nbsp;three pitches of ice and longer tandem snow climbing above the ice. &amp;nbsp;Odell's is just south of Pinnacle Gully, and Central Gully (nearby the Huntington Ravine Trail used in the summer by hikers). &amp;nbsp;The plan is to start at 7 AM on Saturday March 17, hike up (long) and into Huntington Ravine, and climb Odell's. &amp;nbsp;We finish by strolling over to the Lions Head Trail, and back down the Trail to the Joe Dodge Lodge. This climb will end around 4 PM, or earlier if we are fast at hiking. &amp;nbsp;Afterwards, we can head out for a well-earned Odells brew. &amp;nbsp;Although it is easy,&amp;nbsp;this is a popular climb. &amp;nbsp;Therefore, we will need to be on our guard. &amp;nbsp;In addition, Odell's is&amp;nbsp;avalanche prone.&amp;nbsp;If conditions in the gully are poor, or weather forecast is bad, we'll try another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;We will need one lead climber per second climber (or two seconds). &amp;nbsp;The leader must be capable of WI2, preferably with experience with climbing Odell's Gully. &amp;nbsp;Leaders will need to know how to belay off the anchor with Reverso in order to belay two second climbers simultaneously in a staggered manner. &amp;nbsp;Seconds will need to have experience in top rope climbing at a minimum. Also, this climb will involve 8 miles of hiking. &amp;nbsp;You will need recent hiking experience as well. &amp;nbsp;I will be a leader for this climb. &amp;nbsp;Whether you are leader or second, please answer the questions I ask in the RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;All will need their own mountaineering boots, crampons, harness, locking biner+belay device, helmet, balaclava, two or more pairs of gloves (they get wet), water proof (eg, Gore-Tex) tops and bottoms, warm fleece layers, and thermal wicking layer. &amp;nbsp;In addition, each must have&amp;nbsp;their own ice tools (axes). &amp;nbsp;But, because this is an alpine climb, try to keep light. &amp;nbsp;Leaders will need rope, quickdraws or similar, webbing, ice screws, and several locking biners for anchors. &amp;nbsp;We'll have to coordinate to make sure we bring the right gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;Let's meet up at 7 AM at the AMC Store in Pinkham Notch. &amp;nbsp;Be ready to go, so come earlier to get your boots on and packs set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;For more information, check out &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/messages/boards/thread/10228789"&gt;the FAQ's on ice climbing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Odell's,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.summitpost.org/o-dells-gully-huntington-ravine/156268"&gt;http://www.summitpost.org/o-dells-gully-huntington-ravine/156268&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://vimeo.com/9492026"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;For weather, &lt;a href="http://www.accuweather.com/en/us/bartlett-nh/03812/weather-forecast/2174533"&gt;Accuweather&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/"&gt;Mount Washington Observatory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current ice climbing conditions: &lt;a href="http://neice.com/"&gt;neice.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://neclimbs.com/"&gt;neclimbs.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If staying overnight, consider lodging at the White Mountains Hostel:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/"&gt;http://www.whitemountainshostel.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ken Domino</member_name><member_id>4332297</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332163509000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328911493000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Odell's brew</name><id>51879262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331982000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/51879262/</event_url></item>