<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Fresh Pond Parkway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.383263</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Water Department</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9775322</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142548</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Well, that's not really what it's called, but that's what it looks like and is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us and see where your fresh water comes from. Follow Cambridge's water supply from being rain in the western suburbs, to your tap. It's really a much more fascinating story than you likely think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://strawberryjampackedlife.files.wordpress.com/2010/08/dsc024331.jpg" width="283" height="188" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, there's no art or culture without fresh water, so this is the basis of it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come tour this beautiful building, see relics of earlier water plants, and view the beautiful terrazo floor that maps the flow of water in Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free samples of the product will be available after the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tour Information: &lt;br /&gt;

 With the Fresh Pond Reservation as a dramatic backdrop, the Walter J. Sullivan water purification facility is located on the former site of the old water works buildings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The building relates to the site's natural surroundings, using complementary exterior materials of granite, brick, slate and cast stone. A two-story interior main lobby was designed with arched windows that allow natural light and unobstructed views of Fresh Pond. The stone entrance and two stone medallions of the state and city seals were saved from the former water treatment plant to become part of the new lobby. They form the background for the lobby's water fountain, designed in materials of granite, terrazzo and stainless steel. Art within the building lobby, designed by a local artist, celebrates water by way of a unique terrazzo floor design and an 11-foot glass water column that is an interactive display for the public. The column is connected to an exterior drinking fountain and comes to life with lights and bubbles when the drinking fountain is used.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be standing to the left of the entrance door - we'll go in at 6:00.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351051332000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350067587000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Museum of Water - Guided Water Works Tour</name><id>86713372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350338400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/86713372/</event_url></item>