<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Anderson St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station</name><city>Portland</city><id>669831</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256200</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for the second film in our &lt;b&gt;2009|2010 Permaculture Movie Night&lt;/b&gt; Series.  This month we will be viewing &amp;quot;One Man, One Cow, One Planet,&amp;quot; a New Zealand film about the work of biodynamic practitioner and teacher Peter Proctor as he travels around India essentially helping to &amp;quot;undo&amp;quot; the work of the Green Revolution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the film's web site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What does an environmentally friendly biodynamic food system capable of feeding everyone actually look like?   This film is a blueprint for a post-industrial future. It takes you into the heart of the world's most important renaissance...Why YOU should see this film:  Modern agriculture causes topsoil to be eroded at 3 million tons per hour. (that’s 26 billion tons a year).  Human mass is replacing biomass and other species. The carrying capacity of the earth is almost spent. To maintain our comfort zone lifestyles we will soon need five earths to sustain us in the style to which we have become accustomed.  The mantra of free trade has failed the world’s poor. There is a better way.  Human created climate change is destroying the Planet. Ecosystems collapse is not some sci-fi fantasy. It is real and it is happening. Right now.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is not a potluck event but feel free to bring a beverage or fruit or sweet treat to share during the film if you so desire!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie will start sometime between 7:00 and 7:10pm.  Optional discussion to follow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Thank you to our friends at Zero Station for hosting the 2009|2010 Permaculture Movie Nights*&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257798005000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253029396000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Permaculture Movie Night:  One Man, One Cow, One Planet</name><id>11378063</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257292800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/11378063/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/1/global_10729297.jpeg</photo_url></item>