<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>292 Centre Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.358246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-527-7726</phone><name>Prana Restaurant</name><city>Newton Corner</city><id>1033348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Optimum Health Solution, Raw New England Community, and Prana Cafe present: Transformational Breath Workshops with Judith Kravitz. &amp;quot;The Breath is the gateway between the visible and invisible world.&amp;quot;-Babaji You are invited to join us for times of inner alignment!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will:&lt;br /&gt;*Learn breathing techniques for improving and increasing your energy level and sense of well-being.&lt;br /&gt;* Receive an individual breathing analysis (Sat. only).&lt;br /&gt;* Learn how to correct restrictive breathing patterns.&lt;br /&gt;* Learn how the Transformational Breath can help you live a healthier and more joyful life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introduction - Tuesday, May 25 5:30 -9 pm at the Prana Cafe, 292 Centre St. Newton MA.for directions visit www.thepranacafe.com &amp;amp; click on &amp;quot;Contact&amp;quot;.  $25 Admission - $10 at door for speaker &amp;amp; $15 required inside for your choice of salads, desserts &amp;amp; homemade snacks.  to pre-order, see menu on www.thepranacafe.com, click on &amp;quot;Classes or Events&amp;quot; &amp;amp; call your choices in to 617-527-7726. For more information on Transformational Breathing™ go to &lt;a href="http://www.breathe2000.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.breathe2000.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intensive - Saturday, May 29 1-7 pm with 2 Breath Sessions at the Oriental Culture Institute/Tam Center for Health, 15 Cottage Ave, #501, Quincy, MA 02169.  $75 pre-registration, $100 at the door.  Bring organic, unprocessed, raw/vegan/living plant-based food ready to serve dish to feed 6-8 people.  include recipe and serving implements.  Parking $8. Bring blankets &amp;amp; pillows, wear loose comfortable clothing. Contact: Rox at 603-286-8333 or roxlindbert@aol.com to register for May 29&lt;br /&gt;For more information on Transformational Breathing go to &lt;a href="http://www.transformationalbreathing.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.transformationalbreathing.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Judith Kravitz is an ordained minister with a Doctorate in Metaphysics, she is the co-creator of the Transformational Breath process, and has been constantly expanding it over three decades.  The mother of eight cildren, she was originally inspired by a personal experience of self-healing a malignmant tumor on her throat, based on principles and skills acquired through her work with the breath.  Judith now travels worldwide sharing this amazing process.  She has trained over 3000 facilitators and has personally led hundreds of thousands of people in groups and individual sessions.  Her book, Breathe Deep, Laugh Loudly:  The Joy of Transformational Breathing. is the ultimate breather's manual, indispensable as we embrace major transitions in the paradigms for health and well-being.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will thank yourself again and again for attending these workshops!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information email: betsy@optimumhealthsolution.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.essenic.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274861329000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270475525000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Judith Kravitz @ Prana Cafe</name><id>13090015</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274823000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/13090015/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/6/9/global_15273945.jpeg</photo_url></item>