<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Belmont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374594</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 331 3161</phone><name>Sofra Bakery and Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>992122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149983</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This new bakery and cafe is the brainchild of Ana Sortun, owner/chef of Oleanna restaurant and author of the fabulous &amp;quot;Spice&amp;quot; cookbook. I am on a mission to taste every one of the exotic Middle Eastern pastry creations offered at Sofra, from Syrian shortbreads to umm-ali (Egyptian bread-and-butter pudding) to chocolate hazelnut baklava.  There are savory snacks too, cheese boureks, stuffed flatbreads, and lots more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why a Monday afternoon? Because I've asked the management when their slowest time of the week is -- and that's what they told me. It's not a big place, and we really don't want to venture in there on a weekend! And who knows -- leaving work a tad early for something like this just might have you looking forward to a Monday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know we won't get many people to show for this, so I'm not charging a reservation fee for this Meetup. And wait, folks, there's more. . . I'll treat the first 3 people to RSVP to the beverage of their choice.  Of course, you have to show up to collect!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a real small place. I'll be hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246826424000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245547782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea/Turkish Coffee and Exotic Pastries at Sofra</name><id>10698434</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246305600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/10698434/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/b/global_9255275.jpeg</photo_url></item>