<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Castle is all decked out for the holidays.  Kevin will host an outing to tour the Castle with an optional hike first for those who are interested, and the tour after starting at about 12:45 PM.  Details are below. Meet at the Grand Central Terminal at 12:45 PM if you only want to tour the Castle. If you want to tour the Castle at 10 AM, that is fine too but Kevin will be leading the hike portion with members of a Hiking Group (about 50 people going!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join in on the tour of Gillette Castle which will be all decked out for the Christmas holiday season in a Victorian theme. We'll first hike the trails on the grounds of the castle. The trails are easy to easy-moderate. Mostly we'll hike the old railroad bed of the mini steam train that ran on the property. We should even be able to hike through the old tunnel dug for the train! After the hike we'll have lunch and take the tour of the Castle, which should be about $10 paid at the ticket booth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start with the hike at 10 AM and we should finish that by about Noon. We'll then take up to 30 min. to eat a picnic lunch (please bring your own or some for others if you want to share) at &amp;quot;Grand Central Terminal/Picnic Shelter&amp;quot; as marked on the map. There are some picnic tables. We'll start touring the Castle at about 12:45 PM. The tour should be done by about 2 PM. The tour is optional and those who wish to leave after the hike may. Depending on the hike, times may be earlier for lunch and the tour of the Castle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are very welcome for the event. Pets on a leash are permitted in picnic areas and on hiking trails.  Pets are not allowed in buildings or on decks, terraces or walkways leading to the castle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the outbuilding (marked as food concession on the trail map) next to the main (i.e. big) parking lot as you head towards the castle. The building had bathrooms. Just look me, Kevin the Organizer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; (67 River Rd., E. Haddam, CT), &lt;b&gt;park in the main parking lot&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Gillette+Castle+State+Park&amp;amp;city=East+Haddam%2C+Town+Of&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=67+River+Rd+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++East+Haddam%2C+Ct+06423&amp;amp;zipcode=06423&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.42756&amp;amp;longitude=-72.4286&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=1023069087" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=41.42756, Long.=-72.4286]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/gillettecastlemap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information&lt;/b&gt; about Gillette Castle State Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325204" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DEP announcement of holiday event at the Castle&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.depdata.ct.gov/calendar/viewev.asp?id=3811" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.depdata.ct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Article about last year's Victorian Christmas Celebration&lt;/b&gt;, 2008:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.courant.com/itowns_mr/2008/12/christmas-victorian-style-at-g.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://blogs.courant....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260198539000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-28</urlname><id>364032</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Heights Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253497002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A holiday visit to Gillett Castle</name><id>11423167</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-28/events/11423167/</event_url></item>