<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE JUNE MEETUP HAS  BEEN RESCHEDULED TO NEXT SATURDAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the awful heat and humidity today, it really isn't safe to go forward with today's Sunday meetup.  We have  rescheduled to next Saturday to accomodate Father's Day next Sunday.  Sorry for the late notice, but we were hoping that the weather might change.  See you all next Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're getting together at a brand new location in Middleboro!  This time, we're being hosted by our Puggy wannabe, Jack Russell Terrier Wizzar and his family, Dave and Shari.  Don't worry, the yard is completely fenced, and Wizzar and his mom and dad can't wait to have all  those Puggies come to visit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know.  We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR LAST MEETUP?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite a dismal forecast, the weather surprised us by staying bright and sunny all afternoon, just so we could have our May meetup.  About 33 people and their Pugs showed up (plus my two French Bulldogs, a Jack Russell Terrier, and the Poodle next door).  We were joined this time by two unexpected guests - a news reporter from the Brockton Enterprise and her son.  They don't have Pugs, their own dog is a Shepherd/Husky cross (BIG DOG!). but they sure had a good time with all of our little guys and gals.  We hope to see our Puggies popping up in the pages of the Enterprise any day now!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Chris and Jeff again for providing the soft doggie treats - the only treats that Clovis can eat, and he LOVES them.  Also, thank you to the folks who brought the homemade brownies (they were to die for) and the chocolate chip cookies.  Even though our monthly host provides the soft drinks and the paperware, we depend on our members to bring the snacks, for both dogs and people.  They haven't failed us yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be biscuits for the dogs and soft drinks and something to snack on for the adults! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups and the South of Boston Small Breed Dogs Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend.  Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis, Cletus and Stoney's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213639999000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211137545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug June Meetup</name><id>7962684</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213466400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/7962684/</event_url></item>