<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Australian Short Film Today&lt;/b&gt; is the place to see premieres of Cannes and Oscar nominees and Tropfest winners, the first works of directors who went on to make major feature films, and the latest works featuring top Australian talent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tickets are $10 for group members&lt;/b&gt;: The American Australian Association is pleased to offer members of the Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group a $5 discount on ticket prices for tonight's event. You may book online by checking the AAA membership pricing box  (at the Brattle Web Site) &lt;b&gt;or  simply mention Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group if you plan to buy your tickets at the box office ( recommended).&lt;/b&gt; Thank you for your support - this promises to be an exciting program and we look forward to seeing you at the event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;. An engaging program featuring award-winning latest and greatest short films from Australia, including comedy, drama, animation, and even a period piece about a 19th century prison break. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The combined running time for these films is a little less than 2 hours which would get us to the restaurant before 8pm- which is a good thing on a work night! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can fit this into your schedule- looks like a wonderful selection of shorts:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SWEET &amp;amp; SOUR&lt;br /&gt;17 min., animation&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director: Eddie White&lt;br /&gt;The first official animated co-production between Australia and China&lt;br /&gt;Chinatown. The Year of the Dog. A bittersweet love affair.&lt;br /&gt;Sydney Film Festival: Dendy Award Best Short Animation 2007&lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Film Festival: SBS Television Award 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DUGONG&lt;br /&gt;18 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director: Erin White&lt;br /&gt;Producer: Melanie Brunt&lt;br /&gt;A moment-in-time drama about a loner who returns home to repair the past after twelve years.&lt;br /&gt;Flickerfest: Nominated Best Short Film, Best Short Screenplay 2007.&lt;br /&gt;Screened at Sundance 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAR POOL&lt;br /&gt;9 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer: Stephen Irwin&lt;br /&gt;Director: Martha Goddard&lt;br /&gt;Producer: Veronica Wain&lt;br /&gt;How much damage can one mother do to her teenage son?&lt;br /&gt;St Kilda Film Festival: Best Comedy 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;KATOOMBA&lt;br /&gt;30 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director: Leon Ford&lt;br /&gt;Producer: Melissa Johnston, Nicole O'Donohue&lt;br /&gt;You never know a friendship is over until it's too late.&lt;br /&gt;Sydney Film Festival: Dendy Award for Best Fiction Short 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HELL'S GATE&lt;br /&gt;21 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director: Jonathan Auf  Der Heide&lt;br /&gt;Producer: Maggie Miles&lt;br /&gt;Film School: VCA&lt;br /&gt;1822, a true story: Eight convicts escape from Macquarie Harbor, a penal settlement of extreme punishment, only to find a world even less forgiving...the Australian wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;National Film and Sound Archive Award for Best Director 2007; Village Roadshow Corporatation Award for best graduating student production.&lt;br /&gt;BETWEEN THE FLAGS&lt;br /&gt;7 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director/ Producer: Jayce White&lt;br /&gt;How many rioters does it take to start a riot?&lt;br /&gt;Sony Tropfest: Best Comedy 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROAD RAGE&lt;br /&gt;7 min.&lt;br /&gt;Writer/Director: Mark Bellamy&lt;br /&gt;Producers: Mark Bellamy, Lyndal Mebberson&lt;br /&gt;A busy morning, a near-accident. A driver, shaken and angry, goes on a quest for revenge and corners the offender.&lt;br /&gt;Sony Tropfest: People's Choice Award 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gee- this last one sounds like a Massachusett's film.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the films.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216245247000</updated><rating><average>3.8599998951</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214666935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Australian Short Film Today </name><id>8233946</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216071900000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8233946/</event_url></item>