<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event will feature Skyhook Wireless, provider of native location on the iPhone.  George Polak, lead developer, will present their new iPhone SDK, called &lt;a href="https://www.skyhookwireless.com/localfaves/" target="_blank"&gt;Local Faves&lt;/a&gt;. With Local Faves you can easily add location-aware features like checking in, tagging, rankings, notifications and cool map views to any iPhone application. The SDK saves you months of development time, keeps your app content fresh and dynamic, all while driving deeper user engagement and viral growth of your app.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local Faves can be seamlessly integrated into your app, Skyhook just provides the underlying screens and infrastructure. For instance a sports app becomes much more than checking scores when you can tag a team or game as your favorite, comment on the game or players and share with your friends on Facebook, Twitter or Flickr. If you're cheering for your home team on away turf, find other fans around you and which bars you will feel most at home wearing your team's colors. Or if you happen to be a boxing fan, follow other fans and see the best venues for watching the next showdown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Download and get started with &lt;a href="https://www.skyhookwireless.com/localfaves/register/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Local Faves here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Content, food &amp;amp; refreshments sponsored by Skyhook. Location provided by Microsoft.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Hochman</member_name><member_id>11247608</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275499553000</updated><rating><average>3.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>iPhone Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>iphone</urlname><id>1244625</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>iPhone Developers Roundtable - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272316643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Meetup #2- Featuring Skyhook Wireless &amp; Localfaves</name><id>13298278</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274911200000</time><rsvp_limit>125</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/iphone/events/13298278/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/global_5214294.jpeg</photo_url></item>