<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So our first edition of the rotating book club leader is July 27th 
&lt;a&gt;@ 7:00pm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;inside Life Alive unless &amp;amp; if the weather is nice we'll meet outside somewhere (but&amp;nbsp;I'll send out an email the day before to give everyone a final head's up as to if we will meet inside or outside)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discussion leader this time will be none other than our very own... (drum roll please....)Jules!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has picked "The Book Thief" by Marcus Zusak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A blurb&amp;nbsp;about&amp;nbsp;the book below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Death himself narrates the World War II-era story of Liesel Meminger from the time she is taken, at age nine, to live in Molching, Germany, with a foster family in a working-class neighborhood of tough kids, acid-tongued mothers, and loving fathers who earn their living by the work of their hands... Zusak not only creates a mesmerizing and original story but also writes with poetic syntax, causing readers to deliberate over phrases and lines, even as the action impels them forward. Death is not a sentimental storyteller, but he does attend to an array of satisfying details, giving Liesels story all the nuances of chance, folly, and fulfilled expectation that it deserves. An extraordinary narrative.&amp;ndash;Francisca Goldsmith, Berkeley Public Library, CA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Originally released as an adult book in Australia but released in the US as Young Adult, I think this book is not limited by its marketing category and will give lots of fodder for discussion. It was criticized by one critic for "Vonnegut-like whimsy". What I've read so far intrigues me. It also seems like a quick read, appropriate for four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Book-Thief-Markus-Zusak/dp/0375831002/ref=cm_cr_pr_product_top"&gt;http://www.amazon.com/Book-Thief-Markus-Zusak/dp/0375831002/ref=cm_cr_pr_product_top&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*****If you are interested in leading the following book club discussion by all means PLEASE let me know!!! I'm hopefull this will be a rotating seat &amp;amp; everyone who wishes to can have a turn!!!*****&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have a copy of the book out for all to see!!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jules</member_name><member_id>2919261</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paras Hezar</member_name><member_id>12400154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312737298000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309629659000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Book Club Readers~The Book Thief by Marcus Zusak</name><id>24348931</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311807600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/24348931/</event_url></item>