<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #990000"&gt;PLEASE NOTE THE MARCH MEETING IS A DIFFERENT DATE, TIME AND LOCATION THAN OUR REGULAR MONTHLY MEETINGS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;em&gt;This is also a free meeting for all attendees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crowd Funding: Where it stands now - “The Power of Alternative Financing for Entrepreneurs”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Cost: Free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE NOTE THE MARCH MEETING IS A DIFFERENT DATE, TIME AND LOCATION THAN OUR REGULAR MONTHLY MEETINGS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;em&gt;This is also a free meeting for all attendees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;3:00 - 6:00 PM - Networking, Other Events and Refreshments &lt;br /&gt;

6:00 - 8:00 PM - EntreTech Forum Panel Discussion &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Havana Room*, One Broadway, 5th Floor Cambridge Innovation Center, Cambridge, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask any entrepreneur about raising seed capital to get their venture off the ground, and you'll hear a wide range of adventure stories. Lucky ones are able to secure an initial investor and get started, while the majority spends countless months selling their ideas to investors that like the ideas but are hesitant to gamble on an uncertain exit.  Enter crowd funding, a powerful means to directly tap into groups of new and veteran investors.  In last year's EntreTech Forum session, we saw successful Crowd funding efforts that funded small projects up to startup companies. No longer a techie fad, crowd funding has raised more than $10 million for some companies.  Now many want to know how or if it can be used as a mature source for financing ventures. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Join us for this EntreTech Forum where we will have a discussion with an executive panel of advisors from the investment, startup, and legislative areas. They will share their perspectives and experiences on topics that every entrepreneur grapples with as they seek funding, including:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is the outlook on Crowd Funding from a political perspective?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where does the government legislative and Securities and Exchange Commission findings-report on Crowd Funding stand?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do I leverage crowd funding?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does the equity allocation work?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With respect to the IRS, what do we need to be aware of and what are the rules?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If I use crowd funding for seed financing, does this make my company more or less attractive to traditional angel or VC investors down the road?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your own experiences and share them at this lively discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panel:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2013Mtg/Hillel-Tuch.jpg" width="100" height="110" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Alon Hillel-Tuch, Co-&lt;strong&gt;Founder and Chief Financial Officer - RocketHub&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

RocketHub is one of the world’s largest crowdfunding platforms. Alon was born in the land of cheese and clogs, The Netherlands, and speaks English, Dutch, German, and a smidge of Mandarin Chinese. Alon co-authored two whitepapers, entitled &lt;em&gt;Regulation of Crowdfunding: Building On the Jumpstart Our Business Startups Act&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Implementation Of Crowdfunding: Building On Title III Of The Jobs Act,&lt;/em&gt; which have both received critical acclaim and resulted in Alon testifying before the Oversight and Government Reform Committee in US Congress and meeting with the U.S Treasury Department, White House’s Jobs Counsel, SEC, FINRA, and the Ontario Securities Commission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alon holds a B.A. from Hamilton College and received his M.Sc from Columbia University. Alon is a fellow at the Earth Institute and is currently part of the Advanced Consortium of Cooperation, Conflict, and Complexity think-tank on genocide prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2013Mtg/Schlesinger.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Joseph Schlesinger, Founder – ArcBotics, Founder &amp;amp; Director - MakeIt Labs &lt;br /&gt;

Joseph was trained as an electrical and computer engineer at Worcester Polytechnic Institute, and has worked across many fields, with a passion for robotics. A serial entrepreneur since a young age, he is the founder of MakeIt Labs.  MakeIt Labs is an open-access workshop in Nashua, NH, where anyone can come to brainstorm, learn and create with like-minded people. Joseph is currently working on his company ArcBotics, which develops and sells open, low-cost robotics platforms for hobbyists, education and research. ArcBotics is dedicated to helping igniting a wave of innovation in robotics through Open-Source Hardware.  The company aims to provide easily-accessible tutorials, plans, kits and parts for anyone from the enthusiast to the dedicated researcher, to make it cheaper and easier to build robots.  Joseph has successfully raised funding for his business through &lt;strong&gt;Kickstarter&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2013Mtg/giller.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eugene Giller, Founder &amp;amp; Materials Team Leader, File2Part&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Eugene Giller has extensive experience in developing new technologies, materials, and applications for Rapid.  Prototyping, electronics, and optics. Prior to founding File2Part, Inc. he worked for Z Corporation developing new inkjet technology-based approaches for Rapid Manufacturing and Rapid Prototyping. Previously Eugene developed and commercialized a number of formulations used in the electrical and electronic industries. Head-mounted displays produced with materials and processes developed by Eugene were successfully tested by the U.S. Army on the battlefield and also helped people with low vision syndrome. Eugene holds MS degrees in Chemistry from University of Manitoba and Chemical Engineering from Moscow's Academy of Fine Chemical Technology.  File2Part has successfully raised funding for through&lt;strong&gt; Kickstarter&lt;/strong&gt; and is also using &lt;strong&gt;Wefunder.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2013Mtg/dolan.jpg" width="100" height="105" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Peter Dolan, Principal, RovAir&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Four years ago, Pete seized an opportunity to turn a business concept into reality. The new venture’s mission was a simple yet unique idea; rent internet data cards, also known as “air cards”. Peter recognized this great opportunity because of his first hand experience of travelers’ frustrations with the internet in the hotel industry. The company, RovAir, is currently flourishing into a much broader business model that re-defines how mobile broadband data will be utilized by consumers.  RovAir has just launched their crowdfunding campaign and is an &lt;strong&gt;Ambassador for IndieGogo&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderator&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2013Mtg/pierson.jpg" width="100" height="131" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;David R. Pierson, Partner, Foley Hoag Emerging Entreprise Center &lt;br /&gt;

David chairs Foley Hoag’s Venture Capital/Emerging Companies Practice Group. He represents a broad range of emerging companies, including companies in the software and technology, life sciences, cleantech and other industries. David also represents U.S. and foreign venture capital firms in connection with their investments throughout the U.S. His practice at the EEC focuses in particular on start-up companies, and includes providing advice regarding corporate formation, founder arrangements, angel and venture capital financings, equity incentive plans, mergers and acquisitions and other strategic transactions, contract negotiations and general corporate matters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfmar2013.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Cost: Free &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;*This event occurs at the Havana Room located at the Cambridge Innovation Center, One Broadway, 5th Floor. Visitors must comply with Venture Café attendance policies (see &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/vc-credo" target="_blank"&gt;http://bit.ly/vc-credo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;for more details.) Refreshments will be served on the 4th Floor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363910414000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crowd Funding</name><id>83283532</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363892400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83283532/</event_url></item>