<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a ConnYak sponsored event...&lt;br /&gt;Annual ConnYak Rescue Clinic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bluff Point State Park, Groton, CT&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, July 30, 2006&lt;br /&gt;10:00 AM - 3:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Various rescue techniques and scenarios will be demonstrated by members versed in same. This is a hands-on clinic, so plan to be in the water practicing what you saw after lunch. There will be plenty of folks available to share what they know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a flare and emergency signaling demo by the DEP boating division, and free vessel safety checks will be done by the US Coast Guard Auxilliary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.connyak.org/default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.connyak.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location is Bluff Piont in Groton:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lisrc.uconn.edu/coastalaccess/site.asp?siteid=458" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lisrc.ucon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have pretty good directions at the link above..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A ReSPONSE FROM ConnYak&lt;br /&gt;Absolutely, you can have your friends with recreational kayaks  &lt;br /&gt;arrive. It's one of the prime reasons we did this or... have been  &lt;br /&gt;doing it for years.&lt;br /&gt;Big time kayakers with all the equipment and supposed skills get into  &lt;br /&gt;serious problems too because of their ego which leads them into  &lt;br /&gt;situations that they are not really prepared for.&lt;br /&gt;Bring as many friends as you can - spread the word. Everyone has a  &lt;br /&gt;nice time and learns a lot too.&lt;br /&gt;Jay Babina&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THESE ARE THE UPDATE INFOs:&lt;br /&gt;Alfred,&lt;br /&gt;We're trying to get the safety message out to everyone and I agree, recreational kayakers are the ones most at risk due to lack of knowledge. Yes, it usually takes an &amp;quot;incident&amp;quot; for the recreational kayaker to realize how dangerous this &amp;quot;kayaking&amp;quot; stuff can be.&lt;br /&gt;Please pass the word around. If any of you friends would like to demonstrate or try a rescue, they are welcome. We're trying to get an idea of the participants.&lt;br /&gt;I myself would like to try to reach the recreational boater. They are usually one or two people who paddle together and not an organized club like ConnYak. I would like to find a way to interest them in the club.&lt;br /&gt;See you at the clinic,&lt;br /&gt;Phil&lt;br /&gt;-------------- Original message from Aconsul@aol.com: -------------- &lt;br /&gt;Dear ConnYak Member,&lt;br /&gt;Hi,&lt;br /&gt;I am very glad you are having this event, first to meet with some of the ConnYak Members, I am a member of the Sound Kayakers out of Norwalk and enjoy the ocean as much as recreational paddling.&lt;br /&gt;The main reason for writing is to get your opinion on my opinion. I believe recreational paddlers are more in danger of accidents than sea kayakers..for the most obvious reasons..sea kayakers know they can die quite easily if they are not prepared.. Recreational kayakers have no idea that their kayaks sink way to easily, don't know how to get back in or empty their kayaks along with even knowing how to save their buddies, not to mention most don't even know what a paddle float is and other things.. With that said, do you feel it is a good idea for recreational paddlers to observe the rescue techniques ? I sure do..and the next thing, I would like to know if it is a good idea for some recreational kayakers to bring their kayaks and practice a few &amp;quot;recreational type&amp;quot; rescues, this seems a good idea but I am not sure of the handling of this type of situation verses the necessity of sea kayaks with spray skirts at your events. Another thing, if the recreational yakers survive, they usually become sea kayakers a bit later..Like me..&lt;br /&gt;Please give me some response because i have about 6 recreational yakers who want to observe and maybe a few who want to &amp;quot;get wet&amp;quot; so i can tell them its ok for them to bring their yaks..I will take care of them in the water so as to not interfere with the serious folks.&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;Alfred Anton Reigins&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1147997113000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking Rescue Clinic UPDATE INFO</name><id>4942229</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1154268000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/4942229/</event_url></item>