<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per adult ($6/kids)</description><amount>9.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>ORAGNIZER: Eileen &lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/513/members/2718202/"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHO: All members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join is 10am May 19th at the Butterfly Place shooting more than 500 living Butterflies. (I am going to see if they will let us in an hour early for our group. details to follow.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather is nice we will brown bag lunch in their picnic area (otherwise we will hit a local place for food.). Be prepared to be in a hot room for a couple of hours. Also, You may want to bring your tripod. (See some photos from out first trip here &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/513/photos/."&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is also easy to get too with plenty of parking! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was told that in May most of the flowers will be blooming and we should get some really great photos from this outing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email me with questions or suggestions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers, Eileen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.butterflyplace-ma.com/"&gt;http://www.butterflyp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Place is an indoor living environment which has been carefully designed for the propagation and development of some of nature?s most colorful living creations. This wonderful man-made habitat is contained within a 3,100 sq. ft. glass atrium building towering to a height of over 27 ft. at its peak. Within this atrium?s living butterfly environment can be found a variety of colorful plants and shrubs, each of which has been selected as a source of nectar for the butterflies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At any given time, the atrium may contain up to 500 butterflies representing as many as 50 different species from around the world, although butterflies which are native to the New England region are featured whenever possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Butterfly Place offers a truly unique opportunity to photograph or videotape butterflies in a natural environment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179756630000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176445961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Group Shoot: The Butterfly Place</name><id>5666023</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179583200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/5666023/</event_url></item>