<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Conference Room,Main Floor</address_2><address_1>305 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.730762</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-686-4080</phone><name>Nevins Memorial Library</name><city>Methuen</city><id>403806</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190002</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Specific Topic &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: WELL FORMED OUTCOMES &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Guest Speaker: Tom Maloney&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome thinking&lt;/strong&gt; is a very powerful approach  to achieving what you want. The elements of outcome thinking are drawn  from people in all walks of life who consistently achieve what they want  in a way that is compatible both with those around them and with their  environment. By following the steps to setting a well formed outcome you  are modeling the way these successful people think about outcomes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This way of thinking works in all situations and at all levels,  from setting an outcome for a five minute discussion, to establishing a  vision for a company. The success comes from ensuring that your  thinking about your outcomes meets all the conditions for a well formed  outcome. Each element is crucial to the eventual likelihood of success.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Maloney&lt;/strong&gt; began his personal journey to success in  his early teens, when he first studied creative meditation for goal  achievement with the Silva Method. Since that time he has, through  numerous disciplines, added to his tool kit while assisting others along  their path to achieving their dreams. His passion for studies in the  field of personal development led him to the achievement of his own  personal dream, teaching and empowering others through the Essential  Mind Power&amp;reg; Program.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;Master Practitioner of NLP&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;Certified NLP Coach&lt;/strong&gt;. Tom has dedicated his life to building viable futures from the inside out&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Martin  &lt;br /&gt;978-273-5905  &lt;br /&gt;kenda_assoc@msn.com  &lt;br /&gt;www.poseffects.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Garden Room - Bottom Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300407607000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>We are bringing Tom up to Methuen to tell us about Well Formed Outcomes - NLP Goal Setting</why><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298557339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP Meetup - Methuen- WELL FORMED OUTCOMES</name><id>swkjqypfbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300402800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/16687161/</event_url></item>