<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 Research Pkwy</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.518325</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 238-2380</phone><name>Four Points by Sheraton Meriden</name><city>Meriden</city><id>754650</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.763240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreiacoachingprogram.com"&gt;www.ctreiacoachingprogram.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for full details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of Your Current Situation ... There's Absolutely No Reason You Can't Land Your First Profitable Investment Deal in the Next 120 Days With This PROVEN, TIME-TESTED and EXCLUSIVE OPPORTUNITY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The "CT REIA Coaches" will give you the most effective information, which is the back-bone of the 'SYSTEM,' for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Managing Your Business&lt;/strong&gt; - Eliminate headaches and property management nightmares with this easy-to-use system that we have perfected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Achieving Your Goals&lt;/strong&gt; - We'll help you set realistic and aggressive goals that we think you can personally achieve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Negotiation Techniques&lt;/strong&gt; - You'll learn proven techniques that will help you to go step-by-step through the process of negotiating deals that make you money when you buy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Finances&lt;/strong&gt; - Use the system that we've perfected over the last several decades so you can manage the finances of your business stress-free Real Estate Investing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Property Management&lt;/strong&gt; - You're going to learn several fascinating methods you can use to manage your properties without being a 'do-it-yourself' handy-man or woman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Motivation&lt;/strong&gt; - You're going to gain the laser-focus and inspiration that you need, just from being around peers who are all encouraging each other and changing their lives, one property at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Communication Skills&lt;/strong&gt; - Even if you would never consider yourself a salesperson, or a communicator, you're going to learn a simple script and tactics that we will help you master to command the price and deal that YOU want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In just the first few weeks, you will learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;The 7 Totally Legal Strategies Landlords and Building Owners Can Use to Increase Cash Flow and Minimize Taxes&lt;/strong&gt; (With No Fear of an IRS Audit!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;How to Get a No Money Down/Tax Free Vacation Home&lt;/strong&gt; - This coaching program is worth taking just to learn how to do this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;How to Put Your Business On Auto-Pilot&lt;/strong&gt; - So you can live the life of a wealthy real estate investor instead of a 'mom and pop,' handyman investor who hasn't done anything more than bought themselves a new job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;Need to Know Information About Contracts, Paperwork and Closings&lt;/strong&gt; - We'll show you how to breeze through this information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;The Single Most Effective Way to Run Your Business&lt;/strong&gt; - This one secret will ensure that you build a real 'lifestyle business' ... meaning long vacations and weekends and time freedom beyond your wildest dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;How to Turn 5 Minutes and An Internet Connection Into a Proven Tactic For Renting Your Apartments and Finding Deals.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;How to Build a Successful Team That Will Do Most of the Work For You&lt;/strong&gt; - You don't need to know a thing about changing light bulbs, painting walls, laying carpet or any of that boring stuff. You're going to learn how to leverage other people at the best price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;How to Bring in Other Investors&lt;/strong&gt; - So you can leverage other peoples' money to own and profit from much larger properties than you would be able to own yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* &lt;strong&gt;And many, many more real estate fortune creating secrets&lt;/strong&gt; that I and the other coaches have used to amass personal fortunes quicker and much easier than you could imagine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreiacoachingprogram.com"&gt;www.ctreiacoachingprogram.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for full details.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352945324000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352207949000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Fall 2012 Coaching Program For Real Estate Investors</name><id>90194512</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352934000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/90194512/</event_url></item>