<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>46 Bridge Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.763428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Behind chiropractic office</name><city>Nashua</city><id>7528542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449173</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Election Night Movie Special&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a timely special screening of Hacking Democracy, the # 1 documentary video on altering election outcomes with voting machines!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hacking Democracy, a film by Simon Ardizzone, Russell Michaels, and Robert Carillo Cohen, executive produced by Sarah Teale &amp;amp; Sian Edwards of Teale-Edwards Productions LLC, was nominated for a 2007 EMMY Award in the category OUTSTANDING INVESTIGATIVE JOURNALISM-LONG FORM. This HBO documentary features Black Box Voting's original investigation into the shocking secrecy of the elections industry and local footage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Viewable &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rVTXbARGXso"&gt;online on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First courageously broadcast amid controversy on HBO throughout November &amp;amp; December of 2006, Hacking Democracy exposes the secret dangers of voting machines used during America's mid-term and Presidential elections. Electronic voting machines count more than 90% of America's votes in county, state and federal elections. The technology is also being used throughout the world, including in Canada, the United Kingdom, Europe and Latin America. Though, as concerns grow, worldwide, countries, like Germany and Ireland, are questioning the practice and moving to end the use of electronic voting machines in their elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Filmed over three years, this exposé follows the bold investigations of a team of citizen activists, computer experts, and hackers as they take on the electronic voting industry, targeting the Diebold Corporation. Hacking Democracy uncovers incendiary evidence from the trash cans of Texas to the ballot boxes of Ohio, exposing secrecy, votes in the trash, hackable software, and even election officials rigging the presidential recount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately proving our votes can be stolen without a trace, Hacking Democracy culminates in the famous 'Hursti Hack'; a duel between the Diebold voting machines and a computer expert from Finland - with the survival of the American Republic at stake. Tell your friends. Don't miss this special screening!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some references:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.hackingdemocracy.com"&gt;http://www.hackingdemocracy.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.blackboxvoting.org/video.html"&gt;http://www.blackboxvoting.org/video.html&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://archive.org/details/HackingDemocracy"&gt;http://archive.org/details/HackingDemocracy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a new venue in Nashua at 46 Bridge Street in the rear of a chiropractic office. If you've been in Nashua for a while, you'll know the building as the old Maine Manufacturing Company office. Here's what it looks like: &lt;a href="http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI"&gt;http://goo.gl/maps/2dAI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the parking in the rear and if that is full, there is some available on the right side of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any folding chairs, please bring one for yourself. We're not sure we'll have enough. Also, plan to bring snacks. We can get this location set up better and better to suit our needs, so come on over so you can check it out and make suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please come a little early if you can or be there at 7 so we can get off to a great start for this month's video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the basement room that you access from the rear of the building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352257426000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346258741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Hacking Democracy</name><id>qqflqcyqpbjb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352246400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/79917782/</event_url></item>