<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 16</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.351078</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Imp Trail Head Three Miles North of Pinkham Notch Visitors Center</name><city>Gorham</city><id>4335772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194313</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATED THE START TIME - HAD INADVERTENTLY LISTED IT AS 9 PM WHEN IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN 9 AM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;==========&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeffrey Shutak is a member of our group and asked me to list this event on our page. &amp;nbsp;While I have yet to meet him (will be hiking with him on 11/11) I know that he is actively involved in several other local hiking groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a member-led event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you underestimate the demands; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills and abilities; or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;If you have any questions please contact Jeff through his profile or the comment section below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;==========&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imp Trail Head Three Miles North of&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Pinkham Notch&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Visitors Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Route 16,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Gorham, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;2nd Annual Thanksgiving Day Orphans Hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually you don&amp;rsquo;t really have to be an orphan, just someone who wants to hike and enjoy the company of other hikers on T-Day. A Thanksgiving Day buffet is optional at the AMC Pinkham Notch Visitors Center which is located three miles south of the trail head for Imp Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Need something to lift your spirits on the holiday? The Imp Trail loop may be just what the doctor ordered. The view of the Presidential Peaks at the midpoint of this circuit is guaranteed to rekindle the ardor of any hiking enthusiast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This one is really special! Special attractions: Good exercise and an absolutely superlative view of the Presidential Peaks. This trail make a loop over the cliff that bears the same name, providing excellent views down through the valley and across the way to Mt. Washington.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The complete loop is 6.3 miles with a book time of four hours. This will be a moderate hike. There is one short steep section before arriving at the top for a magnificent view.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will hike as a group and stay together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plan on starting at 9:00 AM which should allow us to finish up at about 1:00 PM. We can then drive down to the AMC Pinkham Notch Visitors Center for a 2:00 PM buffet dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you decide to join us for dinner you will need to call the AMC Pinkham Notch Visitors Center reservation number at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;(603) 466-2727&amp;nbsp;and make a dinner reservation for&amp;nbsp;2:00 PM. Cost is $20.00 for AMC Members and $22.00 for non-members.&amp;nbsp;You will need to call ASAP as the dinner attracts many hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions to trailhead: Take Route 16 North past Joe Dodge Lodge and continue past the Mt. Washington Auto Road entrance. The northern Imp Trail is the second Imp Trail roadside parking area on the right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;==========&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeffrey </member_name><member_id>11221621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322515735000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320787179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Thanksgiving Day Orphan Hike (Member-led Event)</name><id>40460612</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322143200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/40460612/</event_url></item>