<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Members-Free, Non-members</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEREIA&lt;/b&gt; Presents:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Systemetize Your Shortsale Business &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Profitable Parnterships Mentor and Short Sale Phenom:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim Harrington of Ambrose Properties&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Kim Harrington manages Ambrose Properties New England, LLC, an organization that specializes in assisting homeowners, investors, and realtors in short sale negotiations nationwide. Her organization has successfully negotiated hundreds of short sale transactions over the last 5 years, with a proven, systematic approach to the short sale business. Kim is a native of Ohio, and currently resides in Lexington, MA with her husband and two children. She has a BS in Business Administration from Miami University and an MBA from Boston College. She is also a real estate mentor/coach with Profitable Partnerships of New England. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Real Estate Arbitrage: Making BIG Profits Through Short Sales&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Discussion Topics:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;·  Current market cycle and trends&lt;br /&gt;·  The anatomy of a short sale (marketing, negotiation, exit strategy) &lt;br /&gt;·  The state of the financial market and how it is affecting short sale negotiations&lt;br /&gt;·  Benefits of working with a power team &lt;br /&gt;·  On-line tracking system of deals using RealeFlow&lt;br /&gt;·  Building our power team further (working with you to bring in more short sale deals!)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie Trajlinek</member_name><member_id>4673573</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228342323000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nereia</urlname><id>593272</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222906300000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association November Meetup</name><id>8876841</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225929600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nereia/events/8876841/</event_url></item>