<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So my pregnant situation is getting in the way of going to this movie. I'm spending tonight in the hospital (with some very wonderful nurses and a great doctor and my wonderful husband, Paul), so I won't be able to come to Little Fockers and laugh with you all as I had planned. Sorry about this!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At any rate, Hubby Paul (tall blond) is willing to come give you all the discount vouchers for tickets, popcorn and soda in my stead. So he can organize the group, collect the money, buy the tickets for you. Then you can head into the movie and figure out if you want to go out afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry about this, but I'm on pretty strict bedrest for at least a few days (probably a lot longer). Laugh it up for me, eh? ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone's staying warm in this blizzard! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday's showing of Little Fockers starts at 7:50, so let's meet in the ticket lobby by 7:20. Then I can buy us all tickets, we can get snacks, and have a seat for the movie. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If, by any chance, the weather has you still snowed in by Tuesday night, please make sure to keep your RSVP current, so I know whom to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Snowstorm! And hope to see you Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What happens when the Fockers and the &amp;quot;Parents&amp;quot; mix with the adorable couple we know and love in Pam and Greg and their 2 kids? Hilarity will ensue, I'm sure, in the &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810110296/details" target="_blank"&gt;3rd installment of the Meet The Parents series.&lt;/a&gt; Let's laugh together and warm up for New Year's Eve...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The test of wills between Jack Byrnes and Greg Focker escalates to new heights. It has taken 10 years, two little Fockers with wife Pam and countless hurdles for Greg to finally get &amp;quot;in&amp;quot; with his tightly wound father-in-law, Jack. After the cash-strapped dad takes a job moonlighting for a drug company, however, Jack's suspicions about his favorite male nurse come roaring back. When Greg and Pam's entire clan -- including Pam's lovelorn ex, Kevin -- descends for the twins' birthday party, Greg must prove to the skeptical Jack that he's fully capable as the man of the house. But with all the misunderstandings, spying and covert missions, will Greg pass Jack's final test and become the family's next patriarch -- or will the circle of trust be broken for good?  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Unos to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Little Fockers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293805731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289944204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Little Fockers</name><id>15468973</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293581700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/15468973/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>