<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kancamagus Hwy</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>42.972858</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hancock Overlook (near hair pin curve)</name><city>Hancock</city><id>4894362</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.979805</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;read the entire event description&lt;/span&gt; before you RSVP and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt; that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - in that case update your RSVP from a computer to generate them again so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared to respond to an emergency situation or being able to send a night in the woods if you have to. Bring your own stuff (described below) and know how to use it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Total mileage - 9.8 Miles; 2940 Feet of Elevation; Book Time 6.5 Hrs per AMC White Mtn Guide Book.&amp;nbsp; Due to winter condition, our hiking time might be longer than book time. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be climbing two 4000 footers off the Kanc. The majority of the hike will be in and out on the same trail&amp;nbsp; (~3.5 miles) before we get to the Hancock Loop Trail. There will be 5 water crossings on the way in if my memory is correct. We will be going clockwise, going up to Hancock then over to South Hancock. It is a steep climb up to Hancock and a steep climb down South Hancock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;HIKE-IN&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1.8 Miles Hancock Notch Tr &lt;br /&gt;

 * 0.7 Miles Cedar Brook Tr &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1.1 Miles Hancock Loop Tr to reach loop junction &lt;br /&gt;

 * 0.7 Miles Reach to Hancock (4420 ft) &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1.4 Miles Reach to South Hancock (4319 ft) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;HIKE-OUT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 * 0.5 Miles Come back to loop junction &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1.1 Miles Hancock Loop Tr to reach Cedar Br Tr &lt;br /&gt;

 * 0.7 Miles Cedar Br Tr &lt;br /&gt;

 * 1.8 Miles Hancock Notch Tr&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Since Fred W-R and Linda will have same hike one day before, we hope their group break the trails for us! :-)&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; (Thank you, Fred &amp;amp; Linda!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/strong&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted.&lt;/strong&gt; All participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on this trip, but, there are some sections of the trail which are very steep (both going up and going down).&amp;nbsp; As long as you deal with your dog when she/he needs help by yourself, we're okay someone brings dog. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;intermediate pace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;out-and-back trip we will use Hancock Notch and Cedar Brook Trails to reach the Hancock Notch Trail to reach the summit and then follow the same route in reverse back to our cars.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 9.8 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,000 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;It should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 7.5 hours to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip -&amp;nbsp;this estimate allows for slower travel during winter.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;summit area is &lt;strong&gt;not exposed, but&lt;/strong&gt; you will need to be prepared for&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;windy conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Expect to come out in the early hours of darkness if we encounter any significant snow and/or ice. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&amp;nbsp;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Click below&amp;nbsp;for more information about each peak:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6967"&gt;Hancock&lt;/a&gt; (peakbagger.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailsnh.com/NH-4000.php"&gt;Current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(TrailsNH.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. Mountaineering snowshoes with aggressive teeth for traction while climbing.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;While we may not need snow shoes on the hike you need to bring them to the trailhead - know how to attach them to your pack in case we do need to bring them along (the last time I did this I had to go back to my car after a mile in to get them!).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable for this hike. &amp;nbsp;Mountaineering crampons with 10-12 teeth are optional. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clot&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;hing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly conducts heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket (e.g. fleece). Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants (e.g. gore-tex). Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens&amp;nbsp;(e.g. gore-tex).&amp;nbsp;Goggles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles (e.g. nalgene) instead of a hydration bladder (tube could freeze). You may want to bring a thermos with a hot drink. Also, you may want to heat some of your water. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them, know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder temperatures). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be meeting at the parking area on the Kancamagus (Rte. 112), just after the hairpin turn.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My car is Honda CR-V  or Subaru Outback (Blue)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326331162000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324865887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Winter 4K's - Hancock &amp; South Hancock (INTERMEDIATE)</name><id>45462102</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326027600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/45462102/</event_url></item>