<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>“WHEN YOU RESONATE WITH SOMEONE IT IS LIKE MUSIC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HAVE YOU EVER HEARD A CHOIR SING&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL THE DIFFERENT PITCHES COME INTO ONE PITCH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE DO NOT HAVE THE LANGUAGE TO PUT IT INTO WORDS”&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Have you ever wished for an effective tool to help you identify problems in a  relationship? Something that can also help you find a match between you and another person, bring about an experience of mutual comfort?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you wanted to know how to know your future and past and then effect the outcome?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then you want to learn and master Energy Scaling during this three day intensive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost - $275 early registration, 300 late registration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Knowing how to scale is the very key to living with uncertainty and facing challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Energy Scaling is a methodology for “tuning into the same wavelength” as other people, situations or your own emotions to find out what is truly going on and create change harmoniously. It is based on the fact that the human energy system has a built-in resonance-based mechanism to deal with complex situations. If we learn to tune in to our innate ability for energetic scaling then we can stop worrying about what we need to do in a particular situation and allow our energy field to do what it knows how to do naturally - to go directly to find a “matching wavelength” in any given situation. Through scaling you will learn to make deeper connections to people and to your own emotions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can you get from learning this method?&lt;br /&gt;For more information go to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.healingwithouteffort.com/blog.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.healingwit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what people say about Energetic Scaling&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Yuliya Cohen’s innovative exercises are helpful for clinicians in their personal work as well as for clients. A lovely suggestion is for practicing 'scaling' (harmonizing) your field to the field of another person. Cohen suggests a novel way of applying this: When you anticipate a challenging interaction with someone, you can pre-harmonize your field with theirs so that your upcoming interaction proceeds from a more harmonious starting point. Just think of the difficult people in your family, social, work and other relationships with whom this could be helpful!”.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt; Dan Benor, MD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“I scale whenever I feel confused or hesitant because that simple process seems to yield many more answers than anything else. When I scale, I am able to find the answers that I am looking for about most situations.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Workshop participant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I experimented with using energy scaling during a dance and discovered that when I was scaling I was usually instantly asked to dance.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Workshop participant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I find it interesting how many people there are who, like me, live their lives unaware of what surrounds them, and of how much they can personally affect the outcome of their interactions. When I practice scaling, it allows me to gather myself. It forces me to be quiet so that I could become more aware of the energy patterns, to fully understand the situations and to know how to proceed. This exercise has made me more aware and more functional in a society as a whole person.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&amp;quot; Workshop participant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Scaling can help you identify problems in a relationship. It can also help you find a match between you and another person, bringing about an experience of mutual comfort.&lt;br /&gt;    * Energy Scaling can be used for getting in touch and healing internal emotional states as well as states of physical discomfort.&lt;br /&gt;    * Energy scaling is not limited to real time interactions. Distant scaling can be carried out equally well with a person who is absent.&lt;br /&gt;    * Scaling can be used to tune into situations. It enables you to handle a situation that is ongoing, as well as a situation that has not happened yet - to preempt potentially problematic encounters that could happen in the future.&lt;br /&gt;    * Energy Scaling has many far reaching benefits. It can enable you to improve your relationships with family members, avoid conflicts in a work environment, and bring meaning and a sense of ease to dating situations.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291676568000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290661956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Energetic Scaling: Weekend Intensive </name><id>15553138</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291420800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/15553138/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/e/7/global_19858327.jpeg</photo_url></item>