<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hopkinton, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><lat>42.225433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hopkinton State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>3554392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.548653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our 6th Annual Friends &amp;amp; Family BBQ and Romp for Rotties &amp;amp; Pitties! It's time to bring your pooches and join the party! This is our biggest event of the year - both for the camaraderie of rottie and pittie lovers, and as our fundraiser -- and we want you here! This event helps to support our annual rescue activities, and also lets our adoptive families and friends get together for a great time! Register to Romp! | Can't Attend? Sponsor a Participant! Sunday, October 2, 2011 Noon - 4 p.m. Hopkinton State Park Split Rock Group area Rt 85, Hopkinton MA Schedule of events 11:30 a.m - Vendor Set up Noon - Romp begins. Register here to Romp and see our total funds raised ~Thank you all who pledged! Event begins. 12:30 p.m. - BBQ ready -- enjoy! 1 p.m. - Rescue Reunion Parade Download Registration as PDF 1:30 p.m. - Scavenger hunt &amp;amp; Kids games 2 - 3 p.m. - Canine Good Citizen testing 3 p.m. - Raffle Winners Drawn 4 p.m. - Event ends The BBQ For the Love of Dog has the staples - plates, cutlery, condiments, and some basics for the grill. Guests are asked to bring something to share (think outside of the bag -- fruit, various salads, etc). If you want something specific for the grill, bring it along and bring your own beverage. Alcohol is not permitted in Massachusetts state parks. Grill will be fired up for noon. Rompin' for Rotties &amp;amp; Pitties Hopkinton State Park has well-manicured landscaping and marked trails through around lakes and through nature's best. Join the rotties and pitties (and the not-weilers) to delight in all that the park has to offer with a stroll around the park. The directors of For the Love of Dog challenges each of you to BEAT our goal of $1000 EACH in sponsors! We know you can do it! Want to make your walking even more worthwhile? Ask your friends to sponsor you for the dogs. Or - support one of our already registered walkers. Not required, by any means - but the dogs will appreciate the support! There is a $20 registration fee. Rescue Reunion Parade Yup. We want them all there! All of our rescued dogs will be able to participate in the parade. There are a lot of you and we want to see you all showing your stuff. Download Registration as PDF. Can't join us that day? Join us in spirit! Send us your dog's story and photo and we'll display it at the event! What we'll need is your dog's story (you can use the Parade of Rescue Dogs text for a guide) along with a picture. We'd prefer this in a Word document or as a 8 1/2 X 11&amp;quot; PDF. You can email it, along with a donation of $10 or more and we'll include our missing canine alumni at the event! Canine Good Citizen Testing An outdoor event that will not take place in the rain. For the Love of Dog believes that every dog should be a Canine Good Citizen -- but moreso a representative in society of what our breeds can be (and not what the media portrays them to be). Canine Good Citizen testing will be available during the day at a cost of $20 per dog. Your dog does not have to be a purebred to receive the award, nor does it need to be AKC registered. The dog and handler just need to act as a team and complete the testing. Not limited to rescued dogs. Here's what your dog has to be able to do. Raffles Buy some tickets and take some chances! There's always great stuff here! Tickets are $1 each or 6/$5. Donations are still being accepted - whether they are dog-related or non-dog related ... anything that can raise money for our four-legged friends is always welcome. Gift cards are always a great idea. Email Kristine to coordinate! Cool Rottie &amp;amp; Pittie stuff for every taste Not only will all of our one-of-a-kind items be available for sale, we have several vendors that day who will present their wares for sale. Vendors include: Head to Tail Massage Love Thy Pitbull Palmer Family Chiro Fred Levy Art - offering photo shoot on site. $20 for shoot and 1 5X7 print Games &amp;amp; Prizes Move over Scooby Doo! The kids' scavenger hunt was a huge hit last year, and promises to be again this year. Also on deck: Bobbing for Hot Dogs, Chinese Raffle, Sloppiest Kiss, Best Wag and Best Wiggle Butt, and much more! This event is rain or shine&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317658929000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316286661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Romp for the Rotties &amp; Pitties!</name><id>33930142</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317571200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/33930142/</event_url></item>