<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>765 Commonwealth Avenue</address_2><address_1>BU School of Law, 1st floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.350833</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barrister's Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>1082487</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106667</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>“There lives the dearest freshness deep down things . . .”: a reading and conversation in the “Eurospectives” series. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saskia Hamilton is the author of As for Dream (2001) and Divide These (Graywolf Press, 2005) and the editor of The Letters of Robert Lowell (FSG, 2005). She lives in New York and teaches at Barnard College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kieron Winn's poems have appeared in Agenda, The Dark Horse, The London Magazine, Oxford Magazine, Oxford Poetry, Poetry Review, The Rialto and The Spectator, and in a short film about his work on BBC1. He lives in Oxford, where he is a freelance teacher.        &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                                                                                                 &lt;br /&gt;Moderator: Christopher Ricks, William M. and Sara B. Warren Professor of the Humanities at Boston University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public; reception to follow. Presented by AGNI and BU’s Institute for Human Sciences.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Co-sponsored by the Center for International Relations at Boston University, in cooperation with the Boston University Poetry Reading Series, the American Literary Translators Association (ALTA), and Zephyr Press.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Funded by the European Commission Delegation in Washington, DC, with additional support from the Boston University Humanities Foundation.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255132524000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254504604000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading: Saskia Hamilton and Kieron Winn at BU</name><id>11530061</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254783600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/11530061/</event_url></item>