<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi All! I've had to move the date and time due to the limited release, it will only be in a few theaters for a few days, so we will be seeing the 7:45 show at AMC Boston Common instead. Let's plan on meeting in the lower lobby at 7 to ensure we can all get in and sit together. This location is a very easy T ride in on the Green Line if any of you are not inclined to drive in. Parking is generally available under the Common or on surrounding streets and there are other garages as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- Heidi (via Dana)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet to see Black Swan!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't want to see a ballet during the holidays?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Black Swan&amp;quot; follows the story of Nina, a ballerina in a New York City ballet company whose life, like all those in her profession, is completely consumed with dance. When artistic director Thomas Leroy decides to replace prima ballerina Beth MacIntyre for the opening production of their new season, &amp;quot;Swan Lake,&amp;quot; he narrows his choices to Nina and a new dancer, Lily. &amp;quot;Swan Lake&amp;quot; requires a dancer who can play both the White Swan with innocence and grace, and the Black Swan, who represents guile and sensuality. Nina fits the White Swan role perfectly but Lily is the personification of the Black Swan. As the two young dancers expand their rivalry, Nina becomes dangerously more in touch with her dark side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View the trailer here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/video/imdb/vi4024108569/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is in limited release, so the theater or time may need to be adjusted accordingly.  Please note that passes may not be available for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update as the date draws closer!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291912435000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290469827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Swan</name><id>15530857</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291852800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/15530857/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/3/global_19827091.jpeg</photo_url></item>