<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>118 South Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01843</zip><lat>42.696715</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cor Unum Meal Center</name><city>Lawrence</city><id>1412494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.163183</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;10/27/10 Update:  We have confirmed with the administrators, the total commitment for this event is 4-7:00pm.  They need setup,serve and cleanup crews; setup is 4-4:30pm where everyone gets into the areas of responsibility, Dinner serving is 4:30-6:30pm and cleanup is 6:30-7:00pm.  We want to impress that we need to give a serious number of volunteers, so if you are a maybe please wait until you are a definite to sign up.  There is a limited amount of openings, 15 across all three groups, so please if you are interested in volunteering please sign up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you know anything about Cor Unum or have been to their website you will know that Cor Unum's goal is to provide an environment that provides dignity.  For this reason, there is a dress code, everyone must be respectfully dressed.  We are expecting a volunteer packet and if we find there is anything out of the ordinary in the dress code we will post otherwise please dress accordingly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Family away for the Holiday?  No Family to spend the holiday with?  Want to make a difference in someone's life?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well come and join Donna &amp;amp; Janet serving Thanksgiving Dinner at Cor Unum in Lawrence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If all people are created equal, and if all people have the inalienable right to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness, much must be done to feed the hungry in Lawrence, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lawrence, Massachusetts, is one of the poorest cities in the United States, and is the poorest in Massachusetts. With a population of just over 82,000 people, 69 percent of whom are Hispanic, 33.1 percent of the people of Lawrence live below the poverty line. Of children under age 18 in Lawrence, 49.9 percent live in households below the poverty line, as do 27 percent of people age 65 and older.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The combination of economic poverty and an unusually expensive housing market leaves many people in Lawrence without enough money to adequately feed themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The majority of those who are hungry are members of families who work and do not earn enough income to pay for both housing and food. Approximately 75 percent of school-age children in Lawrence qualify for government-subsidized food programs – meaning that three out of four children in Lawrence are at risk for hunger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Existing food and meal distribution centers offer assistance to several hundred adults and children per day in Lawrence. However, given the overwhelming numbers of hungry people in the city, existing centers cannot nearly adequately provide for the needs of the hungry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  THE 11 AM TIME IS NOT A DEFINITE, WE ARE STILL IN COMMUNICATION WITH THE COORDINATOR AT COR UNUM TO FIND OUT WHAT THE TIME COMMITTMENT IS, ONCE WE HAVE THIS WE WILL UPDATE THE SITE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please, only serious RSVP's please.  We need to be able to give Cor Unum an accurate number of volunteers.  If you do sign up with the intention of assisting, but something comes up at the last minute, please contact Donna or Janet ASAP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all at Cor Unum on Turkey Day&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Janet or Donna once entering the building</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290779753000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288054289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer Event @Cor Unum</name><id>15228104</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290718800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/15228104/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/5/1/global_19078433.jpeg</photo_url></item>