<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374401</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #2</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>832579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121895</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you have questions about how to improve your love life?  Would you like to get better results in the world of dating and you're not sure where to begin?  Maybe you have no trouble going to meetup events, but you just aren't making the kind of connections that you hoped for, and you'd like help with that.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you'd like to get answers and help with your specific challenges, then you're going to love this.  Here's what this is all about:  My name is Jason, for the last year I have produced highly structured dating and social skills workshops for this group, and people just like you have gotten a ton of value out of them.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;But even with the success that this group has enjoyed, I honestly believe we can go further and create educational events that are even more fun and more magical.  So in the spirit of that, I've decided to turn this next workshop on its head and do something we've never done before.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;WE ARE GOING TO CREATE THE WORKSHOP TOGETHER... IN THE MOMENT!&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Here's how this will work.  You'll come to the workshop with one or two questions or situations that you'd like help with, and we'll create a lesson or an exercise we can all benefit from right on the spot.  This will allow for ideas that are totally unexpected and unplanned to emerge, and we'll all be energized by what we can create in the moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you have questions about how to make small talk easier (or how to transition from small talk to getting a date)?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would you like to be able to ask someone on a date, but you're nervous and out of practice?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you find yourself getting into conversations that lead nowhere and want help becoming more interesting?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are you unhappy about the way your love life is going, but you're not sure what to do in order to change it?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you have questions about sex?  Maybe you want to know how to have better sex.  Or, maybe you want to know how to have MORE sex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;ALL OF THESE QUESTIONS (AND MORE) ARE FAIR GAME&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This will be the first workshop we've ever done where you can get personalized help with your individual &amp;quot;sticking points&amp;quot; or challenges.  This is sure to be a lot of fun, and I'm excited to see what we can all create together.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Also, you'll be able to submit your questions anonymously on paper so that nobody knows who asked the question (if you choose).  I want you to feel safe and still get your questions answered even if you're too shy to speak up.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The unique workshop is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  We will start the seminar promptly at 3:30 and run until 5:30 (I &lt;i&gt;really do&lt;/i&gt; start on time).  Please plan on arriving early so you have time to settle in and network with the other students.  You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Because this is a new and experimental event, it will be limited to the first 30 people who sign up.  Our workshops often sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, October 25th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive early for registration and personal networking.  We will start promptly at 3:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261527389000</updated><rating><average>4.44999980927</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255921299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HELP!  My Love Life Sucks!</name><id>11657783</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256499000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/11657783/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/global_11298284.jpeg</photo_url></item>