<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I hope you'll join me for the One-man Star Wars show at the Coolidge Corner Theatre. We'll be gathering in the alley by the box office approximately half an hour before hand (7:30pm).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ping me if you need my cell phone number.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OnStage @ the Coolidge presents: ONE-MAN STAR WARS TRILOGY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, November 15 @ 8:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/node/2819" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more details and to get tickets.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your light sabers ready, Boston, because Charles Ross is bringing his wildly entertaining ONE-MAN STARS WARS TRILOGY to the Coolidge. In this hilarious, kinetic solo piece, writer/performer Ross plays all the characters, recreates the effects, sings from John Williams’ score, flies the ships, and fights both sides of the battles from the original Star Wars trilogy, punctuating his virtuosic performance with captivating factoids and editorial asides. No costumes, no sets – just Ross using his yoga-limber body, knack for voices, and manic levels of energy. Did he spend too much of his childhood in a galaxy far, far away? Well, let’s just say that by age 10, he had seen the first Star Wars film more than 400 times and committed virtually every line to memory. Ross has since parlayed this childhood obsession into a one-of-kind theatrical piece, which he has performed to sell-out crowds in more than 180 cities across four continents. Where does he get his strength? It flows from the Force, of course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: $20 general admission/$17 Coolidge Corner Theatre members&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One-Man Star Wars Trilogy performed with permission of Lucasfilm Ltd. All Star Wars elements property of Lucasfilm Ltd. All rights reserved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“HYPERACTIVE...half homage, half satire. FUNNIER than you could possible imagine.” - Spin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Here’s a show assembled by a fan with knowledge that can’t be taught, delivered with a sly wink but an abiding love for the source material.” - Chicago Sun-Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Immediately accessible…It was great.” - Conan O'Brien&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry</member_name><member_id>12227382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289932385000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287175766000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ONE-MAN STAR WARS TRILOGY- OnStage @ the Coolidge</name><id>15122708</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289869200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/15122708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/e/global_18757470.jpeg</photo_url></item>