<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a midweek dinner at the Derby Street Shoppes in Hingham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rustic Kitchen's Bistro atmosphere, wood burning oven, and extensive wine bar caters to not only the experienced diner, but the Business Professional lunch crowd, Mall Shoppers, Tourists, and the after work social scene, as well. The décor is dramatic, yet rustic with a comfortable atmosphere and good music.  Rustic Kitchen has ranked in the Top Ten in various categories in a number of restaurant &amp;quot;best of&amp;quot; listings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu offers a wide variety of homemade pastas, breads and desserts, wood oven baked pizzas and roasted entrees, and specialty dishes adorned with the freshest seasonal ingredients. The ingredients are of the highest quality and the recipes are of exceptional taste.  Many of their products can easily be ordered to take home, especially their Pizzas. Rustic Kitchen's wood burning oven produces some of the best pizzas around, in addition to several oven roasted specialties. All Rustic Kitchen pizzas are thin-crusted and quickly cooked in wood burning ovens. Some of the more popular pizzas served are the Frutti di Mare pizza, the Italian Sausage &amp;amp; Roasted Pepper pizza, and the Margherita pizza.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner prices are $8-$29 including appetizers, entrees and pizza.  Dessert prices are $6-$9.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, May 23rd @ 7pm&lt;br /&gt;94 Derby Street&lt;br /&gt;Derby Street Shoppes&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-749-2700&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:  Max of 16, Members Only *Please Note: This was updated from no max and Guests Welcome to Max of 16 and Members Only @ 10pm on Friday, May 11th.  If you already said you are bringing a guest that guest is still welcome.  No new guests.  Sorry for any inconvenience.*&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline:  4pm on Tuesday, May 22nd (At this time the Organizers will close registrations at the current number of Yes RSVP's or they will set a maximum which will allow a couple more people to RSVP up until the afternoon of the event.  Please note if you RSVP after this deadline you may not be on the attendee list if the Organizers are unable to print an updated list the day of the event.)&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizers: Kathryn R. (&amp;quot;Kathy&amp;quot;) and Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we reach the maximum we will go on a wait list.  Here's how it will work.  &lt;br /&gt;1. RSVP No and state in your comments &amp;quot;if a space opens up I would like to attend&amp;quot; and include the DATE of your RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;2. As space opens up please allow those who are on the waitlist to update their RSVP to Yes and follow step 1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Overview: Rustic Kitchen is located in the Derby Street Shoppes off Route 53 in Hingham, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*From Route 3: Take Exit 15 towards Route 53/S. Hingham - Take a Right off the Exit ramp coming from Route 3 SB and a Left off the Exit ramp coming from Route 3 NB - Follow to the first set of lights.  Take a Right at the first set of lights into the Derby Street Shoppes.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 53NB: Follow Route 53 North to Queen Anne's Corner.  Route 53 will bear off to the right.  You want to bear to the left (of Route 53) onto Derby Street.  Follow about 1-2 miles till you see the Derby Street Shoppes on your left.  Take a left at the lights into the Derby Street Shoppes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1181099425000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178490901000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Midweek Dinner!</name><id>5748402</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179961200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5748402/</event_url></item>