<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.5</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Boston Ballet is performing Jirí Kylián’s Black &amp;amp; White again this year.  I saw it last year and it was wonderful.  The pieces are modern dance – creative, funny, visually sparkling, modern dance.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program includes five pieces:  No More Play, Petite Mort, Sarabande, Falling Angels, and Sechs Tänze.  Kylián does a number of things that could be cheesy, but aren't.  For example, modern dance usually also uses modern music.  Kylián uses Mozart.  And in one piece, part of the stage is lit and part is dark.  The dancers move in and out of the light.  It could be cheesy, but it isn't.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is also a pre-performance lecture at 7PM.  This is free to anyone who has a ticket for the performance.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If people are interested, we can also go for drinks after the performance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE 12May2010:&lt;br /&gt;I've already purchased tickets for the two of us who are signed up.  At this point, you should purchase your tickets directly from the box office.  You can join us for the pre-performance lecture, and/or for drinks after the performance, but during the performance your seats will very likely not be near ours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to join us for the pre-performance lecture, and/or for drinks after the performance, put yourself on the waiting list and I'll send details about where to meet.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DON'T FORGET:&lt;/b&gt;  You have to buy your own ticket directly from the box office.  Being on the waiting list just lets me know that I should send you details about where to meet us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send details to people who get tickets.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>A</member_name><member_id>8074607</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275182394000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273003193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Czech Dance Genius</name><id>13384170</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275177600000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/13384170/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/a/3/global_14836003.jpeg</photo_url></item>