<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>359 Washington Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.751176</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Learning Corridor: Theater of The Performing Arts</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1405482</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.683112</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;I know this is a little short notice but this sounds like a nice venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a really fun event for a great cause! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The annual Community Spelling Bee is a major fundraiser for Achieve Hartford, a non-profit organization with the following mission statement (as posted on their webpage) &lt;a href="http://www.achievehar.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.achievehar...&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;quot;Achieve Hartford! is an independent, nonprofit organization of business and community leaders that focuses on student achievement and supporting effective and sustained school reform in the Hartford Public Schools. We believe that a system of high-performing public schools is essential for our children and for the future of Hartford.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here the description of the Spelling Bee itself, also taken from the website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.achievehar.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.achievehar...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Community Spelling Bee &lt;br /&gt;The Community Spelling Bee is a fun-filled, family-friendly event that is designed to celebrate learning while raising awareness and support for Achieve Hartford! programs and initiatives. It is an evening of lively and exciting competition amongst friends, family and neighbors! Do join us to have a honey of a time this year on Friday, October 22nd, 7-9pm at the Theater of the Performing Arts, at the Learning Corridor, 359 Washington Street, Hartford. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Up to forty teams of three people each (high school age and older) compete in a bustling and spirited competition to spell increasingly difficult words. Teams are encouraged to create a team name; wear unique team T-shirts or costumes, and to bring a cheering section. We make available the word list from which team members can study. The words used in the Bee are drawn from this list. The registration fee to participate is $500; however, there is no charge to cheer from the audience. The evening also includes complementary refreshments (this is an alcohol-free event). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim </member_name><member_id>6478306</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287972836000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287572544000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th Annual Community Spelling Bee (Come support Kelly's team!)</name><id>15169047</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287788400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/15169047/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/4/global_15939476.jpeg</photo_url></item>