<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>Mass. Ave. &amp; Church St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374420</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Church Meetinghouse</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>274946</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118858</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cambridge Forum is pleased to welcome best-selling author FRANCES MOORE LAPPÉ for a discussion of her latest book; &amp;quot;Getting a Grip: Clarity, Creativity &amp;amp; Courage in a World Gone Mad&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because we are creatures of the mind, says Lappé (Diet for a Small Planet), it is the power of our core assumptions about how the world works that determines outcomes. She pinpoints the dominant, failing frame now driving our planet toward disaster. Then, with fresh insights, startling facts, and stirring vignettes of ordinary people pursuing creative solutions, Lappé uncovers a new, empowering frame emerging worldwide.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lappé writes, &amp;quot;My book's intent is to enable us to see what is happening all around us, but is still invisible to most of us. It is about people in all walks of life who are penetrating the spiral of despair and reversing it with new ideas, ingenious innovation and courage.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Some of the 20th century's most vibrant activist thinkers have been American women; Margaret Mead, Jeanette Rankin, Barbara Ward, Dorothy Day - who took it upon themselves to pump life into basic truths. Frances Moore Lappé is among them.&amp;quot; - The Washington Post &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frances Moore Lappé is the author or coauthor of sixteen books. Her 1971 three-million-copy bestseller Diet for a Small Planet continues to awaken readers to the human-made causes of hunger and the power of our everyday choices to create the world we want. Frances is a sought after public speaker and has received seventeen honorary doctorates from distinguished institutions. In 1987 in Sweden, Lappé became the fourth American to receive the Right Livelihood Award, sometimes called the &amp;quot;Alternative Nobel.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I can't make this event. Enjoy the talk.
S.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215313834000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202422080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clarity, Creativity, and Courage </name><id>7286021</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205969400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/7286021/</event_url></item>