<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rt 16</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.257524</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt. Washington</name><city>Pinkham Notch</city><id>860943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.252387</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Optional modified plans for this are to possibly actually camp Saturday night ON the mountain below treeline. This would be a BARE BONES wilderness roughing it type of camping. No tents. GOOD 4 season bag required as temps could get to or below freezing with windchills. SAFE method of ensuring self and sleeping bag will stay dry should weather conditions get wet. Enough food and water for overnighting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As far as hiking east of the Mississippi goes - the 6,288 foot Mt. Washington gots to be on your list. Initial response from the exploratory query indicates some demand to hike this giant a second time in one summer. We're going to follow the same route that John and his team hiked earlier this month. Up the Tuckerman Ravine Trail (spectacular near the top) and down the soft footing Boot Spur Trail. This gives us a total distance of 9.5 miles and an elevation gain of 4,300 feet. Total round trip is about 7 to 8 hours. We'll start at 9:30 AM. Great views and a restaurant at the summit. This is a relentless and strenuous hike, but the pace will be adapted to the group. I would like to talk with everyone signing up for this hike before departure. My telephone number is 401-556-8955 and email: dmccarthy12@cox.net. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting place: Pinkham Notch Visitor Center, Route 16, Gorham, NH.  &lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the front door to the visitors center at 9:00 and plan to be on the trail by 9:30 AM.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center: (from AMC website) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take Interstate 95 North to Spaulding Turnpike North (at Portsmouth, N.H.).  &lt;br /&gt;2. Take Spaulding Turnpike North to Route 16 North.  &lt;br /&gt;3. Take Route 16 North to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center/Joe Dodge Lodge, which is located on the left side of Route 16 approximately 12 miles north of the Glen intersection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take Interstate 93 North to Route 104 East (Exit 23).  &lt;br /&gt;2. Take Route 104 East to Route 3 North (near Meredith).  &lt;br /&gt;3. Take Route 3 North to Route 25 East (intersection in Meredith).  &lt;br /&gt;4. Take Route 25 East to Route 16 North (near West Ossipee).  &lt;br /&gt;5. Take Route 16 North to Pinkham Notch Visitor Center/Joe Dodge Lodge, which is located on the left side of Route 16 approximately 12 miles north of the Glen intersection. &lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Equipment List &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Synthetic shirt and pants. No cotton. No jeans.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Sturdy Hiking Boots. No Sneakers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Rain / Wind Jacket. No Ponchos.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Warm fleece layer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Hat and gloves  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Something warm for the summit. Expect it to be very windy, and expect much cooler temperatures. Weather on Mt Washington is VERY VOLATILE, be prepared!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•2-3 liters Water  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Headlamp  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Trail Snacks  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Lunch  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Bug Repellent  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Gear: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Hiking Poles  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Gaiters  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Sunscreen / Sunglasses  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Camera / Binoculars &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Jeans, Sneakers, or Cotton clothing on the hike! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have a change of clothes in the car for when we get back. More details to come regarding overnight accommodations. &lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional info: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AMC sites:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.o.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.o.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Mountain National Forest site:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fs.fed.us/.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fs.fed.us/...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Random site:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://home.earthlink.." target="_blank"&gt;http://home.earthlink...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More...-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Liability Waiver &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Safety First!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at entrance door to the Visitors Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis </member_name><member_id>8755592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>10283481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282600358000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281933183000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Washington Round 2</name><id>14434734</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282395600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/14434734/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>