<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>In this meetup we will look at how trauma creates actual holes in our energy field, and how that causes energy leaks. I can actually see these leaks in a person. Just as with the oil spill, only when the leaks are plugged, can the healing  begin.  Begin repairing the world with plugging the leaks in your own energy field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The picture for this meetup is, drawn by my client, shows how her energy leaked prior to integration.&lt;br /&gt;The most resistant leaks are created through loss of power and will not be plugged unless the power is explicitly reclaimed using the universal principles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even physical injuries and trauma from accidents can only be healed completely once the body's energy is &amp;quot;folded&amp;quot; to back to restore to the pre-accident state. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most difficult to plug are the leaks created when something was actually stolen or taken away from you because the loss is not energetic, but a physical reality.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;The good news is that the Universe is on your side!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this evening workshop I'll demonstrate to you simple and effective energy healing techniques based on universal principles of energy ownership for plugging your wholes by retrieving your Own Lost Energy. These techniques will bring a profound sense of empowerment back into your life. No digging up memories. No heavy duty process work. Just bringing yourself back to lasting wholeness with love and ease. There will be time for everyone to work with something from your own past experience.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279406657000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278801835000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Repairing Your Leaking Vessel</name><id>14063188</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279234800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/14063188/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/5/global_16312837.jpeg</photo_url></item>