<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1398 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.424763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 643-9090</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668948</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.186264</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cambridge SEO Group meets the first monday of each month. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We invite local Boston seo, affiliate marketing and search engine marketing professionals in New England area to join us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:45pm to 7pm:  Get Your Food/Drinks and Network &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm:  Business Card Bowl:  drop you card in and we will try to make copies for all that attend, before the end of the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm to 7:45:  2 Min Elevator Pitch: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Tell us about you and your business or website interest&lt;br /&gt;* Share something personaly that most people wouldn't know about you? &lt;br /&gt;* Share your networking goals with the group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:45 to 8pm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Fitzsimmons &lt;br /&gt;www.hubspot.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get a behind the scene quick demo to Hubspot.com's beta software for keyword and seo tools.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the mean time, see how your site grade's currently with Hubspots seo review tool at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.smallbusinesshub.com/Tools/tabid/6722/Default.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.smallbusin...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:00pm to 8:15pm: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker 2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Brooks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.madberry.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.madberry.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optimizing AdSense: Strategies, Tips and Resources&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEO focuses on a critical component to making profits online: increasing the amount of organic traffic you bring to your website.  Equally important, however, is increasing the amount of revenue you generate from each visitor once they arrive at your site. Google's AdSense is a very common revenue source for many online businesses. I'm going to discuss a simple strategy for optimizing AdSense that resulted in a 40% increase in revenue per user for my sites with about 4 hours of work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:15 to 8:30pm  Best Websites &amp;amp; Tools:  Share your urls  &amp;amp; Whats Working?  Group Discussion to share success stories of what else is working?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 to 8:45pm: Share Your SEO Tips: Please post within your rsvp your url and then please take the time to review other sites listed prior to the meeting and write out your seo tips to exchange with fellow members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:45 to 9:00 pm:   Open Roundtable Challenge Discussion:  Please be specific about your challenges in your business or website. 3 to 5 min max spent on any one business model. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:00pm: Stand up and network or go home&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all at this informal Boston search engine round table discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cambridge SEO MeetUp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Guest Speaker's Wanted: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working hard to find industry experts and to develop a formal agenda to keep it interesting for all those that attend. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175726863000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173743460000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization April Meetup</name><id>5563259</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175553900000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/5563259/</event_url></item>