<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Friends, &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a unique event coming up on Saturday, February 26, to kick off our 10th anniversary season. I think it's one of the most exciting things we've ever done. Beginning at 12:00 noon, Gary Sredzienski will swim the following route: Odiorne Point (Rye, NH) to Whaleback Lighthouse (Kittery, ME) to Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouse (New Castle, NH) to the Kittery Town Dock at Kittery Point. The total distance is close to four miles, and the water temperature is expected to be about 35 degrees. Gary has been swimming all his life and has done long distance winter swims for charities including Seacoast Hospice, Share Our Strength, and the Krempels Brain Injury Foundation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gary is also a well-known musician who began his professional career as an accordion player at the age of 9. He performs 1960s surf rock, traditional ethnic, and original accordion compositions with the Portsmouth-based group, the Serfs. Gary also hosts a radio show, &amp;quot;Polka Party,&amp;quot; weekly on WUNH-FM in Durham. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the swim on February 26, at 5:00 p.m., Gary and his band, the Serfs, will play at a celebration party upstairs at Captain and Patty's restaurant, 90 Pepperrell Road (Route 103) in Kittery Point.  I would suggest Great Island Common in New Castle as a meetup place. I would move it to at least 1:30, though. Gary has decided that he will start from Odiorne Point around 1:00 or 1:30, so he won't be getting near New Castle until maybe 2:30ish or so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The purpose of this event is to raise awareness and funds for the preservation of our local lighthouses. The funds raised will be split evenly between our parent organization, the American Lighthouse Foundation, and Friends of Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouses.  see video on youtube...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PPuzjCitC0A" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can donate and/or purchase tickets for the post-swim party on our website. We also encourage people to get out on the day of the swim to root Gary on from places like Great Island Common in New Castle and Fort Foster in Kittery. Be creative! It would be great to see people come out with signs encouraging Gary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please forward to this email to your friends and family. Let's all work together to make this event a resounding success! Anything you can do to spread the word is appreciated. We're also looking for sponsorships. If you know of a local business that might be interested, your suggestions would be welcomed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget the party after the swim at Captain and Patty's in Kittery!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you,&lt;br /&gt;Jeremy D'Entremont&lt;br /&gt;Operations Manager, Friends of Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy D'Entremont</member_name><member_id>12517576</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298749729000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295960023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Swim for the Lights"</name><id>16177449</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298745000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/16177449/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/b/4/global_18198436.jpeg</photo_url></item>