<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A walk from Forest Hills T station through the Arnold Arboretum and around Jamaica Pond, then back. We will have lunch at the Dogwood Cafe which is across from the T station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10:30 inside the Forest Hills subway station, in front of the donut shop. There is $4 parking (free on Sundays) and free on street parking nearby. There is another parking lot across from the T which may be free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit these sites for driving directions and the Dogwoods menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.arboretum.harvard.edu/visitors/map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.arboretum....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.arboretum.harvard.edu/visitors/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.arboretum....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.dogwoodcafe.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Arnold Arboretum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Arnold Arboretum is a park for both outdoor enjoyment and scientific exploration. North America's first public arboretum, it is owned by the City of Boston and leased to Harvard University for 1,000 years, beginning in 1882. The 265 acres of rolling land includes meadows, forest and ponds with 4,000 different varieties of woody plants and 14,000 trees, shrubs and vines along with world-renowned horticultural collections. &lt;br /&gt;Peter's Hill, the highest point in the Necklace, provides a glorious view of the Boston skyline. The Hunnewell Center has a visitors center and bookstore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jamaica Pond Park &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Olmsted and most everyone else agreed that Jamaica Pond belonged in Boston's system of parks, and very few alterations were needed to improve upon this natural feature. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The pond plunged to more than 50 feet in depth, a kettlehole formed by an ancient glacier. Natural springs make it the largest and purest body of water in Boston. The state stocks the pond, and fishermen come here to catch trout and indigenous fish: pickerel, bass, hornpout and perch.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside the donut shop.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol T</member_name><member_id>3564111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227143301000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224968470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Arnold Arboretum and Jamaica Pond</name><id>9030852</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226849400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9030852/</event_url></item>