<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Starting January 2010, I will be hosting and moderating Online Spiritual Community Gatherings!  Over the years I have created a variety of local groups by bringing people together to build spiritual community. The purpose of this Online Spiritual Community Chat Room is to connect people in a spiritual community format and discuss spiritual and paranormal issues and concepts regardless of the physical distance between us.  I will be your moderator for the evening, feel free to ask me your spiritual questions and share with the group your ideas and thoughts.  This is a format that welcomes you to ask the simple, silly, odd and sometimes difficult questions.  All paranormal topics are welcomed.  Standard chat room rules apply.  Please read the disclaimer on the chat room page before entering the chat room.  The chat room will be open to enter 5 minutes before it's scheduled time.  The chat room only holds 25 people.  First come first served.&lt;br /&gt;The Chat Room gatherings will be scheduled the first and third Sundays from 5:00 PM to 6:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;*While this group is not structured for personal readings, if information from the other side &lt;br /&gt;and/or from someone’s guide comes through, I will share that with the group**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Chat Room Gathering that is held online.  To connect to the link and join the gathering, go to &lt;a href="http://www.isabeauesby.com/Isabeau_Esby/Chat_Room.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.isabeauesby.com/Isabeau_Esby/Chat_Room.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.isabeauesb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269378337000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261890467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Online Spiritual Chat Room</name><id>12151392</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269205200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/12151392/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/3/global_6795651.jpeg</photo_url></item>