<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01754</zip><lat>42.432468</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>El Huipil</name><city>Maynard</city><id>9307892</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.452324</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There is a developer who wants to bring 2 big-box retail stores to my small town, Maynard. The larger store would be the size of a Walmart Super-Center and the not-so-humongous store would be the size of a Home Depot. I feel this would ruin our small town charm and hurt our downtown area. They have given us a very short window to organize an opposition and now there is less than 4 weeks until a town vote on the issue, so I decided to reach out to the group for a little help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is part volunteering and part regular social walk. The volunteering part is an hour of distributing flyers door to door. We will work in teams of two, one on each side of the street, with everyone in the same neighborhood. I will have maps and routes for everyone and will coordinate by cell phone. We will meet in the municipal parking lot in front of the El Huipil Mexican restaurant and begin walking and distributing flyers from there. After an hour we will group up and continue walking together for a while and I can show you some of sights in town, making our way back. Then we can have lunch the Half Way Cafe, which is near the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an issue I feel strongly about and I would be very grateful for your support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greg&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in in the municipal parking lot in front of the Mexican restaurant</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363455274000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362922242000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>volunteer walk</name><id>108529122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363444200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/108529122/</event_url></item>