<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Drew (Dr. Andrew Neblett, Ph. D) will be giving a lecture on Sunday, January 27&lt;br /&gt;At 7:00 on numerous topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The topics will be include but not be limited to Spectal Energy Investigation, &lt;br /&gt;Expulsion of negative Spectral Engery, Conscious Energy, Hypnosis and&lt;br /&gt;other topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neblettonline.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neblettonl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.neblettonline.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are getting together at a location that will only &lt;br /&gt;Be given via e-mail and known to CT Paranormal members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The members will arrive around 7:00.&lt;br /&gt;The lecture will start around 7:30 and last an hour and a half.&lt;br /&gt;There will be a half hour for Questions and Answers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be coffee and other refreshments available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have heard Drew give lectures at the SGRA Paracon,&lt;br /&gt;SGRA Halloween Festival and at the recent SGRA Winter Forum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(SGRA = Smoking Gun Research Agency)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think that members of Unknown Zone and CT Paranormal&lt;br /&gt;Will enjoy this lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CT Paranormal, please put this event up as one of your Meet Ups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It there is bad weather, as there is at time time of year, then&lt;br /&gt;This event will be cancelled and rescheduled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I might add more to this RSVP at a later date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual, RSVP Maybes will be allowed up to January 26.&lt;br /&gt;The evening of January 26 Maybes will become No. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196448479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drew Presentation of Spectral Energy Investigation and Expulsion</name><id>6831459</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201478400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6831459/</event_url></item>