<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennet Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel</name><city>Cambridge, Harvard square</city><id>3395632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, I was so glad to check out the Regattabar website and find out my favorite Brazilian singer is coming back into town! She has a beautiful voice, but what's more is that she has a great group of musicians playing behind her. Ever since I saw her perform in the area for the first time a couple years, she has remained as one of my favorite artists. Her albums are in heavy rotation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the Regattabar description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sultry, seductive and infused with that inimitable samba swing, the music of Luísa Maita embodies the modern spirit of Brazil. She has been called the "New Voice of Brazil" by NPR and recently was recognized as Brazil's "Best New Artist" by the Brazilian Music Awards, the equivalent of a GRAMMY. Inspired by the bustling urban life found in her native city of São Paulo, her music has a contemporary vibe with influences from alternative pop and downtempo electronic music melded with an acoustic foundation deeply rooted in samba, bossa nova and MPB. Hailing from a country overflowing with musical talent, Luísa Maita rises above the fray as one of the most promising young singers of her generation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy tickets here (and get them early!):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2633" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2633&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As is usual process for our Regattabar meetups, we will be meeting afterward at Casablanca's. Join us for great music and great conversation afterward!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342976218000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338943966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Luisa Maita at The Regattabar!</name><id>67926352</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342911600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/67926352/</event_url></item>