<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I meet with a local group that frequently paddles this river for excersize and its convient location to our work places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can join us if you want..&lt;br /&gt;i get there a bit before 5 and we all hit the water around 5 to 5 30..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sometimes we put in here and retrieve at the weslian boat launch bt the harbor restaurant and bar in middletown.....&lt;br /&gt; a light would be a safety thing to have just in case.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notes: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE, from the north, &lt;br /&gt;Look at your map first.. I really try to add all the turns and stuff but once in a while i have left out something.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;get onto Rte 9 south, (to and in Cromwell) go to exit 19 &lt;br /&gt;Turn (right) off the exit, =west toward Kmart and Stop and Shop &lt;br /&gt;At the first light you see (intersection of rte 372 and rte 3) take the left (south toward stop n shop) onto rte 3= shunpike rd &lt;br /&gt;There is a KFC, MackDonalds, and a Drunkin Doonuts while heading to the next traffic light. Use Drunkin Donuts (driveway) there is an empty lot which is coned off but since there is construction going on , park down in the far back of the Drunken Donuts lot. &lt;br /&gt;There is a water trail sign showing the most dangerous animals and what not to feed the animals...including the banjo boys... &lt;br /&gt;I will have a spare kayak with me for anyone that wants to use it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i found it after the last person became dinner for some wild animal..&lt;br /&gt;No sining &amp;quot; Har... Paddling in a dead mans kayak, looking over my back, incase the gohst wants it back..&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip usually takes 2 hours or so but if we do some exploring ..then its over when its over provided you have not been eaten by wild creatures....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1157751665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tuesday Night Paddle on the Ookie Spookie River in Cromwell</name><id>5120011</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1158094800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5120011/</event_url></item>