<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>at the intersection of Charles St and Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.352848</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common - Charles Street side</name><city>Boston</city><id>754847</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067596</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're playing on Boston Common on Friday. Remember the rule on Boston Common - no cleats!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new and are not sure how to get to the field, check out the details on Boston Common. If you have questions, then contact either of the organizers listed for this game day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the game plan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 - Toss the disc around, meet folks, be merry&lt;br /&gt;* 7:15 - Overview of the rules, safety, etc - then divide into teams&lt;br /&gt;* 7:30 - Play!!!!!! biggrin&lt;br /&gt;* 9:00 - Conclude the meetup with snacks and socializing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what we humbly ask of you (works great as a checklist):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Bring a white t-shirt and a colored t-shirt&lt;br /&gt;* Arrive on time to be guaranteed a spot in a game (RSVP is optional - but helpful for others who want to know if people they played with in a previous game are going to be there smile)&lt;br /&gt;* Bring WATER!&lt;br /&gt;* If you are a regular, please consider bringing a buck for the Frisbee Fund&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, we will supply the frisbees, cones, lanyards, first aid supplies (hopefully will never be used) and our pretty smiles. As we periodically mention, all these supplies are paid out-of-pocket by your loving Frisbee organizers and everyone has been so generous with their donations to-date. Thank you and let's keep the dream alive!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andy&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy</member_name><member_id>6189580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295063607000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294687508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday night-time Ultimate @ Boston Common</name><id>15996031</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295049600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/15996031/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/7/e/global_14074478.jpeg</photo_url></item>