<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The actual screening time is 1:35.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; And while I imagine a good number have seen this film already, there are those like myself who haven't and others who might like to see it again and discuss it with people from our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nominated for 7 Golden Globe Awards and adapted from Ian McEwan's acclaimed novel-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one of the few adaptations that gives a splendid novel the film it deserves.   L.A. Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A mischievous girl accuses her older sister's lover of a crime he did not commit, only to find that her words have irrevocably and permanently changed the lives of all involved in a film that re-teams the filmmakers behind Pride &amp;amp; Prejudice to adapt the best-selling 2002  &lt;br /&gt;novel by author Ian McEwan. The year is 1935, and as the summer heat takes hold, 13-year-old fledgling writer Briony Tallis watches her older sister, Cecilia (Keira Knightley), get undressed and go frolicking in the garden fountain on her family's country estate. The housekeeper's son, Robbie (James McAvoy), a childhood friend and recent Cambridge graduate, also witnesses the innocent act. When Robbie and Cecilia subsequently cross a particularly sensitive boundary and the scheming Briony accuses Robbie of an unspeakable transgression for which the boy is wholly innocent, the repercussions of her unfounded claim threaten to affect all three for decades to come.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;amp;id=9312" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.boston.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Honestly, it appears  the long awaited  just-in-time-for- Oscar-nominations-in-December (JTOND) releases  were a bit of a disappointment this year. Atonement may be the best of the lot, receiving a number of good to almost-great reviews. Nonetheless, I'm sure we will have an engaging discussion afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and then its off to a restaurant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199406411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ian McEwan's Atonement</name><id>7024995</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201372200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7024995/</event_url></item>