<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>52.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/c/2/event_77961442.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not yet been to the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club, this is your time to do so! We are throwing a fun and wild weekend to start the New Year off right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Darlene and I and the rest of the Wedeln crew from Friday, December 30 through Sunday January 1 up at the most beautiful Ski Club in the Mount Washington Valley! But we are also the most active club, &amp;nbsp;spending most of our time outdoors during the day either skiing or riding at Wildcat, Attitash, Sunday River or Bretton Woods. Or Cross-Country skiing in beautiful Jackson, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or take advantage of NH's tax-free after Christmas bargains to be had in the many outlet stores...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then enjoying some needed downtime by the fireplace in our fabulously appointed living room or in our newly constructed social gathering area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Guest Fees are $25 per night plus $2 Amazon Payment fee. This must be paid online &amp;nbsp;in advance. (&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;total guest fees = &amp;nbsp;$52 via Meetup using Amazon Payments - NO REFUNDS GIVEN FOR ANY REASON)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Meals are TBD but are likely $25 - $30 for the weekend to be paid when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Special New Years Eve Social Event will be held. cost is $17 payment required when you check in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you arrive, you will be given a tour of the house and assigned to a room and bed. Rooms are separated by gender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are required to please bring your own:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bedding: (sleeping bag, pillow, or twin sheets, blanket, pillow)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Toiletries (towel, flip flops for shower, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Skis / Snowboards / Snowshoes / X-C skis can be brought up as well or rented easily from local shops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You are required to keep your room clean and may be asked to help keep beautiful ski lodge clean and orderly and keep our prices low by performing some light work around or outside the ski club.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Please Note - Space is extremely limited - so sign up today. You must reserve by Friday, December 23. Reservations will be closed after that date because I will be away visiting with family...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All guests must be 21 years of age or older and be able to provide an acceptable proof of age and identification upon arrival (State issued Driver's License or Government Issued Passport are acceptable forms of age and identification). As a private entity, the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors club reserves the right to remove guests from the premises for any reason.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jonathan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update on Meals:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Meal Package for the weekend is $25/pp and includes the menu highlighted below.&amp;nbsp; Thirty people must sign-up for Meals to secure the chef, so please plan to join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saturday Breakfast:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Option 1 &amp;ndash; Apple Cinnamon Pancakes or Plain with Homefries and Bacon or Sausage. &lt;br /&gt;

 Option 2&amp;nbsp; 2 Eggs, Homefries and Sausage or Bacon. &lt;br /&gt;

 Option 3 &amp;ndash; Healthy Option &amp;ndash; Fresh Fruit &amp;amp; Yogurt w/Granola.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saturday Dinner:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Apple Cider Pork Tenderloin with Cranberry Stuffing, Wild Rice and Fall Roasted Vegetables. &lt;br /&gt;

 Soup &amp;ndash; Butternut Squash Bisque &lt;br /&gt;

 Salad &amp;ndash; Harvest Mixed Green Salad&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Dessert &amp;ndash; Apple Crisp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunday Breakfast:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Option 1 &amp;ndash; Apple Cinnamon Pancakes or Plain with Homefries and Bacon or Sausage. &lt;br /&gt;

 Option 2&amp;nbsp; 2 Eggs, Homefries and Sausage or Bacon. &lt;br /&gt;

 Option 3 &amp;ndash; Healthy Option &amp;ndash; Fresh Fruit &amp;amp; Yogurt w/Granola.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be given out to Meetup Guests who have paid up in advance by December 23.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325524556000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323350719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Happy New Year's meetup @ Wedeln Ski &amp; Outdoors Club</name><id>43807772</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325296800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/43807772/</event_url></item>