<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Health Screenings Dec 2 at Dinner Speaker Series featuring Dr. Bober &amp;amp; Julie Burke&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Waltham Speaker Series &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Optimum Health Solution &amp;amp; Raw New England Community present a rare opportunity to have:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Discounted Strategic Health Assessments&lt;br /&gt;State-of-the-Art &amp;amp; Wave of the Future&lt;br /&gt;with Dr. Thom Bober &amp;amp; Dr. Julie Burke&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thom Bober, DC is a practicing chiropractic physician who focuses on helping people transiton towards whole food solutions for their health challenges.  He consults with health professionals across the country, educating them on systems and serices that educate patients in the need to engage and comply with nutritional protocols.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Julie Burke&lt;br /&gt;founded Newton Chiropractic Centre in 1991, and graduated magna cum laude from Boston College and Palmer College of Chiropractic.  While at Palmer, Dr. Burke taught anatomy and histology.  Her post-doctoral education includes years of continuing study in Network Spinal Analysis in which she has earned the highest level of certification.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When:  Tuesday, December 2,  4:30 - 9:30 PM (Time change since printed flyer)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * 4:30 PM Registration, Set-up &amp;amp; Socializing&lt;br /&gt;    * 4:45 - 9:30 PM  Assessments &lt;br /&gt;    * 5:30 - 6 Film &amp;quot;The pH Miracle- Dr. Robert Young&lt;br /&gt;    * 6:00 - 6:45 PM Dinner - Raw Vegan Potluck &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM  Lecture: Dr. Thom Bober will speak on &amp;quot;The Future of Assessment Technology - The Wave of the Future&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  U Mass Waltham Center, 240 Beaver St., Waltham, MS 02452, for directions call 781-891-0650 x 56&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Six Strategic Health Assessments are state-of-the-art tests, high-tech, and non-invasive. Each service is about 15 minutes, $30 per service or $25 for four or more services. Afterwards, the services are followed by recommendations by Dr. Thom Bober.  (Comparable tests are $50-$125).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cardiovascular Screening&lt;br /&gt;1. Determine the biological age of your arteries before you need intervention.&lt;br /&gt;2. Heart rate variability determines resilience and health of your heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live Blood Analysis&lt;br /&gt;Nutritional Microscopy enables you to see your blood live on a computer monitor.  The health of your blood determines the health of your body.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hemoglobin A1c Testing&lt;br /&gt;Blood Sugar Screening that more accurately evaluates the health of your blood sugar metabolism and your chance of developing diabetes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ultraviolet Facial Digital ultraviolet photography allows you to see the health and  damage to your skin below the surface where the damage first develops.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ionic Detoxifying Foot Bath&lt;br /&gt;Our daily environment is flooded with toxins in our food, water and air.  You cannot avoid it! This causes severe trauma to our bodies. Detoxification is a critical strategy for health. The water will actually change a variety of colors depending on the toxins that come out.  This test is designed and developed to restore the body's energy and balance while facilitating its natural detoxification process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call Betsy Bragg at Optimum Health Solution - Office 781-899-6664 to pre-register.  Only your check reserves your appointment. Mail or bring checks payable to Optimum Health Solution(a 501c3) to 337 Newton St. # 4, Waltham, MA 02453.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Members $5, non-members $10. Please bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based ready-to-serve dish. $10 extra without food.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betsy Bragg, Executive Director&lt;br /&gt;Optimum Health Solution&lt;br /&gt;337 Newton Street, #4&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02453&lt;br /&gt;Office 781-899-6664/Cell 617-835-2913&lt;br /&gt;Fax 617-663-6868&lt;br /&gt;Email betsy@optimumhealthsolution.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229202561000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227165452000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltham RawPotluck &amp; Health Screenings</name><id>9199022</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228253400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/9199022/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/4/f/global_6376687.jpeg</photo_url></item>