<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a pretty section of New Hampshire coast line. The hiking trails are quite flat. Odiorne State Park offers an extensive array of habitats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Science Center lot at 10:00 AM and start the hike at 10:10.   The walk will be about 3-4 miles long.  There are numerous turn back points for those who want a shorter walk. I will ask that you vote on a picnic or lunch nearby.  There are some nice places to have lunch after the hike (Petey's has great chowder). If the weather is nice you may want to bring a lunch. There are many tables in the park to have a picnic. &lt;u&gt;They do not allow dogs at the park&lt;/u&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The address of the Seaside Science Center located within Odiorne Point State Park is 570 Ocean Blvd, Rye, NH 03870.   Their phone # is 603-436-8043.   I would recommend using a GPS or mapping this out in advance as we got a little lost the first time we visited this location &lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 95 North or South &lt;br /&gt;Take exit 5 off of Interstate 95 North or South toward US-1 Bypass/Portsmouth Circle.  Go .6 mi.  to the Portsmouth Traffic Circle. At the traffic circle, take the 1st exit onto US-1 Bypass S.   Continue 1.3 mi.  Continue onto Lafayette Rd (.7 mi).  Turn left at Elwyn Rd and continue on this route for 1.4 miles. At the traffic circle, take the 2nd exit onto New Hampshire 1A S/Pioneer Rd.  Continue to follow New Hampshire 1A S for 1.5 miles.  The Science Center will be on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming from the South some people may want to take Route 1A along the coast from Hampton Beach. It's a beautiful ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some information on the area: &lt;br /&gt;Odiorne Point is the largest undeveloped stretch of shore on New Hampshire's eighteen mile coast. Located three miles south of Portsmouth on Route 1A in Rye, Odiorne offers an extensive array of habitats.  Just north, the shore evolves into a pebble beach which shelters a fresh water marsh. Along the way to Frost Point where a jetty extends into Little Harbor, lies a small sand dune environment. At the end of Little Harbor, Seavey Creek feeds the neighboring salt marsh. Extensive inland disturbances during World War II induced the growth of dense forests in various stages of succession. Large stone walls bound open fields. Fresh water systems are represented within the park by a man-made pond and marsh. Remnants of formal gardens and wildflowers grow side by side; and the man-made military bunkers lie hidden under mounds of earth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in the history of park, visit this link: &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/OdiorneStatePark_History_2010.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to print out a trail map in advance, visit this link: &lt;a href="http://nhparks.state.nh.us/state-parks/alphabetical-order/odiorne-point-state-park/map.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://nhparks.state....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting in the parking lot wearing a meetup sticker.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1284426544000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274581821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Odiorne Point State Park Walk- with Many Stops followed by Lunch </name><id>13566052</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284300000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13566052/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/b/global_11008251.jpeg</photo_url></item>