<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244965</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>1060268</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369168</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>February 21, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HI!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace and blessings! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time is flying by and our next INTERFAITH BOOK CLUB meeting (March 1st) is fast coming up.  For those who have not been able to join us, a reminder that on January 25th we finished reading and sharing &amp;quot;LIVING BUDDHA, LIVING CHRIST&amp;quot; by Thich Nhat Hanh. This book accompanied us in a lively way (good inter-action) as each one of us continue to travel the journey of faith.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In our common thirst for God, for meaning, for a deeper spirituality we were called back to some basic and yet fundamental values which I find expressed by the following lines from LIVING BUDDHA, LIVING CHRIST:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ In Buddhist monasteries before every meal, a monk or a nun recites these 5 contemplations: &amp;quot;This food is the gift of the whole universe - the earth, the sky, and much hard work. May we live in a way that is worthy of this food. May we transform our unskillful states of mind, especially that of greed. may we eat only foods that nourish us and prevent illness. May we accept this food for the realization of the way of understanding and love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ In the sermon of the mount, Jesus said: &amp;quot;Blessed are the peacemakers: for they shall be called the children of God.&amp;quot; Many who work for peace are not at peace. To make peace, our hearts much be at peace with the world. Trying to overcome evil with evil is not working for peace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ To &amp;quot;love our enemies&amp;quot; is impossible, because the moment we understand him/her, we feel compassion and he/she is no longer our enemy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ &amp;quot;There is no way to peace. Peace is the way.&amp;quot; We can realize peace right in the present moment with each look, smile, word and action. Peace is not an end. Each step we take should be peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ To a Buddhist, prayer without practice is not real prayer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ According to Judaism, the entire world, all the good things in life, belong to God, so when we enjoy something, we think of God and enjoy it in His presence. Piety is the recognition that everything is linked to the presence of God in every moment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ The kingdom of God is a treasure. Once you have touched the treasure, you know that the things you previously considered to be conditions for your happiness are just obstacles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ There are many conflicting feelings and ideas within us, and it is important for us to look deeply and know what is going on. When there are wars within us, it will not be long before we are at war with others, even those we love. With the energy of mindfulness, we can calm things down, understand them, and bring harmony back to the conflicting elements inside us. If we can learn ways to touch the peace, joy and happiness that are already there, we will become healthy and strong, and a resource for other. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LIVING BUDDHA, LIVING CHRIST asked of us to set ourselves on a journey for deeper meaning. A journey that brings us together elbow to elbow with people of different faiths and different experiences and yet all united in the common cause of making &amp;quot;this world a house worth living in.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To continue on, on this journey we have chosen: &amp;quot;ONE RIVER, MANY WELLS&amp;quot; by Matthew Fox as our companion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The format of our meetings is quite simple: we gather to share our reflections and reactions on what we read at home. For our next meeting (MARCH 1) we are going to share on the first 80 pages of the book. Even if you not able to read the material &amp;quot;assigned&amp;quot;, don't worry and come anyway. It has always been my belief that your simple presence can still foster deep and creative interaction. Hope to see all of you on March 1. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, our next meeting:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: MARCH 1, 2009 - 4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLACE: PEACE ABBEY - located at: Two North Main Street, Sherborn, MA 01770&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendars and hope to see you at the meeting. Enjoy this new wonderful book and have a great week. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe, sx &lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(508) 429-2144&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: pino.ma@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238360577000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232921126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club March 1 Meetup</name><id>9599166</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235941200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/9599166/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/b/c/global_7393468.jpeg</photo_url></item>