<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Boston Harborwalk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walk the Boston Harborwalk's North-End and Downtown sections. Check out the website below for an interactive map with pictures of some the sights along the way. From the meeting point we will walk east on Causeway St and pick up the Harborwalk at Prince St. We will follow the Harborwalk east and south to Summer St near South Station. Then over to Chinatown for dim sum at Emperor's Garden.  Those who don't want dim sum can choose to order from the menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10 am inside TD BankNorth Garden, formally known as the Fleet Center.  Specifically in the commuter rail train station that is inside the Garden building, meet in front of the donut shop. Take the T to North Station to get there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborwalk.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a sample of what's on the website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Burroughs Wharf&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Burroughs Wharf is home to Boston's Fire Marine unit. Be sure to see both vessels docked on the northern side of Burroughs Wharf. The larger of the two vessels is the 76-foot fire pump boat built in 1972. The other vessel, built in 1992, is a 30-ft high-speed pump boat. Visitors are welcome to view the vessels and the equipment to repair boats, view the equipment in the fire station, or ask questions of the marine firefighters. Behind the fire station are restrooms open to the public. Other amenities at Burroughs Wharf include a water fountain surrounded by landscaped gardens, a promenade, benches, lighting, shelter, signage, public landing area, marina slips, and a water taxi stop. This condominium complex has one of the most pedestrian-friendly walkways on the Boston waterfront. The HarborWalk that wraps around the two luxury condominium buildings boasts incredible views of the USS Constitution and Bunker Hill Monument in Charlestown and the Harbor and is a wonderful location to watch boats plying the waters in the Harbor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rowes Wharf / Boston Harbor Hotel&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Harbor Hotel's majestic, multi-story arch over the wide public plaza marks the throughway from Atlantic Avenue and Downtown Boston to the HarborWalk at Rowes Wharf and Boston Harbor. Here visitors will find luxury yachts at the slips of the Rowes Wharf marina, commuter boats, as well as Harbor cruise boats. The views across the Harbor to East Boston and Charlestown are wonderful. There are restaurants and a gift shop in the Hotel, an observatory known as Foster's Rotunda, a water transportation terminal and gazebo, and a floating dock with free concerts and movies during the summer months. &lt;br /&gt;The lobby of the Boston Harbor Hotel, accessible to all, is home to some of Norman B. Leventhal's renowned collection of Boston Harbor maps. Nearly 90 maps show exploration, development, and changes along the waterfront of Boston and the New England coast from the seventeenth through the nineteenth century. Public restrooms next to the transportation terminal are directly accessible from the HarborWalk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emperor's Garden&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chinatown &lt;br /&gt;690 Washington Street (Kneeland St.) &lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02111 &lt;br /&gt;617.482.8898 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170083145000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169332435000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harborwalk</name><id>5411151</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1169910000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5411151/</event_url></item>