<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>133 Elm Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308689</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Haven Free Public Library</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1575537</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925179</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A free lecture about Fracking is being put on at the New Haven Public Library and I intend on going to it.  I honestly don't know a lot about Fracking, other than green folk are making it out as a huge environmental problem, so it will be good to learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm going to try and get a decent seat at 6:15, lecture starts at 6:30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info on the event can be found &lt;a href="http://onhsa.yale.edu/science-news-lecture-series?utm_source=Daily+Nutmeg+New+Haven&amp;amp;utm_campaign=4b6ec305c7-Daily_Nutmeg&amp;amp;utm_medium=email"&gt;at THIS link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's first come first serve FREE Parking near by in Yale's Lot 51 on Temple Street (Lot is between houses 302 and 320).  Otherwise if parking you'd probably need to find a metered spot on Temple or Elm.  ($1.50/hr until 9pm)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Event description also promises Snacks, but no details on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm going in hopes I will find out if this is like Nuclear Energy and everyone's making a big Frackin' deal out of some thing that can be properly handled, or if there's more serious problems many of us are overlooking.  Right now I suppose I have very little Frackin' clue.  ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - If any of you wear a BSG related costume I will be very entertained... no that's not required and I don't have one, I'm just saying.  :-P&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event is in the Community Public Room.  It's my first time in that room, so I'll be lost to :-P, you can text 315-345-9348 if you don't see me, but phone will be off once lecture begins.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359553363000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359387975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science Lecture: "Fracking: Energy Angel or Environmental Demon?"</name><id>101774512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359501300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/101774512/</event_url></item>