<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Greater Boston Entertainment Leadership Council is a group of leaders committed to enhancing and cultivating the existing arts and entertainment community within Boston while at the same time generating new artistic endeavors aimed at rebranding the Boston Arts Scene to place Boston on the map as an arts and entertainment destination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week, the Council continued the branding process for the Boston Arts and Entertainment Community. With a great turn out and valuable contributions from all members, we were able propel our ideas forward and begin the exciting process of shaping an event which will eventually showcase our brand of the (&amp;quot;new&amp;quot;?) Boston arts community to the public. This week, the Council will continue our branding-shaping process, which has successfully become more focused and cohesive each week.  In addition, we will also begin the initial stages of public outreach. This week, I would specifically like to focus on fundraising ideas: How can we successfully raise money to support our group's cause?  Please ponder this question on 2 levels and bring your ideas to the meeting next weeks - 1) What are some practical outlets where we could raise money?; and 2) How do we appeal to these outlets? That is, what is this &amp;quot;cause&amp;quot; we are supporting are how is it unique?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also have a few &amp;quot;housekeeping&amp;quot; announcements:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Kim will be unable to attend this week's meeting because she will be attending NERFA, the Northeast Regional Folk Alliance Conference, where she will be speaking on panels about the exciting revolution occurring in the music industry today.  In her stead, Shannon will be faciliting the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- We will not be meeting on Thursday, November 22nd, due to the Thanksgiving Holiday.  Our next meeting will be two weeks after that, on December 5th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- The minutes from last week's meeting will be available by this weekend.  Due to some computer issues, Shannon will not be able to access the file until Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- As always, I would like to thank everyone for their contributions.  It was great to see some new faces and hear some new ideas and input about our Boston arts community.  Thank you to everyone that brought a friend; they are of course welcome at any of our meetings.  This week, let's continue that great momentum we've being picking up.  Thanks again and I will see all of next Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194649556000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193849502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Entertainment Leadership Council Meeting</name><id>6650493</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194476400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/6650493/</event_url></item>