<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.762536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-987-6000</phone><name>Bushnell Theater</name><city>Hartford</city><id>890377</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Phantom of the Opera&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;UPDATE:  I have had to push this event back one week to the following Saturday, May 2nd.  I hope that doesn't cause any problems for people.  Most of you have expressed an interest in sitting closer to the stage, so we are going to get tickets as close to the stage as possible.  These tickets are $82 for the Front Orchestra or Orchestra/Front Mezzanine.  If you want to sit together I will need to get our tickets in advance.  Email me for specifics.  Otherwise, you can buy your own tickets and sit apart and then look for us after the show.  We can get drinks or dinner together if there is enough interest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;deschats@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;With some of the most lavish sets, costumes and special effects ever to have been created for the stage, Andrew Lloyd Webber’s The Phantom of the Opera directed by Harold Prince traces the tragic love story of a beautiful opera singer and a young composer shamed by his physical appearance into a shadowy existence beneath the majestic Paris Opera House. Adapted from Gaston Leroux’s classic novel of mystery and suspense, this award-winning musical has woven its magical spell over standing room audiences in more than 100 cities worldwide and is now the longest running show in Broadway history. Phantom returns to Hartford to take your breath away.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241658494000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235843700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Phantom of the Opera</name><id>9845242</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241287200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/9845242/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>