<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ciao Tutti,   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BACK BY POPULAR DEMAND. SPACE WILL GO QUICK AND IS LIMITED. FIRST COME FIRST SERVE. CHRISTMAS CELEBRATION! We would like to have a Paisano(Yankee) Swap. Please bring a gift with you to this meetup. The gift limit is $10.00 so everyone can participate.&lt;/b&gt; This is a local Italian restaurant that is owned by Italians. They come from Naples and speak Italian.We will try our best to order in Italian as well as speak to the best of our ability that evening. I feel the best way to handle dinner is split the bill for food and cocktails on your own. This way if you don't drink you are not stuck with a large bill. I went to another Meetup that handled it this way and works out great. So we will split the food portion and drinks we will pay on our own. I do need only YES if you mean YES. I do have to give an accurate count on the 13th of December so first come first serve. But please RESPOND YES ONLY IF YOU ARE 100% SURE ON COMING. BECAUSE THIS IS A BIG GROUP THE MENU WILL BE LIMITED! Also please bring enough CASH to split the bill easier.&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ciao, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Amato &lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>sign and reservations</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Amato</member_name><member_id>3621990</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292683661000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Italian Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>italian-420</urlname><id>447590</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Italian Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291501040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Parliamo e Mangia al Gianfranco's Ristorante &amp; Bar</name><id>15642708</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292544000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-420/events/15642708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/4/global_2557124.jpeg</photo_url></item>