<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Essentials of Taoism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Healing &amp;amp; Transformation: The Essentials of Taoism is an four-part introductory program for anyone interested in learning more about Taoism. Workshops will be held every Sunday in February from 1 to 5 pm at the SunDo-Taoist Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The series, starting February 6, 2011, includes workshops on The Tao of Natural Breathing and Ancient Wisdom of the Tao Te Ching. In addition to discussion, participants will sample SunDo-Taoist Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For a complete listing of workshops, please see the &lt;a href="http://sundo.org/media/flyers/Introduction%20to%20Taoism.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;online flyer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f5e382"&gt;Participants will receive a 30-page booklet with articles and resources as a supplement to the workshops. After the last workshop on Feb 27, please join us for a group dinner at Ichiban Korean-Japanese restaurant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f5e382"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way you feel in your day-to-day life directly correlates with how well you breathe. Are you breathing a full, open healthy breath? Taoists believe that simply changing patterns of breathing can alter one&amp;rsquo;s perception and life experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taoist breathwork will not only bring about more physical health and well-being it also can open you to unlimited healing potential. An open healthy breath brings about a feeling of well-being that connects you with your highest good and empowers you to awaken new aspects of your life, and thus, draw in more positive experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Led by Taoist Master Hyunmoon Kim, an internationally renowned teacher and director of the SunDo-Taoist Studies Graduate Program at Hanseo University in South Korea, these workshops cover all aspects of SunDo, a mountain practice maintained by hermits in the mountains of Korea. We will also focus on integrating contemporary western psychology with ancient eastern teachings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individual workshops are $45 or $150 for all four. If registering early by February 3, participants can pay just $130. Registrations for all four workshops will receive priority. Space is limited to 12 students and we are only accepting a maximum of three to five meetup members. Registration is required at least 48 hours in advance. So the due date for payment is February 3, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mkzc.org/wp-content/uploads/2009/10/deep-breath.jpg" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297019870000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295133548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Essentials of Taoism</name><id>16061919</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297015200000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/16061919/</event_url></item>