<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;A Christmas Tale&lt;/b&gt; France 2008 150 minutes Starring Catherine Deneuve and directed by Arnaud Desplechin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screens at 1:15 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Desplechin's &lt;b&gt;Kings and Queen&lt;/b&gt; was one of my favorite movies of 2004 and I've been eagerly awaiting  his next film. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A &lt;b&gt;Christmas Tale&lt;/b&gt; To save the life of their young son Joseph, Junon (Catherine Deneuve) and Abel (Jean-Paul Roussillon) conceived a third child. But little Henri was unable to help his brother, and Joseph died at the age of seven. The Vuillard family has never recovered. Many years have passed, and family relationships are more strained than ever. In particular, those between Henri (Mathieu Amalric), a cynical dropout who divides his time between women and drink, and his sister Elizabeth (Anne Consigny), authoritarian head of the family. After a violent argument, Elizabeth banishes her feckless brother, cutting him off from his nephew-a tortured adolescent beset by serious mental problems. Masterfully directed and acted, by turns savage, bittersweet, darkly comic and unbearably moving, &lt;b&gt;A Christmas Tale&lt;/b&gt; shows internationally acclaimed filmmaker Arnaud Desplechin (Kings &amp;amp; Queen, La Sentinelle) at the height of his powers. Kendall description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Christmas Tale score a 100% rating on Rotten Tomatoes. Read more here: &lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/10009929-a_christmas_tale/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rottentoma...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Christmas Tale&lt;/b&gt; succeeds both as an examination of peculiar family dynamics and a showcase for its cast.  The film tries to say so much, with so many characters, that it’s amazing that as much of it works as well as it does. Admittedly, in its second half, there are passages where the film seems both a tad too all-reaching in its scope and a bit too perfectly incisive in its characters’ dissections of their own relationships, but that moment of doubt passes quickly. The overall impression is of a movie that’s generous to a fault. Yes, it’s perhaps too blunt in its delivery, too acutely aware of its own messiness, and too visually flamboyant to feel like a truly great movie, but it’s not far off from being one. It details the complicated, conflicted personalities of a group of individuals with a frankness and callousness rarely seen. Perhaps the most touching, shocking, wrong, and right scene in &lt;b&gt;A Christmas Tale&lt;/b&gt; involves the family gathering together to calculate their mother’s lifespan on a blackboard. It’s a gesture that’s at once loving and appalling. It sums up the film perfectly. MovieMartyr.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film look for Tom with a Meetup sign near the front row</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226365687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>From France: A Christmas Tale </name><id>9135780</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228587300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9135780/</event_url></item>