<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197-203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.743869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 246-5700</phone><name>The Alchemy Juice Bar &amp; Growing Green Co-op</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1035078</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689453</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If there is anything that you ever wanted to know about Tantra, Hindu Cosmology, the merging of Shiva and Shakti, the Chakra System, the Cobra Breath, Kundalini Awakening, Shaktipat, Mantra and other magical things, this is your night! We are very lucky to welcome two stars of Tantra: Dhana Thane and Luba Evans. Dhana Thane is the holder of The Siddhanatha Sampradaya, Shaktipat Lineage descended from the Ancients of India, namely Rshi Dattatreya, the Nine Nathas and Lord Shiva. In recent times the lineage was transmitted to us by Avadhuta Nityananda of Ganeshpuri. The primary objective of this living tradition of truth is the awakening of Kundalini in others through Shaktipat. For the first time Dhana has come to the USA to transmit the teaching and conduct Maha Kundalini Ascension Rituals. Kundalini Awakening is the activation of the dormant spiritual energy residing in the human nervous system. Kundalini Awakening brings forth heightened awareness, increased energy levels, spontaneous and deep meditation and purification of the mental and physical bodies, recognition of your own true essence as an inseparable source of the Greater Universe, in a timeless, spaceless non-identified awareness, referred to as enlightenment in the Vedic Scriptures. It is an innate pre-existent condition available to all. Luba Evans (Saraswati):: Saraswati is a tantra teacher dedicated to the evolution of consciousness since the beginning of times. She is the founder of New York Tantric Meet Up, Boston Tantric Meet Up, Galiana Meditation Retreat and the international movement Tantra Without Borders &amp;#150; entities that reflect her vision of personal growth, healing and spiritual realization. She is an author of a book &amp;quot;Healing the Broken Heart&amp;quot; and a play &amp;quot;When the Gods are Laughing&amp;quot;. Saraswati is an artist, a weaver, a yogini, an authentic tantrika, an exquisitely powerful woman that radiates her creative shakti throughout the world. Saraswati runs regular classes in New York and New England, as well as intensives and residential retreats for open and ongoing groups at Galiana. She also teaches in Europe and India, serving a global community of students. www.galianaretreat.com Dhana Thane and Luba Evans will share how tantric principles can be used in our daily life, lead us in meditation and answer your questions, for example how to develop personal tantric sadhana, how to recognize impurities that we are accumulating, how to cultivate feminine and masculine energy, how to accept yourself through understanding for cosmic aspects of your personal energies. Don't miss this for the world! -- gate gate paragate parasamgate bodhi svaha&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311130706000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310137924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The True Meaning of Tantra - Free Introductory Talk</name><id>25023281</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310684400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/25023281/</event_url></item>