<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>381 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.394272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rosebud Bar and Grill</name><city>Somerville</city><id>7530592</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/2/4/event_183535332.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Massmouth presents an evening of long form storytelling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 tellers with a twenty minute set each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Anderson &lt;br /&gt;

 Diana Valentine &lt;br /&gt;

 and out-of-town favorite Michele Carlo from NYC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rosebud Bar and Grill &lt;br /&gt;

 381 Summer Street  &lt;br /&gt;

 Somerville, MA 02144 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.rosebudbarandgrill.com/"&gt;www.rosebudbarandgrill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission: $10 in advance / $12 at the door &lt;br /&gt;

BUY TICKETS HERE: &lt;a href="http://1stpersonplural.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://1stpersonplural.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIANA VALENTINE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diana hails from Long Island by way of Philadelphia.  When she is not working in the youth nonprofit sector you can find Diana running storytelling events in Somerville for MASSMOUTH and attending StorySpace in Cambridge.   Her storied background is rooted deep in her personal narratives of family and ghosts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MICHAEL ANDERSON&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By day, he's a union lawyer specializing in First Amendment defense. Michael Anderson delivers funny, intense political monologues. After he takes off his tie, he talks to audiences in ways they don't allow in federal court. Every piece is an insurrection, an anarchist pep rally. &lt;br /&gt;

 He has performed in venues from San Francisco to Boston. He starred in Free-Style Shakespeare at Jimmy Tingle's Off-Broadway Theater. He thinks: there's no such thing as free speech if you don't use it. &lt;br /&gt;

 "Put George Orwell essays, Roadrunner cartoons and the first two Clash albums into a blender, and you've got Michael Anderson."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MICHELE CARLO&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michele Carlo is the author of Fish Out Of Agua: My life on neither side of the (subway) tracks (Citadel 2010). Her writing also appears in Mr. Beller’s Lost &amp;amp; Found: Stories From New York, SMITH magazine's Next Door Neighbor and the blog F***ed In Park Slope, among others. As a storyteller, Michele has performed almost everywhere a person can tell stories, including the MOTH’s GrandSlams and Mainstage, and is thrilled to be invited back to Boston. Fish Out Of Agua, the solo show adapted from her memoir, will debut in Spring 2013. For more info: www.michelecarlo.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355193745000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>storytellers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>storytelling-28</urlname><id>1247871</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Greater Boston and MA Storytelling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354129936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st Person Plural</name><id>93205602</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355184000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/storytelling-28/events/93205602/</event_url></item>