<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Main Street </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>42.983831</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-866-574-2955</phone><name>Ann's Conference Bridge</name><city>Manchester</city><id>220034</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.473939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The membership has voted.  For this months brewclub of the month we are going to Milly's Tavern.  Afterward we will go over to Strangebrew.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Milly's Tavern:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Milly's Tavern first opened its doors in January of 2002 at the location of the former Stark Mill Brewery. Milly's opened through the hard work and love of the craft of Master Brewer Peter Telge, a New Hampshire native, who has been brewing his own beers for the better part of 20 years. With the closing of the Stark Mill Brewery and the many changes that have befell the city in the recent years, Peter felt that Manchester, as New Hampshire's Queen City, was sadly falling the way of commercial and contract beers. He, with a dedicated following of fans of his brew, set to work reopening the brewery as &amp;quot;Milly's Tavern,&amp;quot; proudly operating as Manchester's only brew pub. We welcome you as our guests to stop by and try a glass of Peter's hard work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brews:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.millystavern.com/manchester_brewery.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.millystave...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.millystavern.com/dining_menu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.millystave...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Night Club:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is always something happening in our lounge. Whether its from 4-7 pm, or all night, you are bound to have a good time. We offer live music every Tuesday, Thursday, Friday and Saturday. Local DJ spins the top hits the rest of the week. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North&lt;br /&gt;Take 93 South to 293 South, Manchester Exit 6 Amoskeag bridge. Right off exit and second right to bridge, Amoskeag bridge, right onto Canal St. Exit Right at lights to Commercial St. 1/2 mile on the right 500 Commercial St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South&lt;br /&gt;Take 93 North to 293 North, Manchester Bedford. Exit 5 Granite St. Bridge. Right at lights then cross bridge. Left at the first set of lights onto Commercial St. 1/2 mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West&lt;br /&gt;Take 101 East to 293 North, Manchester to exit 5 Granite St. Bridge. Right at lights then cross bridge. Left at the first set of lights onto Commercial St. 1/2 mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From East&lt;br /&gt;Take 101 West to 293 North, Manchester to exit 5 Granite St. Bridge.Right at lights then cross bridge. Left at the first set of lights onto Commercial St. 1/2 mile on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Strange Brew:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We here at Strange Brew recognize that life is short and there are so many things to do and learn, but so very little time.  But there is always time for a good beer.  So why not make that beer the best one possible? &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We encourage you to be bold and daring. Please try something new from our extensive draught list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Address:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;88 Market St.   &lt;br /&gt;Manchester, NH&lt;br /&gt;03101&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220324370000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218296064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brews &amp; Blues Event: Milly's Tavern/Strangbrew</name><id>8509401</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220137200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8509401/</event_url></item>