<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be meeting in the skiers parking lot (lower lot -&lt;b&gt; lot #4&lt;/b&gt;)  of Ragged Mountain and taking an approximately 5 mile trail from the base to the summit of the mountain.  The elevation gain is about 1,200 feet.  This trail does not have a name (or at least not one that I'm aware of), but it is marked.  The trail goes up starting on the northern side of the mountain and follows the trial to the pinnacle peak, the third peak in the Ragged Mountain Range.  We will then follow the ridge to the ski area summit. My husband grew up in Danbury and frequented Ragged Mountain often.  He will be helping me co-lead this hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our goal is to reach the summit around 4, just in time for the skiers to have skied their last run and for us to sled down the ski trails.  So you will need a sled that you can pack up and slide down on.  You can get sleds at EMS.  Zipfy or Slidy sleds work well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am calculating that it will take us about 4 hours to hike and 20 - 30 minutes to descend (on our butts).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is winter - there is snow and ice. Snow shoes are required for this hike - so is some form of traction for your boots (crampons are preferred, microspikes are acceptable). You will also need a headlamp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in participating in this event be sure to answer all of the required questions during the RSVP process. Unless you are someone that I hike with regularly please take the time to answer them with as much information as possible - even if you have answered them before.&lt;br /&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire trip please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Footwear: Hiking boots or trail shoes. Snowshoes and some form of traction (e.g. crampons or microspikes) is mandatory.&lt;br /&gt;    * Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.&lt;br /&gt;    * Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket with hood.&lt;br /&gt;    * Food and Water: High-energy snacks, we will not be eating lunch on the mountain,  enough water to stay hydrated during the trip. Hydration bladders may freeze during winter - bottles with insulating sleeves work best.&lt;br /&gt;    * Other Essential Gear:  Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in cold temperatures). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool.  Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;br /&gt;    * Optional Items: Waterproof/windproof pants. Waterproof gaiters. Trekking poles. Camera. Goggles while sledding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not certified or trained in wilderness first aid. You will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged - indicate in your RSVP if you need a ride or can give one. You are responsible for making your own arrangements so you should check back often and contact others who might want/need to carpool. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: my two dogs will be joining us.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one with the two golden labs.  Moose and Tuckerman.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristen Curren</member_name><member_id>7131394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295839578000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294004096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ragged Mountain Hiking and Sledding</name><id>15887422</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295717400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15887422/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/a/global_20506746.jpeg</photo_url></item>