<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>July 23, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To all of our terrific, talented members  -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time for a vacation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Paris, once the world's center of graphic design,&lt;br /&gt;it is -- as I think they say  --  comme il faut&lt;br /&gt;to take the month of August off as vacation time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That diversion is, I confess, mere pretext:&lt;br /&gt;your interim temporary organizer has gotten&lt;br /&gt;himself so completely over-committed with&lt;br /&gt;and enmeshed in various vast and overwhelming&lt;br /&gt;projects that he can think of nothing else&lt;br /&gt;at the moment but digging himself out from &lt;br /&gt;under various massive tasks under which he&lt;br /&gt;has recently buried himself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But you are all splendidly talented, articulate,&lt;br /&gt;engaging designers  --  so, as one of the old&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night Live characters used to say:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Talk among yourselves!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your interim temporary organizer hopes&lt;br /&gt;to have unburied himself (at least to a degree)&lt;br /&gt;by Labor Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet again on Monday, September 15th, at 7:30 pm,&lt;br /&gt;at the Trident.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep up your terrific and valiant work  --&lt;br /&gt;and have a great summer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lee &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking can be difficult but not impossible to find on Newbury Street. &lt;br /&gt;If you are coming in from outside the city, &lt;br /&gt;I recommend parking a bit farther out and taking &lt;br /&gt;the Green Line B, C, or D routes to the Hynes Convention &lt;br /&gt;Center stop, that's just half a block from the Trident. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.tridentbookscafe.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tridentbookscafe.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tridentboo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But we may well change over to a location that offers far better immediate parking opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;Davis Square in Somerville is a real possibility.  The Diesel Cafe there has a large back room&lt;br /&gt;that we might be able to use.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be located at the front dining area of the Trident, with a small "Graphic</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lee</member_name><member_id>1084681</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248656000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Pixel pushing in isolation can be tough!  Learn something, share experiences</why><group><who>Graphic Designers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>graphicdesign-39</urlname><id>71144</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Graphic Design Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216082434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Graphic Design September Meetup</name><id>8341783</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221521400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/graphicdesign-39/events/8341783/</event_url></item>