<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187114</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>Richard Tosti Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>826225</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236877</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person at door</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Values: &lt;br /&gt;1. We believe that a long-term, fulfilling relationship is built on some fundamental values: Integrity, Honesty, Respect, Loyalty, Reliability, and Non-judgment in our communication with each other. We value each other’s opinion. We listen!&lt;br /&gt;2. We strive to be positive, optimistic, kind, giving professionals. How? We don’t criticize, condemn or complain. We are here to feel good and have a good time.&lt;br /&gt;3. We value diversity in religions, nationalities, and ethnic backgrounds. We cooperate as a team to be successful by inviting other professional people we know. &lt;br /&gt;4. We demonstrate this respectful/ nonjudgmental mindset in two ways: &lt;br /&gt;A. By saying Yes to someone who asks us to dance. (once) &lt;br /&gt;B. By offering positive solutions or alternatives if you disagree with something. (Please don’t criticize, condemn or complain) We welcome suggestions to improve the experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Format: &lt;br /&gt;Location is in a safe, warm, loving and relaxing environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special request to guarantee our success: Dec. 31st.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Women please bring the following food selection: First letter of last name:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-C healthy appetizer- serving for 6-8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;D-R- An entrée- serving for 6-8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;S-Z dessert serving for 6-8&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Men please bring a bottle of wine/soda/water/beer-first letter of last name&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A-C- one bottle of soda and one gallon of water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;D-R- bottle of quality wine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;S-Z- beer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feb. 14th we will reverse the selections- ask women to bring wine and men will bring food and flowers for women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synergy in action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your rushed and bring nothing- fee is $30.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DJ - Dancing will be available -  wear leather soles rather than rubber soles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host- Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &amp;quot;Time of party: 8:30PM -1:00AM&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;quot; Dress code- Formal- Black tie/suit &amp;amp; tie/sport jacket/  &lt;br /&gt;no jeans/sneakers &lt;br /&gt;3. &amp;quot;You can enjoy the music and dance if you like&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purpose is to Socialize with similar people of our age who are searching for a lifetime partner. &lt;br /&gt;40-65 age group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I began these parties in my home in July 2006-twice a month &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Common denominator &lt;br /&gt;Have fun meeting old and new friends &lt;br /&gt;Circulate, talk to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;If someone is alone go up to them and say hi! &lt;br /&gt;Nonsmokers &lt;br /&gt;Please be Friendly, Positive, and optimistic to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please invite other friends, Particularly men. Our personal goal is to always have an equal amount of men and women. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last dance we did have a 50-50 ratio of men and women. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy. Working together to invite quality people. We must take responsibility for inviting people. Again, our personal goal is to have an equal ratio of men and women, hope you will help. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can sign up on &lt;a href="http://dance.meetup.c.." target="_blank"&gt;http://dance.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;You do not need to email me personally. &lt;br /&gt;160 guests only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know the time, the location, what you should bring. Let's have fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions &lt;br /&gt;Temple Shalom Emeth &lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street &lt;br /&gt;Burlington,MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;128 North &lt;br /&gt;Exit 32 B Middlesex Tpk (Burlington/Arlington) &lt;br /&gt;Fork right-Middlesex Tpk Burlington-on the left is Barnes/Noble &lt;br /&gt;Turn Right on to Burlington Mall Rd-on left is Longs Jewelers &lt;br /&gt;Take second light left- after Kohls-Lexington Street (1.4 miles on left)&lt;br /&gt;16 Lexington Street, Burlington MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two Parking lots on the right side of building. Enter through the side entrance . &lt;br /&gt;3rd parking lot two houses up at Church-we have permission &lt;br /&gt;4th parking lot across the street-McGinnis Ave-Mt Hope Church&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on Dec. 31st, Wed.-8:30pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1339201545000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>152</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223056031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Private New Years Eve Singles, Dinner Dance Party 40-65</name><id>8889424</id><headcount>148</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1230773400000</time><rsvp_limit>178</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/8889424/</event_url></item>