<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Park Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02462</zip><lat>42.329384</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Weston Ski Track</name><city>Weston</city><id>1485473</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.271141</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;SOOOOOOOO, this is NOT the awesome snow year it was supposed to be&lt;/span&gt; ................................................&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you all may have noticed, we didn't get the dumping we were supposed to last night.  Great Brook isn't open at all.  I just called WindBlown and they have very limited XC around the pond.  Since that is a long drive for me, I'd prefer not to drive for a few hours for bad conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Weston ski track got a few inches Friday night, has made snow AND IS OPEN!!!&lt;/span&gt; They have XC in a loop in the man made area, and offer snowshoeing as well.  I've only been there when they've had natural snow, so I'm not sure how big the man made area is. They have  a race from 8-10:30, so I'm keeping the time for this at 10:30, but I may get there a bit earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weston has rentals for XC  skis and snowshoes, and if you sign up ahead of time, they have lessons that you can look into, if you like. I'm starting out on XC skis, but may switch it up to snowshoes later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have a cafeteria in the main building that has snacks and drinks, but I don't think actual meals.  Please check out their website for details.  &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;I've only been there once a few years ago, so I'm kind of fuzzy on any other specifics. Please check out their website for more details, including rates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.skiboston.com/skitrack/skitrack.php"&gt;http://www.skiboston.com/skitrack/skitrack.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets plan on meeting outside near the lessons area at 10:30.  I'll have a plum colored coat with black ski pants.  And you can look for Roger with his red goatee (kind of hard to miss!) to meet up. It's always hard to identify people when they are bundled up in the winter....lol!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please update your RSVP and comment Weston, or something like that so I know your yes RSVP is accurate for Weston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see many of you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maryanne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the beginner area. See below, I'll have a plum coat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maryanne</member_name><member_id>9546163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359322592000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357268039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cross Country Skiing or Snowshoeing LOCATION CHANGE--- adults and kids</name><id>97809262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359300600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/97809262/</event_url></item>