<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;It's All About the Money...&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Are you investing in real estate because a view of a &lt;b&gt;Boston skyscraper makes your heart soar&lt;/b&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or, do rolling hills and majestic mountains make you break into a pathetic rendition of “&lt;b&gt;The Hills are Alive with the Sound of Music&lt;/b&gt;??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's get serious folks....&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I&lt;b&gt;t's All About the Money....&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don’t make money at it, it’s a hobby (and an expensive one!) so come learn from two local area experts: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How do you determine the ARV&lt;/b&gt; of a property even in a declining market?  (After Repaired Value) &lt;br /&gt;This is where you start – at the end – what’s it going to be worth when you are done?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How do you determine how much you can afford to pay for a property?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;            Working backwards, and including the ‘gotcha’s’ of a project &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What if you are planning to wholesale it?&lt;/b&gt;  Then how much do you build in for a fee?  &lt;br /&gt;What are the 4 ways you make money from properties? &lt;br /&gt;            Time is your best friend – sometimes! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is the 5th secret weapon?&lt;/b&gt;  And why it is a double-edged sword!  &lt;br /&gt;Kevin Lacasse will show how he maps out comparable sales to determine his ARV, and then how he calculates his costs to work backwards into what he can afford to pay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann Bellamy will review an analysis of multi-family and commercial income properties, and how you make money 4 ways – no, make that 5 ways!  How to value income property and calculate your expenses.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an interactive give-and-take session.  If you have input, come and enlighten us.  If you have questions, speak up, because 10 more people in the room have the same question!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;5:30 - Power Hour - Members only - Investing out of state with Al Piecuch &lt;br /&gt;6:00 - Orientation - Members and Visitors - get more out of your visit and your membership &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;NOTE LOCATION CHANGE! &lt;br /&gt;Free to members, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236723605000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>101</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232062882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association February Meetup</name><id>9533124</id><headcount>101</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235082600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/9533124/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>