<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come to the Senior Center Lounge for our next meeting on Tuesday, August 14 from 7-9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you all are having a decent summer. Arizona has been surprisingly cool for this time of year and I'm getting my pool exercise 5 days a week. Feels good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of "treatments" I've come across I will pass out info on and as usual come with your best treatments and info on what works for you. If you are in a bad place come and talk about that. Our group is so knowledgable you will get some good suggestions on your next step to take in your healing journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am now working with a non-profit organization in AZ helping people with Fibro get affordable health care. I am offering my services at a reduced rate with clients that come through the agency. I've decided to do the same with my Fibromyalgia clients on disability or those with reduced incomes in Reading as well. Call me if you are interested in learning more about trigger point treatment and exercise programs or Fibromyalgia Recovery Programs developed just for you at a discount. Call me at 623-251-7547.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you in August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betsy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS. As always donations are greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345122479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342991775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Time to meet</name><id>74447532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344985200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/74447532/</event_url></item>