<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.241020</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.571820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's a holiday from work for some of us, so I hope a few of you will be able to join me.  We'll paddle for 2-3 hours crossing open water to the big island and then through coves and boggy areas. The weather is forecast to be partly cloudy and on the cool side, not getting above 60 F, so dress in layers to keep warm.  If you don't have time to eat lunch before you arrive we can take a snack/lunch break along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking and launch is on Route 135 between Hopkinton and Westborough centers, approx 42.24166 North and -71.57316 West.  Do not program "Whitehall State Park" into your GPS. That will not take you to the launch site.  The nearest side road is Dale Road in Hopkinton, just west of the parking lot entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must have a whistle and wear a properly fastened PFD.  Although not required by law, it is a good idea to have a pump and paddle float with you.  If you haven't already, it is a good idea to learn how to use your paddle float to do a self-rescue should you go over. You would not want to find yourself in the water any longer than necessary - or worse - not being able to get back into your kayak &lt;span&gt;(especially as the water starts to cool off this time of year).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349738803000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349380375000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle at Whitehall</name><id>85525782</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349708400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/85525782/</event_url></item>