<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1735 Centre St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02132</zip><lat>42.287255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 325 3500</phone><name>Himalayan Bistro </name><city>West Roxbury</city><id>880058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.149756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lunch location: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=475%20Moody%20St%2C%20Waltham%2C%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;Himalayan&lt;/a&gt; Bistro, 1735 Centre St, West Roxbury&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximate cost: $18 (includes lunch, tax, tip, and $1 to support the meetup). May be a little less depending on location. Additional cost for anything you add from the menu (breads, beverages, chai).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GOODREADS - &lt;span&gt;Moving between two worlds and two families, one struggling to survive in the fetid slums of Mumbai, the other grappling to forge a cohesive family despite their diverging cultural identities, this powerful debut novel marks the arrival of a fresh talent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AMAZON -&lt;/span&gt; Somer’s life is everything she imagined it would be—she’s newly married and has started her career as a physician in San Francisco—until she makes the devastating discovery she never will be able to have children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The same year in India, a poor mother makes the heartbreaking choice to save her newborn daughter’s life by giving her away. It is a decision that will haunt Kavita for the rest of her life, and cause a ripple effect that travels across the world and back again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asha, adopted out of a Mumbai orphanage, is the child that binds the destinies of these two women. We follow both families, invisibly connected until Asha’s journey of self-discovery leads her back to India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compulsively readable and deeply touching, &lt;em&gt;Secret Daughter&lt;/em&gt; is a story of the unforeseen ways in which our choices and families affect our lives, and the indelible power of love in all its many forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;--&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Book on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>6571667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345316962000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333327255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>aUGUST 2012 - Secret Daughter by Shilpi Somaya Gowda</name><id>58833812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345305600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/58833812/</event_url></item>