<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ben and Jerry's Ice Cream</name><city>Salem</city><id>1373426</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.896100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Salem, MA is the place to be for Halloween so let’s go check out all the haunted happening going on this year!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;10.29.10 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; Here is the link for the train schedule to get into Salem  &lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/documents/Haunted_Happenings_2010_mbta.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt; .  For those of us leaving from the train station in Newburyport, let's meet at &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;4:00pm&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; at the Newburyport Turnpike parking lot that is off of the rotary on Route 1 Newburyport Turnpike, we can get there early, admire each other in our costumes then get on the train and get to Ben &amp;amp; Jerry's to meetup with the rest of the members at 5:30.  IF you are planning on taking the train out of Newburyport, please take a minute and update your RSVP so we know to be looking for you.  If you will be meeting us at Ben &amp;amp; Jerry's or running late and not able to find us, take the Meetup phone # with you so you can find us 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At all of our meetups we normally wait up to 15 minutes for everyone to get to the destination before we head out to the event, seeing that the trains may not be running on time, the place will be crazy we will probably wait a little longer.  But help out the organizers and give us a call if you are running late, lost or change your RSVP on the site if you are not able to make it.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;10.27.10 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Taken right from the Haunted Happenings website!  Authorities urge people planning to celebrate Halloween weekend in Salem, Massachusetts, to leave the cars at home, take advantage of public transportation, and bring their common sense.  Increased visitation during the first four weeks of October and a good forecast for Halloween weekend are expected to result in record numbers of people visiting Salem on Halloween. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking will be at a premium throughout downtown Salem this weekend, with public and private lots charging an average of $20 cash per car per day.  Visitors are encouraged to take the MBTA Commuter Rail or Salem Ferry to Salem from Boston and points north, avoiding the search for parking and the traffic backlogs that occur once garages and lots are full.  MBTA stations at Beverly and Lynn have ample parking, and are less than a 10 minute ride from the Salem Depot.  Salem’s walkable downtown makes personal vehicles unnecessary once visitors have arrived. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check back and I know what time we will be meeting to get the train out of Newburyport or check out the schedule here &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;9.30.10 UPDATE: I will update the time that we will meet at the train station as the date gets closer they may be running special times.  Please check back for an update.  I will update it as soon as I know it.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nobody celebrates Halloween quite like Salem. Whether you are seeking the changing leaves and cooler weather New England Autumn brings or the ghosts and goblins that Halloween is known for, you will find it all in Salem this October. They have a months worth of events happening but let’s go on Halloween to get the best effect.  If you would like to come in costume feel free, there will be a lot of other costumes so you will blend right in, last year we saw a lot of crazy, interesting and fun costumes.  For more information for all the events that will be going on this day check out the information on this site, &lt;a href="http://www.hauntedhappenings.org/images/2010/2010HHBrochure.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hauntedhap...&lt;/a&gt; and you can even print out a map on the last page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is A LOT going on in Salem, the city will be buzzing w/lots of tours, people and attractions, let’s meetup at 5:30 in time for us to get into town, walk around people watch and check everything out.  There will be a lot of people in Salem if crowds are not your thing then this event may not be for you, we call all hang out as a group or if you want to prowl around yourself you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There is some on street parking, parking lots and parking garages scattered around the town. If you want to drive in be aware that they may shutdown the roads early as they did last year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Taking the Train:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seeing that parking or road closings may be an issue I suggest taking the train into Salem. I will be leaving from Newburyport on the 4:35pm train and will get into Salem approx 5:05ish (if the train runs on time).  Here is the link to the website that will give you the train schedule: &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt;. If you decide to take the Newburyport train in, you can park in any of the lots around the train and we will meet in the parking lot that is off of the rotary on Route 1 Newburyport Turnpike. If you do plan on meeting me there please put that in your RSVP so we know to be looking for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When in Salem where to Meetup:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting in front of Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s on the corner of Washington and Lynde St. (on the Haunted Happenings map #28) which is close from the train station after you come up the stairs and cross the street if you are running late or get lost call the meetup phone @ 978-304-2811.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note we will only wait 15 minutes at the meeting location before we head out to explore the town if you are running late and won’t be there on time, please call the meetup phone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this howling event.&lt;br /&gt;Donna &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/devilish.gif' border='0' alt='devilish' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be out front</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288661104000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284331447000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween in Salem, MA</name><id>14745803</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288560600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/14745803/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/c/global_10673804.jpeg</photo_url></item>