<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 North Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.363266</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 720 3994</phone><name>Ricardo's Ristorante</name><city>Boston</city><id>383728</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053870</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>David Goldstein, who runs the Taste of Chocolate walking tour &lt;a href="http://tasteofchocolate.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tasteofchocola...&lt;/a&gt; group extends a special offer to the Nerd Fun Meetup group. Tickets for this comical whodunnit  type of dinner theater are only $35.00 with the discount code &amp;quot;NERDFUN&amp;quot;. They have 50 spaces left out of 80 total for that night as of 4/5/2010. He'll make sure we sit near each other as a group. The performance is at 7:30 pm. We have permission to arrive early and mingle over cocktails at 7:00 pm. From the few video clips I have seen scattered on the web, the show seems quite funny! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;b&gt;The Mobfather&lt;/b&gt; (&amp;quot;The Show You Can't Refuse!&amp;quot;), a Mystery Cafe presentation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When&lt;/b&gt;: Friday, April 23, 2010 @ 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7:30 pm - 10:00 pm (Cocktails at 7:00 pm, if you wish)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; Riccardo's Ristorante, Boston&lt;br /&gt;                      175 North Street, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;: $35.00 (Usually $49.95)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Mystery Cafe site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/87/riccardos-ristorante" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;You are invited to the Scarplace mansion to attend a surprise 40th birthday party for the Mobfather leader of Boston Mafia. But it is the guests who are surprised when gunshots are fired and the doors are blocked and there’s no way out until the family honor has been restored and the killer captured.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enjoy an interactive murder Mystery up close and personal with your favorite Hollywood mobsters including Marlin Brand 'O'. Figure out who did it while enjoying a delicious Italian family style meal and great live music in the historic North End of Boston. Our talented CharActors add comedy and intrigue and personalized anecdotes to make this a night to remember&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Purchase tickets:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;By Phone&lt;/u&gt;: &amp;quot;Call the box office at 781-784-7469 Ext 202 and mention you are with 'The Nerd Fun Meetup'&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Online&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Go to &lt;a href="http://secure.mysterycafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://secure.mystery...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Enter your billing information and the number of tickets you want;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Enter the Group Name of ‘Nerd Fun’ so we can seat you all together;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Proceed to checkout;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;In the Promotional Code box, enter NERDFUN and click Check Code – it will apply your special group discount to all of the tickets in your reservation, making them only $35 per ticket;&lt;br /&gt;* &amp;quot;Enter your payment information and complete the reservation!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;After You Purchase Your Ticket:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please update your RSVP that you purchased your ticket on the Meetup.com page, so T.J. Maher knows (without bugging David) how many people have purchased a ticket and are definitely going. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Mystery Cafe&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;i&gt;according to David Goldstein on his website&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/about" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;My name is David Goldstein and I founded the Mystery Café in the fall of 1986. It was one of many ideas that I had for my first business, as everyday I would have a new business concept that I would run by my friends [...] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[T]hat was the start of the Mystery Café. We broke 300 mirrors (only 2,100 years bad luck) in the basement of the Cantab Lounge in Cambridge as we renovated the original location of Mystery Café into an 80 seat dinner theater. With the help of writer Phil Lebovits and a script entitled 'Death &amp;amp; Taxes' (later renamed 'Murder on the Campaign Trail'), we opened our doors on April 15, 1987 to a full house. That continued five nights a week, and a dinner theater was born.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It didn’t stop there: a second Cambridge location soon opened and we knew we were on to something good. During the next 7 years we licensed our concept, the logo and the scripts to producers in 21 cities in the U.S. and Canada. Now, in 2009, the Mystery Café is still running strong and you can find mystery dinner theaters located all over the world, in most major cities and in many smaller ones. Look what we started! [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If you haven’t been to the Mystery Café come and check it out. It is a great combination of mystery, music, food, fun, and audience participation. If you’ve been before, come on back! We change the shows regularly and always try new things to make your experience memorable and unique&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/87/riccardos-ristorante" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Appetizer&lt;/u&gt;: Mixed Garden Greens Salad&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Entree&lt;/u&gt;: Choice of Eggplant Rollitini, Chicken Parmagiana, or Homemade Pasta&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dessert&lt;/u&gt;: The Big Cannoli&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Entrees are served family style, so you can help yourself to one of the three choices. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Riccardo's Ristorante&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/ricardos-ristorante-boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Yelp Riccardo's Ristorante has great tasting food, good assortments of wine, an elegant ambiance, but the foodies rate it as only average, especially because it is surrounded by great restaurants in the North End. Er, and they give the service a lot of one star ratings. Eh, we will be served by CharActors I believe, so it won't make that much difference. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Video&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* A short movie of them greeting people is at &lt;a href="http://www.mysterycafe.com/87/riccardos-ristorante" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mysterycaf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* During one performance, they have the audience get up and dance: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DIwaLuL0vLI" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You might want to take the T to this one... I did find on the web a North End Parking Map at &lt;a href="http://www.northendboston.com/parking-garages.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northendbo...&lt;/a&gt;  ... feel free to talk about Parking options in the &amp;quot;Talk about this Meetup&amp;quot; page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Validated parking at Parcels Seven parking garage is available, located on Congress Street by Fanueil Hall. If you are using public transportation, you can ride the Green, Blue or Orange MBTA Lines to nearby Haymarket or Government Center&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parcel Seven Garage is at 136 Blackstone Street, in Boston. According to Google Maps it is a 4 minute walk from Hanover, a right on Cross Street, and a left on North Street. &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=136+Blackstone+St,+Boston,+MA+02108&amp;amp;daddr=175+North+Street,+Boston,+ma&amp;amp;geocode=FfRkhgIdpL_D-ymlRpJmj3DjiTF2R-ikdcqN6A%3BFV5phgIddM3D-ylXf0fhiHDjiTFCKcpGoiCupg&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.362619,-71.055338&amp;amp;sspn=0.002858,0.003465&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.362377,-71.055847&amp;amp;spn=0.00289,0.004812&amp;amp;z=18" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Validated Parking Rates at Parcel Seven Garage:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;According to Shannon Lane Stillings, Creative Director&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;You would pick up your validation ticket at Ricardo’s, and below is what parking at Parcels 7 will cost with that validation:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;1-2 Hours: $1 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;2-3 Hours: $3&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;3-4 Hours: $28&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;4+ Hours: $33&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Just so you know, the show starts at 7:30pm and ends around 10:00pm, so it is possible to fit this all into a 3 hour period which will allow you to get the really good parking rate&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... If this is true, you might want to show up just for dinner at 7:30 pm so you can make sure to get back to your car in time to get the reduced rate, since you only have just under three hours of cheap parking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272412713000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270486247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Mobfather ("The Show You Can't Refuse!") @ Riccardo's Ristorante, Boston</name><id>13091865</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272063600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13091865/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/5/global_14168693.jpeg</photo_url></item>