<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Gennaro's Eatery, an establishment in South Quincy since the Organizers can remember, expanded their tiny eatery in 2006 to more than double their dining room.  This is a quaint and cozy restaurant. Portions are generous, the food is delicious, and there's so much to try you don't know where to begin!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us at 6:45pm on Tuesday, March 4th as we travel to Route 53 in south Quincy to sample the fare of a quaint Italian restaurant that some might describe as a hidden jewel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN and WHERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, March 4th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Gennaro's Eatery&lt;br /&gt;12 Blanchard Road&lt;br /&gt;(Intersection of Blanchard and Quincy Avenue)&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;br /&gt;617-773-1500&lt;br /&gt;6:45pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRICE RANGE: Appetizers start around $4.  Entrees range from $8-$18.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HANDICAPPED ACCESS: Yes         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ORGANIZERS: Angela and Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVENT FEE:  Group Members and Guests: $2pp; Annual Members: FREE (as they are pre-paid); Organizers are FREE.  (If you would like to become an Annual Member please email Angela to make arrangements.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP DEADLINE: Tuesday, March 4th @ NOON&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIN/MAX:  Since this is a small restaurant we are going to set the limit at 14 people.  Min is generally 4 people but we are usually good at having at least 6 people so no worries.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GUESTS: Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  This restaurant does not take reservations.  &lt;i&gt;When it comes to large parties all members must be present in order to be seated.&lt;/i&gt;  We will most likely have to wait between 10-15 minutes (maybe slightly more or less).  &lt;i&gt;If you are going to be more than 15 minutes late please call the restaurant or Angela's cell, which will be emailed to Yes RSVPs shortly before or after the Deadline.&lt;/i&gt;  If members of our party are missing we may have to be seated without the missing members.  Our Deadline is just over 6 hours prior to the Event which gives everyone ample opportunity to make any last-minute changes, not to mention you will be able to call Angela to let her know if you are no longer able to attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to meeting up with you at one of Angela's favorite restaurants!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gennaro's is located on Blanchard Road at the intersection of Blanchard and Quincy Avenue. Quincy Avenue is a major thoroughfare running from Weymouth Landing through a good part of Braintree and Quincy until it ends at Quincy Center (where, in essence, it becomes Hancock Street). People with knowledge of local roads will know that there are many different ways to get to Quincy Ave., but we are posting a set of directions that we hope will be clear enough to follow and useful to those who may be coming from a distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Route 3, take Exit 17 (Union St).&lt;/b&gt; This is the Union Street Rotary. Exit the rotary by turning onto Union Street, passing the Braintree Police Station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go straight through one traffic light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next major intersection is Weymouth landing, where you will see a 7 Eleven convenience store on your left. At this point you can either bear right, heading into Weymouth Landing, or go straight, which brings you immediately to a traffic light. Go straight, then take a left at the light onto Quincy Avenue, keeping the 7 Eleven and Eastern Bank on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Quincy Avenue and go straight through the next six traffic lights. Landmarks include the old General Dynamics shipyard on your right at the fourth light (surrounded by a chain link fence) and The Falls Condominiums on your left at the fifth light. Note that at this light Route 53 bears right onto the Southern Artery - keep going straight on Quincy Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the sixth light you will see Presidents Plaza and the Kam Man Marketplace on your left. Once you have passed Presidents Plaza, be prepared to move into the left lane, because Blanchard Road is your next left at the seventh light. Gennaro's is on the near-left corner. There is a small lot to the right of the restaurant, plus some on-street parking along the road (be sure to obey any &amp;quot;No Parking&amp;quot; signs).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternatively, if you're coming &lt;b&gt;from Quincy Center&lt;/b&gt;, simply follow Hancock Street (the main road through Quincy Center) heading south (toward Braintree) until it ends at the intersection of Hancock St, School St, Elm St and Quincy Ave (just prior to hitting the intersection, you'll pass a Blockbuster Video on your left and Finian's Restaurant on your right). Go straight through the light onto Quincy Ave. Blanchard Road is your second right, across from Pilgrim Plaza and Scammel Street. See parking instructions above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For door to door directions please use mapquest.com or maps.google.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the Lobby area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204994608000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>This is a fantastic restaurant you have to try!</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203099437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tuesday Night Dinner!</name><id>7337252</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204674300000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/7337252/</event_url></item>