<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The General&lt;/b&gt; Ireland/UK 1998 124 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again The Harvard Film Archive has scheduled a retrospective of one of the worlds' top directors with the film-maker present for Q&amp;amp;A sessions. This time it John Boorman who is best known on this side of the lake for the films &lt;b&gt;Deliverance&lt;/b&gt; and (eh-hem) &lt;b&gt;Excalibur&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since John Boorman  will be present, I am suggesting that we meet in the lobby at 6:15 as tickets are on a first-come/first-served basis. This a 2 hour movie on a work-night and more than likely we will not be going to a restaurant afterward- we can play it by ear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Boorman, who won the 1998 Cannes Film Festival's Direction award for this film, previously won the same Cannes award almost three decades earlier for his Leo the Last (1969) about an alienated aristocrat in a London slum. Shot in widescreen color (but printed in sharp black-and-white), &lt;b&gt;The General&lt;/b&gt; is a biographical portrait of ruthless Irish crime lord Martin Cahill, shot down outside his home by a single assassin on August 18, 1994. After this opening, the film then unfolds as a lengthy flashback of the events that led to his death, sketching in the raw beginnings of the youthful Martin  and his link to a local cop, Inspector Ned Kenny Various thefts enable Cahill to support his wife Frances, his four children, and his sister-in-law Tina As the years pass, Cahill rises as a mobster, bamboozling cops, constructing airtight alibis, pulling off a near-impossible jewel heist, and setting up a menage a trois with Frances and Tina. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, it also appears that the subject of the film, Irish crime lord Martin Cahill, broke into John Boorman's house in real life and stole his Gold Record Award for &lt;b&gt;Deliverance&lt;/b&gt; among other valuables. Should prove to be a lively Q&amp;amp;A session. And here's a link to The New York Times review: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?res=9900E0D61438F931A35753C1A96E958260" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Tom with a Meetup sign in the lobby before the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224635950000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Boorman's The General- Director Present</name><id>9006787</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227309300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9006787/</event_url></item>