<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ciao Tutti.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the most popular card games in Italy are Briscola and Scopa. Throughout the Italian countryside you will find groups of four playing these games.  Also in Little Italy's throughout America there will be a game of Scopa or Briscola being played.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Italian cards are also unique and similar in style to Tarot cards.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fieri-boston.org/cards.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fieri-bost...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pagat.com/fishing/scopone.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pagat.com/...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pagat.com/aceten/briscola.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pagat.com/...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would you like to learn these popular Italian Card Games? I will bring three decks of Italian cards and help those who want to learn these very fun card games. A game can have four players or two players.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may also attend, if you are not interested in the Italian card games, for Ice Cream or Cappuccino or another beverage; and, socialize with other Europhiles. All attendees should purchase something from the Cafe when they arrive.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will run between 6pm and 9pm. For those interested we can go for a drink afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;There is a T stop at Harvard Square. Au Bon Pain is in Harvard Square. Parking is tricky so I usually park at Central Square and walk for 20 minutes, but you might want to search for a closer parking spot to Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell number (508) 498-1651  Please call if you cannot find us. &lt;br /&gt;If it rains we might have to change venues to an indoor location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you rsvp, please indicate whether you want to &amp;quot;play cards&amp;quot;. Again you may come just to socialize if card games do not interest you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrivederci Amici.  A presto!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be sitting inside the Cafe. If lost or late call me 508 498 1651 cell</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219097316000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217183240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cafe &amp; Italian Card Games</name><id>8421644</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218924000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8421644/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/4/global_4940804.jpeg</photo_url></item>