<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Gott Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01966</zip><lat>42.687389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 546-2997</phone><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><city>Rockport</city><id>744966</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.631871</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Halibut Point is a uniquely beautiful coastal seascape. Looking seaward on a clear day, the view stretches from Crane Beach in Ipswich to Mount Agamenticus in Maine and the Isles of Shoals off the coast of New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Formerly the Babson Farm granite quarry, the park is managed for scenic, historic and conservation purposes by the DCR and the Trustees of Reservations. An adjacent property, Sea Rocks, is owned by the Town of Rockport and open for public use. Here you can explore the park's trails and tidepools, picnic on its rocky ledges, enjoy its sweeping views, and learn about Cape Ann's historic granite industry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this walk along the seaside.  We will walk from 10 am to 1:15 pm, with time to stop for lunch (please bring lunch with you).  Those interested can join me for a very tasty treat at Helmuts Strudel Shop in Bearskin Neck/Rockport.  If you want to make a day of it, stay and enjoy the galleries, shops, and beaches. Rockport is one of my favorite places in Cape Ann.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a per car parking charge at Halibut Point State Park, so carpooling is encouraged.  I have room for three in my car, from Alewife T on the Red Line. The group will meet in the parking lot at Halibut Point State Park.  (I drive a dark blue Honda CRV.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info at &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Halibut Point State Park is located in Cape Ann in north-eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;From the South and West: Take Rte. I-95/128 north to Rte. 128 north toward Gloucester and Rockport. After crossing the Annisquam River bridge, go three quarters around the first rotary, following signs for Rt. 127 north (Annisquam and Pigeon Cove). After approximately 6 miles, turn left at the park sign and the Old Farm Inn onto Gott Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Downtown Rockport: Drive north on Rt. 127 approximately 3 miles, turning right onto Gott Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine</member_name><member_id>9203184</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279982613000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278233137000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halibut Point State Park and Apple Strudel in Rockport</name><id>13997397</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279461600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/13997397/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/3/global_16171843.jpeg</photo_url></item>