<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>building 2</address_2><address_1>1000 Markst St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.084652</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>RMC Research</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>457303</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.779510</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>See &lt;a href="http://www.nhruby.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhruby.org...&lt;/a&gt; for more info...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at RMC Research (1000 Market Street, Portsmouth, NH) on Monday, 15 February 2010 at 7pm, for the postponed from January inaugural meeting of the 2010 NHRuby season. This year at NHRuby, we’re going to try something a little different. Mixed in with our usual presentations, we’ll be covering the fundamentals of Ruby beginning with Object Oriented Programming (OOP).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Hampshire local, Brian Turnbull, will be leading a hands-on class covering the fundamentals of OOP (Encapsulation, Inheritance, and Dynamic Binding) with special emphasis on OOP in Ruby. We’ll cover the why and how of writing object oriented code in Ruby and touch on designing larger systems using OOP principles. In addition, if the stock Array type is not cutting it for you, we’ll cover creating your own types and learn what makes a complete class in Ruby. But wait! There’s more! It’s not all talk—we’ll finish the meeting with an application of what you learned though a programming exercise designed to flex those new OOP filled brain cells.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you have some programming background, but have been wondering what all this hubbub about objects is, join us. Or you want translate your OOP knowledge to Ruby, this is the meetup for you. If you are already fluent in OOP, you’re welcome and encouraged to help guide the session and assist other members… plus there will be an extra credit challenge in the form of a Ruby game during the programming exercise!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>nap</member_name><member_id>6144459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266451695000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265995785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH.rb Feb meetup</name><id>12589488</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266278400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/12589488/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>