<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join our weekly mindfulness meetup and help us celebrate one year of weekly meetings. We started meeting last year at this time, and while we missed a few weeks, people keep showing up. What we started at the beginning of 2009 has changed over the time, and it continues to be a work in progress, like life itself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It reminds me of the story of the farmer and his ax. When asked about it, he said that it was the best ax he's ever had--he only had to replace the handle twice and the head of the ax once. And so things change: some people enter and some leave our lives, we experience joy, sorrow, accomplishment and disappointment which come and go, we face difficulty and move through it, realizing that we were not destroyed as foretold by our greatest fear. Yet as with the ax, though all the parts may be different from when it started, there is an essence about the utility and purpose that remains constant. It is that essence that we seek to cultivate and illuminate through the awareness, wisdom and compassion that are all part of a mindfulness practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This can be a good time to reflect on our past year, while renewing and strengthening our commitments and convictions for the year ahead. Please join us as we gather in mindful community to celebrate the return of the light. We will listen to a talk about mindfulness, joyfully reveal our insights and epiphanies, share in a short meditation, and end with our intentions. I will bring some refreshments to mark a full cycle of seasons with our group. All levels of meditators and mindfulness practitioners are welcome. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet people at the right side front door - go through the iron gate - until 6pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262819250000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262490170000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One Year Anniversary!</name><id>12203037</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262646000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/12203037/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/1/global_12020385.jpeg</photo_url></item>