<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT E51-145</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>212199</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Boston Investors Business Daily Tuesday Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TECHNICAL INDICATORS AND RISK MANAGEMENT presented by TOM HILL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom will present a few technical indicators (MACD, MA crossovers, the Williams %R), their pros and cons and examples of how to use them. Addition Tom will explain his strategy for reducing risk and how he uses risk assessment to manage money. He will also give a brief report from the recent Traders Expo in San Diego.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TOM HILL'S BRIEF BIO&lt;br /&gt;Tom Hill has been a full time active trader since 2000 and is a Boston IBD member. Tom grew up in the Boston area and studied Mechanical Engineering at Tufts University and MIT. While employed as an engineer he invested in real estate both as a landlord and a condominium developer. He left the corporate world in 1998 to complete a real estate project and then got involved in the stock market. In 2003 after a few choppy years he decided to expand his knowledge of market trading techniques and took several classes including those offered by Pristine. More recently he completed the Market Technicians Association CMT program and is currently looking for sponsors to complete the CMT certification process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting's agenda will have the following agenda:&lt;br /&gt;- 6:30-7:00 Socializing premeeting period&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Meeting Begins:&lt;br /&gt;- Group discussion led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;- Questionnaire Results by Doug&lt;br /&gt;- Technical Analysis update by Harlan&lt;br /&gt;- Stockpicks led by Chris and Mike&lt;br /&gt;- Feature Presentation by Tom Hill&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members value open discussion highly. We try to pack as much open discussion as possible. Expressing ideas and sharing knowledge is paramount to our members.&lt;br /&gt;All levels of expertise are welcome. No question is too simple - as a matter of fact the simplest question often evokes the best discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have friends that you talk stocks with then bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;Location: MIT Building E51. MIT, 77 Mass Ave, Cambridge, MA, USA.&lt;br /&gt;This building is on the far eastern side of the MIT campus, about a ten minute walk from the main entrance, and about two minutes from the Kendall Square 'T' stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free meeting. There is no membership required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184281630000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182729545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston IBD Tuesday Meetup</name><id>5931208</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184108400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/5931208/</event_url></item>