<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There has been an emergency plea from the Ellington school district for volunteers to come out and help clear all the school roofs of snow and ice. The Ellington schools have been closed the past two days after the last snow/ice storm because of concerns for the load on the roofs by snow and ice. School district crews have been working along with volunteer firefighters and volunteer ambulance workers over the past two days to clear the roofs but there is still plenty of snow/ice on the roofs. It is hoped that with volunteer help through this weekend schools will be safe enough to reopen on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am organizing volunteers to arrive at 9 AM at the Ellington High School. You must be at least 16 years old and you must bring a snow shovel. We will report to the Lead Custodian for assignments. You can report to me if you find me first but I will set you up with the Lead Custodian. If there are enough people at the High School, we will send people to one of the other schools in the district (Middle School, Center School {elementary}, Crystal Lake School {elementary}, Windermere School {elementary &amp;amp; intermediate}). Work will be from 9 AM to no later than 5 PM. You can work as long or a little as you have time to help out. You may also arrive later if you must but I encourage everyone to start early!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The district will be looking for help on Sunday, 2/6/11, too but I am not organizing volunteers for that day. You may show up and assist that day too if you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location for meeting:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Ellington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=37+Maple+St&amp;amp;zipcode=06029-3333&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.908491&amp;amp;longitude=-72.459635&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;http://classic.mapquest.com/maps?city=Ellington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=37+Maple+St&amp;amp;zipcode=06029-3333&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.908491&amp;amp;longitude=-72.459635&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ellington High School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;37 Maple Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ellington, CT 06029&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== &lt;strong&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/strong&gt; ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297003614000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296846175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Emergency Plea for Volunteers to Help Clear Ellington School Roofs</name><id>16443829</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296914400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/16443829/</event_url></item>