<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Park Ave and Elm Streets</address_2><address_1>250 Park Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.264890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774-239-0214</phone><name>stART on the Street</name><city>Worcester</city><id>341550</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.819016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It?s that time of year again, Scott and I are doing the stART on the Street Festival in Sept. I wanted to send out the info now so you can save the date! Please come out and join us for this fun day...here are all the details. Mark your calendars now!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need volenteers for the Worcester Meetup Booth at the Event! Please lend a hand and help us man the booth. I'll be looking for folks to commit and sign up at the next meeting. Remember I want to have this be a partial fundraiser for Eric!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: stART on the Street '07: the Creative City&lt;br /&gt;Why: FREE! Central Massachusetts' only cultural street festival!&lt;br /&gt;When: Sunday September 16, 2007 (rain date Sept. 23) 11am - 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring artists, crafters, live bands, street performers, kids activities and a food court Located on Park Avenue from Elm to Pleasant Streets in Worcester, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be among the first attendees to the festival and receive a limited edition goody bag!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The stART on the Street festival has hosted an increasing number of arts and crafts vendors each year, from 165 in 2006 to and expected 225 artists in 2007, all demonstrating and selling their handcrafted items. A main stage area hosts a variety of live bands from rock &amp;amp; roll, alternative country, jazz, world music and more. Street performers entertain on the street level; everything from Africa-Brazilian Capoeira demonstrations, a cappella groups, acoustic music, dance and many more genres of performance art. A Youth Activities area with local organizations hosting interactive art activities has been a popular attraction for families through the years. &lt;a href="http://www.startonthestreet.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.startonthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott and Donna&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190124209000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186595006000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Photography Meetup At stART on the Street Festival</name><id>6146369</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189951200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6146369/</event_url></item>