<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;**NOTE** This trip has been bumped up to a longer journey due to the Sawyer River Road remaining closed. 730AM is a new start time and that is when we're to be at the Dunkin Donuts. From there, we'll drive to the trailhead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back by popular demand - a shot at climbing The Captain, a trailless NH 100 highest peak! The trip will be around 15 miles, climb about 2500' and take perhaps 10 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The start and end of the hike is on a trail and a woods road (closed to traffic) but the middle portion will be a very exciting mix, which will hopefully include scrambling up a rockslide (if the ground is dry) and then at the top, we will be skirting alongside a cliff. This route is not technical, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never bushwhacked before, this may not be the trip for you. I will take the uninitiated, but be forewarned this type of hiking is extremely taxing and you must be very hardy to have a chance of enjoying the excursion. If you are claustrophobic, or do not want scratches all over your body, do not sign up for this trip!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important gear notes are as follows: you need to bring a working compass. Bring a map if you have one. If you do not have a map dont worry I will be bringing a photocopy for everyone, but bring a gallon size ziplock bag to keep the photocopy in, otherwise it will not last the trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email me directly if you have any questions. If all of the survey questions are not answered you risk being removed from the trip, as space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew B</member_name><member_id>4803051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340651954000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339644464000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bushwhack to The Captain 3520'  (NH100)</name><id>69110282</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340537400000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/69110282/</event_url></item>