<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>42 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-6789</phone><name>Cambridge Center for Adult Education</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1170238</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121368</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to meet someone at a social gathering
(meetup events, parties, networking events, bars, etc), but 
&lt;strong&gt;didn't know what to say,&lt;/strong&gt; or started talking to
someone and 
&lt;strong&gt;got stuck in your own head&lt;/strong&gt; no knowing what to say?
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Wouldn't it be great if you had a simple system you could use
again and again to effortlessly know 
&lt;em&gt;exactly what to say&lt;/em&gt; to start the conversation and keep it
going with the people you're talking to?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well that's what you're going to learn at this seminar. Your
conversations will flow effortlessly, and you won't get stuck in
your head or have to worry about what direction to take the
conversation or what to talk about.&amp;nbsp; Instead when you meet
people you know exactly what to say that will lead you to new dates
with them.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Imagine being at a meetup event or get-together and gliding
around the room talking with anyone and everyone without getting in
your own way or being stuck in your head. Imagine having a game
plan so you don't get in your own way and people approach 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;you&lt;/span&gt; to start a
conversation because they see others having a good time talking
with you, and they want to see what you're all about.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:
 &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A simple system that gives you the power to 
  &lt;strong&gt;know exactly what to say,&lt;/strong&gt; 
  &lt;span&gt;so you don't get stuck in your own head or have awkward
  silences in conversations that end with you being rejected.
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An almost magical phrase that I stumbled on that instantly
  gets you back on track if you ever don't know what to talk about
  in any situation.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The simple secrets of getting out of your own way so you can
  meet new people where ever you go.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The 3 "way points" that allow you to get a date whenever
  you're talking to someone new. Follow this check list and your
  conversations will always lead toward a date.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And much more!
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************
   &lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED
   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;The meeting is limited to 20 people due to the size
  limitations of the classroom (we'll be moving around a lot). Our
  meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have 
  &lt;strong&gt;Sunday, June 12th&lt;/strong&gt; available. The meeting runs
  from 
  &lt;strong&gt;3:30pm to 5:30pm&lt;/strong&gt; and is conveniently located in
  Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for
  this workshop right now. Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.
  They always do.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend,
  and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal
  networking.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for a
  professional training that includes these skill-building drills +
  personality feedback. Please remember to bring:
   &lt;br /&gt; 
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;Eric
   &lt;br /&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any
  questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is
  extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems. My cell
  is: 617-903-7371.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Special Note: &amp;nbsp;We will be in 42 Brattle St for this
  meetup in the Music Room. &amp;nbsp;If you're a regular attendee,
  make sure to remember we're in a different room for this
  meetup!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are in the Music Room - 1st floor, 3rd door on the right when you walk in, says Music Room above the door.  The front desk can direct you if you have trouble.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick Richards</member_name><member_id>12716842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308329894000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307413055000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Have Amazing Conversations That Attract The Opposite Sex</name><id>21258551</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307907000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/21258551/</event_url></item>