<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's hit the ropes mid-week! If you couldn't make Jens' uber-popular Monday night MeetUp, come this Wednesday! It is OK if you show up late...just show up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a departure from the usual, I'll be wearing brown corduroy pants with a little bit of horizontal fringe on them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet us at the picnic tables by 7 PM. We'll team up by 7:10 PM. If you arrive later, check the dry-erase board, where I'll post what I'm wearing. Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...and now for the usual stuff... &lt;br /&gt;Please note: you will need to pass a belay test if you are an experienced climber but new to the gym. You can take a belay test when you get there. If you have never climbed before, you should take a class at Metrorock. Please call the gym in advance to make arrangements to take the class. You can use the message board on this meetup to find other people that want to take the class. Metrorock will charge you $16 for a daypass if you are not already a member or a punch card holder. Ladies get a 50% discount on Monday nights! &lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock...." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt;. for directions. You'll NEED them if this is your first time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Brown corduroy Prana pants with horizontal fringe on them (about 1-inch fringe).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brenda</member_name><member_id>4850804</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266624209000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266289064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wild, Wacky, Wonderful Wednesdays at Metrorock!</name><id>12614489</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266451200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/12614489/</event_url></item>