<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Manchester Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.776202</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 589-3370</phone><name>Greeley Park (West)</name><city>Nashua</city><id>970127</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.475064</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wimp Volleyball &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, May 17th., 3;00 or any time before to 7 pm-ish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;NEW LOCATION!!  Greeley Park, -&amp;gt; Manchester Street side!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;N. Nashua NH. 03061&lt;br /&gt;Steve O.  ob@tds.net  603-491-1962&lt;br /&gt;Bill_J  bill@imaginetworks.com  603-557-6055&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the new location!  Same park, different section.  We may move things around a bit this summer and go to different places, (like the beach!) so be sure to check the calendars often - and RSVP 'yes' if you're going to attend.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;IF IT RAINS THIS EVENT IS CANCELED.  IF IT SNOWS, HALLELUJAH!! WE GO SNOWBOARDING!&lt;br /&gt;We will be asking for a $1.00 donation to help with equipment upkeep.  But please remember, your participation is more important than the money.  We would rather you play than pay.  Donations help defray the cost of maintaining/replacing the equipment.  Trust me when I say quality equipment means more fun than frustration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Steve O, BJ, and friends for an afternoon of fun and easy exercise, or just come to watch. Wimp Volleyball is a noncompetitive game. Totally for the fun of moving around trying to hit and return the ball.  We will be following most of the volleyball rules.  But having fun and learning will be more important than winning.  We count the laughs, not the score.  You get three hits to a side, so we work on keeping the volley going rather than trying to end it. The winners are those who sides hurt from laughing to much.  Sometimes we have a larger number attending,  so we will do our best to rotate everyone in and out on each side.  If we end up with a LOT of people, we will  have another net set up for them. So, bring your friends &amp;amp; kids, some drinks to keep cool.  Definitely bring some bug repellent and sunblock too.  Come have some fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will located on the extreme west side of Greeley Park, along Manchester street, in the section where the frisbee/disc golf baskets are.  Kids are welcome to play. But, they must be at least tall enough to have their heads reach the bottom of the net. There is a play ground for kids who don't wish to play, or are too short.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have another event going at the same time, Wimp Volleyball Chatting &amp;amp; Cheerleading. This event requires a lawn chair and the ability to chat.  Photographers are always welcome too!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 us on the extreme WEST side of the park on Manchester St.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill_J</member_name><member_id>4839704</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243969841000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243465281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wimp Wallyball</name><id>10508064</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243796400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/10508064/</event_url></item>