<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This Monday March 12, I'm hosting a French movie, with subtitles, at the Boston Public Library about the sculptor, Camille Claudel and her mentor, the sculptor Rodin.  The movie starts at 6 p.m. and lasts for 159 minutes.  It will be shown in the Rabb Lecture Hall.  According to the library website, this film is an historically accurate depiction of one of the most important collaborations in the history of art.  The library movies are free to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a plot synopsis from the website allmovie.com:&lt;br /&gt;The troubled life of French sculptor Camille Claudel and her long relationship with legendary sculptor Auguste Rodin are portrayed in this passionate biographical drama, featuring an acclaimed performance by Isabelle Adjani. Beginning in the 1880s with a young Claudel's first meeting with Rodin, the film traces the development of their intense romantic bond. The growth of this relationship coincides with the rise of Claudel's career, helping her overcome prejudices against female artists. However, their romance soon sours, due to the increasing pressures of Rodin's fame and his love for another woman. These difficulties combine with her increasing doubts about the value of her work to drive Claudel into an emotional tumult that threatens to become insanity. First-time director Bruno Nuytten had previously served as a cinematographer, and he brings this experience to bear in his loving presentation of Claudel's sculpture and the lavish period setting. The dramatic approach is in tune with the impressive visuals, which present Claudel's life as a grandiose melodrama, a transformation that irritated some critics. However, few questioned the film's value as a dramatic showcase for Adjani, whose fervent portrayal was rewarded with an Academy Award nomination for Best Actress. The American release version was cut to 159 minutes.   This movie will be hosted by Susan.  I will hold up a &amp;quot;Meetup&amp;quot; sign near the front to one side of the lecture hall after the film, and we will go someplace nearby for refreshments and discussion.  Looking forward to meeting up with you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173924455000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173404174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Camille Claudel" film at the Boston Public Library</name><id>5551192</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173736800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5551192/</event_url></item>