<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>GORDY SLACK discusses The Battle Over the Meaning of Everything: Evolution, Intelligent Design, and a School Board in Dover, PA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome Gordy Slack to discuss his new book, The Battle Over the Meaning of Everything, a compelling eyewitness account of the recent courtroom drama in Dover, Pennsylvania that put evolution on trial. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Journalist Gordy Slack offers a riveting, personal, and often amusing first-hand account that details six weeks of some of the most widely ranging, fascinating, and just plain surreal testimony in U.S. legal history; a battle between hard science and religious conservatives wishing to promote a new version of creationism in schools.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A sophisticated examination of the deep cultural, religious, and political tensions that continue to divide America, The Battle Over the Meaning of Everything is also journalist Gordy Slack?s personal and engaging story of the high drama and unforgettable characters on both sides of the courtroom controversy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1184279622000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182725436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading: "The Battle Over the Meaning of Everything"</name><id>5930851</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184106600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/5930851/</event_url></item>