<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Bretton Woods , NH</address_2><address_1>Willey House R.R. Station Site</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03575</zip><lat>44.215038</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ethan Pond Trail</name><city>Bretton Woods</city><id>256382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us in the Ripley Falls parking lot for an lighter Sunday hike. The round trip is a moderate 7.2 miles with just 1450' of elevation gain in about 4.5 hours.  I've wanted to explore this area for a while, but was always busy checking out another summit.  There are tent sites here and a shelter.  I'm planning on a casual pace and I think we will have a good time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ethan Pond Trail is a section of the Appalachian Trail. Not just any pond, but the 3.6 mile hike to Ethan Pond is at the edge of the Pemigewasset Wilderness surrounded by scores of mountains and the Presis, fantastic views of the Presidential Mountain Range! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are some great views on the trail and spectacular views at the pristine pond, including the A.M.C. Ethan Pond Shelter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a nice training and conditioning hike to get in shape for summer and other hikes. All ages are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's possible to camp the night before.  Let me know if your interested. A few of us are booking reservations at the Crawford Notch Campground &lt;a href="http://crawfordnotchcamping.com/campmap.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://crawfordnotchc...&lt;/a&gt;. You must contact them directly to make a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the Ethan Pond Trailhead: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling EAST from Route 3, go 12.7 miles on Route 302. Traveling WEST from Route 16, go 16.7 miles on Route 302. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will see an Appalachian Trail sign and a sign for Ripley falls turn towards Ripley Falls.&lt;/b&gt;  Turn south at Appalachian Trail crossing (Willey Station Road) and follow narrow paved road .3 miles to small parking area just below railroad tracks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are 2 parking areas off that road and we will start from the upper lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet me at the Ripley Falls parking lot /Ethan pond trailhead . up the hill at dead end.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281487047000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276117501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ethan Pond </name><id>13752382</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281277800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13752382/</event_url></item>