<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Queen Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06489</zip><lat>41.621221</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-426-1170</phone><name>Aziago's Restaurant</name><city>Southington</city><id>1167871</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.873328</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Well Readers, our February meetup was cancelled due to inclement weather. We are rescheduling for March. So you still have time to read the selected book and join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We started small...but we will grow! So if you could not make the first one, come join us for March. We will be reading &amp;quot;Have A Little Faith&amp;quot; by Mitch Albom, acclaimed author of &amp;quot;Tuesdays With Morrie&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;5 People You Meet In Heaven&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;For One More Day&amp;quot;! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a bit about &amp;quot;Have A Little Faith&amp;quot;...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Using his characteristically succinct style, Albom’s prose offers readers an elegantly simple perspective on faith, tolerance, service and love while maintaining the complex reality of his characters’ true life stories. The book follows the spiritual journeys of three men—a suburban rabbi, an inner-city pastor and the author himself—which Albom gradually assembles over the eight years he spends getting to know a man—the rabbi—whose eulogy he will one day deliver; over the course of this developing relationship, Albom also meets an inner-city pastor, another relationship that grows in importance for Albom. Weaving these narratives together could, with a less talented writer, muddle into incoherence. Albom’s expertise in piecing together a web of snapshot stories, however, reveals levels of meaning that could not be adequately told in any other way. He avoids repetitious overemphasis—the bane of much inspirational literature—and allows meaning, whether his own or the reader’s, to emerge with a quiet, confident grace. Albom’s latest is a masterpiece of hope and a moving testament of interfaith understanding&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;--Publishers Weekly &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now a bit about the author...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MITCH ALBOM is an internationally renowned and best-selling author, journalist, screenwriter, playwright, radio and television broadcaster and musician. His books have collectively sold over 28 million copies worldwide; have been published in forty-one territories and in forty-two languages around the world; and have been made into Emmy Award-winning and critically-acclaimed television movies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There you have it! Come join us if you can. This is an open discussion forum and we welcome ALL views!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW...for those looking to get a jump start on March's selection, we have chosen &amp;quot;The Help&amp;quot; by Kathryn Stockett. So, if you want to do so...read on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268438988000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267222426000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading With Rose...Our March Meetup...</name><id>12719483</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268265600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12719483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/c/global_13333916.jpeg</photo_url></item>