<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>157 Old Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02664</zip><lat>42.145061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North River Art Soc</name><city>Marshfield Hills</city><id>6343912</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.739334</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;North River Art Society will host an all day drawing/painting marathon at their center in Marshfield on March 24th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the same format as last time: three 3-hour sessions with a model on each side of the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10am - 1pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Session 1 will be from 10am to 1pm with a nude model (Nicole) doing short poses on one side and professional pin-up model Ludella doing a costumed long pose on the other side. Short poses will be 5 mins til first break, 10 mins til second, and one long pose at the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a lunch break from 1pm to 2pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2pm - 5pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Session 2 will be from 2pm to 5 pm with nude model (Kylie) and Sydney and Mike will be back with different costumes for the long clothed pose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 3 will be from 6pm to 9pm with nude model (Ed) and Charisse from King Richard's Faire for the long costumed pose. I don't know what the long pose will be yet. Charisse is a beautiful African American with long dreads. You definitely don't want to leave before the last session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The price for the day is a flat $30 whether you stay for all of it or not. Cash is appreciated since we need to pay the models on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you sign up, I will confirm with you. Space will be limited. So please show up if you are signed up, otherwise you are keeping someone else from coming. If you are not sure you can make it, please don't have me sign you up. We need a set number to make it all work out financially.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will provide some food and beverages again. But the more of you that bring something, the better the spread will be. Wine is never frowned upon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Space is limited so you need to get confirmation from Karl Nestleberger. His email is karlnestelberger@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>karl nestelberger</member_name><member_id>38295022</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364173854000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Art Models and Artists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NE-artists-models-group</urlname><id>408475</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>New England Artists/Models Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362775722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Multi-model All Day Event at North River on March 24th</name><id>108317792</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>39600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364133600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-artists-models-group/events/108317792/</event_url></item>