<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/e/b/event_18921739.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;In this class we will learn about the amazing capabilities originally encoded in our DNA, and why this is relevant at this time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Attendees will also be shown how to access a technique to connect with the highest possible healing currents, which have never been available on planet before!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;The information presented on charts includes location of gates to higher frequency domains (sometimes referred to as spiritual planes),  so you will understand where the highest healing frequencies are coming from.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;We will also discuss the Silver Seed Awakening, Kathara(TM) Bio-Spiritual Healing, the Amenti Project, Aurora Earth, and the latest information on the most advanced energy healing technologies ever on planet!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;In order to get the most out of the Meetup, it is recommended that you prepare ahead of time by downloading and making use of the free info on the links below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;No doubt, questions will arise as you explore this info, since there is new terminology.  This is another reason why it would be helpful to access the info now, and make a list of questions ahead of time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Technique 1:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;a href="http://al-hum-bhra.com/Aug2012/"&gt;http://al-hum-bhra.com/Aug2012/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;This contains a mp3 sound recording you can download from that page. It's &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;a guided journey to the highest levels of creation to access the most powerful healing currents in existence.  The technique takes over an hour, so relax and get comfy first. You can follow right along with the others in the group taking deep inhale and exhale breaths to circulate the powerful pri-mordial plasma healing frequencies to various parts of your multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Some of the terminology will be new to you. Just keep in mind the locations of your chakras and that you have something called a "Wing-Spot" on your back, approx. midway between chakras 4 (heart) and 5 (throat).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;You also have a "Mission Sphere", which is a big ball of energy all around you containing encrypted info about the reason you incarnated at this time.  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;When directed to inhale or exhale from the Aurora Shield, picture that as a glistening undulating disk of light horozontally seperating  the northern and southern hemispheres of earth and extending outward.  Aurora Earth is another version of earth where everything is much more pristine pure and beautiful. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Your 13th chakra is normally already embedded at the center of &lt;br /&gt;

 earth (also called E-core for Earth's core), and it is possible to connect with the center of Aurora Earth that way as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you are confused or unsure as to where to direct your inhale or exhale, just intend "in Divine Right Order".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember that this healing journey in much more than a guided &lt;br /&gt;

 visualization, because it helps your consciousness connect with &lt;br /&gt;

 cosmic constructs which in fact are REAL.  It was translated by&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;E'Asha Ashayana Aneayhea Kananda Melchizedek.  Although she holds the copyrite, she has given permission for anyone to download it FREE from the page which will come up if you click on the image above. After that webpage comes up, you can click where it says to download it, and you will receive the mp3 file which you can play on your computer desktop.  Be sure your speakers are turned on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Information about E'Asha can be found if you click on additional links on that webpage. At the bottom of that page you will see a link, which you can click on to join an e-group where you can ask questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* * * * * *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technique 2:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amentiproject.net/AmentiProject/Techniquesfile"&gt;http://www.amentiproject.net/AmentiProject/Techniquesfile&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This technique should not be done until the first technique has been completed at least one time.  It is a written technique. After printing it out and studying it, read it on to a personal recorder so you can then play it back as a guide while you relax with eyes closed each time you do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do this technique regularly morning and night, it won't take long before you don't need to listen to your recording anymore.  Then it takes just ONE minute to complete!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you get time, view the video presentation on the link below.   Technical diagrams are presented during the 3 interviews with Ashayana Deane. Each of the 3 interviews lasts about 2 hours, so allow sufficient time and take notes.   No doubt you will  have questions, which group organizer will answer with the aid of a beautiful handbook of colored charts which were provided when this set of videos was purchased from &lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com"&gt;www.azuritepress.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are much more clear than what can be viewed during the presentation below, but taking the time to view it ahead of time will be very helpful... so that you will be able to get the most out of this Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://projectcamelotproductions.com/interviews/ashayana_deane/ashayana_deane.html"&gt;http://projectcamelotproductions.com/interviews/ashayana_deane/ashayana_deane.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;NO&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;TICE: PLEASE BRING YOUR OWN REFRESHMENTS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go up 2nd driveway, which has ULCS Clinic sign.  Enter through side door which has Meetup sign. No need to knock. Bring as many guests as you like, since it's FREE!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358337106000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Everyone, on the following link you can download a mp3 file to access the highest healing currents possible.  These are called plasma currents.  There is also an e-group you can join, listed lower on the page.  http://al-hum-bhra.com/Aug2012/  -Aalia</why><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340165333000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Accessing the highest healing currents for total system wellness.</name><id>dnjmqyqkbwb</id><headcount>12</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358290800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/69928292/</event_url></item>