<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The legacy of the Big Mistake continues as survival is more than just living from day to day.  It's time to be heroes again, if only so that the local townsfolk shower you with creme-filled vanilla sponge cake treats.  That and it would be really awesome if you could find a working power cord for the coolest piece of Omega Tech you've found yet, the Sony BetaMAX.  The town shaman (read: crazy old guy who keeps sticking little pieces of paper on his tongue marked &amp;quot;DSL&amp;quot;) says its the wave of the future, definitely the technology to invest in now while the getting's good.  I mean, c'mon, alpha mutations are so yesterday, beta is what it's about now.  Either way, time to grab your trusty gun/improvised blade/street sign mace, head out into the radioactive frontier, and see what turns up to try and kill you... I mean, go out and be hero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The long talked about Gamma World campaign is kicking off on January 15, 2011 at 1PM at Veteran's Gaming.  This campaign will meet roughly once a month and will start at 1st level.  If you came to previous Gamma World events (the Game Day and the special Con module &amp;quot;Pax Extraterrestria&amp;quot;) the characters you played in those adventures can be carried over to this campaign.  If you don't have a character yet, you can roll it up when you arrive on the 15th.  A general knowledge of 4e D&amp;amp;D will help with some of the game mechanics but no previous knowledge of D&amp;amp;D specifically is required.  However, having some dice to make and play your character is highly recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any Questions, post em below or email me (Tanios)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295408426000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293039600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gamma World:  You've Come, You've Seen, You've Been Conquered</name><id>15799577</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295114400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/15799577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>