<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>870 Middle Turnpike West</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.780020</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Laurel Marsh Trail</name><city>Manchester</city><id>9383132</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.568350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Laurel Marsh Trail loop is about 3.5 miles. Mostly easy hike great for beginning hikers with some sections including raised boardwalk over the marsh and bridges. Some wet areas, a few small hills, great Hockanum River and marsh views, water birds, mature forest, giant white pines, and mountain laurel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To permit more parking we are going to use the commuter lot on Spencer Street in Manchester, near the interchange with I-384 and ramps for 84 and 291. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; There is a short access trail from here that will take us to the loop trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike should take about 2 hours at a social (slow) pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recommending waterproofed hiking boots for this trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids and Dogs on leash are fine if well behaved. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read more about the trail here:  &lt;a href="http://www.hockanumriverwa.org/LPCM_LaurelMarsh.htm"&gt;http://www.hockanumriverwa.org/LPCM_LaurelMarsh.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;to parking lot and start:  Check for West Cemetery in Manchester or use 249 Spencer Street, Manchester, to get you in the general vicinity, then look for the commuter lot across from the cemetery and near the highway ramps. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note about dogs:&lt;/strong&gt; While this is a dog-friendly hike, the dog owners need to be responsible. Trail rules require leashes. If you choose to break that rule and let your dog off the leash, please be sure it is okay with the other hikers (some of whom may not be dog people) and be sure you can control your dog when off leash. Finally, please be prepared and clean up after your dog when needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check the directions below - we are meeting in the commuter lot on Spencer Street!  Look for me with my two dogs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367267698000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366681776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laurel Marsh in Manchester, CT</name><id>115697202</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367085600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/115697202/</event_url></item>