<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.794332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>716384</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.664378</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Movie Synopsis&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY tells the extraordinary story of Herbert Vogel, a postal clerk, and Dorothy Vogel, a librarian, who managed to build one of the most important contemporary art collections in history with very modest means. In the early 1960s, when very little attention was paid to Minimalist and Conceptual Art, Herb and Dorothy Vogel quietly began purchasing the works of unknown artists. Devoting all of Herb's salary to purchase art they liked, and living on Dorothy's paycheck alone, they continued collecting artworks guided by two rules: the piece had to be affordable, and it had to be small enough to fit in their one-bedroom Manhattan apartment. Within these limitations, they proved themselves curatorial visionaries; most of those they supported and befriended went on to become world-renowned artists including Sol LeWitt, Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Richard Tuttle, Chuck Close, Robert Mangold, Sylvia Plimack Mangold, Lynda Benglis, Pat Steir, Robert Barry, Lucio Pozzi, and Lawrence Weiner. &lt;br /&gt;After thirty years of meticulous collecting and buying, the Vogels managed to accumulate over 2,000 pieces, filling every corner of their tiny one bedroom apartment. &amp;quot;Not even a toothpick could be squeezed into the apartment,&amp;quot; recalls Dorothy. In 1992, the Vogels decided to move their entire collection to the National Gallery of Art in Washington, DC. The vast majority of their collection was given as a gift to the institution. Many of the works they acquired appreciated so significantly over the years that their collection today is worth millions of dollars. Still, the Vogels never sold a single piece. Today Herb and Dorothy still live in the same apartment in New York with 19 turtles, lots of fish, and one cat. They've refilled it with piles of new art they've acquired. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY is directed by first time filmmaker Megumi Sasaki. The film received the Golden Starfish Award for the Best Documentary Film and Audience Award from the 2008 Hamptons International Film Festival. It has also received Audience Awards from the 2008 SILVERDOCS Film Festival and the 2009 Philadelphia Cinefest. Palm Springs International Film Festival named HERB &amp;amp; DOROTHY one of their &amp;quot;Best of Fest&amp;quot; films in 2009&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are other things to do at Phoenix After Hours:&lt;br /&gt;Phoenix Art After Hours provides a stimulating setting for mingling with friends after work. Sip a cocktail, enjoy music and other live performances, attend a gallery talk, and even see a classic movie or art film. The Wadsworth Atheneum is open until 8 pm the first Thursday of every month, with movie following at 8:00. &lt;br /&gt;$7.00 ADMISSION includes movie - $5.00 to just the below activities - FREE for Phoenix Employees and museum members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTIST SMALL TALKS 5:30 and 6:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;Take a psychedelic trip to Werewolf Karaoke, a four-room installation, with MATRIX 159 artist Justin Lowe &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PSYCHIC ILLS 7 PM &lt;br /&gt;Revel in the sounds of the experimental band that the Village Voice named &amp;quot;Best Psych Rock Band&amp;quot; in their 2006 Best of NYC issue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TAP THE KEG  (Free while supplies last from Olde Burnside Brewing Co.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DAMAGE ON THE DANCE FLOOR: DJ Breakadawn spins dance, trance and hip-hop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GRITTY GRAFFITI: Hands-on graffiti art making project &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wadsworthatheneum.org/do/firstthursdays.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wadswortha...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Convenient parking available at the Front Street Garage, off Prospect Street, behind the museum.  Inconvenient parking on the streets in the area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the lobby of the theatre if it is inside, or around the ticketseller if it is outside.  NOTE:  The rest of the museum and the gift shop close promptly at 8:00pm, so be sure you have all your personal belongings before you come to the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275658289000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274124210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Herb and Dorothy" @ Phoenix After Hours (Wadsworth Atheneum)</name><id>13510675</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275608700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13510675/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/8/global_10759320.jpeg</photo_url></item>