<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;Good news! As of today, two people have agreed to be new asst. organizers (applause! applause! applause!)  and there maybe more. I'll announce their names early next week. Knowing  this I can relax a bit going forward, and I'm glad to post this double-feature as a new event for the group ( I had hoped to all along). The Thin Man is a great, fun U.S. movie from the 1930's and the second feature ain't half-bad either.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Thin Man (Screens at 7:30)&lt;br /&gt;1934) dir W.S. Van Dyke w/ William Powell, Myrna Loy, Maureen O'Sullivan [93 min]&lt;br /&gt;Dashiell Hammett?s great tale of pickled-ex-cop-turned-society-sleuth, Nick Charles (Powell), and his always game wife, Nora (Loy), is a wonderfully successful merging of detective story and screwball comedy. Stars Powell and Loy share sparkling chemistry as they try to track down a killer. The dialogue is as sharp as a whip and the film stands as one of the screen?s funniest mysteries. Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nick and Nora Charles cordially invite you to bring your own alibi to The Thin Man, the jaunty whodunit that made William Powell and Myrna Loy the champagne elite of sleuthing. Bantering in the boudoir, enjoying walks with beloved dog Asta or matching each other highball for highball and clue for clue, they combined screwball romance with mystery. The resulting triumph nabbed four Academy Award nominations* (including Best Picture) and spawned five sequels.  DVD Beaver&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a compete review: &lt;a href="http://www.ruthlessreviews.com/reviews.cfm/id/1239/page/the_thin_man.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ruthlessre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Kennel Murder Case (Screens at 5:45)&lt;br /&gt; (1933) dir Michael Curtiz w/ William Powell, Mary Astor, Eugene Pallette [73 min]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Powell again stars as a society detective, this time the debonair Philo Vance, who investigates a classic of the whodunit genre: a locked-room mystery. A member of a Long Island dog kennel is found bludgeoned, stabbed and, for good measure, shot in said locked room. When the chief suspect, the man?s brother, is also found dead, only Philo can unravel the case!  Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The All Movie Guide gives The Kennel Murder Case 4 stars: proved influential in encouraging the production of other intricate, challenging mystery films. Directed with crispness and efficiency by the reliable Michael Curtiz, the film is a good example of the high production standards of Warner Bros. in its post-silent era. The script is a solid whodunit packed with interesting characters, well-performed and impeccably cast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet-up after The Thin Man when Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. I'll also be holding up the sign after The Kennel Club Murder Case for those who are attending both films. Probably a good idea to mention if you will see both films when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should  be fun and hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196123875000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194118408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Thin Man- A  Whodunit Screwball Comedy +1</name><id>6670287</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195950600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6670287/</event_url></item>