<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Portland, Maine</address_2><address_1>62 Avalon Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.689910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-797-2151</phone><name>Elaine &amp; Francis' Home</name><city>Portland</city><id>162669</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.301710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a special event: the inaugural work party for 2010 and an opportunity to come together and&lt;b&gt; lend a helping hand to member and dear friend Elaine McGillicuddy&lt;/b&gt;.  As many of you know Elaine and Francis have spent the lion's share of the last four years converting their Portland home to a wonderful example of living permaculture (among the many other things they do!).  The have been incredibly generous with themselves and their time as they pursued this passion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Elaine's first spring in her home without Francis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this morning session, we will organize ourselves into 2 or 3 teams to tackle some of the early garden tasks and help Elaine get going for the season.  Some cleanup, some planting of the coldframes, etc are likely tasks.  We will suss out the best use of our time in advance of the work party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to arrive any time between 8:30 and 9:00 am.  Some coffee/tea/am snacks will be provided.  Bring work gloves and wear work shoes.  Dress in layers for the weather.  We will go until about noon or 12:30 and then break for a shared potluck meal.  Please bring your potluck kit and a dish to share!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you in advance and, as always, please email me with work party ideas for sites that are within a 20 min drive of downtown and have the potential to illustrate some permaculture techniques (i.e. some implicit learning).  Work parties are especially well-suited to helping members implement some part of a permaculture design that has been prepared, even in draft form.  We are hoping to put on one morning work party per month April through October.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Date:  Sun April 18th, all other details being the same.  Will post a postponement note on this event page by 7:30 am if there is a change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271805883000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268495256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Work Party: Helping Elaine McGillicuddy</name><id>12866332</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270990800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12866332/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/8/global_5275768.jpeg</photo_url></item>