<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>PLEASE NOTE: This event was rescheduled due to rain on the original date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Somerville Main Streets presents UNDER THE STARS: INTERNATIONAL MOVIE NIGHTS IN EAST SOMERVILLE.  Saturday, September 26th, a hidden parking lot behind an old fire station in East Somerville will be turned once again into a free international cinematic street party!  Italian music and food will kick off the party at 6:30, followed by Pane e Tulipani (Bread and Tulips) screened in Italian with English subtitles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet old friends and new neighbors, while having a night at the movies (international style!) under the stars in East Somerville.  Free and open to all.  Street Party 6:30, Movies 8:00.  Saturday, September 26th.  165 Broadway Behind the Old Fire Station - 10 minutes walking from Sullivan Square on the Orange Line. In the event of rain, the event will be held at the Senior Center at 165 Broadway.&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: The event is held behind the old fire station at 165 Broadway (Somerville, MA 02145).  165 Broadway is 10 minutes walking from Sullivan Square on the Orange Line. (if it rains, 165 Broadway, Somerville).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Saturday, September 26th.  The street party starts at 6:30 and the movie begins at 8:00.  We do not have an official &amp;quot;end time&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COST: Free and open to all!!  There will be vendors selling food on site.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Warren Agin</member_name><member_id>299944</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356157716000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members of this group</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>italian-374</urlname><id>288923</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Italian Language Meetup Group &amp; Lunedì Italiano</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253278442000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Movie Night in East Somerville - Pane e Tulipani</name><id>11404915</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254004200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/italian-374/events/11404915/</event_url></item>