<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Triathanewbie Series workouts are geared toward the beginner to intermediate, sprint to olympic-distance folks.  Half IM and IM folks are welcome to join in however.  Workouts may be adjusted for group size and weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Sunday bikes&amp;quot; are bike workouts that mix distance-pacing with sprints, flats and hills; and are designed to allow optimal muscle group and aerobic exposure.  Details follow:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Start at back of the Coolidge Corner Theater, Brookline - 10:00 am (all rides will be westwardly: Rides will travel through Harvard Square (10:15ish), Arlington (10:45ish), Lexington (11:00ish) Concord (11:30ish), and possibly out into the surrounding metrowest area before looping back to Brookline (12-1ish pm arrival)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 15-50 miles (adjusted for group preference)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time (expected): 1-3 hours (adjusted to account for distance)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring: bike, water, patch kit with spare tubes, cell phone, helmet, weather-appropriate clothing, sense of adventure, your lungs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What I'll bring: small tools, first-aid kit, cell phone, air pump (both schrader and presta), gps unit, a sense of direction, helpful hints/tips &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other: You can meet up with the ride at several checkpoints at the expected times outlined above(Harvard Square, Arlington at the start of the Minuteman trail, and Concord)  Cell phone communication is essential if you are looking to add-in after ride departure from Coolidge Corner theatre as otherwise the group will not stop to pick you up) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please e-mail me for more information or to indicate if you would like to be added to a e-mail list for future unlisted or weekday workout notifications (useful if you don't check the Meetup site alot)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you out there:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be riding a black and silver Specialized tri-bike</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237127935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Triathletes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Tri</urlname><id>584357</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8399963379</group_lon><name>Mass Tri</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233523857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Triathanewbie Series - Sunday bike</name><id>9648764</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236520800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Tri/events/9648764/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/2/global_1776498.jpeg</photo_url></item>