<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1737 Cambridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375317</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University CGIS Knafel (North) Room K262</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>11683302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civilization in Color&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Some Societies Have Thrived on Social Diversity – and Others Failed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xavier de Souza Briggs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday, Apr. 26, 2:00 – 4:00pm &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Room K262, CGIS Knafel Building, 1737 Cambridge St.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a CAPS Seminar, Sponsored by the Center for American Political Studies at Harvard University. All CAPS Seminar lectures are free and open to the public.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How should democratic societies – and the cities that propel them – respond to increased social diversity? Conventional scholarly approaches focus mainly on Western liberal democracies and examine important pieces of this question, such as the relationship between citizenship and group identities, institutionalized inequality, or civic processes, such as they are, for incorporating newcomers. But such approaches struggle to link macro patterns to local ones, to convincingly explain big shifts over time, and, perhaps most importantly, to explain how societies, from ancient times to the present, have defined and employed viable 'repertoires' for handling social diversity – and even thriving on it. Comparisons not only across countries but also across big spans of time yield lessons obscured in our current debates, for example lessons about what kinds of 'integrative projects' are intensive and pervasive enough to matter, how to reconcile cultural distinctiveness (society-as-mosaic) with broader cohesion and governability, and as part of that, the need to bound pluralistic ideals within a viable public order. &lt;br /&gt;

Link to chapters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Xavier de Souza Briggs is associate professor of sociology and urban planning and Head of the Housing, Community, and Economic Development Group in the Department of Urban Studies + Planning at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. He recently served on the search committee for MIT’s next president.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Briggs spent January 2009 to August 2011 on public service leave from the MIT faculty, appointed by President Obama to serve as Associate Director of the Office of Management and Budget in the White House. There, he oversaw a wide array of policy, budget, and management issues for roughly half the cabinet agencies—Commerce, Treasury, Housing and Urban Development, Transportation, Justice and Homeland Security—as well as the Small Business Administration, financial regulators, and other agencies. His portfolio ran the gamut from economic competitiveness to criminal justice and border security, from neighborhood revitalization and poverty reduction to the financial markets, environmental sustainability, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A former community planner, Briggs’ award-winning research and teaching are about economic opportunity, effective democracy and governance, and racial and ethnic diversity in cities and metropolitan regions. He is the editor of The Geography of Opportunity (Brookings, 2005), which won the best book award in planning, and Democracy as Problem-Solving: Civic Capacity in Communities across the Globe (MIT Press, 2008), which examines efforts in the U.S. and other democracies—Brazil, India and South Africa—to lead change on unsustainable urban growth, regional economic restructuring, and the healthy development of the next generation. His latest book, Moving to Opportunity: The Story of an American Experiment to Fight Ghetto Poverty (Oxford University Press, 2010), won best book of the year from the National Academy of Public Administration. Briggs is founder of The Community Problem-Solving Project @ MIT and Working Smarter in Community Development, two innovative online resources for self-directed learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A former faculty member in public policy at Harvard, he has designed and led major leadership development, strategy, and other training programs for change agents in the public, private, and nonprofit/nongovernmental sectors. A frequent speaker on innovation and urban and metropolitan policy, he has also consulted on urban strategy to leading national and international organizations, such as the Ford and Rockefeller Foundations, and he has been an expert witness in civil rights litigation. In the public sector, he ran the urban policy research and development unit at the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development in the late 1990s. He is a member of the Aspen Institute’s Roundtable on Community Change and other advisory groups, and his views have appeared in The New York Times, Salon.com, National Public Radio, and other major media. Briggs holds an engineering degree from Stanford, a public policy and management Master’s from Harvard, and a Ph.D. in sociology and education from Columbia University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The Center for American Political Studies (CAPS) is committed to the interdisciplinary study of U.S. Politics.  Governed by an interdisciplinary group of political scientists, sociologists, historians, and economists within the Faculty of Arts and Sciences at Harvard University, CAPS fosters discussion, research, public outreach, and pedagogy about all aspects of U.S. politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Center affiliates also include faculty and students from KSG, HMS, HLS and HBS, in addition to other various Boston-area universities. Issues of study within CAPS range widely: Electoral Politics, Public Opinion, Civic Participation, Racial Politics, Legislative Politics, Social Movements, Ideological and Intellectual Roots of American Politics, and the Causes and Consequences of Public Policies. The Center also has a long-term interest in the Founding of the American Republic and the Study of Constitutional Government, both of which are programs (along with the Program on Medications and Society and the American Petitions Archive) housed within the broader CAPS organization.  Support for these programs comes from committed sponsored and gift funds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAPS encourages cutting-edge research using a variety of methodologies, including historical analysis, social surveys, and formal mathematical modeling, and it often cooperates with other Harvard centers to support research training and encourage cross-national research about the United States in comparative and global contexts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAPS hosts seminars and provides funding for undergraduate and graduate education in multiple contexts.  A recently launched Mentoring Program for developing the interdisciplinary undergraduate thesis research program will guide students in developing, before their junior year, skills to gather qualitative and quantitative data that will enable them to conduct research and write a quality senior thesis. A rolling graduate and undergraduate seed grant program also supports students in obtaining tools for research, traveling to present a paper or poster at a professional conference, acquiring data, and visiting a relevant field site or archive.  CAPS also offers year-long dissertation research and completion fellowships. &lt;br /&gt;

.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367018198000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366819323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Civilization in Color</name><id>115958182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367006400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/115958182/</event_url></item>