<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.546904</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Beverly Depot Station</name><city>Beverly</city><id>992740</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.885213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's that time of year again...although we haven't really been stuck in our houses this year we are all still dying for the nice weather when we get to see our friends more often and socialize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's get together for a good ole conversation night.&amp;nbsp; This year it will be a little different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be going out to Beverly Depot and they have come up with a set menu for us.&amp;nbsp; They have been very gracious in pulling this evening together for us.&amp;nbsp; The cost of your meal includes salad bar, one side dish, tax &amp;amp; Gratuity.&amp;nbsp; Bevereages and dessert are not included in the price.&amp;nbsp; The below are the menu choices, if you have other dietary needs, please let one of the organizers know prior to the event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10 oz Prime Rib&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baked Scallops&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baked Haddock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chicken Florentine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baked Stuffed Shrimp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pork Chops&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sides are:&amp;nbsp; Baked Potato, Mixed Vegetables, Rice Pilaf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dessert Menus will be available for an additonal cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Price:&amp;nbsp; $26.00 (please note, separate checks will not be available, Cash &amp;amp; Credit accepted)&amp;nbsp; Payable the night of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the conversation.....well the past two years was all about dating.&amp;nbsp; This year whether it's dating, the economy, life issues, we can talk about anything.&amp;nbsp; The one exception we do make is Politics, we find this can get into some heated discussions and this is not the forum for it.&amp;nbsp; So bring your thoughts with you and you never know you may find something out about one of your fellow members that you would never have guessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP for this event as soon as possible so that you dont get shut out.&amp;nbsp; The deadline for RSVP is set in stone with no exceptions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring the Meetup cell phone (978-304-2811) in case you are running late, get lost or need to get ahold of the organizers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not paid your dues for the year, please consider doing so at this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all at the Depot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Meetup, location is downstairs on the Left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331037134000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329783871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner &amp; Conversation Night</name><id>53113682</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330813800000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/53113682/</event_url></item>