<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-0930</phone><name>Wagamama Harvard Square</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802033</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120892</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Set Theory and the Continuum Problem by Raymond M. Smullyan and Melvin Fitting &lt;br /&gt;: 5 Month Book Reading and Discussion &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To All, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the long awaited reprint by Dover of arguably the greatest work of theoretical computer science ever written comes more than simply its availability and the immense pleasure of consuming it.  It also opens up the possibility of a long term project for our group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each Friday I will lead a continuing reading and discussion of this Smullyan/Fitting classic.  We will cover one chapter per week, 5 months altogether, from now until 1/21/11, and collectively read, understand, explain, represent and improve upon its contents.  The results will be published in a volume meant to augment this book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is now invited and urged to obtain their copy and read the next chapter.  If there are any requests, I will scan and post a copy here.  Please bring your copy and be prepared to discuss exactly what Smullyan and Fitting are saying.  Even better, bring and post your own write-up explaining the current chapter and perhaps your own representation of the assertions and proofs given. Go to HOME PAGE – DISCUSSIONS – MESSAGE BOARD – START A NEW DISCUSSION and insert your write-up as the message. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each week will ultimately result in a formal written explanation etc. of that chapter available on this site.  Diminishing summaries of all previous chapters will be included in the discussion at the beginning of each weekly reading. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The final collection of papers will be combined and published, with the authors listed being those who contributed papers.  Special attention and attribution will be given to significant contributions to the material.  Proceeds will fund marketing (publicizing) our efforts and future projects. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 22-week schedule began: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part I. Axiomatic Set Theory &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. 8/27/10: GENERAL BACKGROUND – Infinity and the Continuum Problem &lt;br /&gt;2. 9/3/10: SOME BASICS OF CLASS-SET THEORY &lt;br /&gt;3. 9/10/10: THE NATURAL NUMBERS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Until further notice all meetings will be held at 7PM Friday nights at Wagamama in Harvard Square, 57 JFK Street in Cambridge near the Harvard Square subway stop on the red line, phone 617-499-0930.  Come hungry (for physical food as well)!  We will be standing outside the front door up until 7PM (displaying the book) and inside at the right end (if possible) from 7PM until 9PM.  (Diehards will stay until they close at 11PM.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us to participate in or simply spectate this exciting new project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The great pleasure of this volume, I think, is to see the best theoretician address one of theoretical computer science’s most interesting (simple and unsolved) problems.  Our meetings are intended to make these results accessible to all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in outside the front door up until 7PM and at the right end after 7PM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie</member_name><member_id>2078145</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284164486000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Theoreticians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving</urlname><id>1340773</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281988302000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Set Theory and the Continuum Problem Smullyan/Fitting Book Reading Series</name><id>vfqgpynmbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284159600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving/events/14713423/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_9894127.jpeg</photo_url></item>