<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[color=blue][b]Michael Blair @ (978) 808-1932[/b][/color]

[divider]

UPDATE 11/09: The movie times have finally been posted and the one we will be attending is the 7:00 PM show. We will meet at 6:30 PM by the atm/ticket machine under the stairs. While Monica and I have to head home after the movie if others are interested there are many of place to grab something to eat/drink nearby. 

[divider]

127 Hours is the true story of mountain climber Aron Ralston's (James Franco) remarkable adventure to save himself after a fallen boulder crashes on his arm and traps him in an isolated canyon in Utah. Over the next five days Ralston examines his life and survives the elements to finally discover he has the courage and the wherewithal to extricate himself by any means necessary, scale a 65 foot wall and hike over eight miles before he is finally rescued. Throughout his journey, Ralston recalls friends, lovers (Clémence Poésy), family, and the two hikers (Amber Tamblyn and Kate Mara) he met before his accident. Will they be the last two people he ever had the chance to meet? A visceral thrilling story that will take an audience on a never before experienced journey and prove what we can do when we choose life. From Danny Boyle, the Academy Award winning director of Slumdog Millionaire.

&lt;a href="http://www.foxsearchlight.com/127hours/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.foxsearchlight.com/127hours/&lt;/a&gt;   

Here's the trailer...

&lt;xobject width="400" height="250"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/OlhLOWTnVoQ?fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en_US" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

[divider]

I learned today that this film will be released on (Friday) November 12th at the Landmark Kendall Square Theater.  Still not sure what time it is playing but I am guessing it will be sometime between 7:00 PM and 8:00 PM (Kendall Square usually announces the time and allows tickets to be purchased on-line a week or so before a movie opens). I will send out an update when they announce the show times.

Landmark Kendall Square Theater
One Kendall Square 
Cambridge, MA 02139
(617) 499-1996

Here is the link to the theater's site: 

&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheatres.com/Market/Boston/Boston_Frameset.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.landmarktheatres.com/Market/Boston/Boston_Frameset.htm&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289744988000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288987198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie: 127 Hours</name><id>15353074</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289606400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15353074/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/8/global_19402392.jpeg</photo_url></item>