<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 Centre St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.358440</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 244-4900</phone><name>Bertucci's restaurant</name><city>Newton</city><id>219959</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Apologies.  I meant to make the January meeting January 8, and it looks as if I somewhat screwed things up earlier today by making the meeting &amp;quot;January 7&amp;quot;.  Last week was January 1, on Tuesday, and would not have been appropriate for a meeting.  Tomorrow might be a good day for a meeting because of the New Hampshire primaries and discussions that we could have about our favorite candidates and how the campaign is transpiring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indulge me by making clear your Intentions for tomorrow, Tuesday, January 8's meeting at Bertucci's in Newton (Newton corner, right off exit 17 Mass Pike).  Feel free to come if you are new to the group, if you can, once again, RSVP @ the meetup.com site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In any event we will generally have our meetings the first Tuesday of each month, so plan on next month's meeting first Tuesday in February.  I'm sorry if the switch dates have affected your plans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also congratulations to Dave Shiple (and Stella) who welcomed a baby girl into the world January 1, 2008!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the meet up.com group at Bertucci's</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Bock</member_name><member_id>1795100</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200010006000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>You will have a good time here, good political discussions, nice way to meet other conservatives.  We will try to stick to an agenda, perhaps give time for adherents of various candidates to state reasons for supporting that candidate.</why><group><who>Conservatives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>townhall-61</urlname><id>155655</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Conservatives' Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199761051000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>correction January 8 meeting</name><id>7059389</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199836800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/townhall-61/events/7059389/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/c/global_921756.jpeg</photo_url></item>