<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>355 Prospect Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Leitner Family Observatory at Farnham Memorial Gardens</name><city>New Haven</city><id>181950</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>** UPDATE **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Observation tonight is ON&lt;br /&gt;___________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as many of you know, we've been trying to do an astronomy night at the Yale observatory for a long time, but have been repeatedly disappointed when clouds came along and obscured our view of the heavens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;well this time i think luck will be on our side, for we now have powerful friends! the Director of the Student Observatory and astronomy lecturer (and most importantly, NHC member) Michael Faison will be in attendance, and delivering a lecture at 8pm entitled, &lt;a href="http://www.astro.yale.edu/publicnights/LFO-public-current.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;What's Your Sign? Astrology vs. Astronomy&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; (also check out the blurb below). if the weather cooperates (and it will...right, Michael?!) then the observing session will follow immediately thereafter. there are two telescopes, each in its own dome, that are powerful enough to get good looks at planets, moons, nebulae, etc. in the past sights have included the rings of saturn, the red storm spot on jupiter, the galilean moons, and various galaxies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the domes are open to the outside air, so dress appropriately. for those driving, there is limited parking in the parking lot, so you may need to park on Prospect street. the observatory is on the corner of Prospect and Edwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;please keep in mind that even if the weather is foul (but it won't be, right Michael?!) the lecture is still on. BUT, if all you're really interested in is the observing, then you can check &lt;a href="http://www.astro.yale.edu/publicnights/" target="_blank"&gt;this link &lt;/a&gt;on the astronomy department's homepage after 5pm the day of to see if the public night is going ahead as planned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;pre-party? post-party? definitely possible. thinking maybe drinks at Rudy's Bar (372 Elm St) before and/or after. stars and beers go well together. will update.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;your contact for this event? take your pick:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Faison&lt;br /&gt;Kim (203) 540-7388&lt;br /&gt;Ben (203) 554-5144&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What's your sign?  Astrology vs. Astronomy&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Astrology and astronomy have a very important historical connection. For thousands of years, In societies all over the world, people have observed the heavens and tried to find connections between events in the sky and events on the earth.  Our modern view of the Universe came out of Ancient Greek models that tried to predict how the planets would move in the sky for purposes of astrological prognostications.   However, astronomy eventually turned intoastrophysics, a scientific field which is constantly evolving as we gain more knowledge about the Universe.  Western astrology, on the&lt;br /&gt;other hand, has not changed significantly in over 2000 years.  Modern astronomy is a field of science, whereas astrology is a pseudoscience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn about the connections and the differences between astronomy and astrology in this lecture, which is free to the public and open to all ages.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189296281000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188914810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>** UPDATE ** Thurs 9/6 - Stargazing and Lecture at the Yale Observatory</name><id>6294958</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189123200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6294958/</event_url></item>