<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Richmond Square</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.827108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-521-9229</phone><name>Waterman Grille</name><city>Providence</city><id>699167</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.380879</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The Waterman Grille (next to that pink building at the end of Waterman St. and in Richmond Square)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Waterman Grille is a cozy spot overlooking the Seekonk River at the end of Waterman Ave. in Richmond Square. It's so at the end of Waterman Ave., you may have never seen it, but its a gem. If you've ever driven over the Henderson Bridge to East Providence, aka The Red Bridge, you've probably seen it on the right (at least you can' t miss the pink building). This is a fave locale by many, so walk, drive, and get yourself to this cozy little oasis on the far East Side! As promised, there is lots of parking. We won't have to park in snow banks this time. So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a scarf or black cap in the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361494547000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361055488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Waterman Grille on the East Side!</name><id>104934122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361228400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/104934122/</event_url></item>