<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Blue Hill Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02121</zip><lat>42.306700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Franklin Park &amp; Surrounding Areas</name><city>Dorchester &amp; Roxbury</city><id>1356958</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083900</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is Boston's rendition of the world famous Carnival based in Trinidad and Tobago. It comes in 2 parts on Saturday:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Early morning J'ouvert: costumes, steel drum bands, dancing with the bands (my recommendation is that you come out with clothes you don't mind getting dirty...LOL). Official start is 5AM, but in my experience the movement of steel bands doesn't start until 7AM. This is my favorite part of Carnival. Anyone interested can join me ~ 7AM. Steel bands start at corner of Blue Hill Ave and Morton St. and will parade up Blue Hill Ave up by Franklin Park. I usually am on the middle island of Blue Hill Ave wearing red, white, and black (which may not narrow it down. Anybody of Trini descent may be wearing the same colors LOL...) it being early makes it tough, but its worth it once the sweet pan music hits you and you join in...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parade: 12PM coming up from Grove Hall and going down Blue Hill Ave past Franklin Park. Big trucks, soca music blasting, flag waving, great costumes, plenty dancing, jumping up. Much like J'ouvert, this is infectious with a much more upbeat pace. Finding a meetup place for this will be more difficult as it can get very crowded up near Franklin Park. Possible meetup locations might be inside Franklin Park (not on the BH Ave portion) or closer to Grove Hall (there is usually some room in front of St. Katherine Drexel Church at 517 BH Ave.).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out and enjoy! Hope to see you out there! &lt;br /&gt;-Kenny Hyde&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283016308000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282709839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Caribbean Carnival 2010</name><id>14533721</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283011200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/14533721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/global_5310243.jpeg</photo_url></item>