<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>On January 13 the Hooksett fire you may have heard about inflicted great hardship on two of our members: Tanner's parents; Michelle Boisse and family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They did not have renters insurance and were only able to salvage some clothes from a dresser.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Currently they are living at a relative's in Merrimack, and are in need of help. Some of the immediate necessities they needed have been met, but they will have to purchase everything again; beds, pillows, pots and pans, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They would appreciate any donation helping them rebuild their lives from the ground up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in helping please contact &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/photos/521166/"&gt;Linda &lt;/a&gt; (Tanner's adopted Mom and ex-neighbor).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also post your questions  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/calendar/9554527/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and Linda will reply as quickly as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Christine,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I spoke to Michelle and she said what they need most would be money or gift card donations to help them rebuild.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has been getting donations for a lot of the day to day essentials for them and the pets and  as far as household essentials people have been dropping things off for them so they don’t know what they would need.  I know she did mention a coffee pot.  Anyway..what they need most is money to be able to help them buy a bed, furniture etc…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe we can setup a donation fund.  Any donation no matter how small would be helpful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to monetary donations, if anyone has anything old they don’t use anymore, here are some ideas as to things they can use:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pots&lt;br /&gt;Pans&lt;br /&gt;Cooking Utensils&lt;br /&gt;Coffee Maker&lt;br /&gt;Vacuum&lt;br /&gt;Bedding for Queen Sized Bed&lt;br /&gt;Litter Box and Scooper for the Cats&lt;br /&gt;Balls for Tanner (any size….he is a lunatic and loves anything from tennis balls to soccer balls)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If checks are sent, they can be made out to:  Norm &amp;amp; Michelle Boisse&lt;br /&gt;And Mailed to:  Linda Kaplan&lt;br /&gt;                         16 Hale Avenue&lt;br /&gt;                         Hooksett, NH 03106&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have items, email me lkaplan@pageafterpage.com and I will get back to you to make arrangements to get them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanking everyone so much for their caring and generosity &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4894798</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda</member_name><member_id>7109503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232924959000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232367612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tanner's parents need help</name><id>9554527</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232751600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/9554527/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/b/global_6994267.jpeg</photo_url></item>