<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Simons IMAX Theater - Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1245284</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050826</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I saw a lot of friends at the Teton Gravity Research movie on Friday (at the House of Blues).  Great movie but you may have asked yourself &amp;quot;where are all the snowboarders?&amp;quot;. Well TGR has 2 big movie premieres this Fall - 1 for skiers and 1 for snowboarders.  The Snowboard movie is called &amp;quot;Deeper&amp;quot; and it is coming to Boston at the end of November.  This will be co-run with the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoors Club.&lt;br /&gt;-----&lt;br /&gt;here is the big write up..... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get psyched for shredding season and come watch the most progressive big mountain snowboarding film to date, &amp;quot;Deeper&amp;quot;, by Teton Gravity Research (TGR)! &lt;br /&gt;Comp ticket to Sugarbush Resort for everyone in attendance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Jeremy Jones and other top freeriders as they travel to the world's snowboarding meccas and venture past the boundaries of helicopters, snowmobiles, and lifts to explore untouched realms. Hang on tight as Jeremy faces the biggest challenges he has ever encountered in snowboarding. All night hikes, sleeping on peaks, camping 65 miles from civilization, 20 below temperatures, 10 day storms, and 20 mile days bring the adventure back into riding. Deeper puts the viewer in the athletes' boots, from the trials and tribulations to mind-boggling breakthroughs in the sport of snowboarding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MOVIE TICKETS: &lt;br /&gt;We will be attending the 6:45 p.m. show on Nov 30. &lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 and available online without surcharge. &lt;a href="http://www.tetongravity.com/tour/deeper/event.aspx?tid=729" target="_blank"&gt;Click here to buy tickets in advance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEET US AT: &lt;br /&gt;The Chart House Restaurant for drinks and appetizers from 5:15 to 6:15 p.m. &lt;a href="http://www.chart-house.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for more info on the Chart House, including happy hour menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR &lt;br /&gt;The IMAX theater at the Boston Aquarium at 6:25 p.m. We'll be heading into the show at 6:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for anyone wearing "Wedeln Ski Club" logo clothing.  or call me at 617-596-5579.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291159632000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289933193000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TGR Snowboard movie "Deeper" at Aquarium IMAX</name><id>15466784</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291155300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/15466784/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/7/2/global_19690722.jpeg</photo_url></item>