<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/8/2/event_110188802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This looks like it will be an interesting twist on the old fairy tale....not exactly the Disney version we all grew up with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show time is at 6:45, I will be at the theater by 5:45.  Please note, that since it is showing in the big theater downstairs, I will stand near the ropes by the concession stand until/unless they let us line up in the inner lobby.   So if you do not see me outside the ropes, look for me in line.  Please get there early as it is chaos when film shows downstairs.   Getting there early means you will have a better chance of sitting with the group.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together. This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;I STRONGLY advise buying your ticket ahead of time.  The fact that they have scheduled it in the big theater shows how popular it is.   It will probably sell out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. We gather in the hallway outside of the room we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after and bring cash.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; June 1, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Universal Pictures &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Rupert Sanders &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt;Evan Daugherty, Evan Spiliotopoulos, Hossein Amini, John Lee Hancock, Jez Butterworth &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;Kristen Stewart, Charlize Theron, Chris Hemsworth, Sam Claflin, Ray Winstone, Ian McShane, Eddie Izzard, Bob Hoskins, Toby Jones, Eddie Marsan, Stephen Graham, Ray Winstone, Lily Cole, Sam Spruell, Liberty Ross, Noah Huntley &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Adventure &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.snowwhiteandthehuntsman.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SnowWhiteandtheHuntsman.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;In the epic action-adventure "Snow White and the Huntsman," Kristen Stewart ("Twilight") plays the only person in the land fairer than the evil queen (Oscar® winner Charlize Theron) who is out to destroy her. But what the wicked ruler never imagined is that the young woman threatening her reign has been training in the art of war with a huntsman (Chris Hemsworth, "Thor") who was dispatched to kill her. Sam Claflin ("Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides") joins the cast as the prince long enchanted by Snow White's beauty and power. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The breathtaking new vision of the legendary tale is from Joe Roth, the producer of "Alice in Wonderland," producer Sam Mercer ("The Sixth Sense") and acclaimed commercial director and state-of-the-art visualist Rupert Sanders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  The movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand, unless/until they let us line up in the inner lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338762349000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334466338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snow White and the Huntsman (6:45PM Show)</name><id>60626122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338673500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/60626122/</event_url></item>