<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>401 Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.343983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 424-6111</phone><name>Regal Fenway 13</name><city>Boston</city><id>721114</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102784</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Why not be sentimental and begin my new assistant organizer role with one of the great classics of all times.. I know it's a Wednesday night and all.. one of a kind classic treasures... Given that it premiered 70 years ago, I'm really looking forward to seeing this on the big screen and in HD no less... Thank you John V.  for passing this on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I have my ticket and John V. has his..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this will be a weeknight, please indicate whether you can stay for the post film discussion at a nearby eatery.  I'm working on making a reservation at Boston Works.  The Red Sox are not in town.  I'm thinking as a first question is to think about the first fond memory you have of seeing this classic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am planning on getting there by 6:00 if you would like to meet beforehand and sit together let me know by answering the questions and I will grab a table on the second floor of the theatre (with a meetup sign) in front of the box office. .  After the movie, I'll go back to the tables in the lobby.. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the details..:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NCM Fathom, Warner Home Video and Turner Classic Movies present The Wizard of Oz 70th Anniversary Hi-Def Event featuring the first ever High Definition presentation in movie theatres nationwide of The Wizard of Oz.  This One Night Event will take place in over 440 movie theatres nationwide on Wednesday, September 23rd at 7:00 p.m. (local time).  In addition to the feature presentation of The Wizard of Oz, this exclusive event will include a special introduction by Robert Osborne, a classic film historian and host of Turner Classic Movies, followed by “To Oz! The Making of a Classic,” a look into how L. Frank Baum’s classic novel was transformed into one of the most beloved films of all time including archival interviews, behind-the-scenes footage and rare musical outtakes. Also featured will be an exclusive clip of the Scarecrow, Ray Bolger, dancing in High-definition for the very first time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets on-sale NOW! Limited seats available. Here's the link with a short video &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/lc7fyb" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/lc...&lt;/a&gt; and if you choose not to click on it.. You can also go to Fandango to order your tickets..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The colorful characters and unforgettable songs of The Wizard of Oz come alive as never before as the cinematic treasure is brought into the digital age with this entirely remastered Hi-Def presentation.  Celebrating its 70th Anniversary, The Wizard of Oz originally opened at Grauman’s Chinese Theater in 1939.  It received five Academy Award nominations, including Best Picture, and captured two Oscars® -- Best Song (“Over the Rainbow”) and Best Original Score -- plus a special award for Outstanding Juvenile Performance by Judy Garland. Its magical story and heartfelt performances have enabled it to grow from a perennial classic to its current status as a treasured icon of popular culture.  Whether seeing it for the first time or the 100th time, it is only fitting that audiences nationwide will have the chance to enjoy the 70th Anniversary of this multi-generational favorite in movie theatres for an exclusive One Night celebratory event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Over the rainbow in the front of the box office on the 2nd floor with a meetup sign dangling from my magic wand..:-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane</member_name><member_id>4305566</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1253969295000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251601254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Wizard of Oz 70th Anniversary Hi-Def Event (One Night Only)</name><id>11235698</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253746800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11235698/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/c/global_10447388.jpeg</photo_url></item>