<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:00 - 07:30 Self Introduction, exchange business cards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:30 - 08:00 Best Practices for Corporate Blogging - Presenter: Zach Hofer-Shall, a Social Media Consultant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:00 -           Discussion, networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are fortunate to have a social media expert, Zach Hofer-Shall, to give a presentation on corporate blogging. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zach Hofer-Shall is a Social Media Consultant specializing in helping companies of all sizes utilize the social web to connect to their customers, engage in the conversation, and push interactive marketing and organic search engine optimization initiatives.  He has launched and advised over 20 blogs in the last few years, some of which have gained tens of thousands of monthly readers.  He currently runs a personal blog on Web 2.0 technology at &lt;a href="http://ampersanddot.com/blog" target="_blank"&gt;http://ampersanddot.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you would like to present a case study, let me know ahead of time. I do want to make sure that the presentation is valid and good use of everyone's time.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a block away from Taven on the Square. We will be in the lower level.  Finding parking on the street is pretty easy around there. It's in the same area of Taven on the Square. There are also two metered parking lots near by.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victor</member_name><member_id>3780423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217545766000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><why>You will love it because you will learn and meet new friends.</why><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising</urlname><id>984032</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Internet Marketing and Advertising  Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214352381000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Best Practices for Corporate Blogging</name><id>8208213</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217372400000</time><rsvp_limit>42</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonInternetMarketing-Advertising/events/8208213/</event_url></item>