<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2761 Dixwell Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06514</zip><lat>41.369999</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 287-2546</phone><name>Meadowbrook Park</name><city>Hamden</city><id>304868</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.940002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FREE CONCERT TONIGHT: &amp;quot;Jay &amp;amp; the Americans&amp;quot; -  Former lead singer, Jay Black, is back with his hits Cara Mia, Come a Little Bit Closer, This Magic Moment, Only in America and She Cried.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gather @ 6:30.  (Show starts @ 7:30).&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Look for me/us under three shiny BLUE STAR-shaped BALLOONS (may or may not be fully inflated/deflated) attached to a white stick w/ red reflector - LOW TO THE GROUND so as not to block the view of those behind us!  At concerts, I traditionally stake out an area with 2-4 large blue-on-blue U-Haul moving blankets, likely fairly in the center, or uphill, from the stage, not too close to loud speakers and fairly not too far from the center path.  I'm 55, 5'11&amp;quot;, 215#, brown hair, w/ glasses.  If in doubt, call my cell# from an easy-for-me-to-spot-you location and I can direct you to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; BYO picnic dinner/snacks and beverages of choice.  As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Parking can be a pain, so I recommend arriving by 6:30-ish - allowing time to find and get to know each other, picnic, relax with a drink, play Bocce (with colorful balls in a clearing).  We typically stay till after the crowd disperses enjoying the company of old and new friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; This event is also being posted on the &amp;quot;Singles Event&amp;quot;, but without RSVP's, so likely several more people joining us than post on MeetUp.  For Hartford County concerts we typically gather 12-24... C'mon NEW HAVEN COUNTY - come out to meet new local friends and have fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; IF RAIN:  Call the Parks department directly (203) 287-2546 and make your own decision.  Please check back here after 3:00 Friday for any updates!   If &amp;quot;officially&amp;quot; cancelled, then we'll simply not MeetUp this time.&lt;br /&gt;However, this will be a BEAUTIFUL evening for some &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot;!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595&lt;br /&gt;rep06450@cox.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hamden Arts Commission's&lt;br /&gt;2007 Free Summer Concert Series&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FREE Concerts are held on Fridays at 7:30 pm at the Town Center Park at  Meadowbrook&lt;br /&gt;2761 Dixwell Avenue, Hamden&lt;br /&gt;(203) 287-2546&lt;br /&gt;mcoleman@hamden.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Friday, July 20: Jay Black&lt;br /&gt;The former lead singer of Jay &amp;amp; the Americans is back with his hits Cara Mia, Come a Little Bit Closer, This Magic Moment, Only in America and She Cried.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185143764000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182214386000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jay &amp; the Americans "This Magic Moment" and other great hits!</name><id>5906634</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1184970600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5906634/</event_url></item>