<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Raymond St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.361523</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Home of  Meetup  Organizer</name><city>Allston</city><id>2144751</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.133492</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you would like to attend, please email stories@massmouth.com and further directions will be sent to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an extra workshop organized by a massmouth member with Nicolette Nordin Heavey and Andrea Lovett as facilitators. &amp;nbsp;There are only a couple of spots left. &amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The charge is $30.00 for the 2 hr. workshop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;H&lt;/span&gt;ave you ever wanted to get up and tell a story from your life but unsure how to get started?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want to improve your ability to engage an audience and impact them?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you have some life experience and wisdom to share with others, and you would like a place to learn how to do that as well as a platform to practice it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you answered "yes" to any of these questions, you're going to love this meetup. &amp;nbsp;Norah Dooley and Andrea Lovett, the founders of massmouth, the largest storytelling organization in Boston, will lead a special "in -home" workshop. &amp;nbsp;In this fun, interactive event, you'll stretch yourself as you learn how to craft a kickbutt 5 minute personal story from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a lot easier andfaster than you think, especially when you have an easy-to-follow formula for story creation. &amp;nbsp;Believe it or not, you will have you story completely done in a matter of minutes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll get to practice several variations of your story throughout the class with a partner, and, at the end, you'll be able to share your story with the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, in order to help you imporve as fast as possible,you will be recorded with a high-quality camera and mic so it can be reviewed at home. &amp;nbsp;Or post the video on YouTube, facebook, discussion forums, or put it on a DVD and send it to family and friends. &amp;nbsp; It's a great way to share your story with others and helps other get to know you. &amp;nbsp;Plus, you can show the story to more experienced speakers and storytellers and get some extremely valuable feedback, if you want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of whether you do anything with your video, this proves to be a fun and engaging event that will transform you into a much better speaker and storyteller in just 2 short hours. &amp;nbsp;You will walk away with a video AND more confidence and skill in front of an audience; and that will stay with you for the rest of your life.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Respond to stories@massmouth.com and directions will be forwarded</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>massmouth</member_name><member_id>9876195</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308950315000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>storytellers performers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>massmouth-story</urlname><id>1513465</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>CLOSING DOWN THIS MEETUP GROUP: massmouth storytellers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307978908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Tell  a Kickbutt 5 Minute Story-Sorry, full</name><id>22013101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308783600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/massmouth-story/events/22013101/</event_url></item>