<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>June's meet up group will host Gayle and Rich Colman of Colman Knight Integral Wealth Advisory Services.  Gayle and Rich Colman are nationally recognized innovators in the field of Integral Finance, and are furthering awareness through public speaking engagements and seminars to elevate the Financial Planning profession and the field of Wealth Management. Their integral approach helps clients find ease and comfort with money in their life, and the path to a life fulfilled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Colman Knight Advisory Group has consistently been named one of the Top Wealth Managers in the country by the Bloomberg Financial Report. Gayle and Rich Colman have been in the Wall Street Journal, Boston Globe, Boston Herald, and the local affiliate to CBS news. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gayle and Rich are pleased to bring to you a night of Integral Wealth.  Daniel Gilbert, Harvard professor and author of ?Stumbling Upon Happiness?, states that money is one of the most important forces in being happy; but what people don?t understand is that it is not money that creates happiness, but the integral relationship with money and wealth. Using an Integral approach, we?ll explore how to assist you in better understanding your relationship with money so that money enhances your life and wellbeing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please go to their website to learn more:&lt;br /&gt;www.colmanknight.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole Trudel Churchill</member_name><member_id>3348175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182961558000</updated><rating><average>3.8599998951</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179274667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Ken Wilber Group June Meetup</name><id>5782040</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182467700000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/5782040/</event_url></item>