<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>21 Dow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.997532</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Queen City Ballroom</name><city>Manchester</city><id>709498</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464434</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I decided its time to have a refresher course and maybe learn some new moves.  Hopefully some people want to join me.  After the four week rotation, we can see where we want to go from there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Queen City is located above the Sanel Auto Parts Company @ 21 Dow Street.  The building is on the same side of the street and next to Golds Gym.  Look for glass doors on the side opposite Golds Gym, very near the road and then go up the stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Beginning Sampler Classes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These classes are designed for the novice who may not be able to commit to a weekly schedule, or the student who would like to experience a class (or several classes) before registering for a four-week semester. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The student who attends multiple weeks of beginner sampler classes will be exposed to the most popular partner dances. This enables the student to determine his/her area of interest and therefore assists in determining placement in the beginner level 1 classes (see below). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each class is 45 min and &lt;b&gt;$9.00 per person&lt;/b&gt; or 1 punch. &lt;br /&gt;No partner is required. &lt;br /&gt;No preregistration is needed. &lt;br /&gt;The basics of two different dances are taught on a rotating basis. &lt;br /&gt;Print out a free coupon for your first beginner sampler class! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.queencityballroomnh.com/freebie/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.queencityb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Queen City Ballroom&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are preparing for a special event such as a wedding or a cruise, or just hoping to gain some confidence on the dance floor, the Queen City Ballroom can help you achieve your dreams. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the north section of Manchester, NH, our studio is bright and airy with a great view of the city and features two nicely finished hardwood dance floors totaling more than 1,700 square feet of dance space. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Try us and see what a positive change dancing can make in your life! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.queencityballroomnh.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.queencityb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert</member_name><member_id>4121028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296180149000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260125326000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginning Sampler Class: Foxtrot, Swing </name><id>12029971</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263766500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/12029971/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/3/global_12113315.jpeg</photo_url></item>