<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1842 Whitney Avenue, Hamden, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.365849</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Best Video &amp; Coffee Bar</name><city>Hamden</city><id>10871462</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.908348</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Would You Do? Ethical Dilemmas in Great Films&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film is part of a series with an optional discussion after the film. There is a $5 admission charge and seating is limited. It is best to call the venue to reserve your space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best Video &amp;amp; Coffee Bar &lt;br /&gt;

1842 Whitney Avenue, Hamden CT &lt;br /&gt;

203 287 9286 &lt;br /&gt;

www.bestvideo.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fail-Safe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the novel by Eugene Burdick and Harvey Wheeler, Fail-Safe is set for the most part at Strategic Air Command headquarters, where a misguided transmission sends a squadron of bombers hurtling towards Russia, fully prepared to drop their atomic weaponry on Moscow. Air Force commander Frank Overton desperately tries to establish radio contact with the bombers, but once the pilots have passed the "fail safe" point, they've been instructed to disregard any reversal of orders. &lt;span&gt;Featured in the cast of Fail Safe are Walter Matthau as a hawkish scientist, Fritz Weaver as a round-the-bend colonel, and Dom DeLuise (billed as "DeLouise") as a weeping sergeant. Fail-Safe is followed by a government-dictated disclaimer insisting that the events leading up to the nuclear disaster depicted in the film could not possibly happen. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Best Video &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Our 5200 square foot facility is home to over 60,000 movie titles on DVD and VHS. Additionally, we work closely with several huge warehouse suppliers who can deliver to us any one of over 100,000 more titles daily. Choose from newly released, recently released, or our collection of rare and out-of-print classic and cult films.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Best Video is not just a place where you can pick up a great film. It’s a place that offers live music and spoken word events, Sunday kids matinees, and a coffee &amp;amp; wine bar where you can hang out. It is also a place that hires local people, patronizes local vendors and suppliers, and keeps its revenues and salaries in the local economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a time when community small business institutions are being bulldozed by soulless corporate chains and distant online behemoths we believe there is still a place for a local-rooted business with heart and soul that thrives on catering to your needs on a face-to-face, personal basis.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event space in back</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363400718000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357526484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fail-Safe</name><id>98295362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363042800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/98295362/</event_url></item>