<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Because of Halloween (evidentally) I can get to one of these Science on the Screen movies at the Coolidge (FINALLY!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We'll meet at 6:30, I'll have a meetup sign. the show starts at 7pm.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coolidge Corner Theatre's Science on Screen series returns with a special screening of The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoise with guest speaker Dr. Robert Stickgold. &lt;strong&gt;Winner of the 1972 Oscar for Best Foreign Language Film (France) and the National Society of Film Critics&amp;rsquo; best picture prize, Luis Bunuel's surrealist masterpiece wickedly skewers bourgeois presumption and hypocrisy as a group of well-to-do friends repeatedly attempts to have a meal together, only to be interrupted by a series of bizarre events, both real and imagined.&lt;/strong&gt; No one in cinema handled dreams better than Bunuel, and in this comic satire, he brilliantly interweaves flashbacks, dreams, and dreams within dreams into the narrative. &lt;strong&gt;Before the film, Dr. Stickgold will discuss the science of dreaming.&lt;/strong&gt; How does the latest research advance our understanding of where dreams come from? How do dreams contribute to the off-line reprocessing of newly formed memories? Are Freud&amp;rsquo;s theories dead? &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Stickgold is associate professor of psychiatry at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and Harvard Medical School, where he is the director of the Center for Sleep and Cognition. His research examines the nature of sleep and dreams from a cognitive neuroscience perspective, with an emphasis on the role of sleep and dreaming in memory processing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets: $9.75 general/$7.75 students and Museum of Science members/free for Coolidge Members. More info at &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science"&gt;www.coolidge.org/science&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.coolidge.org/sites/default/files/images/banners/banner_40.jpg?1317653817" width="606" height="340" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/v/hy27guq83kQ"&gt;Watch Trailer&lt;/a&gt; 1hr 42mins // directed by:&lt;span&gt;Luis Bu&amp;ntilde;uel&lt;/span&gt; // featuring:&lt;span&gt;Fernando Rey, St&amp;eacute;phane Audran, Jean-Pierre Cassel, Paul Frankeur, Delphine Seyrig, and Bulle Ogier&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1320672153000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318441550000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoisie</name><id>37138412</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320186600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/37138412/</event_url></item>