<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>908/910 Chapel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.306507</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203 624-6200</phone><name>Keys to The City</name><city>New Haven</city><id>858497</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.926858</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>****Updated information****&lt;br /&gt; The cover charge at Keys to the City on Sat night is $7 and there is a two drink minimum. The waitress can do separate tabs. I will let her know when I get there that we are interested in that since it will be a big group and that should reduce the chance of any confusion over paying the bill. Some tables reserved under &amp;quot;Andrea&amp;quot; so look for us or ask the person at the door where our group is. &lt;br /&gt;***********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Andrea to celebrate her birthday with drinks and lots of music!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have always had fun at dueling piano bars and thought that my birthday would be the perfect time to check out Keys to the City. In other places I've been to, the piano players have been entertaining and it is always fun to make requests and have your songs played. I hope that you can join me for lots of music, drinks, and fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keys to the City will reserve seats for parties if they have room. They asked to be told the number of people coming as soon as possible.  I can’t make any promises for getting seats, but will call them a few weeks before and again the week before to reserve seats for the definite “Yes” RSVPs.  I don't know how crowded they get since I haven't been so I also can't make any promises about open seats that night especially later in the night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it looks like bad weather, we will reschedule for another night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keys to the City has a $7 cover charge and a 2-drink minimum.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can check out info about KTTC online: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://botteganewhaven.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Keys to the City website&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send out a cell phone contact number to the Yes and Maybe RSVPs a day or two before the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask at the door for our group - under the name "Andrea"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236269559000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232901224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Keys to the City - Sat Feb 21st @ 9 pm</name><id>9597078</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235268000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/9597078/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>