<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>French St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.650002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boardinghouse Park</name><city>Andover</city><id>354829</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.160004</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What could be better than breathing in fresh country air, taking in the stunning landscape of Lowell National Park while being serenaded by a the dulcet tones of banjos and fiddles? If you're into Bluegrass, Dixieland or Oldtime country music and would like to participate, or you're purely there as a spectator, this free event is an enjoyable day out. Banjo and fiddle players of all ages, from experts to beginners, compete for cash prizes and trophies in this annual competition. Interested in learning to play? Workshops on Mountain Dulcimer, Oldtime Fiddle, Oldtime Banjo, Twin and Bluegrass Fiddle, and Bluegrass Banjo are held in the morning and the competition gets started at noon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over 75 contestants compete for prizes  This event is free of charge (donations are welcome) and is a full day of music, food and family fun.  Old time banjo, fiddle and dulcimer workshops begin at 10AM and the Contests begin at Noon and continue through the afternoon till 6PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This looks like a blast!  I went to one in Vermont a few years ago and couldn't stop my feet from stomping.  Since it's an all day event, I'll post a meet up place and time at a later date.  I'll also bring a cell phone for meeting up with those who need to come earlier or later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission and Registration Free&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael B</member_name><member_id>2958968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189433350000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>divorcesupport-249</urlname><id>368805</id><group_lat>42.1899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston/Burbs Life after Divorce Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188049658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>28TH ANNUAL BANJO &amp; FIDDLERS CONTEST in Lowell</name><id>6240420</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189260000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/divorcesupport-249/events/6240420/</event_url></item>