<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sharing our New Possibilities Free Monthly Class with you.  Hope you'll join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Are you feeling a little bummed out that summer is over?  &lt;br /&gt;•Do you wish you could feel like you do on vacation every day?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Well guess what?  You can!  This evening, in addition to doing one or two guided meditations on feeling good, I’ll be leading you through a process to help you bring a vacation frame of mind into every day.  The benefits are beyond what you might be imagining.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Remember the short article I shared with you on living every day in a vacation frame of mind? (Now in our files section)  &lt;i&gt;Turns out that this frame of mind is pretty much identical to an enlightened, allowing state of mind.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Join us in this special evening and you’ll:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• &lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;Experience deeply relaxed states&lt;br /&gt;• Get into really “feeling good” states&lt;br /&gt;• Be able to bring a vacation frame of mind into your everyday life – even work, and still be productive – perhaps even more so!&lt;br /&gt;• Learn some tricks so you can have more emotional choice, versus being at the effect of moods and emotions happening to you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sound good?  Hope you’ll join us for this wonderful opportunity!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Remember, this is a public event, so all are welcome; and the more people we have, the better the collective energy and experience.  So,&lt;u&gt; please invite others to sign up and join you.  Forward this to your friends, family and groups.  The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required.  Please let us know if your plans change, too, so we won’t be waiting for you unnecessarily.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;A big thank you to Wayland Wellness for co-sponsoring this evening with New Possibilities Coaching!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255808765000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252078685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Evening of Guided Meditations and Living in a Vacation Frame of Mind</name><id>11289458</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253920500000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/11289458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>