<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When you build components for your own applications, you are working in a controlled environment and can make a lot of assumptions about how your component will be used.  However, if you want to release components out into the wild?  It is inevitable that folks will use your component in ways you didn't consider; and they're going to blame you if it doesn't work.  This presentation will cover some tips and tricks to help you optimize your components for reuse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;br /&gt;Jeffry is a technical entrepreneur and the brains behind Flextras, a set of interface components for Flex Developers.&lt;br /&gt;He has a Computer Science degree from the days before business met the Internet and owns DotComIt, an Adobe Solutions Partner specializing in Rich Internet Applications. Jeffry is an Adobe Community Expert and produces The Flex Show, a podcast for Flex Developers. Jeffry is also co-manager of the Hartford CT Adobe User Group, author of 3 ColdFusion books and over 30 articles, and has spoken at various events all over the US.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his spare time he is a musician, old school adventure game aficionado, and recording engineer. He also owns a Wii. You can check out the components at www.flextras.com/?c=107 , read his blog at www.jeffryhouser.com, check out his podcast at www.theflexshow.com or check out his company at www.dot-com-it.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259007052000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247515937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bullet Proofing Flex Components</name><id>10867404</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249599600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/10867404/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/f/global_5719263.jpeg</photo_url></item>