<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person for Food</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hands-on Paper Prototyping&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if you could design and test your website or application, before spending any time and money coding it? Imagine being able to know before you release your product, that it meets the needs of your customers, and is easy to use? How about showing your ideas off to stakeholders, and get valuable feedback that your can incorporate right away within minutes?&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Welcome the the world of Paper Prototyping...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video below is a video recording of someone doing a usability test on the paper prototype. This can be done before any software code is written, and is a great way to test and iterate on your design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;xobject height="350" width="400"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/GrV2SZuRPv0&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;feature=player_embedded&amp;amp;version=3" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="400" height="350" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sketching and Evaluating Your Design Concepts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Boston PHP and Christine Perfetti as we teach you the essentials for creating low-fidelity paper prototypes to flesh out your design ideas and gather feedback from users early in the development process. Using common office supplies, development teams can build and test a working prototype of a product in a matter of hours. Christine will share prototyping techniques for simulating all kinds of user interface widgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this hands-on session, you'll learn to create a fully working paper mock-up of any proposed design, which you can use to collect usability data through usability testing. You'll discover what aspects of your design work well, and what users have trouble with. Using paper mock-ups, you can make changes very quickly, even during a usability test! It may sound counter-intuitive, but it's usually faster to develop and change a paper mock-up than an electronic prototype. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The high point of this presentation is the interactive design exercise. Using everything you've learned, you'll build a fully working product within a couple of hours and test real users interacting with the design. Because it's a competition, you'll find yourself totally immersed, working at top speed.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is part of our new hands-on series where we break away from our usual presentations and get you in the drivers seat practicing what you learn. If you loved our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/15797436/"&gt;Steve Krug Usablity events&lt;/a&gt;, then you will love this one too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make this an effective learning event without it being too crowded, we will need to limit the number of attendees. Also we must ensure that those that RSVP will actually come and not change at the last minute. That is why we are&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;charging&amp;nbsp;attendees&amp;nbsp;$7 for attending&lt;/em&gt;. We will use this money to offer food and drinks at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Christine:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://www.perfettimedia.com/wp-content/themes/perfetti/images/christineperfetti_headshot_small.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/members/1139245"&gt;Christine Perfett&lt;/a&gt;i is CEO and Founding Principal of &lt;a href="http://www.perfettimedia.com"&gt;Perfetti Media&lt;/a&gt;. If you've ever met Christine, you know she's passionate about teaching design and product teams how to tackle their problems. For more than a decade, she has taught hundreds of teams and consulted with dozens of clients on product strategy and user experience techniques. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 With her extensive knowledge of human factors and user research techniques, Christine has been a top-rated presenter at the User Interface Conference, the Internet Marketing Conference, CHI, and the Usability Professionals' Association Conference. She's co-presented with User Interface Engineering's Jared Spool at many User Experience and Design events, including the UIE Roadshow. Christine has also taught Human Factors at the Tufts University Gordon Institute for Engineering Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00 - 6:30: Doors open, Food, Drinks, Networking &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 - 7:15: The essentials of paper prototyping (talk) &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 - 8:45: Designing your paper prototype (in groups) &lt;br /&gt;

 8:45 - 9:30: Testing your prototype (in groups)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>1ST Floor. Look here for parking: http://bit.ly/adRzem</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Perfetti</member_name><member_id>1139245</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Murphy</member_name><member_id>4790321</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather O'Neill</member_name><member_id>12680969</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324590955000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>28</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>77</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319282986000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paper Prototyping: Sketching and Evaluating Your Design Concepts</name><id>38300482</id><headcount>68</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323903600000</time><rsvp_limit>77</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/38300482/</event_url></item>