<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per room per night</description><amount>120.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I am spending a few weeks in Nashville and have found a very nice vacation rental home - 3 bed/1bath in a residential neighborhood about 5-10 minute drive north of downtown. It has a fenced in backyard and is in walking distance to state park and walking trails. I will be driving down with my two dogs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, I thought I'd put this out there to see if anyone might be interested in joining me for a weekend or a little bit longer vacation. If you could contribute $100 per room per night - 2 rooms avail each with Queen size bed(no taxes or anything else). Flights (southwest best option, sometimes direct) and any other incidentals like food are on your own. I'd recommend getting a rental car so you could explore on your own, or have money for taxis. The house is fully furnished and has basic necessities to cook dinner or whatever we'd want to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I lived in Nashville for 6 years so I can be a tour guide or give you ideas on things to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Possible weekends available would be July 16-19, July 23-25, or July 30/Aug 1. Of course if you'd like to stay an extra day or so we could talk about it. I'm setting the rsvp limit to 8 in case there are more people that come different weekends. The owners also have two other houses but not sure of their availability and the cost would be a little bit more for just a weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thanks! val&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279992476000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267911627000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Weekend in Nashville</name><id>12803200</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279987200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/12803200/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>