<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Star Room on 4th Floor</address_2><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 577-8812</phone><name>MIT Stata Center - Star Room</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>588318</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091419</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>** No charge for this event! **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re a baseball fan, you know a lot about the game:  the&lt;br /&gt;teams, the players, the rules, the traditions, and the words&lt;br /&gt;to “Take Me Out to the Ballgame.” But do you know enough about&lt;br /&gt;the science of baseball answer these questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)      How does a curveball curve?&lt;br /&gt;2)      Does a fastball &amp;quot;rise?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;3)      How does a knuckleball work?&lt;br /&gt;4)      What do baseball scouts actually do when watching games?&lt;br /&gt;5)      What is sabermetrics?&lt;br /&gt;6)      What matters to more Theo Epstein: scouting or sabermetrics?&lt;br /&gt;7)      How much does muscle strength matter in baseball?&lt;br /&gt;8)      Do steroids help baseball players?&lt;br /&gt;9)      What is pitch f/x?  Hit f/x?&lt;br /&gt;10)     Should players who used steroids be admitted to the Hall of&lt;br /&gt;Fame?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to raise your own game this season, Andy Andres and&lt;br /&gt;the MIT Science of Baseball program would like to pitch you&lt;br /&gt;some science before you take the field—or your seat. If you&lt;br /&gt;think that the answer to that last question has nothing to do&lt;br /&gt;with science, what you learn might change your mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, April 30&lt;br /&gt;6-7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;MIT Campus, Stata Center&lt;br /&gt;32 Vassar Street, Room 32-155&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;**We can scoot around the corner after this event to watch the Sox @ Baltimore**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Andy Andres, a diehard Red Sox fan, earned his PhD in Human&lt;br /&gt;Nutritional Sciences and Physiology from Tufts University. He&lt;br /&gt;is a member of the Faculty at Boston University's College of&lt;br /&gt;General Studies in Natural Sciences and Mathematics where he&lt;br /&gt;teaches biology and physics. At Tufts University, he teaches&lt;br /&gt;one of the first college-level courses ever offered in&lt;br /&gt;Sabermetrics.  For 17 years, he taught a seminar in exercise&lt;br /&gt;physiology and ergogenic aids for athletic performance at&lt;br /&gt;Harvard College.  In the summer, Andy teaches science and&lt;br /&gt;coaches baseball in the MIT Science of Baseball Program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a Datacaster/Stringer for Major League Baseball Advanced&lt;br /&gt;Media, Andy is responsible for scorekeeping games at Fenway&lt;br /&gt;Park for various Internet applications, including mlb.com's&lt;br /&gt;Gameday and Bloomberg Sports. For Ron Shandler’s BaseballHQ.&lt;br /&gt;com, he analyzes baseball statistics and writes baseball&lt;br /&gt;research analyses.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272933726000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270598865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Science of Baseball talk by MLB Datacaster</name><id>13108122</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272664800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/13108122/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/0/global_14194528.jpeg</photo_url></item>