<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Northern Connecticut Land Trust will sponsor a presentation on Sunday, March 16, from 7:00 PM ? 9:00 PM, at the Somers Town Hall auditorium exploring various theories that explain how the Mountain Lion is reoccupying the Northeast.  The Mountain Lion, also known as  Puma, Panther, Cougar, or Catamount, is the most widely distributed mammal in America, ranging from deserts to humid coastal forests, and from sea level to 10,000 foot elevations.  Come listen to Bill Betty, a Rhode Island native who studies these amazing creatures, as he gives a 90-minute presentation and discusses sightings and evidence of the big cats in our Nutmeg State. Displays and books on nature?s perfect predator will be available.  The program is free and will offer refreshments during the intermission.  Donations to the Land Trust are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Northern Connecticut Land Trust is an all-volunteer land preservation organization serving the towns of East Windsor, Ellington, Enfield, Somers, Stafford, Vernon.  The Trust has preserved 800 acres of open space, including 2 working farms.  Further information on Trust activities and news can be viewed at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northernctlandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northernct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership may be at this event. Just mingle with the other avid listeners!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions via Mapquest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/600+Main+St+Somers+CT+06071-2119/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Town Hall Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;600 Main St.&lt;br /&gt;Somers, CT&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership may be at this event. Watch RSVP's.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205881891000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Interesting lecture on funa changes in our area!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204864081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presentation: NCLT's Are Mountain Lions Returning to New England? in Somers CT</name><id>7482564</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7482564/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>