<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi gang,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the 7 who showed up for the September meeting about the rational basis of naturalism, good animated discussion as usual. It was pointed out that people don't always choose their worldviews rationally, so we need to make naturalism appealing not just to the head but to the heart. Exactly right, so I invite ideas about how to best market naturalism.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For October, given the upcoming elections I thought we might consider the connection between naturalism and political liberalism, if such exists. Naturalists are by and large empiricists, who therefore discount the often supernatural or dogmatic basis for discriminatory attitudes against women, minorities, gays, those of other worldviews, etc. It seems this would tend to lead them in a progressive direction unless there's a justifiable naturalistic basis for discrimination. Is there such a thing? I've explored this question a bit in a piece called &lt;a href="http://www.naturalism.org/enlightenment1.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Empiricism and Equality&lt;/a&gt; and in a book chapter &lt;a href="http://www.naturalism.org/progressivepolitics.htm" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you October 13.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org  &lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month):   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring and promoting a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>find us downstairs in the corner table most likely</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226366625000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220918784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Does naturalism tend toward political liberalism?</name><id>8717598</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223938800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/8717598/</event_url></item>