<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When:  Oct 2nd-3rd&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Milan Hill State Park, Route 110B, Milan NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Milan Hill and Weeks State Park Fire Towers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Milan NH and Lancaster NH&lt;br /&gt;State Owned&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the second in a series of short hikes and trips to various fire towers in NH.  I'm hoping for some great foliage - &lt;b&gt;on this date, the foliage is predicted to be AT PEAK in the North Country!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the evening of Oct 2nd, I plan to camp in Milan, NH in a yurt at Milan Hill State Park.  You can camp in whatever you like - share the yurt with me or bring a tent, RV or Pop-Up.  If you are not sharing the yurt, you will have to make your own reservations.  Milan Hill is one of the NH State Parks and can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.com/milan.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also skip the yurt and simply come along for the ride, visiting the Milan Hill and Weeks Fire Towers.  If you want to visit the towers, but do not want to camp, just say so in the comments or send me a note.  I'll work with you to coordinate meeting time and place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why Milan Hill State Park?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Milan Hill State Park is  a primitive campground, home to one of the northernmost fire towers in NH and within driving distance of the Weeks State Park Fire Tower, which is a beautifully built stone fire tower set atop Mt. Prospect in Lancaster.  Milan Hill can be used as a jumping off point for canoeing, kayaking, hiking, whatever you like!  If you are interested in those activities, I will do some research to see what is offered in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will camp out in Milan on Friday evening.  We can spend Saturday enjoying the scenery and foliage from atop the Milan Hill and Weeks State Park Fire Towers.  We can explore the North Country a little too and see what we stumble upon!  We'll return to Milan on Saturday night.  On Sunday, I intend to drive 1hr south to climb Mt. Garfield.  You can join me, or do some paddling or exploring on your own.  I will look up locations and outdoor activities if you are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Yurt holds up to 4 adults.  I will have one of my dogs, which are allowed in the park. &lt;b&gt;It will cost $20-$29 per person if we have 2-4 people share the yurt&lt;/b&gt; (with the lower price being the amount per person with 4 people)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional.  If you do not provide a phone number for follow-up (to confirm details as we get closer to the hike) I will remove your RSVP. &lt;/span&gt; I will only use your contact information for this meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The State Park website describes Milan Hill State Park as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Milan Hill State Park is located ten miles north of Berlin near popular areas for hiking, picnicking, fishing, canoeing, kayaking, and wildlife viewing. From this hilltop campground and the fire tower located there,&lt;b&gt; you can get a complete view of the mountain ranges in New Hampshire, Maine, Vermont, and Canada.&lt;/b&gt; The park has undergone an extensive renovation and this primitive camping area has added four yurts and relocated six campsites.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The State Park website describes Weeks State Park as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;John Wingate Weeks Historic Site's Mt. Prospect estate was built at the direction of John Wingate Weeks, leading conservationist, U.S. congressman, U.S. senator, and Secretary of War under Presidents Harding and Coolidge. The 420-acre Mt. Prospect estate was given to the state of New Hampshire in 1941 by John Weeks' children, Katherine Weeks Davidge and Sinclair Weeks. &lt;b&gt;Set at the very top of Mt. Prospect in Lancaster, New Hampshire, the house and grounds provide a 360-degree panorama of mountain splendor, including the Presidential Range of the White Mountains, the Green Mountains of Vermont, the Kilkenny Range, the Percy Peaks, and the upper Connecticut River Valley. Enjoy a historic Tower and the Lodge&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the NH Fire Tower Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So there are  the 48 White Mountain 4,000 footers and the NE 4,000 footers and then there are the New England 100 Highest....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what if you aren't quite ready for all that time and elevation gain? Or what if you just need some small worthwhile hikes and inspiring views in-between those trips to the Whites?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not climb our State's fire towers for a little exercise?  The State of NH has a program to &amp;quot;increase the public's recognition of, and appreciation for, the critical roles that our fire towers play in the protection, stewardship and sustainable use of New Hampshire's forests.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who doesn't appreciate that?  And with all hikes less than 2 miles (and many less than 1 mile!), who wouldn't be willing to get a little workout for a guaranteed view?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There are 15 Fire Towers currently in use on public land in New Hampshire.  Ascending just 5 of these towers, some of which are accessible from State Parks and auto roads, qualifies you for a Tower Quest Patch.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Information about the Fire Tower program can be found here:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhdfl.org/fire-control-and-law-enforcement/fire-towers.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhdfl.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a series of short trips and hikes to visit these locations.  I'm hoping to do most of them in the fall, when the foliage will make the payoff even better. I hope you'll join me!  And if not, I hope you'll pass on the word about this program to others who might be interested!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda with two dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286199889000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284913178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Fire Tower Series:  Camping at Milan Hill State Park (NH): Share a Yurt!</name><id>14821674</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286029800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14821674/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/e/global_18169006.jpeg</photo_url></item>