<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Middlesex will be off the hook this Saturday!  Come out and experience why we are one of the best meetup groups in Boston!  All members are welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are returning to Middlesex Lounge in Cambridge after a very long hiatus - this will be a great opportunity to meet new people and get your groove on!  Middlesex has been a premiere spot in Boston since its opening, and it is known for great music and a great crowd.  &lt;b&gt;I expect a big turnout, so RSVPs will fill up quickly - don't miss it!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  &lt;b&gt;I cannot emphasize enough the importance of going EARLY to Middlesex Lounge&lt;/b&gt;.  Its status as a premiere lounge in Cambridge means the lines can become very difficult.  I recommend getting there by 10pm.  Going early avoids the line drama, and you have more time to talk with nightlife members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8:30 pm at Middlesex Lounge, which is located at 315 Massachusetts Ave in Central Square.  &lt;b&gt;We encourage everyone to arrive early to have time to meet people, as the venue will get louder and more crowded as the night progresses.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Please look for us to find the group &lt;/span&gt;.  Cover: $5 after 9pm, I believe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZERS: Our pictures are located on the left-hand side of the site. &lt;b&gt;For help/questions, Andrew's cell: 617.459.5145.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue.&lt;/b&gt;  If traveling by T, Central Square the closest T stop on the red line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Andrew + Rebecca&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance: 617.459.5145</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>2881088</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6966003</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1266021219000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>62</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265381224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Nightlife Returns to Middlesex Lounge, This Saturday, February 6</name><id>12526908</id><headcount>62</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265506200000</time><rsvp_limit>62</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/12526908/</event_url></item>