<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Kennedy School</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6786892</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Social Safety Net?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Harvard University&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontline with Faculty Seminar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All FwF seminars are open to the public&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PEGGY LEVITT | Professor of Sociology, Wellesley College &lt;br /&gt;

SARAH VAN WALSUM | Professor in Migration Law and Family Ties, Vrije University in Amsterdam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday, Mar 4 | 12:00 – 1:00 pm | Taubman, NYE A, 5th floor, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 21st century, more and more people will live lives across borders and belong to several communities at the same time. But while people live transnationally, they continue to be served by education, legal, health care, and pension systems that are stubbornly nationally bounded. In this session, we’ll explore if and how institutions are responding to this new reality and creating a new social safety net.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peggy Levitt is a Professor of Sociology at Wellesley College and a Research Fellow at The Weatherhead Center for International Affairs and The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University, where she co-directs The Transnational Studies Initiative. She was the Willie Brandt Guest Professor at the University of Malmö in Spring 2009, a visiting lecturer at the University of Limerick in Fall 2008, and a visiting professor at the University of Bologna during the summer of 2008. She is currently the Visiting International Fellow in the Dept. of Cultural Anthropology at the Vrije University in Amsterdam. Click here for Professor Levitt’s bio and publications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah van Walsum is a Professor in Migration Law and Family Ties at the Vrije University in Amsterdam. For Professor van Walsum’s full cv and publications, click here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frontline with Faculty Series is a venue for Harvard faculty affiliated with the Hauser Center to share their work and research with faculty colleagues, as well as students in an informal setting that will allow for spirited discussion, debate and exchange. The seminars link faculty experts from Harvard Schools and beyond on a wide range of topics.  The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University seeks to expand understanding and accelerate critical thinking about civil society among scholars, practitioners, policy makers and the general public, by encouraging scholarship, developing curriculum, fostering mutual learning between academics and practitioners, and shaping policies that enhance the sector and its role in society.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362429002000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357590425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A New Social Safety Net?</name><id>98419422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362416400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/98419422/</event_url></item>