<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>95 Conant St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.455685</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-780-9179</phone><name>Karen And TJ's</name><city>Concord</city><id>1440757</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401711</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Living Among Meat Eaters: The Vegetarian's Survival Handbook by Carol J. Adams&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are one of the over twenty million Americans who have adopted vegetarianism, you know that living with and eating with meat eaters can present a myriad of difficult issues. Summer barbecues, Thanksgiving dinner, or even a simple business lunch can be cause for discussions questioning vegetarianism as a lifestyle choice&amp;mdash;leading at best to awkward situations, and at worst to anger and defensiveness. Beyond these often tense encounters, simple day-to-day tasks like grocery shopping and preparing the evening meal can be tough, especially when your husband, wife, partner, or child doesn&amp;rsquo;t share your commitment to living as a vegetarian. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In this bold and original book, Carol J. Adams offers real-life advice that vegetarians can use to defuse any situation where their dietary choices may be under attack and suggests viewing meat eaters as blocked vegetarians. Always insightful, this practical guide is full of self-tests, strategies, meditations on vegetarianism, and tips for dining out and entertaining at home when meat eaters are on the invite list. Offering more than fifty of Carol Adams&amp;rsquo;s favorite vegetarian recipes, Living Among Meat Eaters is sure to become every vegetarian&amp;rsquo;s most trusted source of support and information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328012172000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323050884000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club Discussion: "Living Among Meat Eaters" by Carol J. Adams</name><id>43392232</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327780800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/43392232/</event_url></item>