<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Joint Event with &amp;quot;Seeking the Joy of Organized Living&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Girls Just Want To Have Fun&amp;quot;.  We will meet at the Panera Bread in Brookline on Harvard Street.  They have given us the front patio on the left on Wednesdays at 7pm. They will even turn the heat up to make us more comfortable. This is great meeting place for people with or without cars. Hopefully, we can get a good sized crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come have dinner and share ideas about how to clutter less, organize your surroundings. This will allow you to be more productive in your life.  Optional: Bring a journal with ideas about what you would like to put in your home (sanctuary). What do you need to get rid of?  You can work on it while you are at the meetup. I will have books available that I borrowed from my library. Hopefully, they will be helpful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***If you RSVP as a maybe and cannot make it, please change your RSVP to a no one day before the event by 7pm.*** &lt;br /&gt;_____________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Creating a Sanctuary&lt;/u&gt; by Andrew Weil&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Your home - whether big, small, or somewhere in between - should be your sanctuary, a place where stress is left at the door and your soul is nurtured. For a more comforting environment, gradually implement the following changes into your home:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Bring the outdoors in. Cut flowers and blooming bulbs, or pieces of wood, rocks and other natural elements can create a feeling of nature indoors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Bring green plants into your home, especially varieties that filter indoor pollutants. According to the Foliage for Clean Air Council, these include Gerbera daisies, Boston ferns, English ivy, chrysanthemums, Areca palms, spider plants and golden pothos. The Council recommends having two plants for every 100 square feet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Paint a room to correlate with how you want to feel while in that room. For instance, blue and green promote a relaxed feeling and may be good for the bedroom. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Surround your senses with beauty. Artwork, fragrance, smooth textures and calming sounds all provide a pleasant environment in which to relax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Set aside a room or area for peace and calm. A place for spiritual reflection and meditation can provide shelter from noise and distraction. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Clean out the clutter. A low-maintenance home is refreshing after a day of hectic meetings, errands and chores. Fewer items can mean less frustration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Create an atmosphere of love. Display handmade or meaningful gifts from loved ones and photos of family and friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Allow natural light to flow into your home. To take advantage of the sun's cycle without heating up your home, hang linen curtains (organic cotton, if possible) on windows that face north or south. If you have a nice garden or view from a window or two, keep those windows uncovered as much as possible when you are home. Read a book instead of watching television, or listen to music. If you desire or enjoy background noise, consider installing a small fountain to provide a soothing hum.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As you walk into Panera, we will be on the patio on the left side. This section will be open only to people from our event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1265415255000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264786661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joint Event:: Organizing Tips For Your Home in 2010  -  "Creating A Sanctuary"</name><id>12459710</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265241600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/12459710/</event_url></item>