<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Seaport Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.349520</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>SeaPort World Trade Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>383112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.040596</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Don't miss the networking event of the year! After a cocktail reception on the exhibit floor, the annual BSA/Build Boston Gala and Design Celebration begins with a visual presentation and exhibition of award-winning designs from the past year and features a buffet, DJ, and cash bar. Don't miss this opportunity to celebrate with hundreds of your building industry colleagues. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The BSA is offering special discounted tickets to the Build Boston Gala and Design Celebration for young professionals. Tickets will be $20 instead of $95! There is a special focus on young architects this year, so I hope you will all come. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, this opportunity turns into a pumpkin if you do not register by Thursday November 8th! (I will turn off the RSVP function on this site on November 8th at 5PM)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to go, an RSVP on this site is not enough (although helpful so others can see who to look for when they arrive.) You will need to contact the BSA or come by in person to preregister.  bsa@architects.org or 617-951-1433, ext. 221.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the Design Gallery by the (cash) bar at 6:00 pm. (The Design Gallery is in the back right corner of the tradeshow floor.) We will leave at 6:30 pm to go over to the Gala together. Please be in the gallery before 6:45 or you may not find us in the crowd of 5-600 people! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gala has great food and and a cash bar and it's not as fancy as the &amp;quot;gala&amp;quot; name might infer. Just come as you are after work!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**********************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BSA/Build Boston Gala and Design Celebration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The annual BSA/Build Boston Gala and Design Celebration is a unique celebration of the building industry, of award-winning design, of young designers?and of Build Boston?s 23rd anniversary. This year?s Gala includes a special focus on young architects and the diversity of our industry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the annual networking event in the industry, it all begins with a cocktail party on the Build Boston exhibit floor and moves into a custom-designed setting that includes an installation of interactive art. Spectacular views of the city and the harbor outside are complemented by exhibits of award-winning designs inside as you enjoy a fabulous buffet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don?t miss this opportunity to celebrate with hundreds of your building industry colleagues. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reminder for architects: receptions and other social events such as this, while delightful networking opportunities, cannot offer AIA continuing-education credits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you register for the Gala, you will automatically be registered to visit the exhibit hall any day of the show. Exhibit hall hours are noon -7:00 pm daily. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: except for this special Gala promotion for young professionals, the BSA does not process Build Boston registrations.  If you would like to sign up for other Build Boston events or workshops, please go to www.buildboston.com.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196358122000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193348839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Invitation to BSA's Build Boston Gala and Design Celebration </name><id>6617131</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195167600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/6617131/</event_url></item>