<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Poole Road</address_1><state>Ne</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.845467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monadnock State Park</name><city>Jaffrey</city><id>10863012</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.088676</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The New Hampshire Division of Parks and Recreation in partnership with the Society for the Protection of New Hampshire Forests and Eastern Mountain Sports, will sponsor a free, guided hikes at Monadnock State Park on New Year’s Day as part of America’s State Parks, First Day Hikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Society for the Protection of New Hampshire Forests Land Stewards, Mt. Monadnock Volunteers, and Parker Trail adopters John and Lise Bigl as they host the First Day Hike of Mt. Monadnock's Parker Trail, an approximately 3 mile RT including Little Mountain which has a wonderful Eastern view of the Wapack Range from Mt. Watatic to North Pack Monadnock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Parker Trail is an easy East to West hike connecting the Monadnock State Park HQ to the Old Toll Rd. THIS IS NOT A SUMMIT HIKE. It's what you could call a nice 3 mile RT walk in the woods with a couple very very brief steep sections. The total elevation gain is about 400 feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/whats-happening/first-day-hike/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.nhstateparks.org/whats-happening/first-day-hike/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John &amp; Lise</member_name><member_id>42966142</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357063236000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356645310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Day Hike at Mt. Monadnock State Park</name><id>96726592</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357052400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/96726592/</event_url></item>