<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Pinkham Notch, NH</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.400000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wildcat</name><city>Gorham</city><id>465446</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190000</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person per night</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come and join the Wedeln Race Team at our first race of the season.  Since we want you to come cheer us on you'll have access to the same race day lift ticket rates we get $35.  This is only available as a guest of Wedeln, so you must stay at the house Friday night to get the ticket.  Mostly because, darn it, we've got to be at the mountain by 8am so it will easier to get you hooked up if you're leaving the house with us and we know what you look like!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sorry for the late notice but if you're interested in this you must E-MAIL ME by WEDNESDAY AT MIDNIGHT.   pottebaum.tara@gmail.com.&lt;/b&gt;  Include your full name, your actual e-mail address and a phone number and someone will get back to you on how to get to the house.  Please note the house is $20 for the night and its dorm/hostel style accommodations - i.e. bring your own twin bed bunkbed type sheets, blankets, pillow etc.  (simpler - sleeping bag!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in staying Saturday night sister houses are hosting social events that involve ice breakers to encourage mingling.  One social involves tricking people into saying &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; and the other is a graffiti party where you write on others shirts.  If interested in the socials, do bring a t-shirt you're ok with being written on by multi-colored pens.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can come make it!  Its my first race, plan on commiserating with me at the bar afterward!  =)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tara&lt;br /&gt;pottebaum.tara@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4353463</member_name><member_id>4353463</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>4521773</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>5121941</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Audra</member_name><member_id>5480374</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Hey you know you're itching for an excuse to get out and ski or ride this season on all that snow you've been hearing about up in the white mountains!  The snow just keeps on falling!  Good company and a discount lift ticket are a bonus!</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199311059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ski Wildcat with the Wedeln Race Team - ($35 lift tickets!)</name><id>7015441</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199538000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7015441/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/e/global_2109326.jpeg</photo_url></item>