<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Thu Jun 4&lt;br /&gt; Black-eyed &amp;amp; Bluesfest 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in Bushnell Park for our 10th Year Anniversary Festival. This year will be chock full of great music, brews and BBQ. Line up is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;Hartford Advocate Black-eyed &amp;amp; Blues&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, June 4th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;5 PM-11 PM&lt;br /&gt;Bushnell Park Pavilion&lt;br /&gt;Downtown Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;Admission Absolutely Free!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bluelights (5:00-6:00 PM)&lt;br /&gt;They are like “Roots Music in Overdrive.” They draw on a wide variety of traditional music to create a new style infused with the energy of the rock ‘n’ roll music of our generation.&lt;br /&gt;Eran Troy Danner (6:15-7:15 PM)&lt;br /&gt;This band is a stripped down, no frills, back to the basics Blues band that has won the acclaim and admiration of true Blues fans everywhere. This red hot trio performs straight forward honest Blues and has opened up for Blues legend BB King, Lucky Peterson, Eddie Turner, Eddie Kirkland, and Blues Traveler.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alexis P. Suter (7:30-8:30 PM)&lt;br /&gt;Alexis P. Suter has a big voice and knows how to use it. Whether singing about spiritual ecstasy or earthly troubles Alexis makes every song she performs her own. Suter and her top-notch band regularly open Levon Helm’s Midnight Rambles, twice-monthly house parties at Helm’s home and studio in Woodstock NY. That is also where all the tracks on her latest album were recorded last year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Christine Ohlman &amp;amp; Rebel Montez (8:45-9:45 PM)&lt;br /&gt;This beehive knows how to rock, from NBC’s SNL to many festivals around the world, Christine really touches her audience. She just keeps lighting up clubs with her hot guitar and eclectic live shows. Be prepared for a night of big time music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bronze Radio Return (10:00-11:00 PM)&lt;br /&gt;Brandishing a soulful, bluesy and highly engaging brand of rock, this hard-working Hartford quintet has been making a lot of noise outside of the Nutmeg state, with tour dates currently on the books from upstate New York all the way down to Virginia.&lt;br /&gt;The music will make you dance, sing along and feel good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Ages - No Coolers - No Food - No Dogs - Line-up subject to change&lt;br /&gt;Factory sealed water bottles allowed.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>21</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244322351000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242697898000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blackeyed Blues Fest</name><id>10442533</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244149200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/10442533/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>