<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Another in a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines! Hikes will be taken at a slower pace, with plenty of rest stops along the way!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a loop hike up over Mount Grace and Little Grace. In order to make the loop complete, the final 0.7 mile is a road walk. &lt;br /&gt;              &lt;br /&gt;Distance:    4.6 miles  &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain:  1200 feet (cumulative)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description and trail map: &lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/GraceMA080516.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Grace State Forest encompasses close to 1,700 acres of woodlands in Warwick, Massachusetts.  The park is split into three sections by Northfield Road and Route 78 with the largest and most popular section in the middle which includes the 1,617-foot Mount Grace and the 1,226-foot Little Grace. From the fire tower atop of Grace's summit, are fantastic views of the surrounding hills, forests, and distant mountains. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mountain and forest take their name from a Colonial era incident. During a skirmish against the Wompanoag Indians in 1676, Mary Rowlandson of Lancaster (a town 40 miles to the east) was captured, along with her infant daughter Grace. On a march toward Canada the baby died and was buried at the foot of the mountain that now bears her name.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for an uphill walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket, a hat) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;The main entrance for Mount Grace State Forest is on Route 78 in Warwick, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * From Rt. 2 (east or west), get on Rt. 2A East (exit 13) in Erving and follow it for about 2 miles.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn left onto Rt. 78 North and follow it for 6.9 miles.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn left into a large parking lot, shortly after a brown &amp;quot;state forest&amp;quot; road sign, a three-car brown garage, and a brown (former) administration building, all on the left side.&lt;br /&gt;    * There is a large &amp;quot;Ohlson Field&amp;quot; sign in the parking lot but it is not readily visible from the road, especially since there could be cars parked in front of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Conservation Trust Fund has set up a colorful donation can between the parking lot and the administration building. Any contributions received are used for the improvement of Mount Grace State Forest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Rain cancels! I will keep an eye on the weather!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be camping at Tully Lake in Royalston this weekend.  There may be sites available if you'd like to join me! &lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/places-to-stay/tully-lake-campground/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is cross-posted with &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/New_England_Over_40_Hiking_Group"&gt;New England Over 40 Hiking Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there by 10:45.  I have a bright orange backpack, a blue-green Corolla and a big smile.  774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286752920000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286148370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It hike to Mt Grace &amp; LIttle Grace</name><id>14987883</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286636400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14987883/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>