<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>252 Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9716</phone><name>Tech Superpowers Digital Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>824604</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing our fifth Creative Show &amp;amp; Tell for 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for our monthly Meet, Greet,  Show &amp;amp; Tell, bring your work, or photos of your work to share with the group and get useful feedback on from other creative peoples! Perhaps you have an idea for something new or want to revive and old creative hobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry if don't have anything to show, just bring your creative mind and meet others like your self. If nothing else these are great networking events. You are sure to leave with more than you came in with. :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a special version of our Show &amp;amp; Tell as we will be meeting in the Tech Superpowers Digital Lounge, we're talking Macs and lots of them. This is your opportunity to show off your digital bling, be it on the web, on a CD, or thumb drive. All you non-digital artists are welcome too, just like our other events, no matter if it's a quilt, a sculpture or a bonsai I'm sure we will all dig it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What people are saying about this monthly event..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ I Finale made it to a Meetup! Everyone is is friendly and some had brought their work to share, which was great and isn't required. A fun group, I can see this group getting bigger soon! ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“  Great group of people. I especially enjoyed viewing everyone's work. ” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ These just keep getting better, I just wish there was time to talk to everybody. Every one of these events has included some of the most interesting creative minds I have ever met. I leave feeling light, yet challenged to reinvigorate my own creative soul and share that bounty when next we meet.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“  Always fun to look and talk about everyone's work that they bring.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ A wonderful group of people - this was my first time at a meetup - and great to compare notes on various artistic endeavors. The event was well-organized. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Wonderful time, everyone was really connecting and showing their work. These just keep getting better and better - can't wait for the next one! ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ It was great to meet everyone and see what we're all working on. Harvard Square is a convenient location, but while I like Finale, it was surprisingly loud. Maybe we should look into another location, so it's easier to hear each other, or go earlier in the day, so we're not dealing with the Saturday night rush?  ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ Great group of people! I made some great contacts! ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will run with a minimum of 4 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. If this is your first event I will be collecting the $5 annual dues at this event if you have not paid already.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have the place to ourselves!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1240853076000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238870998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Creative Meet, Greet, Show and Tell #2</name><id>10114816</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240174800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/10114816/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/6/global_7969942.jpeg</photo_url></item>