<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come share decluttering Victories AND Motivational Lessons to help us ALL refocus more this autumn to include clearing and organizing our homes, cars - ALL our living spaces - and ultimately our lives, in time for the holidays ... for EXTRA-satisfying end-of-year celebrations!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you started excavating your Stuff to discover hidden Treasures - financial and/or sentimental gems, as well as the glorious spaciousness - breathing room - of freed-up space?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OR have you discovered the dreaded black mold colonizing walls that had been hidden by Stuff ... and perhaps been startled to discover, amidst dust kittens, various creepy-crawlies inhabiting piles of stuff ... perhaps brown recluse spiders ... or tiny (or sizable?) furry pests?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When considered objectively/spiritually/philosophically, it can actually ALL be Good - offering us the Gift of Motivation to make needed changes in our lives ... as one prayer I love implores:  &amp;quot;Lord, help me to &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; waste this suffering!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggestions for an alternate venue are welcomed ... some free meeting spot or quiet restaurant in a convenient location accessible by public transport would be ideal. Bertucci's at Alewife is one option, for example, facilitating access by public transport as well as by car, for people coming from either within the city or outside it -- your thoughts on such?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO -- a successor is welcomed to head up this group as organizer, going forward.  Everyone has had this past summer to think about this.  Please notify me if you have an interest.  Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 7:30 pm - Socializing (feel free to bring goodies if you want some!). I might bring a digital camera to post a photo of the meeting on our Meetup web site IF participants grant permission (please notify me of any privacy concerns).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 ~ 8:30 pm - Discussion&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~8:30 - 9:00 pm - As time permits: Group problem-solving, buddying up for accountability, consideration of this Meetup's SUCCESSION, future meeting topics and schedule, venue (e.g., Bertucci's at Alewife?  or resume at Panera Bread at Coolidge Corner in Brookline? The Democracy Center near Harvard Square?), candidate presenters, organization (including assistant organizers), activities, resources ... how best to help YOU?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On-street metered parking is available near the church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public transportation: Bus #69 (from Harvard Square, or ~15-minute walk from there) and Bus #83 (from Central Square, or ~15-minute walk from there) pass through Inman Square, Cambridge, where FUPC (our current venue) is located.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup signs will be on table(s).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298596172000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284735003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOTIVATIONS:  Health and Wealth Aspects of Clutter</name><id>14803168</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285628400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/14803168/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/8/global_3017160.jpeg</photo_url></item>