<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NH RUG Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wiki.nhruby.org/index.php/Upcoming_meetings" target="_blank"&gt;http://wiki.nhruby.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Our next meeting will be held on Tuesday, October 21, 2008, from 7-9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: It will be held at the offices of RMC Research in Portsmouth, NH. View map of 1000 Market Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT: Nick Plante will be talking about the Rails Plugin system. Abstract: The Rails plugin system allows you to add powerful features to your applications by altering or enhancing key pieces of the framework. Plugins tend to be easy to use and can save precious development cycles, freeing you to focus on the elements that make your project truly unique. Although plug-ins are often dead simple to use, authoring them is not always quite as straightforward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation will give developers an overview of the Rails plugin architecture and the hooks that are provided for creating your own. We'll take a look at the genesis of a typical plugin, and see how we can extract and generalize our code, repackaging it in a modular way such that it can be reused across projects and redistributed within the Rails community. Along the way, we'll also learn a thing or two about Ruby metaprogramming practices, and examine strategies for testing and redistributing plugin code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Turnbull will also be giving an introduction to RESTful web services as a follow-up to his HTTP talk last month. REpresentational State Transfer is the theoretical underpinnings of HTTP/1.1. This talk will explain what REST is, present examples of existing web services using REST, and also covers the practical application of REST and the Atom Publishing Protocol in creating a web service.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there?</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228258020000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221610241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast NH Ruby and Rails October Meetup</name><id>8771934</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224630000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/8771934/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>