<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hola Amigos:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's Salsa at Habana Club in Cambridge!&lt;/b&gt; The perfect place to take some Salsa classes, meet new people, practice our Spanish, and party all night long. &lt;b&gt;From 9pm-10:00pm is the Salsa lesson&lt;/b&gt;, followed by dancing with everyone else for the rest of the evening.  All levels of Spanish are welcomed!  You can read more about this venue &lt;a href="http://havanaclubsalsa.com/salsa_saturdays.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Come ready to rotate and talk to as many people as you can.&lt;/b&gt; We are all friendly and eager to get to know you. This is a very informal gathering. It will provide all of us with the opportunity to practice speaking Spanish in a real setting and get somewhat more acquainted to the Latino culture. Remember our objective is having fun while we are speaking Spanish &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an event sponsored by &lt;a href="http://www.spanishblackbelt.com" target="_blank"&gt;SpanishBlackBelt.&lt;/a&gt; No meetup fee will be charged but there is a $12 cover charge at the door for the dance club fee/Salsa lesson&lt;/b&gt;--the lesson is a little fast-paced but informative, the students rotate dance-partners throughout (great for getting to meet new people), and the lesson is taught by very nice instructors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP if you are planning on coming. Hasta muy pronto !!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If instead, or in addition, you want to attend one of our &lt;b&gt;regular Spanish classes&lt;/b&gt;, please &lt;a href="http://adults.spanishblackbelt.com/spanishtraining/checkout/searchcolor.asp?area=Boston%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to access all Small Group sessions currently being offered by Spanish Black Belt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup badge and a big smile!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Guilianna</member_name><member_id>10674481</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540090000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Fanáticos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Spanish-Boston</urlname><id>1542675</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston's Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273073112000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Add some Salsa to your Spanish this coming Saturday!</name><id>13392869</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273366800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Spanish-Boston/events/13392869/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/0/global_14849856.jpeg</photo_url></item>