<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt. Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.371338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-699-1221 </phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>363595</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116469</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;FYI: This is not a GWH event, I am posting it in case people are interested in attending.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are You Good Without God?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Chaplain on His Best Selling Book&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Are you good without God? Millions of Americans are,” has recently appeared on Boston’s MBTA, the New York City subway, and on billboards across the country, stirring up passionate discussion about atheism and Humanism in America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week, Harvard's Humanist Chaplain Greg Epstein, the person perhaps most responsible for catalyzing this conversation, will be discussing his work and his new best selling book Good Without God at Harvard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good Without God, released in tandem with the launch of new branches of the United Coalition of Reason, a national organization that works to raise the visibility of local atheist and non-theist groups, recently appeared on the New York Times Best Sellers list, and has been the recipient of nationwide media coverage, including ABC World News with Diane Sawyer, Good Morning America and Fresh Air with Terry Gross, since its release in October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Good Without God is not just a brilliant book title but an indispensable and humane ideal,” said Harvard Professor Steven Pinker, author of The Language Instinct and How the Mind Works. “Greg Epstein’s wise and warm explanation of the Humanist worldview goes beyond the recent atheist bestsellers and speaks to the moral and spiritual impulses that have traditionally attracted people to religion.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Epstein’s book, now in its fourth printing, has been a resource for the vibrant and growing Humanist community at Harvard, but it has also begun a nationwide conversation about Humanism, cultivating what Boston University professor Stephen Prothero calls “religious literacy” about the nonreligious. Good Without God stresses interfaith dialogue and pluralism as important to Humanism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“In Good Without God, Greg Epstein shows us what it means to cross boundaries, build bridges, and work toward a society where people from all backgrounds live in equal dignity and mutual loyalty,&amp;quot;&amp;#8232; said White House advisor on religion Eboo Patel. Patel, who was recently named by US News &amp;amp; World Report as one of America’s top leaders, serves as the founder and director of the Interfaith Youth Core.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After an extensive book tour of more than 16 cities in two months, Epstein has returned to Cambridge and to Harvard. On Thursday, February 18, the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard will host an evening where Epstein will discuss his book, his experiences as one of the only Humanist chaplains in the country, and what Humanism can mean at Harvard and beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public. Light refreshments will be served. Students and members of the broader Harvard community who have considered getting involved are particularly encouraged to attend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will not be attending.  This is a Harvard Humanist event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266707317000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266424164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greg Epstein discusses his book, "Good Without God"</name><id>12628091</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266534000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/12628091/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/2/global_7423922.jpeg</photo_url></item>