<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to do the Hancock&amp;rsquo;s (North and South) on Saturday, July 16th, beginning at eight a.m... Both Hancock&amp;rsquo;s are 4,000 footers. This will be a moderate to fast paced hike - We will take the Hancock Notch Trail to the Cedar Brook Trail to the Hancock Loop trail - total mileage (round trip) is 9.8 miles and about 6 hours and 15 minutes. Because of the distance and elevation involved please ensure that you have been hiking similar mountains recently. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ Be prepared for cool temps, rain and potentially poor weather conditions, one never knows in the Whites. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is dangerous especially in cool/wet weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. Answers to FAQs &amp;bull; This is NOT a traverse, so we WILL NOT have to car pool. &amp;bull; We will meet in the lot for the HANCOCK NOTCH TRAIL HEAD, located near the hairpin turn in the Kancamagus Highway. &amp;bull; Sunset on this day will be approximately at 8:30 pm. &amp;bull; Headlamps are not required for this hike, but strongly suggested as a safety precaution. Always be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary. &amp;bull; Bring plenty of water &amp;bull; This terrain for this hike could be wet and we will possibly encounter some muddy conditions, so you might want to bring a change of socks and dry shoes for the ride home. &amp;bull; This hike is not very exposed. &amp;bull; We will NOT pass a shelter or an AMC hut. &amp;bull; We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. I require that hikers in my group wait at trail junctions and at summits to allow the group to make decisions and reset their pace along the way. &amp;bull; I do keep a steady pace. &amp;bull; If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day. I want you to be around for another day too. &amp;bull; I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the last couple of days leading up to the hike. Most of the payoff comes in the form of fabulous views and enjoying the outdoors so, if the weather looks like it will be miserable or dangerous, we might reschedule. Please plan accordingly. I like to be prompt and will NOT wait for you at the trailhead if you are not on time and do not call me. My cell phone is 603-986-0473 Book time is about 6 hrs. 15 min &amp;amp; 9.8 miles Hancock Notch Trail to Cedar Brook Trail 1.8 miles, 1 hour 5 minutes, 400 feet. Cedar Brook Trail to Hancock Loop Trail .7 miles, 25 minutes, 200 feet Hancock Loop Trail Total Time/Mileage: 9.8 miles, 6 hours, 15 minutes ------ THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (OR CHANGE YOUR RSVP TO NO). PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT. I will be in a Chocolate Colored Chevrolet Equinox with kayak rack on top.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310822304000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310053471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hancocks</name><id>24895301</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310817600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/24895301/</event_url></item>