<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 North Lowell Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.805862</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Windham Senior Citizens</name><city>Windham</city><id>11396382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.298988</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;FEBRUARY 12 SCREENING OF “CRYING WOLF” in WINDAM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you know that the EPA believes that water can be classified as a pollutant? And as a result, right now in Virginia, there are people who are in jeopardy of having their homes taken away and torn down so grass can be planted to help manage the rainfall around a small stream outside of Washington DC. For news story, see – &lt;a href="http://video.foxnews.com/v/2026594092001/epa-illegally-regulating-water-as-a-pollutant/" class="linkified"&gt;http://video.foxnews.com/v/2026594092001/epa-illegally-regulating-water-as-a-pollutant/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No one is against preserving and protecting our natural resources. Conservation is an important consideration for current and future generations, but the environmental movement has been co-opted by radical ideologists who seek to impose their political agendas on Americans, under the guise of protecting the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On February 12th, the Southern NH 9.12 Project will host a free viewing of the award winning documentary “Crying Wolf”. This one hour movie provides a new insight into environmental extremist regulations that are being imposed on us by unelected bureaucrats – and how those regulations drastically reduce our fundamental liberties and freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie will be shown at 7:00 PM on Tuesday, February, 12th at the Windham Senior Center, 2 North Lowell Road, Windham. This event is free and open to the public, and people of all ages are encouraged to attend.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360724831000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359322388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Crying Wolf" Screening</name><id>101662252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360713600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/101662252/</event_url></item>