<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>270 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349902</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hollis Street Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>1356182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065245</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the annual Big Foot walking tour 5-hour Labor Day event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, travel back in time and walk in the footsteps of colonial Bostonians as we trace the original shoreline of the Shawmut peninsula. As early as 1641, Boston began to reshape itself by filling in coves and tidal flats along the harbor. The process continued over three centuries such that today's downtown Boston is double in size.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The earliest surviving map of Boston was drawn by Captain John Bonner in 1722. Starting from the Neck, we will push modern Boston aside and walk through 18th century by tracing the outline of the Bonner Map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through the original South End, along a bustling colonial waterfront, and around the trimount, explore the geography of colonial Boston and its notable buildings, wharves, bridges, and mills. Come experience the culture and learn of the politics, economy, and beliefs of early Americans in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put on your tricorne hat and visit a time when steeples defined the Boston skyline, animals grazed the pastures near South Station, the Back Bay was wet, and few wanted to live on Beacon Hill. From the malt shop of Samuel Adams to the swimming hole of a young Ben Franklin, take in the sights of the ships, the smells the rope walks and the tastes of oysters and chocolate along the causeway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Big Foot tour is offered only once annually and features a different theme designed and researched by the guides each year. Get out this Labor Day and see what makes Boston By Foot tours so unique.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost is $20/person or $5/Card-carrying Boston By Foot members.  FMI on becoming a BBF member, please visit the website at www.bostonbyfoot.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the &lt;b&gt;Hollis Street Plaza next to the Wang Theatre&lt;/b&gt; (270 Tremont Street) at &lt;b&gt;9.45am&lt;/b&gt; to be assigned to a guide. If our group exceeds the number they have pre-determined for each group, we may be separated, but there should be plenty of Nerds to mingle with whatever group you end up in.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Megan</member_name><member_id>10021028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>25</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283956954000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282662185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BBF BIG FOOT Tour - Walking the Edge: Tracing Boston's Colonial Shoreline</name><id>14524422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283780700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14524422/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/b/global_5310283.jpeg</photo_url></item>