<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>494 Elm St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.985120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Murphy's Taproom</name><city>Manchester</city><id>412273</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Started in the spring of 2007 by two Free State Project members, Taproom Tuesday gained national attention during Ron Paul's New Hampshire campaign as the place where Ron Paul supporters and freedom lovers of all stripes gather to meet, greet and socialize. It's still happening every Tuesday, and you're invited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet the activists who are hard at work for liberty here in New Hampshire. After a hard day of testifying at the State House, there's no better place to unwind than among a crowd of people who get liberty and are willing to work for it. In the same room you'll find people who are working to cut taxes, preserve privacy, protect gun rights, and legalize drugs -- and they may be the same person!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taproom Tuesday has no formal agenda, but on any given Tuesday you may find a group of people planning something specific which you can plug into and get involved. You've heard it said that, win or lose, the Ron Paul Revolution isn't over with the presidential campaign. We're proving it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People regularly come to Taproom Tuesday in Manchester from the Seacoast, Keene, and even Grafton and Hanover. You'll find that you really aren't alone, and you'll learn how we're already making a difference. Join us and stay for as long as your schedule permits.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We usually have nearly half the restaurant filled on the left side near the fireplace. If the parking lot is full, you can park at the car audio shop next door, as long as there is no event at the Verizon Arena.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205445877000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203535445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taproom Tuesday</name><id>7372170</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205272800000</time><rsvp_limit>125</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/7372170/</event_url></item>