<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Celebrated in pre-WWII France for her bestselling fiction, the Jewish Russian-born Némirovsky was shipped to Auschwitz in the summer of 1942, months after this long-lost masterwork was composed. Némirovsky, a convert to Catholicism, began a planned five-novel cycle as Nazi forces overran northern France in 1940. This gripping &amp;quot;suite,&amp;quot; collecting the first two unpolished but wondrously literary sections of a work cut short, have surfaced more than six decades after her death. The first, &amp;quot;Storm in June,&amp;quot; chronicles the connecting lives of a disparate clutch of Parisians, among them a snobbish author, a venal banker, a noble priest shepherding churlish orphans, a foppish aesthete and a loving lower-class couple, all fleeing city comforts for the chaotic countryside, mere hours ahead of the advancing Germans. The second, &amp;quot;Dolce,&amp;quot; set in 1941 in a farming village under German occupation, tells how peasant farmers, their pretty daughters and petit bourgeois collaborationists coexisted with their Nazi rulers. In a workbook entry penned just weeks before her arrest, Némirovsky noted that her goal was to describe &amp;quot;daily life, the emotional life and especially the comedy it provides.&amp;quot; And it does just that, by focusing—with compassion and clarity—on individual human dramas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This is possibly the most devastating indictment of French manners and morals since &lt;i&gt;Madame Bovary&lt;/i&gt;, as hypnotic as Proust at the biscuit tin, as grueling as Genet on the prowl. Irene Némirovsky is, on this evidence, a novelist of the very first order, perceptive to a fault and sly in her emotional restraint.&amp;quot; —&lt;i&gt;Evening Standard(London)&lt;/i&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There is nothing sentimental or tragic here; reality is what she's after.... In light of what happened to Némirovsky, her vision is remarkable.&amp;quot; —&lt;i&gt;The New York Times&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283214420000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280276303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Némirovsky: Suite Française</name><id>14235065</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283119200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/14235065/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/a/7/global_5819031.jpeg</photo_url></item>