<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb is going to be leading a very meaningful workshop about Spiritual Enlightenment.  Here is a description of the workshop from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“There is great suffering in having desire and not getting what you want. The average human being deals with loss, rejection, painful feelings and disappointment, as well as the good feelings and getting what you want. What goes up must come down though. Enlightenment and letting go of ego helps you accept everything ‘as it is‘, and keeps you in a state of ease and joy no matter what is happening. Herb will go into this in depth and talk about his gradual process of being more free of suffering. Don't miss this unique opportunity to feel happier in your life.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264378068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260339909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Letting Go of the Ego - Spiritual Enlightenment - 10 Steps to Freedom </name><id>12050362</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264204800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/12050362/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/5/global_7649237.jpeg</photo_url></item>