<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374401</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-903-7371</phone><name>Private Location #2</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>832579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121895</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you get nervous about approaching someone new and starting a conversation with them?  Do you wish you knew how to approach people that you're attracted to, and talk to them in a way that will make them interested in getting to know you?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you answered yes to either of those questions, then you're going to love this month's workshop.  You'll learn simple, proven conversation starters that are non-threatening, and practically rejection proof.  Once you master this simple skill, you'll have the confidence to approach people in any situation, and you will know what to say to get them talking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Imagine being at a Meetup event and gliding around the room talking with anyone and everyone.  You'll surprise yourself with how easy and effortless it is to strike up conversations with total strangers and get to know them.  Once you have this skill, you'll be able to make friends and attract lovers anywhere you go, anytime you want.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 simple, proven conversation starters you can use in almost any situation (including one that works REALLY well in places like coffee shops and malls, and another one that works almost 100% of the time at parties and social gatherings).&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What to actually talk about after you start the conversation (and which topics people find interesting). &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How you can quickly become confident at meeting new people so it's never scary again.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The secret to getting people to open to you, even if you just met them.  Once you understand this, you can build deep friendships &amp;amp; relationships with anyone you want.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Little-known places where people are more friendly and open to being approached.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A proven method for ending a conversation that will leave people feeling good about you. If you've ever wanted to end a conversation with someone, but were worried about offending them or hurting their feelings, then this is perfect for you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 attraction-boosting tips that will make people even more receptive to talking with you (it's easier to meet attractive strangers when you look your best, and these tips will maximize your chances of success).&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;PERSONALITY FEEDBACK&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's just the first part of the workshop.  Then we will go into one of the most popular activities this social skills group has ever done... personality feedback!  It's been many months since we've done this, and people have been asking when we're going to start up again.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;You will have an opportunity to participate in small group evaluations of other members, and you'll also get to experience what it's like to receive both positive encouragement and constructive feedback about how you come across to others.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This is often the most revealing part of the workshop, because it's so personalized.  Some members became away of things they were doing for years that were turning people off, and some learned that they come across much better than they realized (which dramatically boosted their confidence in all social situations).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The meeting is limited to 35 people due to the size limitations of the classroom (we'll be moving around a lot).  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, June 27th available.  The meeting runs from 3:30pm to 6:30pm and is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking. &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for a professional training that includes these skill-building drills + personality feedback.  Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems.  My cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278267145000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277037944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Approach People And Start Conversations + Personality Feedback</name><id>13853868</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277667000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/13853868/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/8/8/global_8242488.jpeg</photo_url></item>