<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Saturday, Jan. 24, 1 p.m. to ??? (I'll be there until at least 8; others may want to stay later.) Come for an hour or two; come for the whole day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AGENDA:&lt;/b&gt; No scheduled activities. Arrive and leave when you want. Work on your own projects at your own pace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom; access to Wi-Fi if you need to use your computer while you're there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $5, regardless of how long you stay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt; Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt; Your own materials and projects to work on (just as you do for the regular Meetup; if you're a newbie, see &amp;quot;What to Bring to a Meetup&amp;quot; in the Files section.) A few basic supplies--scissors, glue, tape, etc. -- are available for loan. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/b&gt; You &lt;u&gt;must&lt;/u&gt; RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. If your plans change, PLEASE switch your RSVP to “no” ASAP. If you RSVP &amp;quot;maybe,&amp;quot; please switch your RSVP to &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; as soon as you possibly can. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If you must cancel less than 24 hours in advance -- or after the Open Studio has started -- PLEASE call the Open Studio host (in this case, Anne). I'll e-mail my phone number to you after you RSVP, along with the Studio address.&lt;b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we need to cancel due to weather or for any other reason, we'll post a message here AND e-mail or call anyone who's RSVP'd as far in advance as possible. Doesn't look like that will be a problem this time, though. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Looking forward to seeing you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Anne</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233422261000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232319910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Open Studio in Holliston, Sat. 1/24, 1 p.m.-? </name><id>9551587</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232820000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/9551587/</event_url></item>