<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>281 Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02466</zip><lat>42.346405</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.244.7455</phone><name>The Silk Road</name><city>Auburndale</city><id>1334999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.246864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join us as we travel to the Silk Road, a destination for fine fabrics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was created by one of our very own meetup members, Gay Appleby Rogers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located just outside of Boston in Auburndale, The Silk Road provides a homely atmosphere for visitors to experience and purchase a fine assortment of beautiful fabrics. It is also a place where you can come to practice your sewing, take sewing lessons from Gay herself, or read up on and discuss the latest fashion and sewing trends from her wide assortment of books and magazines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Silk Road was just recently opened and our meetup will be among the first group of people to visit. This will be a time to network with one another, check out the space, enjoy refreshments, and hear from Gay about the Silk Road. And most importantly, to check out the amazing fabrics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-If you are driving, there is tons of free parking. &lt;br /&gt;-If you are taking public transportation its right off the Worcester Commuter Rail line Auburndale Stop, or you can take the D train on the Greenline and its a short walk from there along Grove Street. &lt;br /&gt;-There is also a bus you can take as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-If you have any questions about directions or anything else, don't be afraid to ask us. You will also find the email and number for the Silk Road on the event page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you soon!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a sign on the door. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley Willett</member_name><member_id>1480973</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jamall Oluokun</member_name><member_id>6487580</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>gay appleby rogers</member_name><member_id>12261401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282170705000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280420234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Silk Road: A Place for fine fabrics. </name><id>14252842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282083300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/14252842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/5/global_16793797.jpeg</photo_url></item>