<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to invite you to a seminar being offered by Father Peter Bowes.  Father Peter is an incredible Teacher, an inspiring musician, the author of several books on the Christian Mystical path, and the co-director of the Order of Christ-Sophia.  Father Peter is one of the few Teachers I have met who speaks from a deep well of personal experience and speaks right to my soul.  Don't miss this chance to discover the true magic of the Christmas experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peace be with you,&lt;br /&gt;Shakur&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Mystical Interpretation of the Christmas Story&lt;br /&gt;If you desire to have a more meaningful Christmas this year, come join Father Peter Bowes and get your season started with an in-depth look at the inner meaning of Christmas, and how we can enter into the experience of a truly spiritual Holy Season. Mystics interpret all the events in the life of Jesus and Mary as not only being literal events, but also symbolizing each step along the spiritual path for those who desire transformation. In the Christmas story, not only do Jesus and Mary symbolize specific aspects of us, so do Joseph, the wise men, the shepherds, the star, the animals in the stable, and the stable itself.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542628000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195345829000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: A Mystical Interpretation of the Christmas Story</name><id>6761248</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196382600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/6761248/</event_url></item>