<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 George P. Hassett Drive </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.418622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-395-0402</phone><name>Springstep</name><city>Medford,</city><id>1119289</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an evening of dance at Dance Caliente, a local Latin &amp;amp; Ballroom dance company based in Medford. All dance levels are welcome, particularly beginner. We went to their last one and it was a lot of fun.&amp;nbsp; At Springstep in Medford, Dance Caliente will be hosting their quarterly dance party, "A Night Out with Dance Caliente!"  Dance Caliente's parties are lovely, low-key, and comfortable events. More like a cafe than a nightclub, their parties feature a wide range of Latin, Swing &amp;amp; Ballroom dance music, short lessons, and complimentary coffee, tea and desserts.  Tickets are usually $15, but we our tickets will be $11 (cash at the door). We will also have some tables set aside for the group.   We will meet inside the event entrance area, if you have trouble finding us, or running late, please call Catherine at 774 232 0000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking nearby. We will probably head to a nearby bar for post dancing drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) upstairs inside event entrance.  Please call 774 232 0000 if you have trouble finding us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305335535000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Enjoy 3 hours of Latin and Ballroom dancing on one of Boston's best dance floors! Complimentary (and oh so delicious) desserts, a group lesson, and impromptu demonstrations round out the evening.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303965835000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening of Dance Lessons and Dance Party, Discounted Tix</name><id>17463790</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305331200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/17463790/</event_url></item>