<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>127 Wall Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yale Law School Levinson Auditorium</name><city>New Haven</city><id>8590252</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928146</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;I was on the North Face site and found this event - looks pretty interesting! I won't be able to attend but I thought I would list it on the site in case you happen to be in the area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;While you can RSVP here and coordinate with other randomites who might be going, you must purchase your ticket using the link provided below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conrad Anker - Return to Meru&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;High-altitude mountaineering demands one skill above all others: the ability to suffer. Mount Everest, which Conrad has climbed three times, is the peak that's always in the media, but more challenging mountains rise in the Himalaya, including India's ice-coated granite fang, Meru. Its East Face had defied climbers for two generations. The saga of Conrad's ascent of Meru's formidable east face, which had defied climbers for two generations, begins with a failed attempt in 2003, followed by a treacherous attempt in 2009, when an epic storm froze feet and forced retreat. Three years later, grit and determination brought Conrad and his team back to complete the climb, which Conrad regards as his most challenging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Here is a link to some more information about this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thenorthface.com/en_US/exploration/expeditions/24-garwhal-himalaya-india/"&gt;http://www.thenorthface.com/en_US/exploration/expeditions/24-garwhal-himalaya-india/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;The Presentation begins at 7:00 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Reserved Seat at Presentation Only = $8.00 per person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;There is a VIP Reception following the Presentation. Post-show VIP reception will be held at &lt;a href="http://www.shoptrailblazer.com/Trailblazer-New-Haven.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Trailblazer&lt;/a&gt; and will benefit &lt;a href="http://www.raggedmtn.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Ragged Mountain Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Ticket to VIP Reception and Presentation = $20.00 per person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Location&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Yale Law School Levinson Auditorium&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;127 Wall Street&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;New Haven, CT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Use the link below to purchase tickets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;a href="http://thenorthface.inticketing.com/events/241541"&gt;http://thenorthface.inticketing.com/events/241541&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Conrad Anker’s specialty, simply put, is climbing the most technically challenging terrain in the world. This quest has taken him from the mountains of Alaska and Antarctica to the big walls of Patagonia and Baffin Island and the massive peaks of the Himalaya.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Conrad’s Antarctic experience spans a decade, with first ascents in three regions. In 1997, Conrad teamed up with Alex Lowe and Jon Krakauer to climb Rakekniven, a 2,500-foot wall in Queen Maud Land. In the Sentinel Range, Conrad climbed the Vinson Massif via three new routes. His climbs in Pakistan’s Karakoram include the west face of Latok II along the “Tsering Mosong” route (which begins at the same height as the summit of Denali) where he climbed 26 pitches on a vertical cliff and then topped out at 23,342 feet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;In 1998, Conrad and Peter Croft made a first ascent of Spansar Peak via a 7,000-foot ridge in one day. In Patagonia, he climbed the three towers of the Cerro Torre Massif. On Yosemite’s El Capitan he joined Steve Gerberding and Kevin Thaw to establish “Continental Drift,” a steep “nail-up” on the right side. And in Zion National Park, Mugs Stump and Conrad first climbed the intimidating “Streaked Wall”.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;In May of 1999, as a member of the Mallory &amp;amp; Irvine Research Expedition, Conrad discovered the body of George Mallory, the preeminent Everest explorer of the 1920s. The disappearance of Mallory and Sandy Irvine on their summit bid in June 1924 is one of climbing’s great mysteries, and Conrad’s discovery and analysis of the find has shed new light on the pioneering climbs of the early expeditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;In October 2011, Conrad, Jimmy Chin and Renan Ozturk summited one of the last great unclimbed features of the Himalayas by topping out on the Shark’s Fin route on the northwest face of 20,700-foot Meru in the Garhwal Himalaya. In the game of high-altitude, big-wall mountaineering, the previously unclimbed route represents one of the world’s ultimate mountaineering tests, with the lower third a classic alpine snow-and-ice route, the middle a mix of ice and rock, and the final section an extremely difficult, overhanging headwall. The Shark’s Fin has drawn many of the world’s top alpinists over the past 30 years, none of them able to finish the route.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Conrad graduated from the University of Utah and lives in Bozeman, Montana, with his wife and three sons. Anker serves on the board of the Conservation Alliance, the Rowell Fund for Tibet and the Alex Lowe Charitable Foundation. “My involvement with these organizations is intrinsically rewarding,” Conrad says “and it’s among the most important work I do. It feels good to be able to give back to our community of humans and to the natural world.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350580360000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344308712000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conrad Anker - Return to Meru (Educational Series)</name><id>76659462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350514800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/76659462/</event_url></item>