<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>corner of Sargent Ave and Manchester St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.771756</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Volleyball area</name><city>Nashua</city><id>984819</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Wimp Volleyball &lt;br /&gt;

Open to Teens and adults,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No dogs please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, Mar. 18th., 3:00.pm., or anytime before to 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the corner of Sargent Ave and Manchester St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nashua NH. 03061&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OPEN to ADULTS &amp;amp; TEENS. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Host: Steve Obermiller&amp;nbsp; ob@tds.net&amp;nbsp; 603-491-1962 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

IF IT RAINS SNOWS, OR IS WET? THIS EVENT IS CANCELED. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/9/6/event_4002902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; They say it will be in the 60s &amp;amp; 70s on Sunday. So please, join Steve O. and friends at anytime for late afternoon of fun and easy exercise, or just come to watch. Wimp Volleyball is a noncompetitive games. Totally for the fun of moving around trying to hit and return the ball. We will be following the rules. But, having fun, getting some exercise, and learning will be more important than winning. In these games, we work on trying to keep the volley going. Rather than trying to end the volley. We do not count the score. We count the laughs. The winners are those who sides hurt from laughing to much. We usually have a larger number attending. So, we will rotate everyone through. If we have enough of those people who must win to play, and follow exactly to the rules. We will have another net set up for them. So, bring your friends and teens, an your drinks to keep cool and hydrated and Bug repellent. &lt;br /&gt;

Also we often go out afterwords ( 6 pm. ) for some food or drink. So, plan to join us for that also. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We will be asking for a $1.00 donation to help play for the equipment. But please remember, your attends is more important than the your money. We would rather you play than pay. The money is only to help pay for and maintain the equipment. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We will also have another event going at the same time, "Wimp Volleyball Chatting &amp;amp; Cheerleading." This event requires a lawn chair and the ability to chat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 us on Sargent Ave and the Meetup signs on our cars.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332164168000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331756601000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wimp Vollleyball</name><id>56363672</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332097200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/56363672/</event_url></item>