<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>For the love of Pete:  How many times do I have to attempt to update this blasted site?!!  Next meetup will be Sunday, February 5 at 5PM, same bat time, same bat channel:  a.k.a. Starbucks.   It's close to the T's Green line (Arlington Station), so hopefully it is easily accessible to most people.    This location has a great downstairs section which  usually has very few customers, save a few identity-challenged pre-teens of dubious gender who have found a secret Wi-Fi hot spot where they can look at lord-knows-what on their computers.  For our purposes, it tends to have ample seating... and great people watching if you arrive early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've lately been discussing Q&amp;amp;A from Robert Mayhew's new book, Ayn Rand Answers, which is a compilation of her answers to questions from many speaking engagements over the years. However, if you feel inspired to bring up any current events, news-worthy items, movies, books, etc., which we could discuss from an Objectivist standpoint, please feel free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you in February.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have to pay meetup.com $19.00 per month to use their site, so if anyone is willing to donate a couple of green-backs to &amp;quot;the cause&amp;quot; I'd be most grateful.  At the last meeting several people put in a voluntary contribution at the end of the gathering. Oddly enough, it had overtones of passing the collection plate at church, but I enjoy that kind of irony, so we'll probably continue to collect money in that fashion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>2499401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ayn Rand Fans and Objectivists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aynrand-150</urlname><id>211108</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Ayn Rand Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1136156773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Ayn Rand February Meetup</name><id>4824461</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1139176800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aynrand-150/events/4824461/</event_url></item>