<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 New Liberty St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522655</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Salem Visitor Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>7876962</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.892360</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what REALLY happened in the Witch City of Salem Massachusetts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Historic Salem, the "Bewitching Seaport", was founded by Puritans in 1626, as a quaint fishing village. Salem however became better known as a place once visited by the devil himself, the Salem Witch Trials of 1692... &lt;br /&gt;

 You have heard the stories, now come with us and hear the truth about what besieged Salem in the year of our Lord 1692.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll start @ 3:00pm with a guided 90 minute walking tour dedicated to the Witch Trials. Our guide will explain the history and the events leading up to and including this misunderstood time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the tour concludes we will have some time to ask questions and discuss related topics with Eric our tour guide. (please don’t be shy about tipping – he’s an excellent guide and a history student).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s not all, there’s more……..lots more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner anyone? Between 5:30 - 6:00pm reservations are planned: Establishment to be announced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner there will be a short break (about an hour) to either relax, shop in the quaint village, or whatever you may find exciting ………. There’s plenty to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now don’t go home yet! There’s still more…….&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the tradition of Halloween and being in probably one of the scariest places for this time of year we’ll do one – last - thing. But before we do, you must be warned that this can be ……………. well, a bit spooky at times! At 8:00pm on this FULL MOON night we will take this 90 minute lantern lit stroll with our ghostly guide that will combine captivating storytelling, macabre humor and stellar presentation to regale you with true tails of documented paranormal activity, chilling cemeteries, centuries-old murder &amp;amp; Colonial witchcraft. They’ll also share with us their own personal encounters with Salem’s dearly departed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our guide was personally selected for his profound historic knowledge of Salem and his incredible professional experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost for this event is only $28. (this does not include; transportation, parking, food, beverage, tax, tips, or any purchases).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP ASAP and I’ll respond with payment instructions. Only people who are paid-in-full are officially on-board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;****We will meetup outside the VISITOR CENTER @ Armory Park on 2 New Liberty St. between 2:30 – 2-45:pm. Parking is just across the street at the Liberty Street parking garage. Additional parking at the Derby street parking garage is also available. Maps will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349095460000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346172292000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SALEM Historical 1692 TOUR &amp; Ghost TOUR</name><id>79742492</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348943400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/79742492/</event_url></item>