<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>SPRING?SUMMER OUTDOOR MEETUP!!!! STARTS MONTH OF MAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take a moment to read the ENTIRE update, as I have updated  the new meetup dates/locations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEETUPS AT 1:00PM&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;Please note our next SUNDAY meetup will be held BOTH at Doggie Day  @ 1PM&lt;/span&gt;  as well as the Boston Common @ 11AM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.cityofboston.gov/FreedomTrail/bostoncommon.asp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cityofbost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As in years past we typically meet on main green located near the BOYLSTON T stop. (Therefore, if you were to exit from park street , walk down the path in the park towards the boylston stop and most members meet on the grassy open area).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will continue the same set up as last year. Where by, both meetups are held on the same day so as to accommodate for rainy days and those folks who like to get outside early before the heat sets in. Members can choose to meet at &lt;b&gt;11am at the common&lt;/b&gt; and/or &lt;b&gt;Doggie Day later in the day at 1PM&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;I only ask that anyone who plans on attending please note in the RSVP which location you plan on going to. This way we can keep track of numbers at Doggie Day and the park. &lt;br /&gt;Also, please remember that there is no enclosure for pets at the common so a leash may be needed. Most members usually bring water and a blanket to sit on the grass and enjoy the (hopefully warm and sunny weather). &lt;br /&gt;Please be mindful of pet treats/snacks and remember to ask other owners if it's ok to share any snacks you bring with someone else's pets. We have a varied group and some pooches may be on special diets and/or have special needs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope all is well. As always feel free to contact me with any questions. &lt;br /&gt;Susana &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indoor meetup will be held at Doggie day &lt;b&gt;(1-3pm)&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should anyone have any questions, feel free to contact me. &lt;br /&gt;Susana&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276445366000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270681080000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua May Meetup</name><id>xtbdnynhbpb</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273417200000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/13118611/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/global_6840113.jpeg</photo_url></item>