<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;HOW MUCH $$$$&amp;nbsp; DOES A 209A ORDER COST YOU?&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And how much is it worth to you to not have a 209A order against you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MGL 209A destoys families. We have begun an inititiative petition drive to repeal this law. The first step was to submit the petition to the Massachusetts Attorney General and in September, following approval by that office, we will begin gathering signatures for the repeal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This&amp;nbsp;requires a major&amp;nbsp;effort from everyone who understands the destruction this law is causing. Your help is needed. Successful initiative petitions&amp;nbsp;in Massachusetts rely on both volunteers and paid signature gatherers. Repealing/amending MGL 209A in Massachusetts will cost $137,822. That is how much, at an average $2/validated signature, commercial companies charge to collect signatures.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Should the Attorney General's office certify our petitions to repeal/amend MGL 209A we will have just two months to collect the required 68,911 signatures.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Individuals spend thousands, if not tens of thousands, in legal and other fees to fight restraining orders. How much can you contribute to save yourself or a family member from the financial&amp;nbsp; and emotional cost of this law? We need individuals now to help organize the signature collection effort and to financially commit to fund the signature drive should the AG's office give the go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us and pass the word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Initiative Petitions are linked on the Mass. AG webiste:
 &lt;br /&gt;Repeal - 
&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/Cago/docs/Government/2011-Petitions/11-02.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/Cago/docs/Government/2011-Petitions/11-02.pdf&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Amend - 
&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/Cago/docs/Government/2011-Petitions/11-30.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/Cago/docs/Government/2011-Petitions/11-30.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joe Ureneck&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;857 350-0575&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The Massachusetts Constitutional Convention of 1917 and the Initiative Petition to Repeal MGL 209A&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;
A Memorandum of Law was submitted to the Attorney General's office in 
support of the Initiative Petition to Repeal/Amend MGL 209A ('Domestic 
Abuse' law). The AG's office will decide by the first week of September 
whether or not our Petition(s)  will be allowed to go the voters.

The Memorandum can be found here:
&lt;a href="http://www.fatherhoodcoalition.org/cpf/docs/Memorandum%20of%20Law%20Petitions%2011-02%20and%2011-30.doc"&gt;http://www.fatherhoodcoalition.org/cpf/docs/Memorandum%20of%20Law%20Petitions%2011-02%20and%2011-30.doc&lt;/a&gt;

Many quotes in the Memorandum are taken from the Debates of  the 1917 
Massachusetts Constitutional Convention which are found here: 
&lt;a href="http://www.archive.org/details/debatesinmassach02mass"&gt;http://www.archive.org/details/debatesinmassach02mass&lt;/a&gt;

The issue before the AG's office is whether the participants in the 1917 
Convention intended to exclude Petitions such as the Repeal/Amend 209A 
from the Initiative Petition process. I argue the record shows they did 
not and so our Petitions should be certified.

I encourage you to write letters of support for certification of the 
petition(s) to the Attorney General's office.

Attorney General Martha Coakley
One Ashburton Place
Boston, MA 02108 -1518
Phone: (617) 727-2200

Email: 
&lt;a href="mailto:ago@state.ma.us"&gt;ago@state.ma.us&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joseph Ureneck</member_name><member_id>8050884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315440690000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fathers' Rights Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition</urlname><id>1412531</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Chapter of The Fatherhood Coalition</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312725225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Support the Initiative Petition to Repeal the MGL 209A 'Domestic Abuse' Law !</name><id>28557531</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315436400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Greater-Boston-Chapter-of-The-Fatherhood-Coalition/events/28557531/</event_url></item>