<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>DeCiccio Family Auditorium / Room 1</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02912</zip><lat>41.826191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 863-3650</phone><name>Salomon Center for Teaching at Brown University</name><city>Providence</city><id>1116631</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;So, this Monday we're doing a twist - A lecture about chocolate on the Brown campus followed by a chocolate tasting at the Haffenreffer Museum (we'll walk over from the lecture). Then if the mood suits walk over a block or two and socialize a bit on Thayer street!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lecture will go about an hour and begins at 5:30 - if, like me you won't be able to make it on time, just sneak in the back. (Geralyn says its okay and the auditorium is big). The lecture is followed by the chocolate tasting at the Museum just across the Green.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go through the arch at Brown and Waterman Streets into the Main Green, Salomon&amp;nbsp; Building is on your left. 101 Salomom is the main auditorium for the building.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://brown.edu/Facilities/Haffenreffer/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://brown.edu/Facilities/Haffenreffer/" target="_blank"&gt;http://brown.edu/Facilities/Haffenreffer/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before Columbus Discovered Chocolate&amp;mdash;Cacao Cultivation and Courtly Appetite in the Classic Maya Lowlands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cacao bean - foundation of chocolate - is loved and consumed throughout the world as a candy, sauce, or drink. Archaeological evidence now points to the Maya region of southern M&amp;eacute;xico and northern Central America as the place where cacao-based cuisine developed. Between the 7th and 9th centuries CE, the cultivation of caca&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;o trees expanded and this "food of the gods" became a highly desired item at Classic Maya courts. Anthropologist Patricia A. McAnany (University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill) brings this time alive through presentation of new research on cacao. The talk will be followed by a tasting of Taza and Mars chocolates; a perfect appetizer before your Valentine's Day dinner plans. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is the second in a series of four programs in this year's Barbara Greenwald Memorial Arts program, entitled Tastes of the Americas. Each program features a presentation about the featured food followed by a tasting at the reception. Each event is sponsored by the Brown University Department of Anthropology, the Center for Environmental Studies at Brown, donors to the Barbara Greenwald Memorial Arts Fund, and the Friends of the Haffenreffer Museum of Anthropology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for  Geralyn. I'll wearing a silver scarf and sneaking in the back of the auditorium @ 5:45pm.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Geralyn</member_name><member_id>8469688</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297726666000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Hey, its Valentine's Day and there's chocolate to try!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297615024000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - In Honor of Chocolate!</name><id>16549005</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297722600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16549005/</event_url></item>