<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Beehive is organizing a party for St-Jean Baptiste for the French Canadian in the area ! It's held June 22dn at 17hr30, all details are on their web site. Am I the only French Canadian in the group ? I'll be there ! Come party !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is enough interest Alex, can coordinate a table reservation for 3-4 members. Please let us know if you are attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the official description from Connect to Canada:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MUSIC: &lt;br /&gt;

6:00PM to 7:30PM Isabelle Cyr and Yves Marchand &lt;br /&gt;

8:00PM to 10:30PM Nicolas Pellerin et les Grands Hurleurs &lt;br /&gt;

No cover charge, cash bar, dinner reservations recommended &lt;br /&gt;

Prix fixe menu served in addition to regular menu. &lt;br /&gt;

The Beehive Restaurant located in Boston&amp;rsquo;s trendy South End is at it again on June 22nd, 2011 with their newest celebration &amp;ldquo;La F&amp;ecirc;te nationale du Qu&amp;eacute;bec&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Quebec National Day&amp;rdquo;, a journey of exploration in traditional Quebec food and music which is nuanced, subtle and most of all captivating. The Beehive will be decked out representing our friends to the north in proper fashion as they&amp;rsquo;ve partnered with the Association Qu&amp;eacute;b&amp;eacute;coise en Nouvelle-Angleterre, the Quebec Delegation of Boston, The French Cultural Center and Svedka Vodka. &lt;br /&gt;

Highlighting the true friendliness of Quebec and its people, dinner will kick off at 5:30PM with a La F&amp;ecirc;te nationale du Qu&amp;eacute;bec Specials Menu in addition to The Beehive&amp;rsquo;s regular fare. The evening&amp;rsquo;s food will feature both traditional Quebec fare such as: Creton (Pork Pate) with Accoutrements ($10.50), Tourti&amp;egrave;re (Rustic Meat Pie), Homemade Ketchup, Pickles, Salad ($22) and Oreilles De Crisse (Pork Rinds) ($6), as well as, highlight products from Quebec such as Raw Malpeques Oysters, Maple Cider Mignonette(6) ($15), Seared &amp;ldquo;Brome Lake&amp;rdquo; Duck Breast with Wild Mushrooms, Plum Sauce and Pan-Fried Rice ($25) and Roasted Quebec Pork Shoulder, with Whisky Maple Baked Beans and Old Style Mashed Potatoes($24). In the mood for some Quebec cocktails (and who isn&amp;rsquo;t?) why not try some of The Beehive&amp;rsquo;s fun featured cocktails for the evening such as the "Caribou de Ville&amp;rdquo; ($11.50) blending together red wine, American Honey Wild Turkey splashes of Flaernum and maple syrup, served on the rocks with a cinnamon stick, or the "Quebec Urbain" ($11.50) made with Svedka Clementie, blood orange juice and muddled frest mint served on the rocks. &lt;br /&gt;

YOU CAN TAKE THE BAND OUT OF QUEBEC BUT YOU CAN'T TAKE QUEBEC OUT OF THE BAND. Beyond featuring amazing food and libations, The Beehive will host two very special performances from award winning Quebec artists. From 6:00-7:30PM the singer-song-writers, Isabelle Cyr and Yves Marchand take the stage followed from 8:00-10pm by Nicolas Pellerin et les Grands Hurleurs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>zander</member_name><member_id>6527233</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308826997000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308276558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St-Jean Baptiste celebration in Boston !</name><id>22511141</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308780000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/22511141/</event_url></item>