<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>jctn of U.S. 4 and VT 100N</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05751</zip><lat>43.650000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Killington Ski Resort</name><city>Killington</city><id>463823</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.790000</lon></venue><fee><label>accom and lift pass</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>285.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hey Aussies!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So i have had a few responses through Meetup but a bunch outside the site, i have 15 confirmed, a mix of Aussies and Americans so I've reserved a 3 condos for now and we can add to that accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details as followed hav'nt changed much apart from the fact that i have arranged it so that you can pay your deposit and balance directly to the company that i found the deal with, Tour de Sport. Call Matt on 888 364 0141 and quote booking number 551177 and you will be &amp;quot;all set&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know when you have so I can keep track of it, thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Damo &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most attractive deal that i have seen is for $175 per person for the Fri/Sat night accom in 3 bedroom condos (half a mile on free shuttle route from the mountain with kitchen, bath, fireplace, tv, dvd, hot tub etc) and $110 for a 2 day lift pass inc all tax/charges etc which i think is really good considering lift tickets are usually $80 per day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we have enough interest which i think we should i can go ahead and book, i would like to do this by jan25th. they need a $50 ea deposit as a whole group then i think it makes sense for everyone to pay their remainder direct to them depending on whether you need just the accom or a lift pass and rental ($60 for the weekend) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I reckon we would have a great time up there, even if you dont ski or ride its a great opportunity to get out of Boston, play and party with some other fellow Aussies and see some of New England in the winter. Invite your friends as well!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see some positive feedback, any questions feel free to call/email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Damo&lt;br /&gt;857 204 0495&lt;br /&gt;damo_h77@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Damo</member_name><member_id>4884584</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204600087000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Larrikins</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>aussie-145</urlname><id>222356</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Aussie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199128991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Killington ski weekend!!</name><id>7000695</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203724800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/aussie-145/events/7000695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/5/2/global_1121202.jpeg</photo_url></item>