<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on feedback here are the two choices for July:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Road&lt;/b&gt; By Cormac McCarthy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Road follows a man and a boy, father and son, journeying together towards the sea for many months across a post-apocalyptic landscape, some years after a great, unexplained cataclysm. The boy's mother, pregnant at the time of the disaster, committed suicide after the birth of her son because of her certainty that she would be raped and that she and her family would be killed by more ruthless survivors. She preferred to choose the manner of her death. The man carries a revolver with two bullets meant for suicide, one for him and one for his son...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Three Cups of Tea&lt;/b&gt; by Greg Mortenson and David Oliver Relin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1993, Greg Mortenson attempted to climb K2, the world's second highest mountain, in the Karakoram range of northern Pakistan, as a way of honoring the memory of his deceased sister Christa.[5] After more than 70 days on the mountain, Greg and three other climbers had their ascent interrupted by the need to complete a 75-hour life-saving rescue of a fifth climber. After getting lost during his descent, he became weak and exhausted, and by chance alone, instead of arriving in Askole, where his porters awaited, he came across Korphe, a small village built on a shelf jutting out from a canyon. He was greeted and taken in by the chief elder of Korphe, Haji Ali...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the books on the Table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251574592000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245868240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July's Book Discussion - Three Cups of Tea &amp; The Road.</name><id>10726695</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248732000000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/10726695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/f/global_9523311.jpeg</photo_url></item>