<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>HOLIDAY INN SELECT WOBURN</address_2><address_1>15 Middlesex Canal Park </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.497452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-897-4000</phone><name>Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grill </name><city>Woburn</city><id>1173954</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.158722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let's go dance to Don't Call Me Shirley at (another) new venue&lt;span&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A little bit about the location: The Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grill is well renowned and recognized as being one of the top sports bars in the Boston area. The recently revamped atmosphere has attracted many New England sports fans to come see what the hype is all about. With over 30 big screen TV's including an 85" Plasma sports fans can catch all of their games at once in one place. We welcome everyone to join us and cheer on The Patriots, Bruins, Celtics and The RedSox.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will be scheduled on my 2 Meetup sites, (Our Circle of Friends and Connection &amp;amp; Friends) there may be more people going to this event then you see. IF you are on both sites please only RSVP on 1 site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a minute now and put the Meetup phone into your phone, that way if you are are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute: 978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues? Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at any event. Thank you in advance for paying your dues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BAD Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a courtesy to everyone in the group come back to the event page and change your RSVP if your plans change or call me/send a message through the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside come on in and find us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364931670000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361237082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't Call Me Shirley New location</name><id>105260782</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364691600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/105260782/</event_url></item>