<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Turtle Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01845</zip><lat>42.649097</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Turtle Lane Maple Farm</name><city>North Andover</city><id>1527956</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060814</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Turtle Lane Maple Farms is the only active sugaring farm in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go out and learn how they tap the sap, and see the boil.&amp;nbsp; We may even get to sample the stages of the boil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little about the owners and how they got started with this business:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re a family of 6 who have discovered this as a great new way to enjoy and explore the wonders of nature. Kathy&amp;rsquo;s from suburban Chicago, so this is all new and fascinating for her. Paul is from New Hampshire, and his love for maple sugaring began many years ago when this was an experiment that he did in his mom&amp;rsquo;s kitchen&amp;hellip;with nearly fatal results! We don&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing this indoors due to the impact it will have not only on the kitchen, it&amp;rsquo;s appliances and wallpaper, but on other parts of the house as well&amp;hellip;talk to Paul&amp;rsquo;s mom for more details on that! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We have four kids: Siobhan, Meaghan &amp;amp; Kara Murphy and Kaleigh Boulanger. They started us in this hobby several years ago when Paul hosted a trip to New Hampshire for Maple weekend. We visited several sugar houses, and the girls begged us to try this at home. So, we tapped the red maples we had on our property, and boiled sap on the barbecue grill in our back yard. This has grown over the years to a more formal &amp;ldquo;back-yard&amp;rdquo; operation, complete with a professional evaporator and a sugar house.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;We invest our time, money and passion to teach our children and now the North Andover community, more about agriculture and some of the wonders of nature. Although 250 years ago life revolved around farming, today people rarely think beyond the grocery store. This hobby gives us the opportunity to get in touch with where our food comes from and gaining a greater appreciation for the wonders of nature. You will see us about town as we tap trees and collect sap on a daily basis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So let's go out and see this family project in action.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a free event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Parking is on the street in front of the house, we will meet in front of Donn'as Toyota Corolla and will proceed as a group to the back of the house to the Sugar House.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please remember, even tho this event is being held on the 1st Day of Spring, foul weather can still cancel this event.&amp;nbsp; Please check the site prior to leaving for the event.&amp;nbsp; If you are running late or get lost please call the Meetup phone at 978-304-2811&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hope to see you all at the Sugar House.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Donna's Car (silver Toyota Corolla)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vicki</member_name><member_id>4058114</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300745429000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>We all like Maple Syrup with our Pancakes and Waffles so lets be a bunch of saps and go see how its made.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298233636000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maple Sugaring  Tour@ Turtle Lane Maple Farm</name><id>16636089</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300644000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/16636089/</event_url></item>