<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Mike Leibensperger (Cap'n Mike) has offered the following event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: A day of sailing on Boston Harbor!&lt;br /&gt;When: Sat. September 20th, 10am to 5:45pm (sunset)&lt;br /&gt;Event Capacity: six additional persons&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September is the best time for sailing in New England: plenty of steady breeze, comfortable temperatures, and of course the beauty of the Boston Harbor Islands.  We'll leave the dock, just off Commercial St. in Boston's North End, around 10am.  Plan to bring a bag lunch, bottled water, sunscreen and sunglasses.  We'll return at about 5:45pm (sunset).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full details will be emailed to participants once they've signed up.   I have lined up a fellow freethinking sailing club member to crew for me, so the trip is open to complete landlubbers.  If we get six people plus the two of us, it'll be cozy, but we shouldn't have to throw anyone overboard to lighten the boat.  We will go rain or shine, so check the weather forecast and bring rain gear if appropriate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions?  Contact Mike Leibensperger aka &amp;quot;Cap'n Mike&amp;quot; on the Boston Atheists meetup members list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WAIVER OF RISK: Sailing can be dangerous.  People can be injured or even killed through human error, equipment failure, or for no known reason.  BY SIGNING UP FOR THIS EVENT YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT (a) you waive all claims for liability against Boston Atheists, the Boston Sailing Center, and all persons connected with these organizations, (b) you accept all responsibility for any harm that you may suffer through your participation in this event, (c) you will not seek compensation for injury or death, and (d) YOU HAVE READ THIS PARAGRAPH CAREFULLY AND UNDERSTAND THAT BY SIGNING UP FOR THIS EVENT YOU ARE GIVING UP ALL CLAIMS OF ANY KIND FOR LOSS OR INJURY IN CONNECTION WITH THE EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>details mailed to attendees</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>184665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222613857000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221531310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>All at Sea Without a God!</name><id>8765540</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221919200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/8765540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/8/9/global_5531001.jpeg</photo_url></item>