<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/a/b/event_48738091.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Enjoy dinner at 7 and stay around for the moonlight special. College Night College students enjoy one free entr&amp;eacute;e for every two students who bring in their school ID! Happy Hour 4-6pm Free food samples, $3 Bud Light Drafts, and $5 Original or Straberry Margaritas Moonlight Specials 9pm-1am Come enjoy $3 Bud Light Pints, and $5 Original or Strawberry Margaritas!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Jessica
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;"Every month at Margaritas, on the night of the full moon, we will &amp;nbsp;throw a really big party and crazy things can happen. Throughout the evening our lounges are piled high with giveaways, contests, flavorful specials and lots of fun and excitement. Even better, 5% of the evening's gross lounge sales are donated to a local charity. Area businesses, organizations and distributors get in on the fun by supplying fantastic prizes and throughout the night."
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;This particular evening will be raising funds for Give2theTroops, an awesome organization that sends care packages to troops overseas:
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;"Since December 2002, we've supported approximately ONE MILLION deployed U.S. troops with loving care packages and letters from all over the nation. This was made possible only with the help of tens of thousands of generous and patriotic friends in the U.S. and abroad. To date, we've sent more than 117,000 enormous boxes (APPROXIMATELY 70 LBS EACH) and more than 30 million letters and cards from caring citizens. This is the least we can do to show our troops how much we care about them. Our troops need to know that we support and appreciate the sacrifices they make for us, our families, and our future. This is about giving back to those who give all&amp;trade;."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text or call Jessica at 203 556 6130</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessica Ward</member_name><member_id>12802558</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315956233000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311172377000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Madness at Margaritas</name><id>26404431</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315868400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/26404431/</event_url></item>