<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our incoming call center in Marlborough, MA is up and running!  This is WAY more fun than cold calling, and the calls are flooding in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan to operate all day, every day, until further notice.  We have 5 phone lines now, but if we get enough volunteers and donations, we'd like to expand!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll use the meetup calendar to schedule volunteers. I'll create different meetup events for various timeslots throughout the day. RSVP for as many slots as you can. We'd like 7-8 volunteers onsite at all times, although we can operate with fewer when necessary.  (We need people for sending emails, stuffing envelopes, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's how it works. A computer system somewhere makes many simultaneous calls with our recorded message. If the call recipient is a Ron Paul supporter, they press &amp;quot;*&amp;quot; to talk to a live volunteer. The system transfers the call to us, and one of our 5 phone lines rings. The system automatically throttles its output calls to keep our incoming lines busy, but not overflowing. (Cool, eh?)  The computer system deals with hangups, answering machines, and rude responses. You only get calls from Ron Paul supporters!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This specific meetup event is for the timeslot on Sunday from 11 am - 2 pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Cunningham</member_name><member_id>1757740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201622671000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201183000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Phone banking</name><id>7185403</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201449600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/7185403/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/b/global_2993979.jpeg</photo_url></item>