<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>78.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>TANTRA, THE PATH TO LOVE AND EXPANSION&lt;br /&gt;An All Day Immersion Workshop&lt;br /&gt;December 12, 2010 10:00 AM-5:00 PM - ORGANIC LUNCH INCLUDED&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Tantric community is growing. Many of you have attended workshops and have had the opportunity to experience Tantra and the bliss, freedom and personal expansion that it brings. Tantra is best discovered in a workshop setting where true transformation can take place. In this workshop Taste of Tantra, sponsored by The Ashimore Center will be offering our first full day immersion into the Tantric world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all deserve love in our lives, but can we permit ourselves to surrender to it? We all wish to feel sensual and sexy, but why are we inhibited? We all find it difficult to face our fears and we all have boundaries that may not be crossed, can we address these? During this day long workshop we will be learning how to connect with love by clearly defining ourselves; our wishes, our fears and our boundaries. We will learn to open ourselves up to love.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tantric Path recognizes the body as the gateway to our emotional and spiritual self. We will be utilizing the body’s energetic sources to surrender to love, heal past wounds, define our desires and our fears and learn to live in the present moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be using the keys of Tantra to expand our awareness. You will have the opportunity to practice exercises that you have learned in the past. You will be learning new exercises to further your expansion. You will learn new tools to empower yourself to live in a state of pleasure and love. As you give yourself permission to enjoy pleasure you will begin to free your physical and emotional well-being from boundaries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workshop is open to all regardless of Tantric experience. Individuals and couples are welcome to attend. Please bring a sarong and water bottle to the workshop. You may also wish to bring a floor chair and cushions to this event. Please dress comfortably in clothing in which you can move.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: $78.00 (regular registration, after Novermber 25th) Your fee includes lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Register you may click on the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.co.." target="_blank"&gt;https://www.paypal.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE ASHIMORE CENTER&lt;br /&gt;ashimoremethod@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>8713567</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292273002000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290467439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra - The Path to Love &amp; Expansion</name><id>15530359</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292166000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/15530359/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/1/global_19876305.jpeg</photo_url></item>