<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Drug Development in the 21st Century: The Personalized Medicine Revolution&lt;br /&gt;A Presentation by Dr. Aaron Ciechanover, Nobel Laureate and Distinguished Professor&lt;br /&gt;When:              Wednesday, December 15, at 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Marriott Hotel&lt;br /&gt;                        Kendall Square           &lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;RSVP to: &lt;a href="https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?llr=h6rishdab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e3246xnne7da9129&amp;amp;oseq=" target="_blank"&gt;https://events.r20.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This event, brought to you by the Elkan R. Blout Distinguished Israeli Biomedical Research Program at the Boston Biomedical Research Institute, will feature Dr. Aaron Ciechanover. Dr. Ciechanover, the distinguished research professor at the Technion-Israel Institute of Technology, Haifa, Israel, shared the 2004 Nobel Prize in Chemistry with Drs. Hersko and Rose for the discovery of ubiquitin-mediated protein degradation.  His many other honors include the Albert and Mary Lasker Award for Basic Medical Research in 2000, the Israeli Prize in Biology in 2003, the Sir Hans Krebs Medal in 2006, and the Royal Society of Chemistry Centenary Prize in 2009. Professor Ciechnaover's discovery of the ubiquitin-proteasome system has implicated regulated proteolysis in the pathogenesis of many diseases and as a target for therapeutic intervention, including one successful anti-cancer drug.  By establishing a new paradigm of how cellular processes are controlled, Professor Ciechanover's research is ushering in a new era in drug development and medical care, which he will discuss in his lecture.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292458946000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289876258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drug Development in the 21st Century: The Personalized Medicine Revolution</name><id>15460824</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292454000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15460824/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>