<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1400 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Coop Bookstore</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>769942</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119304</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Carjacked: The Culture of the Automobile and Its Effect on Our Lives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Book reading and signing at the Harvard Coop Bookstore).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion/Signing with Catherine Lutz &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Carjacked details the complex impact of the automobile on modern society and shows us how to develop a healthier, cheaper, and greener relationship with cars.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 07:00 PM-08:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;Place: Harvard Coop Bookstore, Level 3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link: Go to &lt;a href="http://harvardcoopbooks.bncollege.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://harvardcoopboo...&lt;/a&gt; and click on &amp;quot;Calendar of Events&amp;quot;, way at the bottom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;To find us:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 6:30 PM, Tracy will stand outside with a Meetup sign. At 6:45 PM, we will all go inside and grab seats. (Please come early if possible, because it can be difficult to find seats if we wait too long). In the Coop, Tracy will still have the Meetup sign on her pocketbook so that you can find her. Please let her know you are there, so that we can herd everyone for dinner afterwards. (Tracy will try to sit up front in true Nerd style, so that you can find her, but no guarantees).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tracy is 5 foot 2, eyes of blue (literally!), with brown hair and glasses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Would you like to grab dinner or drinks afterwards?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the lecture, we will probably go to John Harvard's on Dunster Street, for dinner or drinks (alcoholic or non-alcoholic). Here is the location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Harvard's Brew House &lt;br /&gt;Harvard Square &lt;br /&gt;33 Dunster Street &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02138 &lt;br /&gt;(617) 868-3585&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;Directions to Harvard Coop Bookstore:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Coop Bookstore is in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By T:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take the red line to the Harvard Square stop. Go up several stairs, and get out at the main entrance, where all the news stands are. (This is Mass Ave, but watch out: There are multiple interpretations of &amp;quot;Mass Ave.&amp;quot; You want the entrance with lots of news stands). Cross the street, and the Coop is right in front of you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get out at the Church St exit by mistake, then you will be at the corner of Church St and Mass Ave (slightly different from the &amp;quot;Mass Ave&amp;quot; above). Turn left, and walk down the block, and the Coop is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Car:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't bother. :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is VERY difficult to find parking in Harvard Square. I highly recommend taking the T. If you go by car, the easiest way is to go West on Memorial Drive to the JFK Street intersection. There is a parking garage on JFK Street, I believe.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracy</member_name><member_id>6525487</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267147971000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264792121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carjacked: The Culture of the Automobile and Its Effect on Our Lives</name><id>12460577</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266883200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12460577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/4/global_9344884.jpeg</photo_url></item>