<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our next meeting will be held on August 11, Thursday at 7:00 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've had a challenging summer and wasn't sure exactly if and when I could come back to Reading but I'm travel ready and have made my plans.&amp;nbsp; Sorry for the short notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be caring and sharing this meeting.&amp;nbsp; Bring any and all good, positive information you might have for the group.&amp;nbsp; As always personal concerns are a topic of discussion as well.&amp;nbsp; We are here for support and help with our journey through the maze that is Fibromyalgia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still offering Lifewave patching sessions for anyone that wants to try them.&amp;nbsp; I am seeing amazing results with pain, energy, detoxification and deep healing with these patches.&amp;nbsp; To learn more go to lifewave.com/ewps to see videos and comment on these nanotechnology patches.&amp;nbsp; They not only work well for pain issues but for brain dysfunction i.e. Parkinsons, MS etc.&amp;nbsp; Suzanne Somers the ambassador for the company uses the Glutathione and inflammation patches to help the immune system fight cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to set up a session (usually takes 15-20 minutes to get the proper placement and results) call me at 623-251-7547 and we can set up a time at my office.&amp;nbsp; There is no cost for this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you in August I hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betsy&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Senior Center Lounge on Pleasant Street Reading upstairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Timmerman</member_name><member_id>3507700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313204364000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People With Fibromyalgia</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fibromyalgia-301</urlname><id>586410</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>The Reading Fibromyalgia Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312078282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>get together</name><id>27652721</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313103600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fibromyalgia-301/events/27652721/</event_url></item>