<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On March 20, the Coolidge is showing the last movie in its Raising the Barre series.  This is a film version of the Bolshoi Ballet dancing to choreography by Alexei Ratmansky (who is now at American Ballet Theater).  The man is a genius choreographer the likes of which we have never seen.  He can do everything.  When our group saw Bolt, a ballet he choreographed for the Bolshoi, which was also shown by the Coolidge, we could not stop laughing and exclaiming over the choreographic invention, talent, storytelling, use of mime, dance chorus, humor, and inspiration.  It was fireworks by dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm looking forward to the same kind of experience in this work.  I'll be at the theater at 10:45 am to meet people and get seated and after we'll go out for a meal and conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one promises to be thrilling.  See the Coolidge's explanation below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choreography Alexei Ratmansky, reconstructed from the original choregraphy by Vasily Vaynonen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced in the 1930s, in Leningrad, at the then Kirov (today Mariinsky) Theatre, and soon transferred to the Bolshoi, THE FLAMES OF PARIS was to become a ballet favorite. It was presented on the eve of the anniversary of the October Revolution, and later continued to be included in the ranks of works which were always brought out for an airing on anniversaries of this sort. And this is hardly surprising, the flames of Paris, after all, is about the conflagration of the great French Revolution. And it had a new 'hero' type which, up to then, had not been encountered in ballet - one of its main characters was the populace, revolutionary in mood and ready for action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delighting in Vasily Vaynonen's rhythmically refined dance combinations - his nickname was Vaska-the syncopator - choreographer Alexei Ratmansky has attempted to make maximum use of the preserved fragments in his new ballet. Interwoven into its fabric, are the Vaynonen Basque dance, the Mireille and Antoine Mistral pas de deux, the farandola, two carmagnoles and, of course, the famous Jeanne and Philippe pas de deux, the perennially popular ballet competition and concert number.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300709385000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>A note on this performance.  I'm sure it will sell out.  Please be sure to get your tickets ahead of time.  Word is spreading and many people are attending.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295192248000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raising the Barre - The Flames of Paris</name><id>16066837</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300633200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16066837/</event_url></item>