<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Cummings Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.560047</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cummings Center</name><city>Beverly</city><id>943062</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887695</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This was a hit last time and I ride it all the time so I'm going to make it available on a regular basis to anyone who would like to join.  Details (such as lunch) may change depending on the group's feelings but the route will remain the same more or less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a beautiful ride through Cape Ann that will showcase the rugged coastlines of Magnolia and Gloucester and the pastoral horse farms of central Essex.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving from the Balch street entrances of the Cummings center in Beverly we'll wind our way through Beverly farms over to 127, north through Manchester-by-the-sea and Magnolia past Hammond Castle to Gloucester and the magnificent shoreline and homes of Eastern Point.  Heading west after that we'll get into some of the most beautiful and quiet country roads the North Shore has to offer with a stop at JT Farnham's in Essex for an al fresco lunch overlooking the scenic Essex river and surrounding marsh.  Then it's back in the saddle for more bucolic farm vistas and country lanes.  A quick detour through Bradley Palmer State Park and a skirt of the Massachusetts Audubon Sanctuary brings us back to 97 and a 6 mile ride back home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About 50 miles in total.   I'll be planning on doing this in about 5-6 hours (depending on the length and frequency of stops) finishing with an average riding pace of about 13-14mph.  However, maps and cue sheets are available in the group 'files' section under the 'more' menu above and I'll have extras available at the time of the ride too for those who want to go faster or slower.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few words about the pace from my perspective.  First it is an average of saddle time only.  Second the route includes several sections of easy (not to say slow) pedaling for rest and recovery.  Areas I myself don't like to burn through.  So while the pace in the beginning will be quicker, in these areas towards the middle third of the trip it will be somewhat slower.  The final 6 miles or so are more or less a straight shot and merit a good final push for speed.  All that said however the previous paragraph takes precedence in that members are free to set their own paces.  There are 2 planned stops at Stage Fort Park in Gloucester and at JT Farnhams for lunch.  These ought to be good places to catch up to folks in front or behind a given group, though of course the ideal is to stay together throughout. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things to bring&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A bike (road or hybrid whatever you feel comfortable on) and helmet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A spare tube and patch kit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Water or sports drink and plenty of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Powerbar/Cliff bars or similar energy snacks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Money for lunch (Farnham's is Cash or Check only though there is an ATM), water, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunblock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cummings Center is located on route 62 (Elliot street) in Beverly and is about a 5 min pedal north of the Beverly commuter rail station.  The route map is below cue is available in the group files under the 'more' menu above.  Feel free to contact me with questions or comments.  Balch Street entrances are in the rear of the Cummings center campus.  We'll meet close to the East Drive Entrance.  See route map.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapmyride.com/route/us/ma/beverly/298127870935530460" target="_blank"&gt;Route Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan</member_name><member_id>11982073</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287431644000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281111244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>50 mile - Cape Ann Loop</name><id>vkxcpynnbvb</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287235800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/14340472/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/e/global_17238590.jpeg</photo_url></item>