<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>When I'm on stage, I'm trying to do one thing: bring people joy. Just like church does. People don't go to church to find trouble, they go there to lose it. James Brown&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;The Night James Brown Saved Boston&lt;/b&gt; by David Leaf (2007, 74 min.). On April 5, 1968—the morning after the assassination of Martin Luther King—as America’s inner cities went up in flames, trouble was also brewing in Boston’s ghetto neighborhood of Roxbury, MA. As Boston mayor, Kevin White tried to determine whether to cancel the evening’s James Brown concert, a call from a prominent Boston DJ pointed out, that if the concert was cancelled, Boston might see the biggest uprising since the Boston Tea Party. Rather than cancel the show, they sought the help of James Brown himself. The Night James Brown Saved Boston tells the story of that night with amazing concert moments and personal reminiscences by James Brown’s band members, colleagues, awe-struck concert-goers, Boston city government officials, and the pointed commentary of several distinguished observers of African-American history. Discussion follows August 17 screening. MFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It began with WGBH TV/Radio's insanely upper crusty announcer saying in a voice so cultured it would make Alistair Cooke sound like a thug, &amp;quot;We invite you to stay tuned for a live memorial concert at the Boston Garden featuring Negro singer Jimmy Brown and his group.&amp;quot; I swear. That's what he said. The fact that the announcement didn't cause riots in and of itself is miraculous. &lt;br /&gt;As the show opened, Brown's musical director began to introduce the mayor as &amp;quot;the honorable . . .&amp;quot; and Brown grabbed the mic and said, &amp;quot;I've had the pleasure of meeting him . . . and lets just call him 'swinging cat,' 'cause he's one swinging cat!&amp;quot; Fantastic. Right off, the temperature cooled. Brown handled things the way the cops, the pols, the preachers couldn't do. Don't miss it. Really.  NY Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MFA will have a panel discussion and afterward we will go to a local restaurant for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a meetup sign after the MFA discussion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219170610000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218071410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Night James Brown Saved Boston</name><id>8493588</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218996900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8493588/</event_url></item>