<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Celebrate your independence &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Independence beyond the political…. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When did you become independent or at least declare your independence? What event marked the moment? What food marked the moment? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting a driver’s license? &lt;br /&gt;Going to college? &lt;br /&gt;Paying for college? &lt;br /&gt;The first apartment? &lt;br /&gt;Running away from home?&lt;br /&gt;Wealth?&lt;br /&gt;First step?&lt;br /&gt;Leaving the corporate cog position to gear up on your own? &lt;br /&gt;Toilet training (yours or someone else’s)? &lt;br /&gt;Divorce? &lt;br /&gt;That cross country trip? &lt;br /&gt;Hitchhiking in Europe? &lt;br /&gt;Radioactive spider bite? &lt;br /&gt;Breakthrough in the therapist’s office? &lt;br /&gt;Finally off the crutches? &lt;br /&gt;The first paycheck? &lt;br /&gt;First legal glass of beer or wine? &lt;br /&gt;A quiet moment alone? &lt;br /&gt;That monkey finally off your back?&lt;br /&gt;Graduation day? &lt;br /&gt;Removing the training wheels? &lt;br /&gt;Safely crossing the Rio Grande? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe your independence is tied to a country, such as the USofA? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Figure it out…bring a food that means independence for you… we will be celebrating all forms of independence together so we are dependent on you joining us for the fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember, this is about your creativity and personal interpretation.    &lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook onsite unless your recipe takes more than an hour to prepare. The fun is in the cooking here all together.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather permitting we may be out side in July, bring a lawn chair!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>my home so you will notice me and the dogs, will send address a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250289492000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244851634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes July Meetup</name><id>10640700</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247266800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/10640700/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/c/global_9117708.jpeg</photo_url></item>