<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.521828</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-745-9500</phone><name>Peabody Essex Museum</name><city>Salem</city><id>669327</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.892640</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What's better than a trip to the museum to see a photo exhibit? Three photography exhibits, that's what. The Peabody Essex is a delightful and successful museum and within easy reach of our area. Admission is $15, which works out to only $5 per exhibit - you can't beat that with a stick. If you do, museum security will escort you out, anyway. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Additional $1 fee helps offset the CAPE Group's Meetup fees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Plan on a lite lunch at the Atrium Caf&amp;eacute; or, if you tire of hobnobbing with the Hoi Polloi, the Garden Restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/1/2/event_101858162.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up is an &lt;strong&gt;Ansel Adams&lt;/strong&gt; exhibit - "&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;At the Water's Edge&lt;/span&gt;".&amp;nbsp;Wherever he photographed, Ansel Adams' appreciation for water was never far from the surface. He was drawn to the subject in all its forms, from rain, fog, mist and clouds to ice and snow. He also photographed water's effects in tide pools, weathered buildings and erosion patterns. His fascination with surf and crashing waves fed his interest in waterfalls and rapids in the High Sierra. In Yellowstone, it fueled his photographs of Old Faithful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As in the famous&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Surf Sequence&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;ca.1940, Adams often photographed water in ways that embrace seriality, motion, and time as meaningful modern themes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At the Water's Edge&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;combines famous images with extraordinary but lesser-known examples, expanding knowledge of Adams' work and building appreciation for the artist as an important and innovative modernist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/4/4/event_101858212.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concurrent with this exhibit is &lt;strong&gt;Jerry Uelsmann&lt;/strong&gt;'s "&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Mind's Eye: 50 Years of Photography&lt;/span&gt;".&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Surreal, funny and provocative, Jerry Uelsmann's photographs are icons of American photo history. His most famous technique -- seamlessly fabricating photographs from unrelated negatives to create imaginary scenes -- cemented his standing as a leading light of non-literal photography. The exhibition combines Uelsmann's most celebrated works with many never-before-seen pieces for his first retrospective in 40 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/6/2/event_101858242.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we'll see &lt;strong&gt;Man Ray&lt;/strong&gt;'s and &lt;strong&gt;Lee Miller&lt;/strong&gt;'s "&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Partners in Surrealism&lt;/span&gt;".&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;From 1929 to 1932, Man Ray and Lee Miller -- two giants of the European Surrealism movement -- lived together in Paris, first as teacher and student, and later as lovers. Their mercurial relationship resulted in some of the most powerful work of each artist's career, and helped shape the course of modern art and photography. Combining rare vintage photographs, paintings, sculpture and drawings, this exhibition tells the story of the artists' brief but intense association and reveals the nature of their creative partnership.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside (weather permitting) the main entrance. We'll go in at 10AM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340170308000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331988730000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peabody Essex Museum - Triple Photo Exhibit</name><id>56714722</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339855200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/56714722/</event_url></item>