<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 6 miles round-trip (including South Baffle and Baffle Dams) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy (gently-rolling paved roads, level dirt roads on dams)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo: Daytime at Baffle Dam, 8-mile view south!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/6/6/event_120367782.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These night hikes are are "stop and smell the roses" type hikes, so it could take longer than expected. We enjoy strolling, watching and listening to whatever creatures are stirring. We enjoy taking pictures. We enjoy the quiet and the beauty and all that the Quabbin has to offer. On this hike, we'll undoubtedly sit on the Baffle Dam for a bit, enjoying the solitude and taking pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions are at the bottom. This is one of the boat launch fishing areas, so there may be signage on Rte 32A to help.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is another permit required hike!&lt;/strong&gt; You will need to apply for a (FREE) permit, call the rangers the day of the hike with the Gate #, access time, and your permit #, display the letter-size permit on your dashboard, and carry the business-card size permit with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Night access permits are good through October 12th, so if you think you may want to attend such a hike this year, apply now (via mail with SASE, or in person at the Visitor's Center). &lt;strong&gt;Details and link to application:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/events/71384462/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Walking-Group/events/71384462/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bug spray &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Pemetherin or "deep-woods" strength DEET; Quabbin has deer ticks, though the only place we may brush against bushes is on the small island between the dams.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;something to drink&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a snack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a camera if you wish, and tripod &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(The cheapest tripod at WalMart is $15.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;maybe a light coat if the temperature drops after dark&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flashlight or headlamp &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(There are thin strips of poison ivy along the edge of the road across the dam; while easy to avoid, you'll need your flashlight to step over them! Although I am hoping to use the nearly full moon to guide us most of the time.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should also bring a sense of adventure as these night hikes are new, so we don't know what to expect as we explore the different gates!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the camera inclined folks, a small tripod is a MUST after the sun fades as exposure times increase to the point that it would be impossible to get a clear picture otherwise. I did not bring one, and could not take pictures after the sun was well below the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that this is a 6:30 start time as it is getting darker earlier...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;QUABBIN REGULATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No pets (same reason).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry-in, carry-out" (take your trash with you when you go).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No fires or alcohol.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove anything from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No night access without special (FREE) permit! (See above.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There &lt;strong&gt;is&lt;/strong&gt; an outhouse&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;with sanitizer&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;near S. Baffle Dam, 2.5 miles into our hike&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;make sure you can hike this far before using it&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The boat launch probably has one, but it's not on our hike, and it's some distance from the gate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS TO GATE 43A &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gate 43A is on Greenwich Road in Hardwick, Mass. Greenwich Rd is on the left, about 6 miles north on Route 32A if coming from Route 9. From Route 122 it's on the right, probably at least 9 miles south.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you turn onto Greenwich Rd, the gate is about 3 miles. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Park in the small lot OUTSIDE the Gate 43A...do NOT drive inside Gate 43 and pay $4, that will CLOSE AT NIGHT and is for boaters and people without night permits! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please drive towards the gate and park in the small lot *outside* the gate. DISPLAY YOUR LETTER-SIZE PERMIT IN YOUR WINDSHIELD, and carry the card-sized one with you. Enter Gate 43A, not 43!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346211597000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345605674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset hike in the Quabbin - Gate 43A to Baffle Dam</name><id>78811702</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346193000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/78811702/</event_url></item>