<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>41 Foster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.410343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Arlington Center for the Arts</name><city>Arlington</city><id>689719</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.145401</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you've never been to a True Story Theater performance, then you're in for a treat. What they do is bring up one volunteer at a time from the audience to tell a person story from their life that is related to the theme (which in this case is &lt;strong&gt;"dating disasters and triumphs"&lt;/strong&gt;).  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The actors will listen very carefully to the story, and then "replay" the story for the whole audience. They act it out in a very unique way using things like singing, dancing, improv, comedy, wardrobe changes, props... you name it. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 There's nothing like it, and the depth and beauty of what they can do in such a short period of time is nothing short of remarkable. I encourage you to join me for an unforgettable experience that will very likely touch your heart. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;*************************************************&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Where is it?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;The event is conveniently located at The Arlington Center For The Arts. Please plan on arriving by 7:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 7:30pm and go until 9:00pm.  There are plenty of bus lines that go to the center, and there is also lots of parking both on the street and in a big parking lot near the center.  This page has details and directions: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.acarts.org/directions.php"&gt;http://www.acarts.org/directions.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Do not confuse this place with The Arlington Center which is a yoga studio on Mass Ave.  This is a totally different (and much larger) place.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Room rental contribution:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;There is just a 5 dollar contribution to help cover the cost of the theater rental.  They don't mind performing for free, but I don't want them to lose money on it either :) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot.  I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Warmly,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Jason&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park in the parking lot and follow the signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369805116000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>55</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369188872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*SPECIAL PERFORMANCE* - True Story Theater - Dating Disasters and Triumphs</name><id>120594612</id><headcount>50</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369783800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/120594612/</event_url></item>