<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;As of today, Wednesday 2/3, the workshop has only one seat available.  Please contact Dan directly to see if you can reserve it.  This site is no longer accepting rsvp's.  See below for the link to his site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks...Dianne&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Dan Splaine is taking his show on the road with this unique &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photography Workshop On Wheels!!  &lt;br /&gt;Combination class and field trip!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dan Splaine, of TEST of TIME PHOTOGRAPHY, has arranged for a mini-coach for a day to hold a combination workshop and location shoot at the World Championship Sled Dog Race in Laconia, New Hampshire.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mini-coach leaves at 10:00 AM SHARP from Nashua, NH.  During the drive-time to Laconia, the rolling workshop will cover SPORTS and ACTION photography as well as shooting in winter conditions.  The trip north will be spent going over the workshop topics, followed by a quick lunch break at a Laconia restaurant (&lt;i&gt;lunch on your own&lt;/i&gt;) where the conversation will continue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The class will be followed by a live photography session on location at the WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP SLED DOG RACE.  We will photograph the action at the race area and practice the techniques described in the workshop.   The race offers an exceptional range of subject to shoot as well as some challenging conditions.  This is a great chance to improve your live action and sports photography skills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DETAILS OF THE TRIP:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHEN:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, February 13th 2010 from 10 AM to 5 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ITINERARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depart Welcome Center at EXIT 6 off Rt 3 in NASHUA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Photo workshop while traveling to Laconia &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunch upon arrival in Laconia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Then off to the races at 1:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Arrive back in Nashua between 4:00-5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;$45 per person (includes workshop and transportation) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DEPOSIT:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Deadline for reservations and payment is FEBRUARY 1st.  Space is limited so book this workshop ASAP! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATION:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Due to the contractual obligation with the mini-coach company, this is a non-refundable fee.  Once you make your payment (deadline February 1, 2010), there is no refund.  This event will not be cancelled due to weather.  It's on snow, rain or shine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT REGISTRATION AND PAYMENT INFORMATION:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;All registrations will be taken on the TEST OF TIME website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  You may use the Paypal link provided at this URL.  &lt;a href="http://www.testoftimephoto.com/Photography-classes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.testoftime...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;***PLEASE NOTE*** &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This workshop is being run exclusively by Dan Splaine.  We are posting it on the CAPE group page for informational purposes only.  Your RSVP on the CAPE group's meetup page &lt;u&gt;will not constitute a confirmed reservation&lt;/u&gt;.  You MUST register for this trip at the TEST OF TIME website link provided above.  No reservation will be confirmed until payment is received via the TEST OF TIME website link.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you have any questions please email DAN SPLAINE at &lt;a href="mailto:photoclass@testoftimephoto.com" target="_blank"&gt;photoclass@testoftimephoto.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a unique opportunity to get some winter shooting in under circumstances that are a little more comfortable and convenient.  We'll be able to leave the driving to the professional and have a warm place to retreat to if the elements get overwhelming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome Center at EXIT 6 off Rt 3 in NASHUA  - mini-coach leaves at 10:00 AM SHARP.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>5274985</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267156250000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263092312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Workshop On Wheels</name><id>12274437</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266073200000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/12274437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/4/global_12556100.jpeg</photo_url></item>