<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Run of the Charles &lt;/span&gt;Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak Race&lt;/strong&gt;, the signature event of the Charles River Watershed Association (CRWA) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;will take place on Saturday, April 30, 2011.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The event features a variety of races for all skill levels, from expert to novice.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;New England's largest canoe and kayak race, there are 6, 9, and 19 mile races; a 24-mile, five-leg canoe relay race; and a 26-mile professional marathon. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Among the most challenging features of the &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Run of the Charles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;are the six portages where boats must be carried around an obstruction.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;The dams in Newton, Wellesley, Waltham and Watertown forced paddlers off the river and onto their feet, shouldering their boats while they ran to the spot where they could get back on the water and resume paddling.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Paddlers raced across Route 16 on the Newton-Wellesley line and across Moody Street in Waltham, running for nearly a &amp;frac12;-mile on each of these portages alone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Annual Run of the Charles showcases the ongoing improvements in the Charles River, while drawing 1,500 paddlers and hundreds of spectators to enjoy a day on the river.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;race&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; builds support for the CRWA, which seeks to protect and enhance the health, beauty and enjoyment of the Charles River and its tributaries.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;CRWA&amp;rsquo;s prominent role in protecting and restoring the Charles River since 1965 accounts for a much healthier Charles River today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The work of CRWA encompasses all 80 miles of the Charles River, which meanders through 35 eastern Massachusetts towns and cities within the 308 square miles of the Charles River watershed.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;The nearly 1.5 million citizens who live in the watershed, totaling 23% of the state's population, benefit from a clean and healthy Charles River.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;CRWA's successes have led many organizations across the country to emulate its science methods and watershed management models.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more information about the race or to register visit &lt;a href="http://www.crwa.org/rotc/rotc.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.crwa.org/rotc/rotc.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily Singer</member_name><member_id>7452900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304378077000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>the trails up north will be muddy and this benefits a good cause.</why><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301278810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 29th Run of the Charles Canoe and Kayak Race</name><id>17080989</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304164800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17080989/</event_url></item>