<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston Plone User Group is organizing 2009 Boston World Plone Day, and all are invited to attend. It will be held in the Forum Room at Harvard University's Lamont Library, at the corner of Mass Ave and Quincy Street. Pre-registration is required for this free event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;World Plone Day is a once a year event when people interested in the Plone open source content management system get together to share experiences, ideas, and fun. Seminars, presentations, lectures, and discussions explore what Plone is and what it can do for you and your organization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2008 Boston event was held last November and featured apples, cider, and model airplanes from Wingware - not to mention presentations and panel discussions. This year's event is being moved up to April, so it will not be so close to the annual Plone Conference, which is held in October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.00 - Registration/Check-in (30 minutes)&lt;br /&gt;2.30 - Introductions/Logistics (10 minutes) - Aaron VanDerlip, Jazkarta&lt;br /&gt;2.40 - Introduction to Plone (20 minutes) - Nate Aune, Jazkarta&lt;br /&gt;3.00 - Case Study: Boston Community Change (20 minutes) - Brian Goodman, City of Boston&lt;br /&gt;3.20 - Case Study: Harvard School of Engineering and Applied Sciences (20 minutes) -  Michael Trachtman, Jazkarta, and Eliza Grinnell, Harvard SEAS&lt;br /&gt;3.40 - Case Study: Plone for Web Portals (20 minutes) - Kyle Homstead, Chronicle Tech&lt;br /&gt;4.00 - Plone for Collaborative Product Lifecycle Management (20 minutes) - David Buck, ZWeave&lt;br /&gt;4.20 - Search Engine Optimization Best Practices and Plone (20 minutes) - David Crouch, Ten24Web&lt;br /&gt;4.40 - Case Study: Advancing Green Chemistry (20 minutes) - Sally Kleinfeldt, Jazkarta &lt;br /&gt;5.00 - Genius Bar (20 minutes) - All&lt;br /&gt;5.20 - Closing/Door Prizes (10 minutes) - Sid Koul, New England Wildflower Society&lt;br /&gt;5.30 - Adjourn to Social Event at local watering hole&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Plone:&lt;/b&gt; Plone.org is the leading Open Source Content Management System (CMS) freely available on the web today, as awarded by many online and print media outlets. Since 2001 and worldwide, Plone enables normal end users with no technical expertise to create and manage dynamic web sites. Corporations and Non-Profit entities using Plone and related technologies include Boston.com, Akamai Technologies, N.A.S.A., Oxfam America, Novell Inc., Discover Magazine, Penn State University, Duke, Cornell and many others. Find out more at &lt;a href="http://www.plone.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.plone.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sally Kleinfeldt</member_name><member_id>2175963</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sid Koul</member_name><member_id>2310802</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aaron VanDerlip</member_name><member_id>7526011</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243555103000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Plonista</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonplone</urlname><id>207992</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Plone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238026005000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Plone Day</name><id>10036675</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/events/10036675/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/4/3/global_6668627.jpeg</photo_url></item>