<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>523 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.483658</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Church</name><city>Woburn</city><id>785336</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150909</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for this fun night with our children on school vacation. Meet and mingle and see if we are what you are missing in your life. &lt;br /&gt;

Families/School Vacation-Pot Luck dinner and Pound Auction Tuesday, April 17, 6:30 pm, United Methodist Church, Woburn. &lt;br /&gt;

Bring something for the pot luck to share. What is a pound auction? Each family brings at least one wrapped item valued at $5 or less. The kids bid on the item usually in $.25 intercrements. This highest bidder wins the item. Mike will run the auction for the kids. Everyone will win a bid and usually for under $3. No one goes home empty handed. This has always been a great time for the kids. Be sure to RSVP so we can look for you when you arrive!! E-mail Sandi the organizer if you have any questions. &lt;br /&gt;

Directions to Woburn United Methodist Church &amp;#150; 523 Main Street, Woburn &lt;br /&gt;

Rt. 128/Rt. I-95 - Take exit 35/Rt. 38 toward Woburn/Wilmington. Go on Rt. 38 South/Main St. towards Woburn. Go just over a mile to the Church. Pass King Gas Station and take a left on Harlow Court (after the church). The hall is located on the left, near the back of the church building &amp;#150; the door is accessible on Harlow Court. Parking: There is on-street parking, or instead of taking the left onto Harlow Court, there is a municipal lot on Rt. 38 on the left after Express Fuel. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>8198815</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334856249000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Single Parents</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pwp817</urlname><id>1298426</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Parents Without Partners- Single Parents</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333673687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open House/School Vacation/Pot Luck dinner and Pound Auction</name><id>59456032</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334701800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pwp817/events/59456032/</event_url></item>