<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Suggested Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>or what you feel is right</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The meet-up will be at Peter's Park in the South End off Washington Street.  It is located directly across the street from 1244 Washington Street. The dog park is over near the tennis courts.  It's a very popular park, so you should see a bunch of dogs running around.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the change in time to 2:00 pm.  We're hoping the later time will make it easier for people to make it and also to coordinate with the English Bulldog group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: If it is raining, snowing or too cold, a cancellation notice will be sent via email and posted on the meetup website 2 hours prior to the meetup time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a $15 a month meetup fee. This is a GROUP fee and if not paid, our Boston French Bulldog meetup’s, would not exist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer is in charge of paying this fee every month. It would be greatly appreciated if at each meetup, each member can submit a donation that goes towards the monthly $15 fee. Give $1, give $10. If at the end of the meetup, the organizer has not collected enough to meet the $15, she will pay the difference. If she receives more than $15, the extra would go towards the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to allow payment by PayPal, I had to put a minimum &amp;quot;Suggested Donation.&amp;quot;  This is just to cover the meetup.com fee.  You can give whatever you feel is appropriate.  The cost is $15 per month, so you don't have to give every month either.  Whatever works for you.  And you can do it through PayPal or at the MeetUp.  Hope this helps!! &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540378000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1152990198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Bulldog August Meetup</name><id>5025660</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156010400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/5025660/</event_url></item>