<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Federal St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01109</zip><lat>42.109196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Scibelli Enterprise Center, across from STCC, downstairs media room</name><city>Springfield</city><id>9576442</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.577682</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will have a guest speaker for our May 1st event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed Sordillo from International Laser Solutions, Inc, a Holyoke MA company will talk all things industrial lasers. Among other things, his company provides laser engraving solutions to businesses and individuals. Laser engraving of a product brings professional look to an otherwise standard processed blank of material.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As other meetings of this type, it will be in a Q and A format, and our attendants should come with questions prepared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No closed-door presenters have been scheduled for this meeting so far, but time slots are still available. Otherwise, non-members and first-time attendants may request permission from one of the organizers to attend this event without being a member. Our policy is that a non-member should attend an open-door meeting first, and that membership is to be paid before or at the door of the closed-door meeting for them to attend our closed-door sessions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Networking starts at 6:30PM (before the main meeting), and resumes after the main presenter, usually at 9PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Pride bio: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 1) Graduated in 1981 from one of the first Laser Electro-Optics Technology (L.E.O.T.) courses offered at STCC and was the first student to build a high power CO2 laser as a senior project. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 2) Entered into the industrial laser field working for a local electron beam welding company that wanted to start laser materials processing. That grew in five years to become a bi-costal materials processing operation. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 3) Founded Pride Laser Consulting in April of 1987 which has gone on to help start two materials processing facilities, build several industrial laser systems, train well over a hundred laser operators while working with the mom &amp;amp; pop shops all the way up to international firms like Proctor &amp;amp; Gamble, Texas Instruments and so on. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Robert Pride &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Pride Laser Consulting &lt;br /&gt;

 691 Federal Street &lt;br /&gt;

 Belchertown, MA 01007 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 (413) 221-0327&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed Sordillo bio:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed Sordillo is the founder and President of International Laser Solutions, Inc,  founded in 1995, ILS at specializes in Laser Engraving for product identification for High end medical, aerospace, and Law enforcement products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A graduate of STCC's Laser Electro Optics program graduating in 1989. In 1989 Ed was hired by MIT Lincoln Laboratories at Hanscomb AFB for developing laser systems for the Star Wars Defense Initiative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed moved back to Western Mass to start International Laser in  early 1995 to fill the need for this type of laser technology in the region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ed Sordillo International Laser Solutions, Inc. 413-533-4372&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367460571000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366852767000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ed Sordillo from International Laser Solutions is our speaker for May 1st event</name><id>116059552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367449200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/116059552/</event_url></item>