<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Max Cost</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group as we start our Cooking Classes!&amp;nbsp; Debbi has dozens of cookbooks with thousands of recipes,&amp;nbsp;loves to cook and is willing to share her talents with us.&amp;nbsp; This will be a fun way to learn how to cook new recipes, taste them and socialize! &amp;nbsp;We may even plan an item that we will make next month at tonight's Cooking Class. &amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;This month we are meeting on Sunday to enjoy the pleasures of Brunch, including Breakfast Foods!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today we will be making something that you&amp;nbsp;suggested on the "Cooking Classes!"&amp;nbsp;Discussion Thread.&amp;nbsp; We will peruse the replies and do our best to pick from the suggestions of those who have RSVPed Yes thus far.&amp;nbsp; We will update with more details about a week before the event.&amp;nbsp;Click on the following link to be taken to the Discussion Thread to post your suggestions. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Please let us know what types of Breakfast/Brunch foods you would like to learn to cook by posting in the Talk About It Section&lt;/strong&gt; (at the bottom of this page) &lt;strong&gt;or on the Discussion Thread&lt;/strong&gt; (by clicking on the link here)&lt;strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/messages/boards/thread/17992182"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/messages/boards/thread/17992182&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us know your general availability for our monthly Cooking Classes by clicking on the following link to vote in the Poll.&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/polls/420042/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/polls/420042/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TODAY'S MENU:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sundried Tomato &amp;amp; Spinach Fritatta&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sweet &amp;amp; Spicy Bacon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon Pull-Apart Bread&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minted Fruit Salad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peach/Lemonade Flip (semi frozen non-alcoholic drink)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*All of the food will be purchased ahead of time by the Event Organizers.&amp;nbsp; Cost will be approximately $10-$15 per person (excluding Debbi) plus any applicable Event Fees.&amp;nbsp; Please bring cash.&amp;nbsp; (This is very inexpensive compared to most cooking classes and dinners!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Please let us know in your RSVP Comments if you have a Food Allergy.&amp;nbsp; We will make sure we exclude that from whatever we cook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*After we prepare and cook we will dine and sample our creations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*We will provide a copy of all recipes for everyone to take home with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Please bring 1-2 (one to two) 1-serving (one serving)&amp;nbsp;containers.&amp;nbsp; We will do our best to send everyone home with at least one serving. &amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Please Note: There may be leftovers for some items but not others.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;As this is in a member's home there is an attendance requirement.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; Please RSVP Yes only if you fall into one of the following attendance categories:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-At least 2 events w/ the SSDOMG in&amp;nbsp;2011 &amp;amp; 2012&amp;nbsp;and/or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-At least 3 total events w/ the SSDOMG and&amp;nbsp;South Shore Walkabouts in 2011 &amp;amp; 2012 and/or&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-4 SSDOMG events in the last 2 years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If in doubt please RSVP Yes and we will let you know otherwise.&amp;nbsp; We want to make sure we have met up with you at least twice. &amp;nbsp;(Please Note: Those who attended the NYEE Appetizer Social - even if it was your first event - are welcome to join us! &amp;nbsp;In addition, if you joined the SSDOMG in 2012 and have attended at least one event you are welcome to join us.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a few hours of fun, food, friends and learning to cook and enjoy some new foods!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March Cooking Class &amp;amp; Meal: Brunch!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saunday, March 11th @ 11:30am-2:30pm (approximate end time +/- 1/2 hr)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debbi's Home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quincy, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phone #: To be emailed with directions to Yes RSVPs at or shortly after the RSVP Deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Inside Debbi's apartment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela and Debbi (2011 &amp;amp; 2012 AM)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cost&lt;/em&gt;: Between $10-$15, TBD @ Event based on cost of Food &amp;amp; # of Attendees (minus Debbi)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: [Current 2012] Annual Members - FREE, Members - $2 each; $12 to become a 2012 Annual Member&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Minimum of 5 by Tuesday, March 6th.&amp;nbsp; Maximum of 8 members.&amp;nbsp; These numbers include the Event Organizers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Sorry, this is members-only event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;10am on Saturday, February 10th&lt;/strong&gt;. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event. &amp;nbsp;In addition, we will be buying the food based on the # of Yes RSVPs. &amp;nbsp;Absolutely no RSVP changes will be allowed after 9pm on Friday night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please bring cash.&lt;/em&gt; You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&amp;nbsp; This has been the SSDOMG's policy for over 5 years now and it helps avoid confusion when paying the bill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This event takes place rain, snow or shine.&amp;nbsp; In the case of an extreme weather forecast we will update this&amp;nbsp;information around the RSVP Deadline. &amp;nbsp;Please check back here for further information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please see the Pages for more information about the SSDOMG's policies and procedures which help ensure a smoother, relaxed, fun&amp;nbsp;dining experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;: Will be emailed to Yes RSVPs shortly after the RSVP deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will give the Yes RSVPs directions right to Debbi's door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbi  </member_name><member_id>22304061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331590920000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329066372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Cooking Class &amp; Meal: Brunch!</name><id>52056362</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331479800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/52056362/</event_url></item>