<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>101 North Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01756</zip><lat>42.122640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-473-7539</phone><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary</name><city>Mendon</city><id>669262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.566860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Maple Farm Sanctuary is an animal sanctuary providing lifelong homes for abused, abandoned and unwanted farmed animals while promoting veganism and respect for all life through public information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are also volunteers opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;Email: maplefarmsanctuary@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What:     3rd Annual Open House  - Picnic, Music, Barn Tours.&lt;br /&gt;Where:   Maple Farm Sanctuary, 101 North Avenue, Mendon, MA&lt;br /&gt;When:    November 2, 2008 (Sunday)   1:00 - 5:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Cost:      $10.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maplefarmsanctuary.org/home/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.maplefarms...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The family-friendly event will feature a presentation from&lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm Sanctuary co-founder Cheri Ezell-Vandersluis who&lt;br /&gt;will share the compelling story of how she and her husband,&lt;br /&gt;Jim, abruptly ended their profitable generations-long meat and&lt;br /&gt;dairy farming business to create a safe haven for animals.  We&lt;br /&gt;encourage event participants to get involved in protecting the&lt;br /&gt;rights of all animals by raising awareness about the cruelty&lt;br /&gt;that exists in the factory farming and fur industries.&lt;br /&gt;Attendees will also be treated to live performances by vegan&lt;br /&gt;musical guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tours of the beautiful Maple Farm Sanctuary grounds will be&lt;br /&gt;available throughout the event.  Tour participants will have&lt;br /&gt;the opportunity to learn the animals' stories and meet Cassie&lt;br /&gt;the cow, Piggie Wiggy the potbelly pig, Lucky the pony,&lt;br /&gt;Butterscotch the goat, along with llamas, chickens, horses,&lt;br /&gt;dogs and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sanctuary has taken in a fraction of the billions of farmed&lt;br /&gt;animals that are bought, sold, tormented and slaughtered by the&lt;br /&gt;meat, dairy and fur industries. They will live the remainder of&lt;br /&gt;their lives in peace, free to roam and meander the land.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are approximately 80 animals living at Maple Farm&lt;br /&gt;Sanctuary. This includes cows, horses, sheep, llamas, ducks,&lt;br /&gt;chickens, pigs, turkeys, dogs, goats, and a miniature pony.&lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm is located on 121 acres of beautiful farm land in&lt;br /&gt;Mendon, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michelle G. (Maple Farm Sanctuary Volunteer)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226013566000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223472563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary Open House</name><id>8921946</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225648800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/8921946/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/4/global_5794388.jpeg</photo_url></item>