<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Podunk Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03275</zip><lat>43.146908</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bear Brook State Park</name><city>Allenstown</city><id>5094622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note we will be using a different entrance to the park than we did on the previous 2 hikes here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turning off of NH-28 (Pinewood Road) in Allenstown where you see the sign for Bear Brook State Park proceed 3.2 miles on Deerfield Road. Turn right onto Podunk Road where you will see the signs in the first 2 pictures . Proceed 0.3 miles and turn right into the parking lot just before where the road splits and both roads are gated closed for the season (pictures 3 and 4).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;If you are traveling on Deerfield Rd coming from Deerfield just after the sign for Bear Brook Stables turn left onto Podunk Road at the sign in picture one.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 . &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;From the parking lot we will start and end a loop hike that is approximately 5.3 miles long. The total uphill gain for the hike is approximately 400 feet. Being a loop hike each time you ascend (elevation gain) or descend (elevation loss) somewhere on the hike you will be doing the opposite, eventually later on in the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This hike will use the Little Bear Trail and the Hayes Farm Trail to end up at Hayes March which is described in one guide book as "the view overlooking this wide watery expanse is one of the finest in the park". &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Next we will use the Carr Ridge Trail to hike to the Cascade Trail where we can view the cascades along Catamount Brook. Then finally we will hike along the Bear Brook Trail getting views of Bear Brook to get back to the starting point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/e/6/event_85011942.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/7/e/event_85012862.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 14px"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/d/1/0/event_85016592.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/d/c/event_85018332.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Drive a little ways past the driveway for 10 Podunk Road.  Where Campground Road and Podunk Road are gated closed for the season turn right into the large.parking lot for the X-C Skiers and Dog Sledders (pic 4) that is just before the gates and park.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326887031000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326166078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bear Brook State Park - 5.3 mile loop hike.</name><id>47444772</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326639600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/47444772/</event_url></item>