<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>156 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01834</zip><lat>42.768979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Groveland Fairways</name><city>Groveland</city><id>1075120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.018866</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's time to pay tribute and honor to survivors of breast cancer with a Passionately Pink Day! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; October is National Breast Cancer Awareness month and Groveland Fairways along with Dinkwater Productions will host the 5 Funny Females Comedy Tour. The debut of the Comedy Tour at Groveland Fairways on Saturday, October 17,2009 will raise funds that are critical in the search for the cure for breast cancer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Susan G. Komen Passionately Pink For the Cure is a fundraiser that encourages the community to take part in raising awareness of breast cancer. Pick your pink from subtle pink accessories to head-to-toe pink costumes and come out to see the all female comedy tour. The tour is hosted by stand up comedienne and NYC Friar’s Roaster, Susan Alexander along with Bethany Van Delft and Ellen Moschetto from the Boston Comedy Festival, Jessie Baade from Nick at Nite’s Funniest Mom in America, Chantal Carrere from ABC’s Fat March. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have retail therapy provided by Silpada Jewelry and Mary Kay Cosmetics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event includes a delicious appetizer buffet provided by Harborside Catering. Cash Bar&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256245408000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>women-303</urlname><id>472102</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Girls Night Out Shopping Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253818711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5 Funny Females Passionately Pink Event</name><id>11457679</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255824000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/women-303/events/11457679/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/d/global_10879037.jpeg</photo_url></item>