<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Class&lt;/b&gt; France, 2008 128 min. Directed by Laurent Cantet. Based upon the autobiographical novel of François Bégaudeau, the film features actual students and teachers in the cast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;One of the most anticipated  U.S. releases of the year, &lt;b&gt;The Class&lt;/b&gt;, was the first French film in 20 years to win the Palme d'Or, the top prize at the Cannes Film Festival and is a front-runner for the Best Foreign Language Film Oscar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note:&lt;/b&gt; The actual start time is 12:35 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;François (played by François Bégaudeau, who wrote the screenplay based on his own experiences) and his fellow teachers prepare for a new year at a high school in a tough neighborhood. Armed with the best intentions, they brace themselves to not let discouragement stop them from trying to give the best education to their students. Cultures and attitudes often clash in the classroom, a microcosm of contemporary France. As amusing and inspiring as the teenaged students can be, their difficult behavior can still jeopardize any teacher's enthusiasm for the low-paying job. François insists on an atmosphere of respect and diligence. Neither stuffy nor severe, his extravagant frankness often takes the students by surprise. But his classroom ethics are put to the test when his students begin to challenge his methods...  Kendall description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Class&lt;/b&gt; is a prime document of French post-colonial blues, though its relevance to American urban education could not be any greater if it had been made in the Bronx or Trenton or South Los Angeles. I would be surprised if this brilliant and touching film didn't become required viewing for teachers all over the United States. Everyone else should see it as well--it's a wonderful movie. &lt;br /&gt; New Yorker&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Offers a rich microcosm of today's multi-ethnic French population and fascinating insights into the complicated dilemmas and misunderstandings which teaching -- and indeed learning -- can entail.&lt;br /&gt;Screen International&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to The NY Times Review: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2008/09/26/movies/26clas.html?ref=movies" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And here's a link to the trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/video/imdb/vi3159556121/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a nearby restaurant for what I am sure will prove to be a lively discussion to say the least.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233024231000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Class at Kendall Theater</name><id>9608998</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234632600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9608998/</event_url></item>