<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A warm hello to you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;December’s Law of Attraction Meet-up Agenda &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most powerful gift you can give yourself, and thus to others, this holiday season:  &lt;br /&gt;Your Expanding Circle of Spirit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For me, the holiday season is symbolically about spiritual renewal - reminding ourselves that we are all born of spirit. &lt;u&gt;We are spirit&lt;/u&gt;. So for our December meeting, I wanted to come up with something that would have you powerfully feel your connection to Spirit/Source Energy. This is, after all, the foundation of the Law of Attraction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin with a Sacred Journey guided meditation.  This will have you bring your sense of spirit into various aspects of your life - your environments, behaviors, capabilities, beliefs and values, sense of self and your greater vision. This alone is a very powerful experience; but I'm going to take it even further.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there, we’ll then do a group exercise that will have you bringing this strong sense of spirit to problematic areas in your life and other contexts in which you want to feel your spiritual self present. We'll go through a lot of them. You're going to feel your spiritual field expand more and more, and we're going to connect that to what everyone in our group is feeling. So it will expand even more.  We’ll be creating an Expanding Circle of Spirit that will be carried forward into your daily life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My words may not do this justice. But just imagine feeling connected to your sense of your Spiritual self - to all Source Energy, and expanding that feeling more and more and more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So PLEASE find a way to join us, Tues., Dec. 16th. And invite others to join you, as well!  Remember to RSVP! (but, please, only if you know you will really be attending).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I CAN'T WAIT! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warmest heart,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann Ide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May the whole world live in happiness and peace.  It begins within you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be upstairs.  Go to back of front lobby for stairway.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232499364000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227056807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Your Expanding Circle of Spirit</name><id>9189353</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229472000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/9189353/</event_url></item>