<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>270 Broadway</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.820449</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 621-9660</phone><name>Columbus Theatre</name><city>Providence</city><id>786998</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.426594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On a stiflingly hot August morning in 1892, the parents of Lizzie Borden were found brutally axe-murdered in their home in Fall River, Mass. Lizzie Borden was the prime suspect. This led to a sensational murder trial, in which Lizzie was acquitted. But many people still believed she was guilty. This remains one of the most notorious -- and unsolved -- murders in history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lizziebordenlive.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lizzie Borden Live&lt;/a&gt; is a one-woman show about the real Lizzie Borden. The play is currently touring around the country, and will be in Providence for two nights at the historic &lt;a href="http://www.columbustheatre.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Columbus Theatre&lt;/a&gt;. The show has already won several awards and looks amazing! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Columbus Theatre is also pretty cool to see. It seems to have as colorful a past as Lizzie -- it is one of those beautiful old movie theatres that at one point degenerated into porn. It is now a venue for the esteemed Rhode Island Film Festival, and gets some pretty good films and shows. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please order your own ticket online -- this theatre is open seating, so we can sit together. And it has over 1,000 seats, so I don't think we'll have a problem. Also, it's fairly easy to get street parking on Broadway. The show starts at 8 p.m. -- let's meet at 7:30 to sit together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the show, if you're interested, we can go for drinks and apps at Julian's, a few doors down.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in theatre lobby at 7:30 pm -- I will email my cell after you RSVP</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228662199000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223815207000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lizzie Borden Live</name><id>8946488</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226795400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/8946488/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/e/global_5835022.jpeg</photo_url></item>