<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>397 Westminster Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821278</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Celtic Lounge Downtown</name><city>Providence</city><id>1378600</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415297</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar and restaurant scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Celtic Lounge at the corner of Westminster and Empire Streets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you remember the old Finnegan's Wake from the past, you'll be pleasantly surprised when you walk into Celtic Lounge. In 2011 this restaurant and bar changed management and has been completely renovated. It's a BIG difference and so much better! The bar is big and the lighting is warm. &lt;strong&gt;The drinks and food are good and best of all, there is a GIANT PROJECTION TV to watch the Patriots play the Houston Texans THIS MONDAY!!!&lt;/strong&gt; I have confirmed with the management that the game and sound will be on, so come on down, check out the Celtic Lounge during the MNM, then settle in and stay to watch the game!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thecelticlounge.com/"&gt;http://www.thecelticlounge.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Christopher and I will tag-team the hosting duties. I'll be there on the earlier side and he'll be there after 8pm, so look for us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the black hat or scarf in my picture, but we're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher</member_name><member_id>10240270</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355432843000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354935943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Celtic Lounge &amp; Patriots vs. Houston Texans!</name><id>94542592</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355180400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/94542592/</event_url></item>