<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;With an 8:00 start time, this Meetup starts a little later than most of our events. We're trying to figure out what time works the best now that we have two little ones in the house. We're hoping the big one will be on her way to bed as people are arriving. Because of the late start time, we'll make sure we have a game out ready to play right away (as normally, if we start a Meetup at 7:00, with all of the chatting, we don't start playing a game until nearly 8:00 anyway).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should you have a favorite game please bring it; otherwise, you know we're well stocked. You are also welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who have never attended a traditional game night, we usually split up in different rooms or areas to play smaller games of players' choice and then come together for a larger game or two at the end of the night. However, sometimes we just play large party games for the majority of the evening. It depends on the mood of the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats (one of whom is the Official Cat of Salem!), but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a hopefully well-behaved 2 year old, who will obviously not be locked up for the evening, but she will be in bed for the later part of the Meetup. We also have an infant, who isn't much of a game player, as he just eats and sleeps all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312765510000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312148076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Traditional Game Night</name><id>27726841</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312675200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/27726841/</event_url></item>