<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>559 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Paramount Center at Emerson College</name><city>Boston</city><id>1396188</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062536</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>1940, U.S.  The cinema of writer-director Preston Sturges—a prodigious talent whom film critic Manny Farber called &amp;quot;the most spectacular manipulator of sheer humor since Mark Twain&amp;quot;—is timelessly witty, often satirical and always compassionately sensitive to its characters’ human frailties and desires.  In &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Christmas in July,&lt;/span&gt; described by Andrew Sarris as one of Sturges’ emotionally richest and sweetest films, the American dream of overnight success is debunked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The most underrated of Sturges’ movies—&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Christmas in July&lt;/span&gt; is &lt;i&gt;a riotous comedy-satire about capitalism that bites so deep it hurts.&lt;/i&gt; This captures the mood of the Depression more completely than most 30s pictures, and the brilliantly polyphonic script repeats the hero's dim-witted slogan so many times that it eventually becomes a kind of crazed tribal incantation. As usual, Sturges's supporting cast is luminous, and he uses it like instruments in a madcap concerto.” – Jonathan Rosenbaum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As summarized by the Pacific Film Archive: a coffee company's advertising jingle contest turns into a corporate nervous breakdown when, by an absurd fluke, the prize is prematurely awarded to striving clerk Dick Powell for his entry, &lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&amp;quot;If you can't sleep, it isn't the coffee, it's the bunk.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tomatometer:  94%&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tragically underseen, this Preston Sturges comedy is all of 68 minutes long (including the credits) and is a freakin' laugh riot from start to finish - Christopher Null&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I do plan to get my fill of Linus and Wonderful Life, how about a Christmas event that few, if any, of us have seen.  Join me for a Friday before Christmas 'freaking laugh riot' at the wonderful new Bright Family Screening Room in the restored Paramount Theater.  After, we'll continue the laughing and maybe the rioting with drinks next door at Bina, or up the street at Rock Bottom, or wherever will have our motley crew.  God bless us, everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can be purchased in advance at &lt;a href="https://artsemerson.org/Online/default.asp?doWork::WScontent::loadArticle=Load&amp;amp;BOparam::WScontent::loadArticle::article_id=46D8854D-AAEF-497C-A669-61CFB8AE179C" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See You at the Movie,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for John holding a red Meetup sign after the closing credits.  We will wait as a group until the theater is empty before leaving for post-film discussion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292725550000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290559194000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas in July</name><id>15541989</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292630400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15541989/</event_url></item>