<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Waveny Park</address_2><address_1>681 South Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06840</zip><lat>41.126831</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.972.1895</phone><name>Carriage Barn Arts Center</name><city>New Canaan</city><id>771603</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.485588</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>New Canaan Society for the Arts presents:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spectrum 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Juried Art Exhibition&lt;br /&gt;4-6PM&lt;br /&gt;Admission to art exhibitions is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Carriage Barn Art Center&lt;br /&gt;in the Betty Barker Gallery&lt;br /&gt;A unique Nineteeth Century stone barn on the grounds of a former estate is home to the exceptional exhibition and performance space of The Carriage Barn Arts Center in Waveny Park, New Canaan, CT.  The Carriage Barn is sponsored by the New Canaan Society for the Arts (NCSA), a member-supported, non-profit community cultural organization.&lt;br /&gt;Dedicated volunteers restored the historic barn in 1977 and established NCSA to promote community interest through participation in and appreciation of the visual and performing arts.  NCSA continues its mission today as a welcoming, inclusive arts center that encourages creative expression, celebrates artistic achievement, and enriches the community as a whole.&lt;br /&gt;The Carriage Barn is host to several premier art exhibitions annually, including two major juried events and curated exhibitions of member and invited artists, as well as art classes for adults and children, lectures, and a variety of live musical performances in the NCSA Acoustic Series and the Waveny Chamber Society concerts.  All events are open to the public.  Admission to art exhibitions is free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>will wear the bw scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273003733000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270052956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spectrum 2010</name><id>13048389</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272830400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13048389/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/a/global_14046426.jpeg</photo_url></item>