<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Westborough Spirituality Meetup member,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How are you?  &lt;br /&gt;How was your holidays? Wish you all well!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is our December meetup which everyone has been waiting for. Hope you all can join me! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We had a wonderful discussion last time. Thanks for all your sharing and inputs. It was great!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last time, we discussed about &amp;quot;Causation&amp;quot;. It is like an old saying&amp;quot; What comes around goes around&amp;quot;. Everything happened to us has a reason. If we haven't understood that we may suffer from the process of learning.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we can transform our mindset, then everything around us could be very different. I am the one starting the peaceful energy and I am also the one stopping the vicious cycle. Even it is a tinny thing, it may make a huge different.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we are going to share and discuss more about how to transform ourselves. Look at world in a peaceful way! It is also a spiritual practice. So we have deeper understanding about spiritual being.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to meet more friends with the same interest about seeking a spiritual life, please come and share your thoughts and experiences about how to practice spirituality in daily life.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the day and let's create positive energy to the whole world. Hope see you all in our meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It will be the 2nd building on your right hand side when you drive into condos.You can park any place.  call me if you can not find it 6172237166</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan</member_name><member_id>4981726</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293394221000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spirituality-149</urlname><id>670379</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5999984741</group_lon><name>The Westborough Spirituality Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292386992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westborough Spiritual December  Meetup</name><id>15738276</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293390000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/events/15738276/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/6/global_2055446.jpeg</photo_url></item>