<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Sandy Ln</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02889</zip><lat>41.711296</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Warwick Public Library</name><city>Warwick</city><id>716684</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.402734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be discussing the book &lt;u&gt;MARCHING TOWARD HELL&lt;/u&gt; by Michael Scheuer,PhD and a twenty-plus-year CIA veteran. Scheuer headed the agency's Osama bin Laden unit, managed its covert-action operations, and authored its rendition program. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He begins by pointing out that our bipartisan governing elite has an&lt;br /&gt;unquenchable ardor to have the U.S. intervene abroad in all places.&lt;br /&gt;Some prefer diplomatic, others military, humanitarian, covert, and/or&lt;br /&gt;foreign aid mixed with Christian proselytizing.  &lt;u&gt;Marching&lt;br /&gt;Toward Hell&lt;/u&gt; claims that U.S. foreign policy is often based on&lt;br /&gt;faulty assumptions and can be driven by lobbyists whose interests are&lt;br /&gt;different than those of the American people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Scheuer sacrificed his career at the CIA in order to publicly denounce the 9/11&lt;br /&gt;Commission for having become politicized. He did this at a time when&lt;br /&gt;other insiders protected their careers and are only now coming out.&lt;br /&gt;He's also superb at explaining the relationship between the&lt;br /&gt;intelligence community and elected officials in the U.S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: this is a WEDNESDAY...not a Monday as usual.  But as per usual, tasty organic snacks will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a friend and join our discussion even if you have not read the book.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachael McIntosh</member_name><member_id>5611356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283998345000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FreedomIsFundamental</urlname><id>1191429</id><group_lat>41.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>FREEDOM IS FUNDAMENTAL Book Club and Discussion Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280754748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MARCHING TOWARD HELL  by Michael Scheuer</name><id>14289651</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283985000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FreedomIsFundamental/events/14289651/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/a/e/global_16922990.jpeg</photo_url></item>