<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like to invite you to a last minute dinner opportunity at Birch Street Bistro in Roslindale.  Please bring cash, enough to cover your meal, drinks, tax and tip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Magazine&lt;br /&gt;Best of Boston for Neighborhood Nightlife in the Roslindale area. &lt;br /&gt;Zagat - Rating Excellent&lt;br /&gt;Located in &amp;quot;up and coming&amp;quot; Roslindale this &amp;quot;hip bistro&amp;quot; draws locals to its beautiful bar&lt;br /&gt;a chic and inviting place for a drink from the well chosen wine list.&lt;br /&gt;Best of Citysearch - Highly Recommended&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Birch Street Bistro is my new favorite place. The food is tremendous with lots of variety.  The staff is great and the atmosphere is very cool.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert Nadeau, The Boston Phoenix&lt;br /&gt;I thought Roslindale Square was pretty well set for restaurants, but the Birch Street Bistro has eclipsed them all.  Seldom has a restaurant outside the competitive zones shown such accomplishment at opening.  Hardly anything on the menu is really new, yet everything has a twist or an improvement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relax and enjoy the casually chic dining experience of the Birch Street Bistro.  New menu selections include a variety of items that are sure to please.  Zagat and Citysearch have deemed the Birch Street Bistro with excellent ratings all due to customer satisfaction.  The high ceilings with huge oversized guilded hanging lamps and brick wall reflected in huge mirrors make the space dramatic and comfortable.  The music and friendly, professional staff add to the inviting ambiance.  The Birch Street Bistro also has a full service bar and wine list.  Be sure to check out our updated menus!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Birch Street Bistro&lt;br /&gt;14 Birch Street - Roslindale, MA 02131&lt;br /&gt;Tel: 617-323-2184   FAX: 617-323-2183&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: info@birchstbistro.com&lt;br /&gt;Sun-Tues 5-9:00pm |  Wed 5-9:30pm  |  Thurs-Sat 5-10:30pm&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my photo, ask for Lisa @ hostess station</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240023244000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238953533000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Monday Night Dinner: Birch Street Bistro in Roslindale</name><id>10120217</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239059700000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10120217/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/9/global_7992777.jpeg</photo_url></item>