<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Brookside Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.313293</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Egleston Farmers Market</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>11628662</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103462</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Follow us on Facebook, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/419217191491096/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/419217191491096/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/7/0/event_202884432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I wanted to share with you this exciting campaign of Boston Collaborative for Food and Fitness kicking off the weekend of February 16th and 17th at the Egleston Farmers Market and Dorchester Winter Farmers' Market respectively. Celebrate the Fruits of our Ocean, a year-long campaign promoting local seafood in the community. Both winter markets now offer fresh seafood from local dayboat fishermen procured by Red’s Best, a Boston based seafood distributor that offers seasonal dayboat and traceable seafood direct to consumers at farmers markets and as well as wholesalers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking demonstrations from top local chefs will allow market goers to taste a variety of seafood dishes prepared, on the spot, right at the market. The Egleston Market event includes a &lt;strong&gt;Food Truck vs. Restaurant “Seafood Throwdown” on February 16th from 11am-2pm featuring Chef Irene Li of Mei Mei Street Kitchen Food Truck and Chef Marcos Santos from Tres Gatos.&lt;/strong&gt; They will be cooking up their best seafood dishes with an mystery local seafood that is fresh caught and paired with local ingredients from the market. Tastings will be available for pre-registered participants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/6/8/event_202889032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;While many market goers already trek to a variety of markets around the city to stock up on fresh vegetables, meats, eggs and cheeses, they can now shop for seafood from local New England fisheries all season long. This campaign is an educational platform to help the public understand what sustainable fishing means and why it is so important to our community and our ocean. Embracing the diversity of species caught by the local, dayboat, independent fishing boats is even more important now as fishing for the traditionally popular species is curtailed even further. Boston Collaborative for Food and Fitness and its partners are striving to educate the community about the health benefits of seafood, what sustainable seafood is really all about, and the importance of supporting the community based fisheries, how to prepare, store and utilize the entire fish in their recipes, while encouraging people to explore the vast diversity of seafood in the Atlantic Ocean.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Collaborative for Food and Fitness is a city-wide partnership that is dedicated to improve community health through a comprehensive approach addressing issues related to equity in our food and fitness environments. It promotes living a healthy lifestyle by creating conditions for physical activity into the daily lives of residents and addresses the disparity in accessibility to nutritious, local food. BCFF is made up of a diverse team of individuals that represent a variety of sectors including community groups, health care, government, public health, youth development and more. BCFF has partnered with The Northwest Atlantic Marine Alliance and Health Care Without Harm as they strive to improve the community health in similar ways. Through this collaboration, BCFF, NAMA and HCWH are raising awareness about the health benefits of seafood. The promotion of the responsible fishing practices will ensure the sustainability of New England seafood for generations to come.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>seafood event, Egleston Farmers Market, Celebrate the fruits of our ocean, chef demo, sustainable seafood, free event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicola Williams</member_name><member_id>9817670</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361041383000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360350106000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate the Fruits of our Ocean-Sustainable Seafood Event in Jamaica Plain</name><id>103693372</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361030400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/103693372/</event_url></item>