<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Salem, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.523510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>812-240-3236</phone><name>Salem Common</name><city>Salem</city><id>365193</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Getting underway for the 2008 season has proven difficult, not leastwise because of mistakes on my part.  Last week traffic increased my commute by a half-hour, and I didn't have a backup plan in place to help get the Meetup going.  However, there were a few of us who showed up and tossed the disc, which was a good deal of fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Toward the end of last weeks meeting several other groups of people arrived at the Common and began playing frisbee.  I spoke with several of the people, and they all expressed an interest in a weekly get-together.  I will make a concerted effort to continue to spread the word, but in the short-term I think that word of mouth could be a great way to get more people involved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on their comments and my own late arrival, I am posting the next two meetups to start later in the evening.  Right now it is light enough to legitimately play until 8 pm, so a 6:45 start should offer sufficient play time while giving more flexibility for evening commuters.  Flyers have been drafted, and I'll begin placing them around town this week.  I'll also cross-post the event on the Salem Board Game meetup, New in Town meetup, and on Craigslist.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing near the pavilion on the Common with a stack of orange cones and a disc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211064912000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ultimate Frisbee Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemfrisbee</urlname><id>666957</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Ultimate Frisbee Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210537907000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Frisbee on the Common, 5/15/2008</name><id>7918368</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210891500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemfrisbee/events/7918368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/d/global_2046557.jpeg</photo_url></item>