<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Raving fans of your organization make it possible for you to effectively and successfully:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- spread the word about your important organization, cause, event or campaign,&lt;br /&gt;- engage and keep the right donors, sponsors, volunteers and supporters, and&lt;br /&gt;- execute successful fundraising initiatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me in welcoming Lisa Morrissey, President of LIDO Consulting Group, for an engaging and informative presentation that will leave you with practical and effective strategies for developing and growing your organization’s raving fan base who will help you to raise more money; spread your organization’s good word, and increase the number and level of your supporters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa is president and co-founder of LIDO Consulting Group, a marketing strategy company that specializes in customer care and internal branding. LIDO has helped many non-profit organizations to grow and to improve their fundraising efforts by developing and executing marketing and public relations strategies that include providing their supporters with the best customer care experience at each and every touch-point. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  I think I've found a location - will add that info once it's confirmed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you in a couple of weeks!&lt;br /&gt;~Monique&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monique Morimoto Flaherty</member_name><member_id>8025083</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271978111000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270260973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raving Fans! </name><id>13073397</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271804400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/13073397/</event_url></item>