<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>161 Elliott Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.557865</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Danversport Yacht Club</name><city>Danvers</city><id>12130952</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.917450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Let's sample food (appetizers, entrees, and deserts) from some of the areas most loved restaurants in this buffet-style event. Music provided by Bedrock Music, and there will be some auction items. Cash bar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;RESTAURANTS include Legal Seafood, Danversport Yacht Club, Burtons, Century House, Kellys Roast Beef, Maki Sushi Bar, Not Your Average Joes, Stonewood Tavern, Perfectos Cafe, Ipswich Clam Bar, Scosso Ristorante and Martini Bar, Teresas Italian Eatery, Polcaris , Qdoba Mexican Grill, Santoros of Peabody, and LOTS more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;RSVP. Please RSVP only if you ARE going to attend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;TICKETS. $35, at the door or in advance.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;IN ADVANCE: You'll avoid waiting on line if you have your ticket in advance. An advantage !! Mail a check to Peabody Rotary, P.O. Box 94, Peabody MA -- but be sure there is enough time for them to mail you your ticket (in your stamped and self-addressed envelope).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;AT THE DOOR: Credit cards accepted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;FINDING EACH OTHER. Event starts at 6:00. At 6:15, let's meet in back left corner of ballroom. From 6:15 until 6:30 will be strolling around in leftmost row of buffet tables. Look for me in SILVER TOP (with blond curls). If you give me your cell phone number and you arrive later, I'll e-mail you my cell phone number and you can text me when you arrive so we can find each other.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;QUESTIONS. This event is being sponsored by Rotary (the Peabody chapter). Contact Vanessa Silveira at vsilveira@metrocu.org or call her at (978) 326-5801.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Event is in Ballroom, starts at 6:00. Meet at 6:15 in the left back corner of ballroom. I'll be wearing a SILVER top. From 6:15 until 6:30 will be strolling around LEFTMOST row of buffet tables. See below for more details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gale_2</member_name><member_id>10931980</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363741687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362683105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taste of the North Shore</name><id>108125922</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363730400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/108125922/</event_url></item>