<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.076322</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Rusty Hammer</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>1023192</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/a/3/c/event_167671292.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Our book selection for the month of November is &lt;strong&gt;Gone Girl&lt;/strong&gt; by Gillian Flynn.  Here is an overview of Gone Girl from the publisher:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marriage can be a real killer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most critically acclaimed suspense writers of our time, New York Times bestseller Gillian Flynn takes that statement to its darkest place in this unputdownable masterpiece about a marriage gone terribly, terribly wrong. The Chicago Tribune&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;proclaimed that her work “draws you in and keeps you reading with the force of a pure but nasty addiction.” Gone Girl’s toxic mix of sharp-edged wit and deliciously chilling prose creates a nerve-fraying thriller that confounds you at every turn.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On a warm summer morning in North Carthage, Missouri, it is Nick and Amy Dunne’s fifth wedding anniversary. Presents are being wrapped and reservations are being made when Nick’s clever and beautiful wife disappears from their rented McMansion on the Mississippi River. Husband-of-the-Year Nick isn’t doing himself any favors with cringe-worthy daydreams about the slope and shape of his wife’s head, but passages from Amy's diary reveal the alpha-girl perfectionist could have put anyone dangerously on edge. Under mounting pressure from the police and the media—as well as Amy’s fiercely doting parents—the town golden boy parades an endless series of lies, deceits, and inappropriate behavior. Nick is oddly evasive, and he’s definitely bitter—but is he really a killer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As the cops close in, every couple in town is soon wondering how well they know the one that they love. With his twin sister, Margo, at his side, Nick stands by his innocence. Trouble is, if Nick didn’t do it, where is that beautiful wife? And what was in that silvery gift box hidden in the back of her bedroom closet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With her razor-sharp writing and trademark psychological insight, Gillian Flynn delivers a fast-paced, devilishly dark, and ingeniously plotted thriller that confirms her status as one of the hottest writers around.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And some editorial reviews:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Library Journal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy disappears on her fifth wedding anniversary, and while Nick has not been a model husband, could he really have killed her? It's soon evident that if Amy is dead, that's the least of the reader's worries. Flynn's last novel, Dark Objects, was a New York Times best seller, but this one is expected to break her out.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The New York Times&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;…&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Gone Girl&lt;/span&gt; is Ms. Flynn's dazzling breakthrough. It is wily, mercurial, subtly layered and populated by characters so well imagined that they're hard to part with—even if, as in Amy's case, they are already departed. And if you have any doubts about whether Ms. Flynn measures up to Patricia Highsmith's level of discreet malice, go back and look at the small details. Whatever you raced past on a first reading will look completely different the second time around.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;In case you missed the meetup on &lt;strong&gt;One Hundred Names for Love&lt;/strong&gt;, here is my review:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.seacoastonline.com/seacoast-nh-books/2012/10/09/one-hundred-names-for-love-by-diane-ackerman/"&gt;One Hundred Names for Love Book Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just ask the bartender or hostess.  We usually meet upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob Lamothe</member_name><member_id>6364190</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>7202411</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8977543</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352908074000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portsmouth-Book-Club</urlname><id>1147811</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth Book Club Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348680606000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Portsmouth Book Club November - Gone Girl</name><id>dpskncyqpbrb</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352851200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portsmouth-Book-Club/events/84200062/</event_url></item>