<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Thorne Hill Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03846</zip><lat>44.180000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Skimos Lodge</name><city>Jackson</city><id>458965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.190000</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>X-country and downhill ski weekend in Jackson, NH...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been invited by our member Ralph to spend one, two or three nights (Fri-Sun) at the Skimos Lodge in Jackson, NH. This event is limited to the first &lt;b&gt;12&lt;/b&gt; members who respond and send a check reserving your space. If 12 slots are already full email me directly and I will start a wait list. More space may open up depending on how many Skimo members go up that weekend. Skimos is a members only lodge with separate rooms for men and women with shared rooms and bunk beds (new mattresses). Cost is $25 per night, you BYO food, drinks and bedding. The house has a huge kitchen, living room, fireplace, large dining room, etc.  Check out the web site and click on the photo of the house for more photos. &lt;a href="http://www.skimos.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skimos.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition there is a chef that provides Saturday night and Sunday night dinner for $14 per meal to anyone who signs up in advance.  He also prepares a full breakfast every morning for $6 per breakfast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be three ski club parties in the valley that all guests are invited to.  The first runs from 4pm - 7pm on Saturday.  The evening party runs 9pm-1am Saturday night.  The third is on Sunday from 4pm-7pm.  Tickets are $10 and include an open bar.  The Sat. evening party will feature a live band. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about skiing, taking lessons and rentals go to &lt;a href="http://www.jacksonxc.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jacksonxc....&lt;/a&gt; . For downhill skiers it is conveniently located near Wildcat, Attitash and Cranmore.  Pack your woolies, a bottle of wine and let's go!&lt;br /&gt;Sorry, no maybes for this event. You will be given an address to send your check when you reply and your response will be counted when your payment is received. Last date to sign up is January 10th. If for any reason the event is canceled you will be notified by January 13th and your money will be refunded.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200961332000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198287388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Martin Luther King Ski Weekend</name><id>6952695</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200744000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/6952695/</event_url></item>