<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A noirish thriller from the director of &lt;i&gt;Nightwatch&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Brattle schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ole Bornedal returns to quicken the pulse of thriller fans with this genre-bending tale of a crime scene photographer and family man who is violently shaken out of his suburban malaise following a fateful car accident. Jonas makes his living by capturing gruesome crime scenes in all of their lurid detail, yet lately the beleaguered shutterbug has grown increasingly despondent in both his career and his personal life. One day, while driving through the city, Jonas and his family are involved in a car accident (one of the most spectacular crashes ever committed to film by the way) with a young woman named Julia. Unconscious due to the impact of the crash, Julia is rushed to the hospital. Later, a concerned Jonas makes a special trip to check in on Julia, and finds her comatose in her hospital bed and surrounded by loved ones. Having never actually met her boyfriend Sebastian, Julia's family immediately assumes that Jonas is the man they've all heard so much about as of late. While Jonas is all too willing to step into the role for the time being, his ruse grows complicated when Julia awakens with amnesia and he must fill the role of a man he has never met. Marrying film noir themes with sometimes graphic violence and a winkingly ironic title, Bornedal has crafted a twisting and sharp thriller that proves a nightmarish reflection of one man’s extreme mid-life crisis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info, including trailer, &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/090328.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know in the RSVP whether you plan to stay for the after-film discussion at one of many exciting local eateries!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait in front of the stage/screen after the film (may not have Meetup sign)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236381458000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Just Another Love Story</name><id>9899031</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238274900000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9899031/</event_url></item>