<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>623 Trapelo Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.404760</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John M. Sullivan Post #10334 - VFW</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1114517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.217073</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a dance put on by the Boston Beanstalks Tall Club.  It’s been some time since the BBTC hosted a dance, so if you haven't already been to a Tall Dance, where you are not looking down on the whole group, here's a rare chance since these dances don't happen so often anymore.  I remember my first Tall Dance, and it was quite an experience to be among so many tall, not to mention well-dressed people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a a VFW hall, which may sound casual, but here's the description: &amp;quot;This brand-new, beautifully appointed hall has hardwood floors throughout for dancing, a full bar, and plenty of parking. It has the distinction of being the first VFW post in Massachusetts to be named for a Vietnam veteran. Their bartender will take care of all your beverage needs, there will be plenty of munchies, and a DJ will provide tunes to keep your feet happy!&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's not only open to tall people -- anyone can come, so you can bring a friend if you'd like, even if they are not tall. And please come up and say hello to me, Linda -- I'll be easy to spot because I'll be wearing a black dress with red roses down the front! Perhaps I can introduce you around...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $12 at the door, or $10 in advance, and you can pay through PayPal at this link: &lt;a href="http://tall.meetup.com/15/calendar/11822662/payonlinenow/"&gt;http://tall.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 95: Take exit 28, Trapelo Road, east toward Waltham/Belmont. Continue eastward on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2: Take exit 54, Waltham Street, and follow southward, crossing Route 2. Waltham Street will change to Lexington Street. At junction with Trapelo Road, turn left and continue on Trapelo. The building is on the corner of Trapelo Road and Marguerite Ave. Parking is behind the building as well as on Marguerite Ave.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259023391000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tall Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostontallsingles</urlname><id>1235066</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Tall Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258303288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tall Harvest Dance</name><id>11878779</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258849800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostontallsingles/events/11878779/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/global_7950177.jpeg</photo_url></item>