<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 2-day lovely fall hike on the Appalachian Trail starting at Bulls Bridge in South Kent, CT and heading southbound to Rte. 55 in West Pawling, NY for a total of about 17.8 miles. This is the next segment of the AT southbound from way back in May '06 for the group. We've been doing northbound segments for a while so it's time for a change. We'll spend the night at a shelter on the trail (there's a good chance it will be full so plan accordingly). This hike is for moderate hikers who have done 10 mile hikes before as well as lightly equiped backpacking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Saturday will be mostly cloudy with a high of 54 and an overnight low of 31. Sunday will be sunny with a high of 57. Low 20% chance of rain both days. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at Noon at the Bulls Bridge parking area on Bulls Bridge Rd. (see below). The first day we'll cover 4.8 miles. We'll hike up Ten Mile Hill (named after nearby river) to 1,000 ft. altitude. Then we'll cross into NY and sleep at the Wiley Shelter. We should be getting to the by 4 pm to set up for the night, eat dinner, and enjoy the evening. The shelter hould be reserved for solo hikers so please try to bring a light tent and/or share tent space. If there is space, we can use it after nightfall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the second day, we'll continue starting 7:30 am sharp as we have limited daylight and 13 miles to cover. We'll end at the parking area for the AT on Rte. 55 near West Pawling, NY. Altitude range for the day will be to about 1,100 ft, down to 500 ft., up to 1,200 ft., and finish at 700 ft. We should end hiking by about 5:30 pm. Then we'll shuttle back to the cars at Bulls Bridge. If there is interest, we'll hit a place to eat in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we should come in earlier than I estimated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Full pack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold mornings/nights &amp;amp; cool afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet. Plus second day's clothing.&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket -just in case&lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag -3 season, good to 20 F&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp -LED version best&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking tent -or share/use shelter&lt;br /&gt;* 2 quarts water&lt;br /&gt;* 4 meals for on the trail -DAY-1: lunch, supper; DAY-2: breakfast, lunch (all trash to be packed out!). High energy meals should be planned. Only supper may be cooked but if getting up early (6:30 AM) then breakfast can be cooked too.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;* Bear bag &amp;amp; 15' min light weight rope -for food&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Mess kit -If needed&lt;br /&gt;* Camping utensils&lt;br /&gt;* Pocket knife&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking first aid kit (for blisters &amp;amp; such)&lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking stove and fuel -if cooking&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproof matches&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* AT trail map -Massachusetts &amp;amp; Connecticut: Massachusetts Section 1, 2, &amp;amp; 3 (Map One) (VT line to Dalton, MA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the meetup location &amp;amp; AT starting point, parking area on Bulls Bridge Rd. in South Kent, CT via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=South+Kent&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=275+Bulls+Bridge+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT hike ending point, Rte. 55 in West Pawling, NY via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=West+Pawling&amp;amp;state=NY&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.59&amp;amp;longitude=-73.660599&amp;amp;geocode=CITY" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shuttle from the Manchester, CT area is possible for up to 5 additional hikers (contact Kevin S). If more than 7 people sign up we'll need an additional car at the hike endpoint to shuttle back to the start (contact Kevin S if you can help out).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be with Janice's silver Jeep Liberty at the dirt parking area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226028282000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224131060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from S. Kent, CT to W. Pawling, NY</name><id>8971876</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224346500000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8971876/</event_url></item>