<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>MIT</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 56, Room 114</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8183212</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093460</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be an opportunity to learn more about the plight of the survivors of the gas-leakage tragedy in Bhopal - through the movie and the Q &amp;amp; A at the panel discussion that will follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the Bhopal Disaster:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On December 3rd, 1984, the city of Bhopal in Madhya Pradesh, India suffered the world’s worst industrial disaster. A chemical plant belonging to Union Carbide (now a subsidiary of Dow Chemical) released 40 tons of methyl isocyanate, a highly toxic chemical, immediately killing 4,000 people and affecting over 500,000 residents of the area. Till now, over 25,000 people have died as a result of the disaster, and thousands of Bhopalis are suffering from illnesses caused by exposure and water contamination due to the toxic waste left behind. On average, one person dies every day from its effects. Meanwhile, Indian authorities have failed to bring Union Carbide and Dow to account. Moreover, despite the repeated promises to clean up the toxic wastes, it remains, poisoning the water, the land, and spreading its tentacles every passing day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is also an act of protest against Dow's inclusion as a sponsor of the upcoming Summer Olympic Games in London.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the movie:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Bhopali" is Max Carlson's tribute to the resilient spirit of the Bhopal survivors and victims' struggle for justice. A heart-rendering, impressively polished account documenting the build-up of the disaster and its aftermath, it has won numerous awards, including the best documentary award at the New York Indo-American Arts Council Film Festival and the jury award at the Beverly Hills Film Festival. &lt;br /&gt;

 Movie website: &lt;a&gt;http://www.bhopalithemovie.com/ &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; Movie trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ttD-1oT9M7M"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ttD-1oT9M7M&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the International Campaign for Justice in Bhopal (ICJB):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Campaign for Justice in Bhopal is a group working with members of South Asian and human rights communities to ensure justice for the survivors of the Bhopal Chemical Disaster. Besides trying to engender support for the cause and work towards providing justice, our group is trying to build a movement that seeks to ensure that there are No More Bhopals as a result of gross negligence and lack of corporate responsibility (Union Carbide/ Dow Chemical), here or anywhere else in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/490308427653259/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/490308427653259/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342314426000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342151635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bhopali: a documentary</name><id>73157542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342303200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/73157542/</event_url></item>