<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.378188</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.495.3045 </phone><name>Harvard Museum of Natural History, Geological Lecture Hall </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>845303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116422</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>How can we foster productive discussion and resolution of critical issues when scientific knowledge is not complete? What happens when evidence is enough to persuade experts, but is unconvincing to others? Join us for Persuasion in a Climate of Uncertainty, a panel discussion on science, policy making, and skepticism, on Wednesday, Sept. 29, at 6 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelists include: Sheila Jasanoff, Pforzheimer Professor of Science and Technology Studies at the Harvard Kennedy School; James J. McCarthy, Agassiz Professor of Biological Oceanography at Harvard and past president of the American Assn. for the Advancement of Science; and Bruce Gellerman, award-winning reporter, Public Radio's Living on Earth. Moderated by Allan Brandt, Kass Professor of the History of Medicine at Harvard Medical School. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public in the Geological Lecture Hall, 24 Oxford St. Reception sponsored by Sigma Xi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit the &lt;a href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/lectures_and_special_events/index.php#persuasion" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Museum of Natural History's special events website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth</member_name><member_id>8893636</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285854996000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284673644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Panel Discussion: Persuasion in a Climate of Uncertainty</name><id>14796120</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285797600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/14796120/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>