<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Mount Major near West Alton is a rocky summit with extensive views of Lake Winnipesaukee and the Belknap Range, and even the White Mountains in clear weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The summit of Mount Major has an elevation of 1786 feet. A very nice loop is made by the ascent of the Mt Major Trail and the descent of the Belknap &amp;amp; Brook Trails. Round trip is 3.9 miles, 1150' of elevation gain in a book time of 2.5 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Mount Major Trail Descriptions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

There is an extensive trail network in the Belknap Range; The two most popular routes up Mount Major:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Main Trail (BLUE BLAZES): Take the obvious woods road which leaves the R side of the parking lot as you face the mountain. There are BLUE BLAZES but you won't need them to follow the road. Almost within sight of the parking lot, the road forks; either fork is OK but make sure everyone in your party goes the same way if you don't want to waste much of the day looking for them. After the two rejoin, the blue blazes and the Main Trail turn left at another junction about .8 miles from the parking lot. The road becomes a footpath, often with several branches which usually rejoin. There are a number of rock slabs to ascend, and because this trail is on the N side and gets a lot of foot traffic, it may be the iciest route up in cold weather. The trail climbs over a small knoll then steeply up the rocks to the summit. Distance from parking lot: 1.8 miles. &lt;br /&gt;

On the return, look for blue blazes dropping off to the NE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Brook Trail (YELLOW BLAZES): Follow the Main Trail for .8 miles, then go straight following YELLOW BLAZES where the Main Trail turns L. After a dip, the trail follows an old road up along the brook - in wet weather some of the trail seems like a brook, and crossings may be difficult at times of high water. At the col between Straightback and Mt. Major, turn L on the blue-blazed trail to reach the summit. A route up from the S joins from the R shortly beyond. Distance from parking lot: 2.4 miles. &lt;br /&gt;

On the return, take the trail heading W toward Mt. Belknap, then go R at the col. Do not take the trail to Straightback Mtn., which does not lead "straight back" to the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Directions: Parking lot is on the left hand side or Route 11 just 4.2 miles north of the town of Alton Bay. There is a sign on route 11. Trailhead is on the back right side of the parking lot if you are facing the mountain. There is a small trail on the left back side of the parking lot but this is not the trail for Mt Major. 43.5193°N, 71.2738°W (WGS84)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to Meetup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP for this event. 3 "yes" RSVP's would qualify the event to be a Meetup. (less is an option of the hikers) &lt;br /&gt;

# **All RSVP's must be posted by 9PM the night before the event. Maybe RSVP's will be considered no shows after this time. Any cancellations will also be posted by 9 PM the night before the hike and the other hikers should be notified. &lt;br /&gt;

# Communicate, share cell phone numbers, and be reliable. &lt;br /&gt;

# Carpooling is encouraged- Please add requests and ride offers to your RSVP comments. &lt;br /&gt;

# As always, you are responsible for being prepared for the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If time allows after the hike we can go to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patricks Pub and Brewery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18 Weirs Rd&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gilford, NH 03249-6303 (603) 293-0841&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its just off Rt 11&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362334734000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361823705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Hike Mt Major</name><id>106361712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362322800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/106361712/</event_url></item>