<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Main Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02837</zip><lat>41.530945</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-635-2985</phone><name>The Barn</name><city>Adamsville (Little Compton)</city><id>1168712</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.164072</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For February's brunch, we'll visit a quaint little breakfast restaurant called The Barn in Adamsville RI.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of our members, Susan, has suggested this spot and says it's a nice place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They don't have a web site but here's some info I googled: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Barn&lt;br /&gt;Rustic, yet oh so civilized!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;16 Main Road, Adamsville, Little Compton&lt;br /&gt;(401) 635-2985&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in a real 200-year-old renovated barn, and in a corner of the state that few Rhode Islanders ever visit, you won't find a more bucolic setting for breakfast than The Barn. In good weather the French doors fitted into the big barn door are open, and there is dining on an outdoor patio. The menu includes Adamsville Johnnycakes, which, in keeping with East Bay tradition, are the thinnest we've ever had. There are also several other locally named items, like the Portuguese Omelet (chourico, peppers, onions, cheddar cheese), the Westport River Omelet (lobster, broccoli, Swiss cheese), Eggs Blackstone (two poached eggs, bacon, and sliced tomato served on two English muffins with hollandaise sauce), or Eggs Sakonnet (two poached eggs on two English muffins with asparagus, lobster, and hollandaise sauce). For a breakfast you can hold in your hand, try the Barnwich (Canadian bacon, egg, and cheese on a croissant). Wash it all down with a tall glass of coffee milk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep an eye out for veteran waitress Terri Ryan. She'll be the one balancing your food on her head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Barn is open Monday-Friday, 6am-11:30am; and 7am-12:30pm on the weekend. Closed Thanksgiving and Christmas Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Awards&lt;br /&gt;Providence Phoenix: Best Reason to Break out a Map and Find Adamsville (2002).&lt;br /&gt;Rhode Island Monthly's Best of Rhode Island: Best Overall Breakfast (1990, 1991), Best Breakfast in the Country (1992, 1994, 1995).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maryanne</member_name><member_id>7323514</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266941460000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends who brunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Brunch-Bunch</urlname><id>964634</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Brunch Bunch !</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264099517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Brunch - The Barn</name><id>12384109</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266768000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Brunch-Bunch/events/12384109/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/7/f/global_4147919.jpeg</photo_url></item>