<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Manchester Land Conservation Trust will lead a free hike on Tuesday, July 22 at 5:45 p.m., rain or shine at Risley Park, the Trust’s largest parcel of protected land. Join us after work for a 1-1/4-hour walk around the pond. Children and families are especially welcome. The terrain is rocky and sometimes wet, so hikers should wear sturdy shoes or boots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants should park in the Lake Street lot across from Amy Drive on the north side of Risley Pond; additional parking is available along Amy Drive. Questions may be directed to Malcolm Barlow, President of the Trust, 646-4081 or Susan Barlow at the email sbarlow627@aol.com.  The Land Trust owns and protects 303 acres of open space in Manchester and nearby towns. Find out more about the Land Trust at www.manchesterlandtrust.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aproximate location/directions via MapQuest (to Amy Dr./Lake St intersection):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Vernon+Rockville&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Amy+Dr" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Manchester Land Trust:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.manchesterlandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manchester...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Susan B (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/7644854/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>7644854</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216936573000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>A easy hiking experience!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216702862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MLCT Hike at Risley Pond in Vernon CT</name><id>8386951</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216763100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8386951/</event_url></item>