<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Piper Mountain &lt;br /&gt;Lat/Lon: 43.50370°N / 71.3779°W &lt;br /&gt;Elevation: 2042 ft / 622 m &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whiteface Mountain &lt;br /&gt;Elevation: 1565 ft &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Wonderful hike up Piper Mt with fantastic views then over to White Face Mt for some more great views! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would encourage beginner winter hikers on this trek. This is not a difficult hike little effort for great views!! &lt;br /&gt;Winter clothing a must ( no cotton or jeans) proper foot wear with traction micro spikes or snow shoes.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Are you looking for a summit that is easily accessible, contains spectacular views and is unknown even by locals. Well Piper Mountain in the heart of New Hampshire's Lakes Region is the ideal mountain for you. Located next to the more popular Belknap Mountain, Piper Mountain's long ridge, which has large pockets of exposed ledges, is filled with terrific viewing areas. Views from Piper easily rival if not surpass the ultra popular Mt. Major and Piper Mountain much easier than Mt. Major. The western view from the mountain contains Lake Winnisquam, Mt. Kearsarge, Ragged Mountain and on clear days the Green Mountains.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the I-93 exit in Tilton (exit 20) take route 3 east toward Laconia. Make a right on Route 11 bypass rough six miles east of I-93. Get on to 11A heading towards Gilford. Make a right on Belknap Mountain Road. Head through the town center of Gilford and head for almost 3 miles. Make a left at the old sign pointing to Belknap Mountain. Head up the road all the way to the trailhead which is at the end of the road.  &lt;br /&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during our hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being prepared, traveling with the appropriate gear &amp;amp; knowing how to use it is your personal responsibility. Test and adjust your gear prior to this trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;!! NO COTTON CLOTHING !! - Cotton (a.k.a. the death cloth) has no place in the mountains. If you arrive wearing cotton clothing you will be turned away. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared to hike with this group as a group our motto is: We go in as a group and we come out as a group. We will hike at a pace of our slowest hiker. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Everyone to meet at McDonalds exit 20 Tilton for 9:30am   There is a large parking lot next to MCDonalds. Find us there </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265378440000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263250790000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piper and White Face Mt</name><id>12291705</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264950000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12291705/</event_url></item>