<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>I93</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.052784</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lafayette Place Parking Lot</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>1036046</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.580761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This group is for hikers aged 55-70+ who haven't given up on their love of hiking and being in nature despite their age or level of physical conditioning. We hike at a pace 50% slower than the AMC Trailguide book time.Hike ratings:easy,moderate,strenuous,very strenuous. There are three other hiking Meetup groups if you want a faster pace or more challenging hikes (The New England Hiking Meetup, 4 Seasons Hiking Group, New England Over 40 Hiking Group).The hiking Meetup group,(Fellowship of the Tortoise) does easier,slower paced hikes than this group. Our goal is to stay fit while enjoying the camaraderie of hikers who have similar skills and goals. This is a dog free hiking group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 North,exit at Lafayette Place parking lot on the east side of I93 (if the lot is full get back on I93 north to exit 34B,make a left,go under I93,make a left onto I93 south,exit at Lafayette Campground,park in lot,walk under I93 to Lafayette Place parking lot).We will hike the Old Bridle Path and the Greenleaf Trail to the summit of Mount Lafayette (5,260').Above treeline hiking with views of Cannon and Lincoln Mountains.  8.0 miles round trip, 3,600' elevation gain, AMC book time 6 hours, 9.0 hours estimated time for our group. ----Steve---- Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Grey Chevy pick up truck NH2646423</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338046642000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334619401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VERY STRENUOUS  HIKE-  MOUNT LAFAYETTE</name><id>60865122</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337432400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/60865122/</event_url></item>