<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Washington Square</address_2><address_1>1665 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.338623</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 277-1752</phone><name>Tamarind Bay Coastal Indian Kitchen</name><city>Brookline</city><id>893336</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.137383</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Location:  Tamarind Bay in Brookline&lt;br /&gt;Tamarind Bay&lt;br /&gt;1665 Beacon St, &lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA 02445 &lt;br /&gt;Tel: 617 277 1752&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Short stories by the author of &amp;quot;The Namesake.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion questions are posted on the message board, here:  &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/1439/messages/boards/view/addpost?forum=847982"&gt;http://bookclub.meetu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Review from Publishers' Weekly:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gulf that separates expatriate Bengali parents from their American-raised children—and that separates the children from India—remains Lahiri's subject for this follow-up to Interpreter of Maladies and The Namesake. In this set of eight stories, the results are again stunning. In the title story, Brooklyn-to-Seattle transplant Ruma frets about a presumed obligation to bring her widower father into her home, a stressful decision taken out of her hands by his unexpected independence. The alcoholism of Rahul is described by his elder sister, Sudha; her disappointment and bewilderment pack a particularly powerful punch. And in the loosely linked trio of stories closing the collection, the lives of Hema and Kaushik intersect over the years, first in 1974 when she is six and he is nine; then a few years later when, at 13, she swoons at the now-handsome 16-year-old teen's reappearance; and again in Italy, when she is a 37-year-old academic about to enter an arranged marriage, and he is a 40-year-old photojournalist. An inchoate grief for mothers lost at different stages of life enters many tales and, as the book progresses, takes on enormous resonance. Lahiri's stories of exile, identity, disappointment and maturation evince a spare and subtle mastery that has few contemporary equals. (Apr.) &lt;br /&gt;Copyright © Reed Business Information, a division &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>books on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281801886000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266090147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July 2010 - Unaccustomed Earth, by Jhumpa Lahiri</name><id>12597176</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278777600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/12597176/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_5395668.jpeg</photo_url></item>