<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(across from Fenway Park)</address_2><address_1>61 Brookline Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.347170</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-536-beer</phone><name>Boston Beer Works</name><city>Boston</city><id>868981</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099083</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The tickets for Beer Wars are sold out online.

Michael Pieper will still be at Boston Beer works by 9:45.  He will be at the bar wearing a tie dyed T shirt.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
I know...I know, this event is for TOMORROW. [b]BUT[/b] it's a ONE NIGHT ONLY movie about beer and then we'll be drinking beer. We don't need much prep time for that! It is Thirsty Thursday after all.  

It's going to be a good time! At each location you can look for me (i look like my pics) or my cell (513)307.5955

Here's the beta:

[b]Quick Run Down[/b]:

-Meet up in front of the theater at about 7:15-7:30p 
(may want to call the theater about tickets, bc this is a 'one night only' event.)

-Movie starts at 8pm and supposedly it's a live feed so prob grab seats around 7:30p

 
-Afterward, meet back up outside and head over to [b]Boston Beer Works[/b] (61 Brookline Ave # 2, Boston, MA) for some local brews and beer convos. Their last call is at 12:45, so we'll have plenty of time.

[b]Movie Info[/b]:

&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/uY-Bg5Odi0M&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Fathom and Ducks In A Row Entertainment present Beer Wars LIVE with Ben Stein, a one night event taking you inside the boardrooms and back rooms of the American beer industry. The event will feature the exclusive never-before-seen documentary Beer Wars, followed by a riveting live discussion led by Ben Stein with America’s leading independent brewers and experts.

Playing in movie theaters nationwide on Thursday, April 16th at 8pm ET / 7pm CT / 6pm MT / 8pm PT (tape delay), beer industry insiders will take you behind-the-scenes of their quest for the American Dream. Don’t miss out on this entertaining journey that will reveal the truth behind the label of your favorite beer!

Limited seats available! Buy your tickets today.

S Y N O P S I S:

In America, size matters. The bigger you are, the more power you have, especially in the business world.

Director Anat Baron takes you on a no holds barred exploration of the U.S. beer industry that ultimately reveals the truth behind the label of your favorite beer. Told from an insider’s perspective, the film goes behind the scenes of the daily battles and all out wars that dominate one of America’s favorite industries.

Beer Wars begins as the corporate behemoths are being challenged by small, independent brewers who are shunning the status quo and creating innovative new beers. The story is told through 2 of these entrepreneurs - Sam and Rhonda - battling the might and tactics of Corporate America. We witness their struggle to achieve their American Dream in an industry dominated by powerful corporations unwilling to cede an inch.

This contemporary David and Goliath story is ultimately about keeping your integrity (and your family’s home) in the face of temptation. Beer Wars is a revealing and entertaining journey that provides unexpected and surprising turns and promises to change the world’s opinion on those infamous 99 bottles of beer on the wall.</description><how_to_find_us>At bar wearing tie dyed shirt</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pieper</member_name><member_id>8387210</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240178411000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239817965000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beer Wars (The Live Movie) &amp; Beer Drinking (what we'll be doing after)</name><id>10191612</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239932700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/10191612/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/8/3/global_8164483.jpeg</photo_url></item>