<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the&amp;nbsp;last minute post.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film has a great cast and has received pretty good reviews.&amp;nbsp; Note that the Kendall is showing it on two screens; we'll go to the *4:50* screening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Beginners:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From writer/director Mike Mills comes a comedy/drama about how deeply funny and transformative life can be, even at its most serious moments. &lt;em&gt;Beginners&lt;/em&gt; imaginatively explores the hilarity, confusion, and surprises of love through the evolving consciousness of Oliver (Golden Globe Award nominee Ewan McGregor). Oliver meets the irreverent and unpredictable Anna (M&amp;eacute;lanie Laurent, &lt;em&gt;Inglourious Basterds&lt;/em&gt;) only months after his father Hal (Academy Award nominee Christopher Plummer) has passed away. This new love floods Oliver with memories of his father who&amp;mdash;following 44 years of marriage&amp;mdash;came out of the closet at age 75 to live a full, energized, and wonderfully tumultuous gay life. The upheavals of Hal's new honesty, by turns funny and moving, brought father and son closer than they'd ever been able to be. Now Oliver endeavors to love Anna with all the bravery, humor, and hope that his father taught him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Mills' first film, &lt;em&gt;Thumbsucker&lt;/em&gt;, only hinted at the unique voice this distinctive writer-director displays in &lt;em&gt;Beginners&lt;/em&gt;. His approach to moviemaking reflects his training as an artist and graphic designer: The movie darts, dreams, and sometimes seems to dance. The great Plummer, meanwhile, creates an inspiring, fully rounded man in late bloom, and McGregor responds with a performance to match." A- --&amp;nbsp;Entertainment Weekly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308523290000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308239270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginners</name><id>22435701</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308429000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/22435701/</event_url></item>