<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>252 Newbury Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9716</phone><name>Tech Superpowers Digital Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>824604</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/digilounge" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/files/digilounge5.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston area creatives should know about this place, they offer fast capable Macs with popular design software at low hourly rates in a air conditioned environment.  - tired of working at home with a fan blowing you in the face when it's 90 out?? Spend a day in the digital lounge, there's great coffee right next door and a fun, knowledgeable and friendly staff to help you. It's Krunchier than Kinkos, and cooler than any copy shop, they boast a great playlist and comfy chairs too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tech Superpowers also sells and fixes Macs, want to work with the actual tech who is caring for your machine? This is the place to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now for the info about the event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Earlier this month, Tech Superpowers opened our Digital Lounge at 252 Newbury Street. A combination of a members lounge and cybercafe, the Digital Lounge provides essential services for digitally-savvy Bostonians and travelers alike. Facilities include Hotdesks, Free Wifi, Printing, Xbox, Digital Storage and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thursday, August 27th at 5PM, the TSP Digital Lounge will be having a special open house, so that our long-time clients, press, and neighboring businesses can come in and see this unique space. You can even stay into the night to experience Tuttle Boston, one of Boston's most eclectic social media events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please drop by our Digilounge Open House and come and see what the Digilounge is all about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To RSVP, please go to: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://digilounge.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://digilounge.eve...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To add an iCal reminder for the Open House, click here. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the Digital Lounge, go to: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/digilounge" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.techsuperp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256246621000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250887204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tech Superpowers Digital Lounge Open House</name><id>11167724</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251406800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/11167724/</event_url></item>