<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1755 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.385069</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-441-8727</phone><name>Addis Red Sea</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1140834</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119283</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's a fun opportunity to come out and practice your social skills with other enthusiastic members of this group, and to just have a great time and make some new friends.  We're having a special meet and greet dinner party to celebrate the holidays, the success of our group (which will be 2 years old in April), and each other.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;We're going to have a room to ourselves at one of my favorite restaurants in the Cambridge area - Addis Red Sea.  It's an Ethiopian restaurant, and eating there is QUITE a fun and unique experience.  This is a place you'll want to take your friends (and dates) to for years to come.  I had my birthday party there this past June, and it was amazing!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S HOW THE EVENING WILL GO&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;We'll arrive at 7:00 and get settled in.  Then at 7:15 I'm going to give a free mini-seminar that will teach you some of my most effective social skills strategies.  Here's what you'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;An simple (yet powerful) technique that will make everything you say more interesting and engaging.  People will find themselves paying more attention to you automatically whenever you use this in your conversations.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My proven 3-step method for asking anyone out on a date that almost guarantees they'll say yes.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A fool-proof technique you can use anytime to help keep your conversations flowing smoothly and effortlessly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And just like in the workshops, we're going to have an opportunity to practice everything you learn with some fun exercises.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;PLUS, I HAVE SURPRISE GIFT FOR YOU!&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I just finished developing a secret little tool that will make it much easier for you to meet people wherever you go.  This is not for sale yet at any price, but I'm going to give you a free copy just for coming to the party.  I really think you're going to like what this simple tool will do for your social life.  This is my way of saying thank you for being part of the group and coming out to party with us.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The restaurant is conveniently located in Porter Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  The event starts at 7:00 and we'll start the free seminar promptly at 7:15.  The whole event will finish up between 9-10pm.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you've ever been to one of my workshops then you know that I &lt;i&gt;really do&lt;/i&gt; start my seminars on time regardless of how many people are there.  Please plan on arriving by 7:00 so you have time to settle in and meet the other guests before the seminar.  You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This event will be limited to the first 40 people who sign up due to the size of the room we've reserved.  If you'd like to come, here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Tuesday, December 22nd available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for the party right now.  I run two social skills groups with a combined total of over 900 members, so this will probably fill up fast.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive early to get settled in and meet the other members.  Remember, the seminar starts promptly at 7:15pm.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;There is no cost for this event (aside from what you order from the restaurant.  If you've been hesitant to come to our workshops because of the cost, this will be a great way for you to get a small sample of what we do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the party or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door and then walk downstairs into the private room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>10</waitlist_count><updated>1263761613000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260772394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet and Greet + Dinner Party</name><id>12080291</id><headcount>44</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261526400000</time><rsvp_limit>44</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/12080291/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/0/global_12237152.jpeg</photo_url></item>