<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Trinity St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.766235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BUSHNELL PARK</name><city>Hartford</city><id>664313</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.679720</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come down and enjoy the evening, bring a picnic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hartford Jazz Society's Monday Night Jazz Series&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pavillion in Bushnell Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mixashawn Trio&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A superb set featured a solo effort from Mixashawn, a Native American tenor saxophonist who played flutes, electronics, berimbow, and sang. The entire set was a beautifully connected suite, which unfolded with a series of stories. Mixashawn is a marvelous story teller with a number of intriguing stories and observations.... We all loved his echoplex berimbow song...and his golden tone on tenor was another delight. He put together the entire set so that it flowed together perfectly throughout.”&lt;br /&gt;—Bruce Gallanter, DownTown Music Gallery&lt;br /&gt;(Review of performance of Hemispheric Principles... the Legacy of J.A. Emidy at the Ninth Vision Festival, New York City, May 2004) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mixashawn.com/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mixashawn....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eric Reed Trio&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     When you think of hard-driving swing, daring expression, sophistication and elegance in artistry, formidable technique and a thunderous sound, there are only a small handful of pianists you think of and one of them is most assuredly ERIC SCOTT REED.&lt;br /&gt;     Award-winning pianist and composer Eric Scott Reed began playing the piano at age two and was performing in his father’s Baptist church in Philadelphia by age five. After study at Philadelphia's Settlement Music School and Los Angeles’ Colburn School of Arts, Reed embarked upon a professional career that has taken him all over the world. His credits include Wynton Marsalis, Jessye Norman, Quincy Jones, Patti Labelle and others. Reed has taught at The Juilliard School of Music and gives master classes and lecture demonstrations on the history of music. His other musical ventures include over 20 recordings as a leader, including his latest recording, Stand!, featuring original compositions and arrangements; scoring for Eddie Murphy’s comedy, Life; and musical direction for the Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater. Currently Reed is in residence with the Ebony Repertory Theatre of Los Angeles, as musical director of Regina Taylor's Crowns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ericreed.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ericreed.n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where is the rain venue?&lt;br /&gt;Asylum Hill Congregational Church (Drew Hall)&lt;br /&gt;814 Asylum Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metered parking on the street.&lt;br /&gt;Also: Goodwin Square Garage&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;City Place Garage&lt;br /&gt;Asylum Lot&lt;br /&gt;all within close proximity to the park&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will fly the BW Piano Key Scarf on a tall stake, check out attending pictures to connect.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278497201000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274203454000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hartford Jazz Society's Monday Night Jazz Series</name><id>13520577</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278366300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13520577/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/global_15132337.jpeg</photo_url></item>