<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1338 Memorial Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.092975</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 241-8888</phone><name>Lattitude</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>1467984</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.619433</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>So sorry we had to postpone our visit to the Blue Rock, so we won't be meeting this month, unless you guys have a great idea for an informal &amp;quot;twixt &amp;amp; 'tween&amp;quot; event. (just reply to this email if you do and we can put it on the calendar!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT...the good news is that we are all set for our Feb. meeting at Lattitude in West Springfield!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;here's what people are saying....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I love this restaurant. The Ahi Tuna Tartar is to die for! Give it a try I promise it's a great date night and a nice after work hang out. ~insiderpages.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazing food that will satisfy your taste buds. The menu shifts with the seasons providing nice changes. You must get the brussels sprouts; trust me on that! The service is always great and everyone is happy.&lt;br /&gt;Liked: Food, Service, Atmosphere, Value  ~ google user review&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I had the most AMAZING burger here. It was cooked perfectly, juicy, and the fries that came with it were great. Also the price was right for this place! My colleague had the chicken lettuce wraps and they were so good, he didn't share. :) I took his word for it though since they looked and smelled very good, but I was so busy with my giant awesome burger that I didn't pay too much mind. ~Yelp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lattitude itself is a fascinating place: it seems out of place across the street from The Big E, a Boston-style restaurant in the middle of a much less urban metro.  But it works.  The style of the restaurant is well-crafted, though the area is a little small at times.  However, they make what they make quite well. ~yelp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;get the picture? It's gonna be goood!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;yes? Yes. please RSVP either way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;jessica &amp;amp; Christine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>9683028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302044983000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295903843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lattitude in West Springfield!</name><id>16169098</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298932200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/16169098/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/e/global_21041870.jpeg</photo_url></item>