<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Merrimac Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.811920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waterfront Park</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>6703662</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.871284</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/0/event_133382032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;92.5 the River's 11th Annual Riverfront Festival, presented by Budweiser will hit Waterfront Park in Newburyport on Saturday, July 7th. The Riverfront Festival is a free show open to the public, so attendees are encouraged to get there early with beach blankets &amp;amp; chairs for a day of great live music. Headlining this year’s Riverfront Festival is Mat Kearney joined by Van Ghost, The Brew &amp;amp; the Adam Ezra Group. Check out Riverfront Festival 2012, listen to great music and interact with participating sponsors before, during and after this day of music and fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Riverfront Festival takes place at Newburyport Waterfront Park starting at 1PM on Saturday July 7th. &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;q=newburyport+waterfront+park&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=waterfront+park&amp;amp;hnear=0x89e2e109acaea8db:0x5508797887c45490,Newburyport,+MA&amp;amp;cid=0,0,15341312161815831913&amp;amp;ei=XjLST4jeOdDk6QGK6an_Ag&amp;amp;oi=local_result&amp;amp;ved=0CA0Q_BIwAw"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for a map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; Free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt; There are 3 municipal lots downtown – parking will need to be paid for at the meters.  They are located at Green &amp;amp; Merrimac Streets, State and Harris Streets (next to the Library) and on Prince Place. There are 2 lots run by the Newburyport Redevelopment Authority They are located at either side of Waterfront Park along Merrimac Street Between The Black Cow and Not Your Average Joe’s (West Lot) and Water Street (East Lot)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may also park in legal spots on the street. If you park in a nearby neighborhood, please be respectful of residents and all parking laws - do not block fire hydrants or driveways. Police will ticket or tow all cars which are parked in illegal spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATING:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring a chair or a blanket to sit on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will only wait 15 minutes for you to arrive at the meeting place, please remember that if you are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:  978-304-2811&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not paid your dues this year, this event would be a good opportunity to do so. Thank you for paying your dues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet under the trees in front of Not Your Average Joe's, when we all get there we will go find a place to sit on the grass. If you are running late and don't meetup with us in the front of the building.... come find us on the lawn.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341889403000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340743401000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Riverfront Music Festival</name><id>70853512</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341676800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/70853512/</event_url></item>