<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, John is hosting this film at the Coolidge at the same time, but with 24 signed up I figured there was demand enough for a second meetup. If you are already signed up for John's but would rather see the movie at the Kendall, remember to change your RSVP on the other meetup to "No."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that the film will be shown on two screens at the Kendall, but we'll be at the 4:30 show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the film:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Set on an island off the coast of New England in the summer of 1965, director/co-writer Wes Anderson's&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;(The Royal Tenenbaums, Fantastic Mr. Fox, Rushmore)&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;comic romance/drama&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Moonrise Kingdom&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;tells the story of two twelve-year-olds, Sam (Jared Gilman) and Suzy (Kara Hayward), who fall in love, make a secret pact, and run away together into the wilderness. As various authorities try to hunt them down, a violent storm is brewing off-shore—and the peaceful island community is turned upside down in every which way. Also starring Bruce Willis as the local sheriff, Captain Sharp, Edward Norton as Khaki Scout troop leader Scout Master Ward, and Bill Murray and Frances McDormand as the young girl's parents, Mr. and Mrs. Bishop. Also starring Tilda Swinton, Jason Schwartzman and Harvey Keitel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338833098000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338428383000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moonrise Kingdom (at Kendall)</name><id>67040862</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338669000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/67040862/</event_url></item>