<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Entrepreneurial Brainstorming&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MDGent (the Entrepreneur SIG) is sponsoring a brainstorming session for anyone who is working in a start-up company or is even thinking about starting up a company. We invite key people from start-up companies to discuss any issues they are having (regulatory, legal, marketing (and/or sales), scientific, manufacturing, financing or just about anything else) and would like ideas on how to address those issues. We will have people with specific expertise at the meeting to suggest ideas and, if possible, give referrals to others who can help. This will be an interactive meeting with only a brief presentation in the beginning. Come to this meeting with all of your questions, concerns, or issues, and we will work on them together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mission of MDGent is to foster entrepreneurship; foster development of new medical technologies and services; assist entrepreneurs in evaluating potential projects; optimize the chance of success of any proposed project; optimize the opportunity for all involved; optimize success of the process; provide a networking node for key stakeholders; and finally, become financially self-sustaining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Fee (includes a light supper):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Advance On-site &lt;br /&gt;MedDev Group member $15 $20 &lt;br /&gt;Nonmember $25 $30 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Date: January 26, 2011&lt;br /&gt;Time: 5:30 - 9:00PM&lt;br /&gt;Location: Rebecca's Cafe&lt;br /&gt;Info: judy@vitalnow.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Rebecca's Cafe, 275 Grove St., Newton (Auburndale) MA - adjacent to Riverside T Station&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information:&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Judy Isaacson&lt;br /&gt;Email:  judy@vitalnow.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296084519000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293463873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Entrepreneurial Brainstorming</name><id>15827982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296080100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15827982/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>