<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Wibur Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02865</zip><lat>41.922653</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lime Rock Preserve</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>8583692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.466133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The preserve is laced with trails illustrating a wide variety of distinctive New England habitats including woodlands, forested swamps, streams, open water and calcareous ledges. An abandoned electric rail-bed on western edge of the property provides scenic views of the town reservoir. Some trails get wet and muddy. Please stay on the trails to avoid trampling plants and brushing against poison ivy. &lt;a href="http://www.nature.org/ourinitiatives/regions/northamerica/unitedstates/rhodeisland/placesweprotect/lime_rock.pdf"&gt;Map of the Lime Rock Preserve&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking will be on the road, just find a spot. This is an easy trail, great for beginners. Hiking boots or sneakers are advised &amp;amp; water.&lt;/p&gt;
Things To Do 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to See: Plants&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Red oak, hickory, a diversity of ferns, red and white baneberry, horse balm, violets, bellwort, nodding trillium, jack-in-the-pulpit, trout lily&lt;/p&gt;
Plan Your Visit 
&lt;p&gt;We hope you enjoy visiting our preserves in any season. We ask that you please observe the following guidelines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay on the walking trails, using marked trails wherever they exist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respect preserve open hours (one hour before sunrise to one hour after sunset). Overnight camping is not allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not ride horses, bikes or any motorized vehicle through preserves or on the trails.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not disturb bird nesting areas. Between April 15 and September 1, nesting areas may be off-limits to visitors. People or dogs can easily destroy a nest with one misstep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave your pets at home, for the safety of the fragile ecology of preserves and as a courtesy to other visitors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact our office in Providence to visit those preserves that have restricted public access because of their very sensitive flora and fauna. These places deserve special respect and are best visited only on guided field trips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove any living materials from a preserve or disturb any vegetation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove any trash you create and, if possible, any garbage that you see left by someone else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the entrance</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doris R. B.</member_name><member_id>11538323</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366037532000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365467429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>hike</name><id>113389832</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365955200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/113389832/</event_url></item>