<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know that it's been a long time since our last Meetup, but I wanted to get things started up again. Ideally, I'd like to start holding monthly potlucks. I'm hoping that we can use this potluck to discuss plans for future potlucks. That said, if you are unable to make it this time but have strong preferences about the location/date of future potlucks, please send me an e-mail and I will make sure to bring them up at the Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet on the Dartmouth Green. I'll bring some picnic blankets, utensils and paper plates. If the weather reports start calling for rain, I will send out an e-mail on Friday May 29th with an alternate location. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a dish to share and (if at all possible) label the ingredients. This will help us to avoid any discrepancies that may occur as a result of people having different interpretations of which foods are considered to be &amp;quot;vegan&amp;quot; (ex. honey, white sugar).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We welcome vegans, vegetarians and omnivores at our Meetup events. However, because this is a vegan potluck, we ask that any dishes that you bring be vegan (no meat, no dairy, no eggs, no gelatin). If you have any questions about whether a food item satisfies these criteria or if you need suggestions of easy dishes to make/buy, please feel free to contact me: Lauren.A.Thompson@Dartmouth.edu.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a big sign that says "vegan"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lola</member_name><member_id>915277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254058462000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Pioneers of Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-430</urlname><id>650201</id><group_lat>43.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.2699966431</group_lon><name>NH/VT Vegan Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243022937000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vegan Potluck</name><id>10472648</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243699200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-430/events/10472648/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/9/global_1994793.jpeg</photo_url></item>