<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Legeyt  Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06063</zip><lat>41.952446</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Indian Council Caves</name><city>Barkhamsted</city><id>1787811</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.914032</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/1/a/1/highres_16160897.jpeg" width="371" height="254" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Those of your who love to climb rocks, this is your day. The rocks are an amazing three story jumble of climbing fun. This hike will be a 7ish mile thru hike. Time on the trail should be no more than 4 hours. Please do not schedule yourself super tight with time as we are only as fast as our slowest hiker. This means we will meet at the end point and a couple of folks will drive everyone to the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a technical hike. It is an easier, flat&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as I work on recovery. There is a good view and cool rocks. The trail is doable for many.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It is a pretty wooded area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are meeting at the parking area&amp;nbsp;on the &lt;strong&gt;corner of Legeyt Rd. on Rt. 179&lt;/strong&gt;. Parking at this spot is limited so head down the road and park as far off the side as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will&amp;nbsp;begin on Old Route 20 Rd off of Pine Street and Walnut Hill Road. We will head south on the blue blaze Tunxis Trail.&amp;nbsp;It promises boulders to view. This path will take us across Pine Mountain Rd and over Pine Mountain at a blistering 1391' elevation (from sea level). The trail is rugged but interesting. Our goal is the council caves from here. This is an area of huge glacier boulders with cave-like pockets.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;We will snack here.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Many native american artifacts have been found here but it is not known if the area was used for council meetings. From there we will successfully stumble out of the woods onto Rt. 179 and the cars on Legeyt Rd. Hopefully those of us who drove can get rides back to the start :).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure you have water, sunscreen, snacks, and bug spray. Since we are shuttling people please be on time. We will leave the parking area by 9:45 to be on the trail for 10:00. We should be done by 2:00.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always with me NO DOGS/NO CHILDREN.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are no bathrooms at this location.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GPS PEOPLE-I HAVE NO EXACT ADDRESSES FOR WHERE WE ARE HEADED. USE THE MAPQUEST LINKS THAT SHOW YOU WHERE WE ARE MEETING. The meeting spot&amp;nbsp;is where&amp;nbsp;the hikes end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Barkhamsted&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Legeyt+Rd#a/maps/m::10:41.943677:-72.914118:0:::::/e"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Barkhamsted&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Legeyt+Rd#a/maps/m::10:41.943677:-72.914118:0:::::/e&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306768125000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305745810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Indian Council Caves, Tunxis Trail, Barkhamsted CT</name><id>18866101</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306071000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/18866101/</event_url></item>