<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>109-111 Route 2A</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06365</zip><lat>41.486541</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Captain Grants 1754 Bed &amp; Breakfast</name><city>Preston</city><id>1187812</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.041380</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per room plus tax</description><amount>139.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Come join us for an overnight trip to the very Haunted Captain Grants Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast in Preston Connecticut, where apparitions of a woman and 2 little girls have been seen, where there is a secret cubby where a ghost resides, and physical manifestations often occur!&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry though, I am well, assured that the ghosts who reside here, are quite friendly! :)&lt;br /&gt;Rooms are $139.00, and breakfast is included in the price.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To check out their website you can click here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://74.125.93.132/search?q=cache:OpNqsSsxWlIJ:www.captaingrants.com/+Captain+Grants+Bed+and+Breakfast+Conn&amp;amp;cd=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ct=clnk&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;client=firefox-a" target="_blank"&gt;http://74.125.93.132/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at the Bed &amp;amp; Breakfast Friday evening at 7pm, and then going to dinner at one of the two excellant Italian restaurants within minutes from where we are staying. We will decide that night of where people want to go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first place is a family restaurant called Valentinos, which Ted from the B &amp;amp; B said they have excellant Italian food, and the thin crust pizza there is renown. If we choose to go there, the B&amp;amp;B will give everyone a card for a free glass of wine, or free dessert. There is no web site, but to see some reviews you can go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://newlondon.citysearch.com/profile/2021793/ledyard_ct/valentino_s_restaurant_pizza.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://newlondon.city...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other Italian place which also has very good food, is Bella Fiore, which is a bit more expensive &lt;br /&gt;(though moderately priced) and has better atomosphere. You can find their website here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bellafiorerestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bellafiore...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activities for the night after dinner will include a video that the B&amp;amp;B was featured on a Haunted show, and&lt;br /&gt;both Mohegan Sun and Foxwoods Casinos are close by. The next morning, Ted and his wife (the owners)&lt;br /&gt;will regale us with tales of haunted episodes that have occured in the house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next day, after breakfast for those who want to stay, we can take a trip to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Gillette Castle:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctrivervalley.com/4-Connecticut-CT-in-of/Major-attractions-in-CT/gillette_castle_state_park/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctriverval...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To nearby Mystic Conn, which is a 15 min drive from the B&amp;amp;B, and possibly to a haunted cemetary or bld.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A COUPLE WORDS OF CAUTION:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in this trip, you need to call and book your room ASAP- as there are only (7) rooms,&lt;br /&gt;and (6) more available, and they are first come, first serve, so if someone outside our group wants to book a room, they will be gone. Please note though, that the cancellation policies are strict, and the fee for cancelling&lt;br /&gt;is $50, or the full price if cancelled within a week before the date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To book a room, call: (800) 982-1772 or (860) 887-7589.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring your cameras!! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in and tell them when you check in that you are with the meet up group</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tala</member_name><member_id>5511934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269881683000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Wiccans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wiccan-169</urlname><id>793389</id><group_lat>42.4900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0100021362</group_lon><name>Central Mass Wiccan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265850392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Captain Grants Haunted Bed &amp; Breakfast Trip</name><id>12575573</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269643500000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wiccan-169/events/12575573/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/f/global_3694063.jpeg</photo_url></item>