<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AGENDA for MAY 1st meetup...yep, next Tues!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can have the most wondrous intentions but if our feelings are not aligned vibrationally on the&lt;br /&gt;lighter side of gratitude and joy, don't be surprised if you don't attract what you want. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're very delighted to have Lisa Wessan share with us wonderful ways to Let Go &amp;amp; Lighten Up!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;side note: A loyal, joyous fan of our meetup, Lisa has participated since we started in January, &lt;br /&gt;coming all the way from N Chelmsford   ;o) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa's gift to us is to share her proprietary &amp;quot;Lighter Side of Transformation (TM)&amp;quot; workshop with us &lt;br /&gt;(which people usually pay a lot to participate and experience).  Thanks-a-lot, Lisa!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary: &lt;br /&gt;An academic and experiential workshop incorporating humor and laughter in&lt;br /&gt;four parts &amp;quot;harmony&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part I: Laughter Therapy: overview of the psychological, physiological and spiritual benefits of &lt;br /&gt;laughter from peer reviewed journals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part II: Wit, mirth and laughter -- 3 components of humor.  What distinguishes them? &lt;br /&gt;Why do we care how we use them?&lt;br /&gt;Harmful vs Therapeutic Humor...learn to recognize, so you can use the right kind of humor&lt;br /&gt;...for joyful, intentional living. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part III: Join in the full, interactive group experience of Z Laughter Circle (see&lt;br /&gt;www.MirthMaven.com for details). Together, in small groups, we explore the&lt;br /&gt;wonder, joy and ecstasy of being able to laugh for no reason. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part IV: Questions, discussions, suggestions for further study and integration of &lt;br /&gt;daily laughter practice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's very important to come in comfortable clothes.  So be casual or be square!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to enjoying another wonderful meetup with everyone!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be happy!&lt;br /&gt;Chew-Hoong &amp;amp; Dave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Lisa Wessan, MSW, LCSW, CLL:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa is a joy based counselor &amp;amp; coach, licensed and board certified clinical &lt;br /&gt;social worker, speaker and health educator.&lt;br /&gt;She works with individuals and groups who seek pleasure and fulfillment&lt;br /&gt;in their lives through improved energy and heightened consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa has appeared on CNN's &amp;quot;Paula Zahn Now,&amp;quot; and has been featured many &lt;br /&gt;times in the national press, including The Wall Street Journal, The Daily&lt;br /&gt;News and Adbusters Magazine, for interviews regarding her award winning&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Laughter Therapy for Caregivers&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Team Building with Laughter&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa is also an internationally published author, an active Reiki Master&lt;br /&gt;and on-air host and producer of the monthly Cable TV show &amp;quot;Z Lighter Side&lt;br /&gt;of Transformation.&amp;quot;  Visit www.MirthMaven.com for further information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178233386000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175685677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction May Meetup</name><id>5636224</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178060400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/5636224/</event_url></item>