<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The film stars at 6:20....or rather the commercials and previews start then.   I will be at the theater by 5:45.  It looks like it will be showing upstairs so I will try to snag a table, by the windows near the coffee vendor.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to go in to get seats at 6:10 or so.  If this cuts things a bit close for you, and you miss us before the movie, meet up with us after to go out for dinner and drinks.    We will gather outside the theater(auditorium) where the film is showing and discuss the movie a bit and where we would like to go for munchies.  Do not go all the way outside the building or you could miss us.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't know me, look for my Boston Movie Group Badge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a lot of fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is called &amp;quot;The Mummy: Tomb of the Dragon Emperor&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update the web page with exact movie times closer to the event.    If the movie is upstairs, I will be near the coffee vendor.  I will try to snag a table if possible.  If the movie is downstairs. I will be just inside the ropes near the concession stand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you enjoyed the first two Mummy movies this should be a lot of fun for you.   If you have never seen one of these films it is like an over the top version of an Indiana Jones Movie where the mummies come back to life and try to take over the world!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Release Date: August 1, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Studio: Universal Pictures&lt;br /&gt;Director: Rob Cohen&lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Alfred Gough, Miles Millar&lt;br /&gt;Starring: Brendan Fraser, Jet Li, Maria Bello, John Hannah, Michelle Yeoh, Anthony Wong, Luke Ford, Isabella Leong&lt;br /&gt;Genre: Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Horror, Thriller&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.themummy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.themummy.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: The blockbuster global &amp;quot;Mummy&amp;quot; franchise takes a spellbinding turn as the action shifts to Asia for the next chapter in the adventure series, &amp;quot;The Mummy: Tomb of the Dragon Emperor.&amp;quot; Brendan Fraser returns as explorer Rick O'Connell to combat the resurrected Han Emperor (Jet Li) in an epic that races from the catacombs of ancient China high into the frigid Himalayas. Rick is joined in this all-new adventure by son Alex (newcomer Luke Ford), wife Evelyn (Maria Bello) and her brother, Jonathan (John Hannah). And this time, the O'Connells must stop a mummy awoken from a 2,000-year-old curse who threatens to plunge the world into his merciless, unending service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doomed by a double-crossing sorceress (Michelle Yeoh) to spend eternity in suspended animation, China's ruthless Dragon Emperor and his 10,000 warriors have laid forgotten for eons, entombed in clay as a vast, silent terra cotta army. But when dashing adventurer Alex O'Connell is tricked into awakening the ruler from eternal slumber, the reckless young archaeologist must seek the help of the only people who know more than he does about taking down the undead: his parents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the monarch roars back to life, our heroes find his quest for world domination has only intensified over the millennia. Striding the Far East with unimaginable supernatural powers, the Emperor Mummy will rouse his legion as an unstoppable, otherworldly force...unless the O'Connells can stop him first. Now, in &amp;quot;The Mummy: Tomb of the Dragon Emperor,&amp;quot; the trademark thrills and visually spectacular action of the &amp;quot;Mummy&amp;quot; series will be redefined for a new generation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Mummy: Tomb of the Dragon Emperor&amp;quot; is helmed by director Rob Cohen (&amp;quot;The Fast and the Furious,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;xXx&amp;quot;) and written by Alfred Gough &amp;amp; Miles Millar (&amp;quot;Spider-Man 2,&amp;quot; television's &amp;quot;Smallville&amp;quot;). Reprising their roles as producers in the series are Bob Ducsay, Sean Daniel, Stephen Sommers and James Jacks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222684039000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215514148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Mummy: Tomb of the Dragon Emperor</name><id>8297717</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217628900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8297717/</event_url></item>