<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>799 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363407</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-8356</phone><name>Bertucci's </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>754675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097389</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Going forward, our Meetup group requires some changes if I am to continue serving as organizer - or any other member is invited to step forward and take my place. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Specifically, the group needs to make more financial sense for me to continue, and also should make more "priority/value sense" for other members to derive sufficient benefit from it. I am therefore considering instituting a membership fee as a commitment-enhancing device/indicator/tool: to confirm or even increase the apparent/perceived value of our decluttering, personal change, and goal attainment meetings and activities/efforts in general, in members' minds. I’ve been thinking of a sort of "pay-as-you-go" Meetup to engineer within our group greater personal investment/ commitment to each member's own decluttering projects. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

A free Meetup group and meetings that require no advance payment are too easily dismissed as offering little or no value, I have found (and also been told): people can and do change their minds at the last minute, perhaps to go to other events that seem more worthwhile than our Meetups (perhaps in part because a meeting fee was required in advance by the other group! In fact, I've read in several sources of psychological studies proving that people perceive more expensive as being better, offering more value-- even when the items being compared were exactly the same-- only the price differing!). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

It is coming time for us all (especially me) to become practical and acknowledge that each meeting comes at a cost in usually a number of ways-- including the value of the organizer’s time and efforts spent planning and preparing, coordinating all sorts of factors, administering affairs, communicating with members, sometimes individually, and paying Meetup's monthly organizer fees. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I would greatly appreciate members’ working together (with me, if I continue as organizer) to plan meetings that will be worth at least $10 for more of you to come … or &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; large enough fee to pass the "laugh test":  justifying a person's taking the time and trouble to make a payment online ... and creating at least a twinge of "pain" = self-investment, demanding a bit of focused attention. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

And/Or we could institute paid membership levels, with appropriate benefits accruing to each level (such as No Charge to attend meetings for members who have paid a quarterly membership fee). We might start with a $5 “early bird” payment as the third-quarterly membership fee for whoever pays early, in June, increasing to $10 each for signups on July 1 and then for everyone on the first day of subsequent quarters.  &lt;span&gt;The $10/quarter-year could serve as a friendly niggling quarterly reminder -- like a poke in the ribs -- for us to recommit to decluttering and personal change, reaffirming the value of such enterprise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, of course, members can always decide that decluttering and other such personal change are not worth $10 to them that quarter if they know they must focus on other matters instead -- in the process, pruning our Meetup group to consist only of people who are serious about making noticeable progress on decluttering and other personal change, as I had envisioned when I first launched this group more than four years ago: I had originally launched this group to be a decluttering "activist" Meetup-- yet many meetings have been sparsely attended, and people haven’t offered much input online-- so, some shakeup is clearly needed. Recently I have wondered if money might be a tool of choice to better help us &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; in our decluttering and personal change endeavors? Do come dialogue about such … perhaps following the tour of Mount Auburn Cemetery on June 3?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--Then at quarterly organizational meetings, participants can decide what sorts of meetings would be &lt;em&gt;worth&lt;/em&gt; a $10 fee to themselves and hopefully to any others who have not paid a membership fee: what sort of topic, format, guest speaker(s), venue, follow-up, etc.?&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a red &amp; white Meetup sign at our table (at least until the meeting starts)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339723056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338449235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Organizational Meeting with Considerations of Sustainability/Succession</name><id>67076482</id><headcount>2</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339626600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/67076482/</event_url></item>