<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard Street, Brookline, MA 02446</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1765151</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122467</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Quentin Tarantino's directorial debut came out guns blazing in 1992, and when the smoke cleared, we were left with one of the greatest heist films of all time. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The set up is simple enough: a group of professional bad guys are hired to take down a jewelry store, given colorful nicknames, and told where to divvy up the loot. What could go wrong? Lucky for us, the answer is: just about everything. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Johnny Law shows up, Mr. Blonde is a madman, and one of the thieves may not be who he seems. As this group of stick up men try to hash out exactly where they went wrong, the tension in the room becomes a powder keg just waiting for a struck match. Throw into this mix, one hostage cop, a can of gasoline, and "Stuck in the Middle With You" by Stealers Wheel, and what you have is a recipe for classic cinema flambé. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Harvey Keitel (Mr. White) leads a perfect cast of characters that includes, Tim Roth (Mr. Orange), Michael Madsen (Mr. Blonde), Steve Buscemi (Mr. Pink), and Chris Penn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'll be at Panera for half an hour from 6 to 6.30pm with a Meetup sign on the table. At 6.30 I'll head across to the Coolidge.  After the film I'll be in the lobby for 10 minutes if people would like to go nearby for a quick drink and discussion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See details below...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caroline </member_name><member_id>10711981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346256671000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343572654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reservoir Dogs</name><id>75380342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346108400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/75380342/</event_url></item>