<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7pm concert has possible alternate rain location.  Click this link after 2pm, it's supposed to be posted there:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org/event.php?id=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artidea.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No, it's not a new Japanese monster flick about a flying turtle and a maniacal robot, it's some events at New Haven's annual 2-week long &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org" target="_blank"&gt;International Festival of Arts &amp;amp; Ideas&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be hitting a few things, seeing a free concert on the Green, &amp;amp; going to a free demo/lecture/workshop, &amp;amp; generally wandering about.  Feel free to join-in at whatever time for whatever event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event 1: 4-5:30pm WORKSHOP:&lt;/b&gt; We MAY go down before 4pm, but at the least we're going to the 4pm free interactive &lt;a href="http://artidea.org/event.php?id=72" target="_blank"&gt;gamelan lecture/demo/workshop&lt;/a&gt; by the Yale gamelan group (only 15 people will be allowed to attend so come early!).  165 Elm St, Hendrie Hall basement (enter east door, down stairs, turn left).  P.S.  &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gamelan&lt;br /&gt;" target="_blank"&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; is a gamelan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next we wander around.  Perhaps &lt;a href="http://www.ideatvillage.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Ideat Village&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event 2: 7-8:30pm CONCERT:&lt;/b&gt; We'll be seeing the free &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org/event.php?id=2" target="_blank"&gt;collaboration concert&lt;/a&gt; with Gamelan Galak Tika and Ensemble Robot (details below).  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Due to rain, the concert is being held at Yale's Woolsey Hall, at the corner of College and Grove.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Elm Street Stage on the Green.  You may wish to bring a blanket, folding chair, picnic, snacks, etc.  Bring my cell number so you can find me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to see other events there before 4pm, let me know, we might come down earlier.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if no one wants to see anything specific we may be heading down before 4pm to just look around at what else is happening.  If you want me to call you if we're heading down early, send me your number and let me know if you prefer text messages or voice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT THE CONCERT:&lt;/b&gt; Pieces include a merging of a Balinese gamelan percussion orchestra with various remote-controlled music-making machines, gamelan rock &amp;amp; robo-gamelan heavy metal, and pieces using musical robots such as the &lt;a href="http://www.ensemblerobot.com/robots.shtml&lt;br /&gt;" target="_blank"&gt;Heliphon, Whirlybot and Bot(i)cello&lt;/a&gt;.  If you'd like to see videos or hear some of the music, visit the event's &lt;a href="http://www.artidea.org/event.php?id=2&lt;br /&gt;" target="_blank"&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Ideas page&lt;/a&gt; for video, sound, and links to the groups' homepages and MySpace pages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WEATHER:&lt;/b&gt; At this point it sounds like it won't be raining in the evening. But I'll have an umbrella in my car anyway.  And a jacket, since some of these nights are in the 50's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YER HOST:&lt;/b&gt; Jason, cell #203-901-4957 (calling or texting is fine)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>2254163</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213759253000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213249982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sun. 6/15 - Gamelans vs. Mega-robots</name><id>8128139</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213560000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8128139/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/global_4434096.jpeg</photo_url></item>