<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>703 Westfield Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.555537</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Guiffrida Park</name><city>Meriden</city><id>129143</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.761671</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*Great leaf peeping!* This is a wonderful roughly 2.5 mi. vista hike I have done a few times!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out In the Giuffrida Park parking lot at 3 PM and hike past the dam for Crescent Lake. This part may be a little wet as we have to cross below the dam where the trail crosses the spillway. Then we hike up the steep side of the ridge and climb only about an easy 10 feet or so of traprock. The path to climb is very easy with lots of secure places for feet and hands and can barely be called climbing. The reward is great though as at the top on Chauncey Peak is a WONDERFUL vista of the whole valley, lake, and woods!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail follows the cliff edge to the north with a great view of the lake below and Lamintation Mtn. on the other side of the lake. Eventually, as we get past the lake, the trail will cut down steeply from the ridge line. There is no climbing, but you need to watch your step lest you slip on leaves or scree and slide a little.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The path continues into the forest and up the side of Lamintation Mtn. and we then turn south following the topography. We eventully decend and down by the side of the lake and finish with a pleasent walk through the old evergreens at lakeside and get back to the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll roughly estimate this hike to be a beautiful 1.75 hrs. at a leasurly pace. I don't have a good map for the trail here. If people are up for it we can stop at a good Chinese buffet in Meriden after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;)  is leading on this one so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A good map for a portion of the hike can be found in Map #20, Mattabesett Trail Map #6 in the Connecticut Walk Book published by the Connecticut Forest and Park Association. The link provided here takes you to a topographic map of the area centered on Chauncey Peak. A number of maps (this topo link included) list the lake as being named Bradley Hubbard Reservoir. You can zoom out on the map by changing the View Scale on the left to 1:50,000 or a little higher to get a context.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail is not well marked, especially on Lamintation Mtn. A careful eye is needed for finding the white blazes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the Hartford area:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-91 S&lt;br /&gt;* Take the MIDDLE ST. exit- EXIT 20- toward COUNTRY CLUB RD. (go .2 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;* Turn LEFT onto MIDDLE ST. (go &amp;lt;.1 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;* Turn RIGHT onto COUNTRY CLUB RD. (go 1.6 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;* COUNTRY CLUB RD. becomes WESTFIELD RD. (go roughly .6 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;* The entrance  to Giuffrida Park will be on your right. [***NOTE: Going in this direction (south) it is the FIRST right after the quarry facility. Park entrance NOT marked!!! Looks like a street with no street sign.***]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?z=18&amp;amp;n=4603131&amp;amp;e=686860&amp;amp;s=25&amp;amp;size=l&amp;amp;datum=nad83&amp;amp;layer=DRG25"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?z=18&amp;amp;n=4603131&amp;amp;e=686860&amp;amp;s=25&amp;amp;size=l&amp;amp;datum=nad83&amp;amp;layer=DRG25" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topozone.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1161025310000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1160178538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Giuffrida Park &amp; Chauncey Peak in Meriden CT</name><id>5180522</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1160852400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5180522/</event_url></item>