<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Waterfront</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.810000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Newburyport</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>297849</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.880000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's make a day of it on the waterfront!&lt;br /&gt;We can do dinner at the Grog, Michael's or maybe a potluck picnic, then the band concert, fireworks, and finally drinks and dancing for anyone with any energy left...&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendars...this is a great summer event. We can finalize details as the date gets closer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:00AM - 7:00PM&lt;br /&gt;YANKEE HOMECOMING DOWNTOWN ENTERTAINMENT&lt;br /&gt;Meet around 1 or 2 to take in the sights, enjoy the friends and cameraderie. &lt;br /&gt;Throughout the day there will be live music performances at the Waterfront Stage, Market Square, Inn Street, Pleasant Street and the Boardwalk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00PM - 9:00PM&lt;br /&gt;YANKEE HOMECOMING WATERFRONT CONCERT SERIES&lt;br /&gt;THE UNITED STATES AIR FORCE BAND OF LIBERTY&lt;br /&gt;Waterfront Park&lt;br /&gt;The United States Air Force Band of Liberty The United States Air Force Band of Liberty, is a select group of professional musicians that have been entertaining audiences for over twenty years. The members are highly talented musicians who bring to each concert the skill and knowledge gained from years of study and performing experience ? a great show! This exceptional performing unit delivers programs chosen to highlight the diversity of America?s musical &amp;amp; cultural heritage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:15PM&lt;br /&gt;FIREWORKS&lt;br /&gt;Waterfront Park&lt;br /&gt;Bring your blanket or chair, sit and relax. A spectacular fireworks display is being planned for your enjoyment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186416385000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181259894000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yankee Homecoming Days in Newburyport</name><id>5866583</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186243200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5866583/</event_url></item>