<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWS ALERT&lt;/b&gt;: The Dinner Speaker Event IS CANCELLED TOMORROW, TUESDAY, FEBRUARY 16 DUE TO SNOW City of Waltham declares Snow Emergency. Please email betsy@optimumhealthsolution. org if you have bought a ticket on-line to instruct as to your preference of the following:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;    * donate the money to Optimum Health Solution - Kids&lt;br /&gt;    * apply the money for a ticket to Brenda Cobb March Dinner Speaker event&lt;br /&gt;    * ask for a refund&lt;br /&gt;    * other&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is still available for Thursday, Feb 18 discounted Health Assessments &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Optimum Health Solution is a Non-Profit dedicated to eliminating obesity, chronic disease and mal-nutrition,   especially in children, through the education and advocacy of healthful living. Donations Welcome  &lt;br /&gt;www.OptimumHealthSolution.org/donate.htm&lt;br /&gt;______________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 16th  Dinner Speaker features &amp;quot;Personal Adventures in Healing&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this exciting event where a panel of Raw Foodists share their personal triumphs in overcoming debilitating health challenges.  Randy Jacobs, owner of Life Force Growers-distributor of wheat grass and sprouts, will be moderating our distinguished panel.  Bring your questions and share your healing.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Our guests include: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne Silva, featured in Hippocrates Magazine, overcame Diabetes 2, morbid obesity(430 lbs to 170 1lbs) high blood pressure and colon/prostate cancer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dorothy Torrey- Acid/alkaline Health Coach on Cape Cod recovering from Suicidal Depression, severe osteo-arthritis and a breast cancer diagnosis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Lindsley with his children -Jane &amp;amp; Ray -Successful business man of 25 years and Health Consultant using detoxification techniques and raw food to overcome challenges with super hypersensitivities and allergies to all chemicals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sharon Kane - Fermentation Instructor overcame intestinal dysbiosis that manifested as candida, chronic sinus infections, bronchitis, asthma and fatigue syndrome. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betsy Bragg - Executive Director of Optimum Health Solution challenged with crippling arthritis from multiple injuries, ADHD and compulsive overeating and drinking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early to learn how to make delicious warm, seaweed Soup. Susan Allison www.thoreaufoods.com - chef &amp;amp; wellness coach .  Susan will be preparing and presenting warm seaweed soup. Suan harvests seaweed on the coast.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When:   Tuesday, February 16, 5:30 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Where:  U MA Waltham Center, 240 Beaver St., Waltham, MA see &lt;a href="http://www.optimumhealthsolution.org/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;www.optimumhealthsolution.org/directions.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What to bring and pay:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring your family and friends.  Children under 18 are free admission - just bring a dish of food as their contribution.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Save $5 by buying here: &lt;a href="http://www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog/" target="_blank"&gt;www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Or pay $20 at the door. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring raw organic, unprocessed, ready to serve dish for 8 with labeled utensils or pay an extra $10.  You can pay at the door or pay online here: &lt;a href="http://www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog/" target="_blank"&gt;www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted by &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.essenic.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4177857</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266532818000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263655931000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS Potluck / Speaker: "Personal Adventures in Healing" *CANCELLED DUE TO SNOW*</name><id>12335695</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266359400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/12335695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/1/global_12638257.jpeg</photo_url></item>