<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.272099</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-769-6113</phone><name>Visions By Baker</name><city>Worcester</city><id>415038</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.801903</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Foto Friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has been a discussion on the boards about what folks will be taking on for photo projects in the upcoming year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So to kick of 2012 and get our creativity flowing we have decided to have a meeting to discuss proposed projects and see if we can create a group of photographers to help support one another's ideas and personal projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I suggested that folks take a look at the 100 Print Project that Brooks Jensen of Lens Work Magazine did, which you can view here: &lt;a href="http://www.brooksjensenarts.com/100prints.xml" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brooksjensenarts.com/100prints.xml&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally, I have made a decision to try and take on this 100 print project for the upcoming year. Maybe some of you would like to join in- or create a project more suited for you- but this group would meet to help one another achieve our goals. What I am proposing for the group is this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in regular, structured meetings once a month to discuss one another's projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set and attain goals important to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive support and accountability from the group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solve problems creatively as a result of group dynamics and shared experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone should come prepared to discuss the subject of personal projects, and share thoughts and ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attend all as many sessions as possible- personally I think irregularities in participation will create disharmony and some frustration from other members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate with positive feedback and support other group members in their endeavors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I would hope that this group would become a safe place for members to feel they can be open, honest and trusting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you are interested in being part of this group. Come join us Monday night and see what we can make happen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>First Floor of the Mansion at Visions by Baker</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Baker</member_name><member_id>5043048</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328766714000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327101568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photography Projects for 2012</name><id>48957042</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328572800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/48957042/</event_url></item>