<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>State Park</address_2><address_1>End of Depot Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06340</zip><lat>41.349998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bluff Point Groton CT</name><city>Groton</city><id>321614</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.040001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;UPDATES:&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: A chance of showers and thunderstorms after 1pm. Partly cloudy, with a high near 88. West wind between 5 and 10 mph. Chance of precipitation is 30%.&lt;br /&gt;OK IM NOT WORRIED ABOUT THIS...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa   4     High   1:43 AM     2.8   5:46 AM     Set 12:16 PM      72&lt;br /&gt;     4      Low   8:18 AM     0.2   8:02 PM    Rise 10:51 PM&lt;br /&gt;     4     High   2:20 PM     3.3&lt;br /&gt;     4      Low   9:13 PM     0.2&lt;br /&gt;Ok clean water comming in..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be wearing a GEEKY lyme flourescent green traffic controll vest and orange shoes so you can find me..im sure i will stick out like a green thumb.. but im taking the vest off after a little while... not the orange shoes though&lt;br /&gt;I will have a blue toyota avalon with a multi kayak trailer....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;bring water to drink hat..sunscreen..etc..im guessing its going to be hot...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is good for Recreational kayaks, or Sea kayakers, beginners or experienced...&lt;br /&gt;I can only show you a few things given the paddling trips i have..and here is something devoted to the whole day..and its NO COST...&lt;br /&gt;I went to this last year and it was good for me and for the fellow paddlers...&lt;br /&gt;You will see some interesting things..and then later YOU try them for your self with ample people around to help you and its a good time just to talk and learn things from others that have been kayaking for years...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok as long as you have a PFD ...you will do ok...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the wistle..well..things happen..it wont hurt..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;its not necessary..but if you plan on sea kayaking...bring a spray skirt..&lt;br /&gt;try things with it and then without it...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle float..oh yes..this thing will save your butt, its the primary to learn technique for beginners but a backup safety technique for experienced..so its good for all...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a time that the Connyak people welcome recreational kayakers...it saves lives..cant argue with that...&lt;br /&gt;and its not really a &amp;quot;going&amp;quot; anywhere paddle..except for &amp;quot;going&amp;quot; to learn something or &amp;quot;going&amp;quot; to help someone also...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info is below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Annual ConnYak Kayak Self Rescue Techniques Clinic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bluff Point State Park, Groton, CT&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, August 4, 2007&lt;br /&gt;10:00 AM - 3:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(AL_R Note: the demonstration is around 10, then after you play around till you had enough..or then we paddle out somewhere towards the ocean a little ways out...) Make or buy some food for dinner..i dont care... bring a lunch though..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Various rescue techniques and scenarios will be demonstrated by members versed in same. This is a hands-on clinic, so plan to be in the water practicing what you saw after lunch. There will be plenty of folks available to share what they know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a flare and emergency signaling demo by the DEP boating division, and free vessel safety checks will be done by the US Coast Guard Auxilliary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those wishing to have the vessel safety checks done, note the following requirements to pass:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Every kayak/kayaker must have a PFD, Whistle, Mirror and Flash Light( for night). All items must be secure-no loose items. A paddle would be helpful as well&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is stupid enough to go without a paddle ?? ok ya might forget it...But i have seen those duck like feet gloves..they might be just as good as paddles..dont know..&lt;br /&gt;Loose items...yeh beer cans and fish hooks..? (seriously doing a lot of things will make things come off... even hatch covers..better to see what happens here than out in the deep..right...?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK getting there:&lt;br /&gt;Located at the end of Depot Road, this approximately 800 acre State reserve lies between the Poquonnock River and Mumford Cove. One of the largest natural areas in the State, it contains not only a variety of wildlife, but also a barrier beach, steep cliffs, forested lands and tidal wetlands. You can paddle up beyond the railroad bridge to the north (about 1/3 mile) and down to Bushy Point Beach (about 1 1/4 miles). Hiking and running trails offer vistas of Long Island Sound, Mumford Cove and the Pequonnock River. Public parking available. State-owned. To help you reach Bluff Point State Park and Reserve, some routes leading to this site are posted with the brown and white Long Island Sound Access sign...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depot Road &lt;br /&gt;Groton, Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;Phone - (860) 444-7591 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Fees &lt;br /&gt;None &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Directions &lt;br /&gt;From the East: Take I-95 South to exit 88. Turn right and go to the end. Take a right turn onto Route 1. Take a left at the light onto Depot Road. Go to the end. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit 88. Turn right and go to the end. Take a right turn onto Route 1. Take a left at the light onto Depot Road. Go to the end. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest, GPS or other, use 99 Depot Road, Groron, ct to get you close enough...&lt;br /&gt;takes about 1 hour from hartford...&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;LOOK AT YOUR MAPS...&lt;br /&gt;Rain Cancles the event...i will update as necessary...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186409049000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184257456000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking Self Rescue techniques and Everyone (Rec-Sea)Practice</name><id>6013533</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186236000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6013533/</event_url></item>