<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance is proud to sponsor this event at Harvard Business School featuring Dr. Ory Zik of HelioFocus and Mr. Shi Chuliang of Sanhua Holding Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Zik is the Co-founder of &lt;a href="http://www.heliofocus.com/" target="_blank"&gt;HelioFocus Ltd.&lt;/a&gt;, an Israel-based startup developing a solar booster for solar and conventional power plants.  In January 2010, HelioFocus &lt;a href="http://cleantech-israel.blogspot.com/2010/01/heliofocus-raises-10m-from-chinas.html" target="_blank"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; a $10M Series B investment from China's &lt;a href="http://www.zjshc.com/en-about1.asp" target="_blank"&gt; Sanhua Holding Group&lt;/a&gt; and existing investor &lt;a href="http://www.israelcorp.com/Default.aspx?tabid=76" target="_blank"&gt;IC Green Energy&lt;/a&gt;.  Shi Chuliang is Director, Chief Engineer and Head of Sanhua's Advanced R&amp;amp;D Center. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HelioFocus is also engaged in a &lt;a href="http://cleantech-israel.blogspot.com/2009/11/doe-awards-grants-to-heliofocus-tigo.html" target="_blank"&gt;joint R&amp;amp;D project&lt;/a&gt;, funded by the U.S. Department of Energy, to develop and commercialize a solar-powered micro-turbine in cooperation with California-based Capstone Turbine Corporation.  HelioFocus' technology is the result of 2 decades of research at the Weizmann Institute of Science.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Zik's  and Mr. Shi Chuliang will discuss the HelioFocus - Sanhua solar technology and financial partnership and explore the theme of U.S.-Israel-China cleantech cooperation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;6:30-7:00pm Networking &amp;amp; Intros (Pizza &amp;amp; Drinks)&lt;br /&gt;7:00-8:00pm Presentations and Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;8:00-8:30pm Member Announcements &amp;amp; Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Harvard Business School and a campus map are available at &lt;a href="http://www.hbs.edu/about/visit.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hbs.edu/ab...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you to our co-sponsors, the &lt;a href="http://www.studentclubs.hbs.edu/benv/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;HBS Greentech &amp;amp; Sustainability Club&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.cjp.org/index.aspx?page=1" target="_blank"&gt;Combined Jewish Philanthropies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ory Zik&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Ory Zik is a serial entrepreneur focusing on Cleantech. He co-founded HelioFocus which he led for 3 years as CEO until the successful deal with Chinese Sanhua. The company is developing a solar booster for solar and conventional power plants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to HelioFocus he was the founding CEO of QuantomiX Inc., a company based on his invention which he led from inception in 2001 to commercialization in 2007. QuantomiX solved the problem of imaging live cells and tissues with an electron microscope for research and clinical applications. Prior to that Ory lead a spin-off of El Mul technologies where he co-invented and developed the ‘E-beam on a Chip’ nanotubes-based platform.  He holds B.Sc. (cum laude) in Physics and Mathematics from Tel Aviv University as well as M.Sc. (cum laude) and Ph.D. in Physics from the Weizmann Institute of Science, where he received the Feinberg physics award and the national Amos De Shalit physics prize.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ory is also active in education and environmental protection. In 1992, he was appointed the scientific curator of Israel’s National Museum of Science. In 1993 he founded the Greenpeace Israel Office which he led for 3 years while a Ph.D. students leading clean Mediterranean campaign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shi Chuliang&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Shi Chuliang started his career with Sanhua in China as an engineer after his graduation from Shanghai Jiaotong University 1989. He was appointed as Chief Engineer in 2001, Vice General Manager of Sanhua Holding Group 2002-2006, Vice General Manager of Danfoss-Sanhua Micro-Channel Heat-Exchanger Co., Ltd. 2007-2009. Now, Mr. Shi Chuliang is the Director, Chief Engineer and Head of Advanced R&amp;amp;D Center.  During his 20 years’ career In Sanhua, Mr. Shi Chuliang has held his own patents in engineering and created a new management system with Sanhua characteristics.  Mr. Shi Chuliang received his BS in Engineering from Shanghai Jiaotong University and EMBA from Fudan University.  He is a Director of HelioFocus Ltd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sanhua Holding Group&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sanhua Holding Group is a large private enterprise with integrated capability of product R&amp;amp;D, manufacturing, business operation and service. Since its establishment in 1984, Sanhua has created an industrial structure consisted of refrigeration and air conditioning components, automobile components and real estate, with more than 20 subsidiaries and 12000 employees. Recently entering into the Cleantech industry, Sanhua invested 10.5 million dollar in an Israeli Solar Thermal start-up company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Group has been awarded the Chinese Excellent Enterprise, National Key High-tech Enterprise, National High-reputation Enterprise, China’s Top 500 Manufacturing Enterprises, China’s 500 Most Valuable Brands (No. 115) and so on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As one of the biggest and famous manufacturing enterprise of refrigeration components in the world, Sanhua´s brand has been accepted by global and domestic customers for its representative significance of high quality and excellent service. Sanhua´s logo of 3 flowers symbolizes the 3 foundations of the company: The technology, the talents of the employees and the professional management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268656547000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>85</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264613067000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HelioFocus: The Potential for U.S.-Israel-China Cleantech Cooperation</name><id>12439606</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267745400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/12439606/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/8/global_12823688.jpeg</photo_url></item>