<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wallingford</address_2><address_1>1339 Whirlwind Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.436100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Goeveia Vineyards</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>345258</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.764336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's meet for a wine tasting, and appetizers at Gouveia Vineyards. The winery is  located at 1339 Whirlwind Hill Road in Wallingford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have had two events here in the past and the setting is great. You get the opportunity to taste 5 local wines for 5.00 including the glass or all 7 for 7 dollars. if you prefer, wine is available by the glass. You can bring your own appetizers but no outside beverages are allowed on the premises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am requesting that if you are unable to attend, you adjust your RSVP accordingly at least 24 hours prior if possible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will also be accepting bookings for private wine tastings at that time. Please also bring suggestions for future meetings such as your favorite wine bars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Events: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members will meet at the vineyard to enjoy appetizers and of course, wine. Please indicate on the RSVP what you will be bringing to avoid duplication. Finger foods that would go well with wines would be desirable. Also needed would be paper plates and plastic utensils. The vineyard does not allow visitors to bring wine or bottled beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a 5 -7 dollar fee payable to the vineyard for the wine tasting.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a traveling vineyards button and position myself at the door for 15 minutes. I will also provide a cell phone number to members that have RSVP's prior to the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lynn</member_name><member_id>4669226</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1256247438000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233158220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Reprise:wine tasting at Gouveia Vineyards in Wallingford, CT</name><id>9619392</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234731600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/9619392/</event_url></item>