<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Thursday, Nov 15th is all about networking, networking and networking! You will also hear from local real estate investor Shaun Reilly about a local deal of the month and you will learn or be reminded why your mother was right when she told you to drink your milk!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=b74cc0a3a6&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=13a6f341f2a1d33a&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=inline&amp;amp;realattid=f_h8ek5i070&amp;amp;safe=1&amp;amp;zw" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=b74cc0a3a6&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=13a6f341f2a1d33a&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=thd&amp;amp;realattid=f_h8ek5i070&amp;amp;zw" alt="ShaunReilly_11-2010.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Are you ready to hear from a local investor that Boston AREIA has seen grow and become a successful over the past 3 years?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Shaun Reilly is going to go over a local deal from finding and funding the deal throughout the process of the rehab. Shaun is a full time real estate investor who’s company, Reilly Real Estate, LLC, &lt;br /&gt;

works in both quick turn and long-term strategies. Shaun grew up in Dracut, MA and has been in the Boston area for over 15 years since starting college at Boston University where he earned Bachelor degrees in both Chemistry and Mathematics. He later received an MBA and a Masters of Finance at Boston College’s prestigious Carroll School of Management. Shaun has been investing in real estate since 2007 and went into the business full time in January 2010 when his former employer decided they no longer needed his services--and he agreed with them! &lt;br /&gt;

He is currently building a multi-state rental portfolio while also managing multiple rehab &lt;br /&gt;

flips. Shaun resides in Newton, MA with his wife Megan and two young daughters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you know why your mother was right when she told you to drink your milk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=b74cc0a3a6&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=13a845cf521a8007&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=inline&amp;amp;safe=1&amp;amp;zw" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&amp;amp;ik=b74cc0a3a6&amp;amp;view=att&amp;amp;th=13a845cf521a8007&amp;amp;attid=0.1&amp;amp;disp=thd&amp;amp;zw" alt="20120915_151127.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;David Cuthbert is an independent Financial Advisor and Registered Rep. On Thursday, he's going to show you how you can use long term strategies to hedge the risk with your real estate investments. He will also discuss &lt;br /&gt;

ways to tax diversify your portfolio, and why it is important to take steps now to prepare yourself for the likelihood of future increases in tax rates. And, he will remind you why your mother was right when she told you to drink your milk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monthly Meeting - Thu Nov 15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30 PM - Networking, 6:30pm - Meeting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doubletree Suites, 400 Soldiers Field Road, Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free for members; $25 for nonmembers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353030363000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Thu, Nov 15th is all about networking! You will also hear from local real estate investor Shaun Reilly about a local deal of the month and you will learn or be reminded why your mother was right when she told you to drink your milk!</why><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>70</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350941147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston AREIA Monthly meeting - Networking, Deal of the month and more</name><id>lpnmqyqpbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353018600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/88114402/</event_url></item>