<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you're in town this weekend, hopefully you can make this film.&amp;nbsp;Alexander Payne's films are always great, and all reports say this is no exception. Please note that it will be on three (3) screens, and we'll be at the 4:45 showing. Also, I limited the number who can attend, but this is&amp;nbsp;such a popular film a second meetup could happen. (No pressure, John!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the film:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Alexander Payne, creator of the Oscar-winning &lt;em&gt;Sideways&lt;/em&gt;, comes &lt;em&gt;The Descendants&lt;/em&gt;, a sometimes humorous, sometimes tragic journey for Matt King (George Clooney), a distracted husband and back-up parent to two girls who is forced to re-examine his past and embrace his future when his wife suffers a life-threatening boating accident off of Waikiki. The event leads to a rapprochement with his young daughters while Matt wrestles with a decision to sell the family's land, which was handed down from Hawaiian royalty and missionaries. Co-starring Shailene Woodley, Amara Miller, Judy Greer and Beau Bridges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;The Descendants&lt;/em&gt;, Payne's long-awaited new film, is another beautifully chiseled piece of filmmaking &amp;mdash; sharp, funny, generous, and moving &amp;mdash; that writes its own rules as much as &lt;em&gt;About Schmidt&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Sideways&lt;/em&gt; did." Grade: A -- Entertainment Weekly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Clooney gives such an invisible performance here that you may not notice the depth of the trick - that he&amp;rsquo;s a handsome movie star playing an entitled upper-class lawyer yet still conveying the weary, beleaguered confusion of a guy who&amp;rsquo;s in the same boat we are." 3 1/2 stars -- Boston Globe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film, I'll be near the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322403916000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321983639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Descendants</name><id>42059942</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322343900000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/42059942/</event_url></item>