<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a discussion of Chapter 9 of &amp;quot;The Artist's Way&amp;quot; or Chapter 8 of &amp;quot;Finding Water.&amp;quot; Chapter 9 is &amp;quot;Recovering a Sense of Compassion.&amp;quot; We'll take up topics from the chapters, including enthusiasm, creative u-turns, resistance, and compassion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In writing about enthusiasm, Cameron says &amp;quot;In order to work well, many artists find that their work spaces are best dealt with as play spaces... toys from the five and dime, tiny miniature Christmas lights, papier-mâché monsters, hanging crystals, a sprig of flowers...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe you've already picked up a few fun and/or inspiring items like this on artist's dates or on a walk through one of these beautiful Spring afternoons. If so, bring one or two of your finds along. Maybe it's not even an object, but a mental image your took. Whatever--if it made you smile, it might be fun to share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring a copy of the book you're following, a pen or pencil, and your sense of the absurd. More information on finding either book is on the message board (under the &amp;quot;discussions&amp;quot; tab). Information about parking and public transportation near Gallery 263 can also be found on the message board.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: tomato"&gt;**Please note that we are still meeting at 7pm **&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;If you are able, please bring a $5 donation to the Gallery for the use of their space -- thank you!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet you at the door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>pam romagnoli</member_name><member_id>9024784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271376689000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Artists and Creators!</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Artists-Way-Boston-area</urlname><id>1471304</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Artists Way Boston Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267751307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Artist's Way Cambridge Meetup</name><id>wqsdnyngblb</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270767600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Artists-Way-Boston-area/events/12787784/</event_url></item>