<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Old Gate Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06460</zip><lat>41.233742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Old Gate Tavern</name><city>Milford</city><id>5644262</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.027252</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For over 16 years strong, the &amp;quot;WHAT UP FUNK BAND&amp;quot; has amazed audiences on a national and local level with it's driving high energy performances and dance addictive repertoire. The music of this 7-piece ensemble is achieved through a thoughtful balance of instrumentation and vocal melody. Soulful and always funky, &amp;quot;WHAT UP&amp;quot; derives it's force from diverse cultural backgrounds as well as musical expertise. The unique sight and sound experience of this tight talented unit has graced the stages with R &amp;amp; B legends like: Average White Band, Tower of Power, Little Anthony and the Imperials, Blues innovator James Cotton, Pop icons Taylor Dayne and Richard Marx to name a few. The &amp;quot; WHAT UP FUNK BAND&amp;quot; has an extensive reputation whose resume includes main stage appearances @ national music festivals throughout the northeast, major casinos and nightclubs in the tri-state area (&amp;#147;SANDS&amp;quot; Atlantic City NJ, &amp;quot;MOHEGAN SUN&amp;quot; CT, &amp;quot;LE BAR BAT&amp;quot; NYC) and various state colleges and universities. In addition, &amp;#147;WHAT UP&amp;#148; has been there for the many community events and benefits for charities like 9/11 relief, M.D.A. and cure for cancer research. Whatever your affair, the &amp;quot; WHAT UP FUNK BAND&amp;quot; has got the plan for you. In 1998, the band released it's first original cd &amp;quot; AS FUNKY AS U WANNA B&amp;quot; as a passion project that quickly turned into a hit with it's core fan base. Due to the overwhelming success of the first recording, &amp;quot; WHAT UP&amp;quot; released their follow up cd &amp;quot; SOULFUNKFUL&amp;quot; in 2006 where sales and exposure launched them to national venues, radio play in the U.S. and France, and the 2006 recording of their 3rd cd &amp;quot;LIVE FUNK&amp;quot;. The popularity of the original music has been well received and grown into a unique defining characteristic of the band. Audiences appreciate the vast song selection and how easily the original music is woven into the fabric of the sets. Musically speaking, the 7 separate talents of this band of brothers unite on 1 stage at 1 moment in time to deliver the highest level of performance and professionalism. With an emphasis in the traditional values of playing live music, the band provides a fresh modern sound whose approach, interpretation and direction can creatively adapt to any situation. People of all ages feel the power of the &amp;quot; WHAT UP FUNK &amp;quot; vibe. Let this be your invitation to join the growing phenomena of the &amp;quot; WHAT UP FUNK BAND &amp;quot; experience.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>simone</member_name><member_id>7013797</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331506792000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328996966000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WhatUpFunk is playing at Old Gate Tavern, Milford</name><id>51986162</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331344800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/51986162/</event_url></item>