<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>PLEASE NOTE DIFFERENT LOCATION.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week we are doing something a bit different. Lisa Blake, a local meditation teacher, is offering a five week workshop/book group entitled &amp;quot;Peaceful Mind, Compassionate Heart&amp;quot;. The cost is $15 and she has welcomed us to check out the first session and stay for the remaining 4 Mondays if we choose. Here is the write-up from the sadhaname.com website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Peaceful Mind, Compassionate Heart&amp;quot; is a series of teachings on the basics of Mahayana Buddhism. We will follow the book of the same title by my spiritual guide and friend of 8 years, Khen Rinpoche Lobzang Tsetan which offers rich advice to the newcomer as well as seasoned wisdom to for the long-term practitioner. Khen Rinpoche's book gets to the heart of Buddha's advice and directs us how to use spiritual practice to cultivate a peaceful mind and compassionate heart. Each class will be interactive and cover 2 chapters (around 30 pages), concluding with a 15 minute meditation. The class will meet 5 Mondays beginning Sept. 27 - Nov. 1 (skipping Oct. 18) The cost is $75 plus $15 for the book. There will also be one free scholarship for the class, book not included. Lisa V. Blake has taught meditation to hundreds of students as young as three, as wise as ninety and many ages in between. She is founder of the Maine Mindfulness Project and teaches meditation in educational settings from elementary schools to colleges. She travels and teaches internationally. In addition, she is a meditation practitioner at True North Health Center, Maine’s Center for Functional Health. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next week we will resume our weekly meetups at the First Parish Church on Congress Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;TomC, Organizer&lt;br /&gt;Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285629663000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Peaceful Mind, Compassionate Heart</name><id>qmmdnynmbkc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285624800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/14899037/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/0/global_10129760.jpeg</photo_url></item>