<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Raymond Street - Apt. 1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.361900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 901-8871</phone><name>Jason's House</name><city>Allston</city><id>1376656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134400</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have questions about how to improve your love life? Would you like to get better results in the world of dating and you're not sure where to begin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you have no trouble going to meetup events, but you just aren't making the kind of connections that you hoped for, and you'd like help with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to get answers and help with your specific challenges, then you're going to love this. Here's what this is all about: My name is Jason, for the last year I have produced highly structured dating and social skills workshops for this group, and people just like you have gotten a ton of value out of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But even with the success that this group has enjoyed, I honestly believe we can go further and create educational events that are even more fun and more magical. So in the spirit of that, I've decided to turn this next workshop on its head and do something we've never done before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

WE ARE GOING TO CREATE THE WORKSHOP TOGETHER... IN THE MOMENT! &lt;br /&gt;

*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's how this will work. You'll come to the workshop with one or two questions or situations that you'd like help with, and we'll create a lesson or an exercise we can all benefit from right on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will allow for ideas that are totally unexpected and unplanned to emerge, and we'll all be energized by what we can create in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have questions about how to make small talk easier (or how to transition from small talk to getting a date)?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you like to be able to ask someone on a date, but you're nervous and out of practice?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you find yourself getting into conversations that lead nowhere and want help becoming more interesting?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you unhappy about the way your love life is going, but you're not sure what to do in order to change it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have questions about sex? Maybe you want to know how to have better sex. Or, maybe you want to know how to have MORE sex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

ALL OF THESE QUESTIONS (AND MORE) ARE FAIR GAME &lt;br /&gt;

*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to get personalized help in the areas where you feel stuck, or like you're not getting the kind of results you know you could. This is sure to be a lot of fun, and I'm excited to see what we can all create together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, you'll be able to submit your questions anonymously on paper so that nobody knows who asked the question (if you choose). I want you to feel safe and still get your questions answered even if you're too shy to speak up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

HOW TO GET INVOLVED&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This event is going to be at my home in Lower Allston, right near Harvard Business School. It's very easy to get to both by car and public transportation, and there's plenty of on-street parking. Directions will be emailed to you. We will start the event promptly at 7:00pm and run until 9:00pm. Please plan on arriving by 6:45 so you have time to settle in and meet the other guests. You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Cheap. &amp;nbsp;If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and&amp;nbsp;that's assuming there even&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;a class that could offer you this kind of knowledge, which there isn't. &amp;nbsp;The opportunity to get personal coaching on your specific questions is priceless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Because I want to help as many women as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to. &amp;nbsp;The cost for this event is only $25, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about it...&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;that's 83 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;What else do you spend 83 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Because this is class is being held at my house and not a large seminar room, I have to limit the size to only 10 students. &amp;nbsp;There are over 850 other people seeing this message, so be&amp;nbsp;sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$25 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot. &amp;nbsp;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warmly,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My house is easy to find.  It'll be on the left side of the street, and I'll have a blue rope light on the porch.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324162586000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323380439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Coaching On Dating and Relationships!</name><id>43862592</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323820800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/43862592/</event_url></item>