<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1500 West Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01002</zip><lat>42.306053</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Notch Visitor Center</name><city>Amherst</city><id>3016221</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.529755</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is a Point-to-Point Hike.  We will need to spot cars at either end.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 6-mile hike in the eastern Berkshires of Central Massachusetts makes a fantastic fall hike.  The point-to-point trek along the Metacomet-Monadnock Trail covers a series of peaks including Mount Holyoke, the Seven Sisters, Mount Hitchcock, and Bare Mountain.  Even though the highest summit is only 1010 feet, there are some very steep ups and downs along the ridge.  We will gain over 2000 feet in elevation while crossing the ridge! Views across the Connecticut River Valley are spectacular.  This is by far one of my favorite day hikes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since we need to spot cars, we will meet at the Notch Visitor Center in Amherst &lt;b&gt;PROMPTLY&lt;/b&gt; at 9:00 AM.  From there we will drive 1/2 the cars over to the trailhead on Route 47 and begin our trek across the ridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This hike is best in good weather.  Therefore, rain or snow &lt;b&gt;will&lt;/b&gt; cancel.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that dogs are not permitted on this hike.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What:&lt;/i&gt;  Holyoke and the Seven Sisters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Distance:&lt;/i&gt; 6 miles point to point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Elevation Gain:&lt;/i&gt; 2500'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/i&gt; Moderate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Pace:&lt;/i&gt; Moderate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Exposure:&lt;/i&gt; Minor exposure on this route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Book Time:&lt;/i&gt; 3 1/2 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will be at a&lt;b&gt;moderate pace&lt;/b&gt;. We make every attempt to keep the group together throughout the hike.  Despite the location, this is a deceptively rugged ridge.  Expect many steep sections both up and down.  The views are spectacular.  There is some exposure on the ridge, but it's easily avoided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;To participate you should:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable hiking UPHILL at about 1.5 to 2.0 miles per hour at a 15% incline for about 3 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be comfortable walking &lt;b&gt;at least 7 miles&lt;/b&gt; on uneven terrain including roots, rocks, and granite ledges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have sturdy hiking boots.  &lt;b&gt;No Sneakers&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have rain and wind protection.  &lt;b&gt;No Ponchos&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be able to carry at least 2 liters of water. (Remember, 1 liter weighs 2 pounds!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be in good physical condition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mandatory Equipment List as of 09 October 2010.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This list could change based on trail conditions just prior to the hike.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Synthetic shirt and pants. &lt;b&gt;No cotton.  No jeans.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sturdy Hiking Boots.  &lt;b&gt;No Sneakers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rain / Wind Jacket. &lt;b&gt;No Ponchos.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Warm fleece layer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Warm gloves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 liters Water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trail Snacks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Optional Gear:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hiking Poles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gaiters&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunscreen / Sunglasses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Camera / Binoculars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Jeans, Sneakers, or Cotton clothing on the hike!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that are interested, we will meet in the parking lot at Lincoln Mall on Rte 116 in RI next to the McDonald's at 6:30 AM.  We will leave Lincoln Mall PROMPTLY at 6:45.  As a reminder, we need cars at both ends of the trailhead sufficient to carry everyone, so we may need to take several cars from Lincoln Mall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining Options&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch / Dinner&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will plan to stop for lunch or dinner after the hike.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Trailhead&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-90 (Mass Pike) WEST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 7 for MA-21 towards Ludlow/Belchertown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn Left onto Rood Street.  This turns into Fuller Street and then merges with West Street, becomes East Street, and finally turns into Pleasant Street.  (It's one long street with many names.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn Right on MA-202.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make a quick left on Amherst Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This turns into MA-116.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue to follow MA-116 to the Notch Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total driving time from Providence, approximately 2 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;GPS Info&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Notch Visitor Center's address is:&lt;br /&gt;1500 West Street&lt;br /&gt;Amherst, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails and Other Info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will take the Metacomet Monadnock Trail from MA-47 across the western section of the Holyoke Range, and will end at the Notch Visitor Center on MA-116.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will provide my cell phone number along with a link to a detailed trail map to all &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; RSVPs the week of the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Grey Hyundai Sonata with RI License Plates.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289081357000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286662516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Holyoke and the Seven Sisters</name><id>15057761</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289048400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/15057761/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>