<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Rock with &amp;quot;Pandemonium with Teresa Rodriguez&amp;quot; - Elizabeth Park - FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a fun, BEAUTIFUL evening of &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; on Elizabeth Park's Rose Garden Lawn this WEDNESDAY, 08/15.  Gather @ 6:00 (show 6:30 - 8:00).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; LOOK FOR: a large &amp;quot;Cheers&amp;quot; COCKTAIL-Shaped BALLOON (see this MeetUp's photo).  Also, Al R. will be there with his four orange traffic cones.  &lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; We tend to group farther back, nearer the Rose Garden than to the stage.  This is a combined gathering of MeetUp &amp;amp; Single Event social networking groups, typically 12-24 party together each time (spontaniously, with or without RSVP's), sometimes many more!  New friends are always welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; BYOB and snacks/Picnic dinner, if you'd like... bring extra for the post-party that typically ensues locally.  As always, be discreet, don't litter, and drive responsibly! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; To cut down on email updates, please check back here by 3PM the day of the event for any updated info.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; *** &lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Park &lt;br /&gt;1555 Asylum Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Rose Garden Lawn &lt;br /&gt;West Hartford, CT 06107 &lt;br /&gt;860-231-9443&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, per Elizabeth Park's web site, &amp;quot;Pandemonium&amp;quot; is being &amp;quot;mis-&amp;quot;advertised as &amp;quot;50's music&amp;quot;, however, in checking out their web site, they are actually quite a contemporary, rockin' band full of energy that'll get the crowd dancing! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pandemonium is a four-piece band that's been entertaining crowds all over the Tri-State area since 2001. Performing at nightclubs, colleges, casinos, ski lodges, corporate parties, fundraisers, festivals, weddings...you name it, they've played it. With a library of literally hundreds of songs, PDM can cover anything from Jackson 5 to Bon Jovi, Blondie to No Doubt, The Beatles to AC/DC, Katrina and the Waves to Kelly Clarkson...Guns &amp;amp; Roses, Green Day, Poison, Blink 182, Van Halen...old...new...basically ANYTHING that people can sing along with and jam to. For latest schedule and news updates, visit: www.pdmrocks.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187388274000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187028510000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Pandemonium with Teresa Rodriguez" - Elizabeth Park - FREE</name><id>6173304</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187215200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/6173304/</event_url></item>