<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Conscious Movie:  Promises&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, February 20th • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Description &lt;br /&gt;Several Jewish and Palestinian children are followed for three years and put in touch with each other, in this alternative look at the Jewish-Palestinian conflict. The three filmmakers followed a group of seven local children between 1995 and 1998. They all have a totally different background. These seven children tell their own story about growing up in Jerusalem. Through this portrait of their generation, we see how deep rooted and almost insoluble the problems of the Middle East have become. When the protagonists speak out in an epilogue a couple of years later, it becomes apparent that all have lost their childlike innocence. Written by Sujit R. Varma &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is free.  Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the Orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235349246000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228940179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie:  Promises</name><id>9315937</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235176200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/9315937/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/6/b/global_6579947.jpeg</photo_url></item>