<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I would like to pass out DVD's and fliers here. If there are enough people that want to help I would like to bring a banner there as well. Please give me a call if you want to participate. My name is mark and the number to reach me is  (617) 652-0121. &lt;br /&gt;-mark WeAreChangeBoston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, May 31, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join Veterans For Peace and the Massachusetts chapter of Military Families Speak Out for a ceremony for peace on Memorial Day, to remember and mourn those who died — but also to say that we want no more dead in senseless, immoral wars and occupations for oil and American Empire. Instead of glorifying war, we strive to work for peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1PM&lt;br /&gt;Christopher Columbus Park, near Long Wharf, Atlantic Ave.&lt;br /&gt;(Directions from Aquarium T stop: Follow the signs in the station for Waterfront and Aquarium. As you exit the T station, turn right on Atlantic Ave. and turn right again after passing the Long Wharf Marriott. Enter the park, pass Tia’s restaurant, and the gathering will be at the harbor near Long Wharf)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, please contact at info@massvfp.org or 781–643–3307, or visit&lt;a href="http://smedleyvfp.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://smedleyvfp.org...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275329952000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273274235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Veterans For Peace: Ceremony for peace on Memorial Day</name><id>13418279</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275325200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/13418279/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/global_12798054.jpeg</photo_url></item>