<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Town Hall Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03823</zip><lat>43.167313</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-312-6735</phone><name>Madbury Town Hall</name><city>Madbury </city><id>1136945</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.942390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Fans!  Join us for an evening of  snowshoeing.  We will be exploring Kingman Farm in Madbury, next to Durham, NH.  If there isn't enough snow for snowshoeing, we'll hike instead. So come try out the new snowshoes that you got for Christmas as we explore Kingman Farm's wide array of trails.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the snowshoeing/hiking we'll be having a bonfire at my house on Long Pond Road.  But that address is new and is not on GPS or Mapquest yet, so  use the address of the house next door--12 Hampshire Ave, Durham.  This is just down the road from the snowshowing meetup place in Madbury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your guitar or other musical instrument and we will play and sing around the bonfire! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some other things:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It helps if you have a headlamp or flashlight!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be joined by other meetup groups there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike might take about an hour and a half so dress warmly!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have a couple of extra pairs of snowshoes if anyone needs them but please email me and give me your telephone number.&lt;br /&gt;My telephone number is 603-312-6735 if anyone has any questions or needs directions!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather turns nasty I will email and post a message in case we have to cancel or reschedule the activitity.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the parking lot beside Madbury Town Hall, and NOT at the pullout along Rt 155. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kingman Farm&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Kingman Farm is located on Route 155 in Madbury, New Hampshire. This property contains 334.7 acres of woodland, including a small portion of wetlands. There is an extensive trail system which runs throughout the property which is ideal for mountain biking, hiking, or running. This land is also used for educational field experience for the UNH Natural Resources Department. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History &lt;br /&gt;The University of New Hampshire acquired the Kingman Farm in 1961, and they have consistently promoted preservation, sustainability, improvement, and recreation ever since. There has been a minimal harvesting of any valuable timber in order to promote these objectives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Present Uses &lt;br /&gt;The primary recreational uses of the Kingman Farm are mountain biking, hiking, jogging, snowmobiling, cross-country skiing, and foxhunt training for dogs. There are also a series of mountain bike races held in the fall to raise money for the UNH ski team. In addition the property is used frequently for educational research by UNH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.unh.edu/woodlands/properties/kingman/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.unh.edu/wo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Pets, Please.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294158984000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293381713000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moonlight Snowshoe/Hike at Kingman Farm and Bonfire!</name><id>15821612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293917400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/15821612/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/e/global_2233934.jpeg</photo_url></item>