<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Sheffield Egremont Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01230</zip><lat>42.146654</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass AT: Shay's Rebellion Trailhead</name><city>Great Barington</city><id>1617678</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.385727</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/8/c/event_22546220.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part 2 of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail! Join us on Saturday May 14th to do the second part of a series of hikes that I will be scheduling to do the entire length of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail. We will meet at the Shay's Rebellion Monument Parking Lot, which will be the ending location of our hike.We'll then leave half the cars and drive over to rt 41 and the Race Brook Falls Trail Head (the ending location of the first hike). We'll hike up the Race Brook Falls Trail by a beautiful waterfall (pic to the left). This trail includes several water crossings which were VERY difficult when we did them in April. Water was really running and we sometimes had to search up and down the brook for a location to cross and even then it involved jumping from rock to rock. The water level shouldn't be as high now but be aware that it is possible. Be prepared for plenty of mud and a slippery trail! Hike is 2 miles up to the Appalachian Trail. Once back on the AT we start a difficult .7 mile ascent to the summit of Mt Everett (2602 ft). This is the highest point of this section's hike. It is then 3.5 miles to the rocky summit of Jug End mt (1705 ft) while crossing several other summits on the way. Good views from the top of Jug End. Very steep section of the trail with some exposed rock faces as we come down 1.1 miles to the intersection with Jug End rd. Its then 2.7 miles to our ending point at Shay's Rebellion. Total hike is 10 miles through challenging terrain with a total elevation gain approximated at 2100 ft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a lengthy hike over difficult terrain with some decent elevation gains. We will have to move at good pace because of the length of the hike so I ask that only experienced hikers in good physical condition sign up. I'm limiting the numbers on this hike so please only sign up if you are sure you can make it (which really always applies, but its worth calling out). Please bring plenty of water (I'm bringing 3 liters) appropriate hiking attire (no jeans or cotton, hiking boots not sneakers), rain gear in case the weather turns nasty, lunch, and snacks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Trailhead Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Providence 2 hours 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Newport 3 hours 10 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note the address given above is approximate...the parking lot is on Sheffield Egremont rd about 2 miles south of South Egremont and 2 miles north of where the road starts on rt 7. It is just across the street from the Shay's Rebellion Monument. On the left side coming from the south, right side from the north. Just north of the intersection with Rebellion Road. Google Maps link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=40+sheffield+egremont+rd+great+barrington+MA&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;sll=42.146654,-73.385728&amp;amp;cbp=13,342.14,,0,14.7&amp;amp;cbll=42.146655,-73.385695&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;sspn=0.006295,0.006295&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=40+Sheffield-Egremont+Rd,+Great+Barrington,+Massachusetts+01230&amp;amp;ll=42.146653,-73.3857&amp;amp;spn=0.006236,0.013937&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=17&amp;amp;panoid=VqhE_HqLtLUyYfmpqN26Qg" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?q=40+sheffield+egremont+rd+great+barrington+MA&amp;amp;layer=c&amp;amp;sll=42.146654,-73.385728&amp;amp;cbp=13,342.14,,0,14.7&amp;amp;cbll=42.146655,-73.385695&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;sspn=0....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Route&amp;nbsp;Information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;2 miles on the Race Brook Falls Trail to its junction with the Appalachian Trail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;.7 miles to Mt Everett(2,602 ft).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;1.8 miles to the intersection with Elbow Trail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;1.7 miles to Jug End Mountain (1750 ft)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;1.1 miles to intersection with Jug End Road&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;2.7 miles to Shay's Rebellion Monument&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be in Worcester MA the night before, but please use the comments section to coordinate with other hikers if you want to carpool. Just remember that we do have to carspot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Massachusetts Appalachian Trail Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/8/event_22864520.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Most hikers are a little in awe of the Appalachian Trail, which runs 2,179 miles from Georgia to Maine, and secretly wonder/wish they could hike the whole thing...and I'm no exception. Since hiking the whole thing isnt an option....I figured I would start hiking sections of it starting with Massachusetts. The Massachusetts section runs through the western part of the state through the Berkshires from Sages Ravine at the CT border (near Salisbury, CT) up to the southern end of the Green Mountains in Vermont. So throughout this hiking season I'll be posting various chunks of the trail, in order going from South to North. The trail runs 90 mile in Mass....so it will probably be about a dozen hikes. A few of them will be single hikes but some will be weekend hikes where we hike both Saturday and Sunday to get the most miles under our belt since its a bit of a drive to get up there. It can be challenging to find access points to the trail to properly divide up the sections so if you sign up for these please be patient and keep in mind that there are some logistical issues to car spotting and finding appropriate parking areas (and I have never hiked most of these trails)....we will end up hiking far more than the 90 miles since we will have to hike on connecting trails just to get to the AT. (The first hike is a great example....4 miles of connection trails hiked, plus 1.5 of CT AT....meaning we only get through 5 miles of actual Massachusetts AT on section 1!). I'm going to limit the numbers for these hikes and I will try and give preference to those that are doing multiple sections and not just one. That is, if you have gone on the first two sections I will try and make sure you get into the third section before someone who hasnt done any so far. Depending on how it goes we may increase the limit. We'll see if we even get much interest given the length of the car ride up to the Berkshires. I hope to see some of you out there! MAP NOTE: What we have hiked is in black, current section in red, remaining trail red dots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Shay's Rebellion Monument Parking Lot, look for my bright yellow Ford Escape. Cell: 508-414-8544. Above address is approximate, see directions below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305717392000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Total Mass AT Hiked Before this section: 4.2 out of 89.7     4.7%
Total Mass AT Hiked After this section:  12.2 out of 89.7     13.6%</why><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303429906000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massachusetts Appalachian Trail: Part 2</name><id>17391269</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305379800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/17391269/</event_url></item>