<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>E Branch Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.056168</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lincoln Woods Visitor Information Center</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>478131</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.625130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a tentative date for this hike. Owls Head is a remote summit and we need good weather and trail conditions for an event. All interested hikers will stay in contact and privately provide phone numbers to organizers in case of last minute change of plans. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THREE EVENT OPTIONS: PLEASE SPECIFY WHICH GROUP YOUR RSVP IS FOR. (A: Lincoln Woods hike , B: Owl's Head summit attempt. C: XSKI AND HIKE TO OWLS HEAD)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The start times vary 6:30 am for group B Owls Head attempt, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group A light hike 9 am. This group is leaderless 3 rsvp's create a group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail route to Owl's Head is about 9 miles each way, and begins with an easy walk up the old railroad grade on the &lt;a href="http://hikenh.netfirms.com/TDLincWd.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Lincoln Woods Trail/Wilderness Trail &lt;/a&gt; to just beyond a bridge crossing Franconia Brook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion on winter trail variations, will help finalize our itinerary. We will plan on a recommended bushwhack to shorten the trip, but Mother Nature is in charge and we will obey.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the Lincoln Woods Trail/Wilderness Trail can be fast walking, this is a long hike by any route and an early start and plenty of spare flashlight batteries are recommended in addition to your winter clothing, food and gear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are limited to groups of 10 for this wilderness area hike. Additional hike leaders and expereinced hikers are encouraged to come for extra groups and trail support. We will all have a good time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead: Lincoln Woods visitor information center, off NH Route 112 just E of bridge over East Branch of the Pemigewasset River, elevation about 1180 feet&lt;br /&gt;44.0638°N, 71.5884°W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;WMNF fee site&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 Exit 32 at Lincoln and go E on NH Route 112 (Kancamagus Highway) about 5.7 miles to sign and parking lot on L&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Far End: Junction with Franconia Brook Trail, elevation about 1440 feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with any winter hike, we have no idea what the trail condition will be like until we get there. Hikers should pack for all conditions, and accept that we will only summit if safe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Woods Facilities: portable bathrooms and fee parking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;Disclaimer and things you must know. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204028216000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>The remote Owl's head is easier to summit in good winter conditions. No bugs and smoother trails! 
A hike though the White Mountain National forest in winter is a great experience whether a forest floor  hike or  a challenging summit  ascent.</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202602812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Winter Hike series: Owls Head via Lincoln Woods Trail, Franconia Falls </name><id>7299696</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203852600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7299696/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/7/global_2978599.jpeg</photo_url></item>