<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>P.O. Box 270896</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06127</zip><lat>41.762336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1447422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Learn More and Register at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=457"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=457&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let Sue Nelson Show Some Real Deals and How You Can Benefit Greatly in This Market!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sue Nelson has been talking for the last year about the perfect storm that is raging with the banks and the real estate they financed. What you may or may not know is we are still at the tip of the iceberg! The banks are sitting on tons of Notes and REO product that you and I don't even know about! That's right! There is more being added as these loans come due, in fact, the FDIC says there is $1.4 trillion in "at-risk mortgages" coming due in the next 3 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These banks are not even bringing all of their REO's to market in fear that it will flood the market and force them to lower the value of the REO's they currently have on the books. She has, and continues to pick off great deals in this market! A great deal has equity at closing and great cash flow to protect you through the storms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'm Going to Show You How to Make Some Great Deals!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us on Thursday May 31st at 8:00 for a free bonus webinar, where she will take you from the basics of: What is a Note and a REO? to the more advanced exit strategies that I use. She will also cover the in-betweens of: How do you actually buy from banks? And, How you can make a boatload of money from wholesaling from day one! It's true, if your just starting out and your intimidated at the thought of running a 250 unit apartment building, you can get paid for just finding the deal through wholesaling. I will show you how!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Learn More and Register at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=457"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=457&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338513869000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337865323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Teleseminar: Buying From Banks During The Perfect Storm</name><id>66147012</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338508800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/66147012/</event_url></item>