<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>220 Weybosset Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821106</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 421-2787</phone><name>Providence Performing Arts Center</name><city>Providence</city><id>843851</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.411969</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spring Awakening&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, April 24, 2009&lt;br /&gt;8 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Note: I am no longer collecting any more money for tickets. Please purchase your own ticket through PPAC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This musical is supposed to be amazing! Duncan Sheik did the music, and it won 8 Tony Awards, including Best Musical, on Broadway. Tickets may sell out for this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;SPRING AWAKENING is the groundbreaking fusion of morality, sexuality and rock &amp;amp; roll that has awakened Broadway like no other musical in years.&amp;quot; You can watch videos and get more info on the &lt;a href="http://springawakening.com/home.php" target="_blank"&gt;Spring Awakening&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet in the lobby after the show and head to &lt;a href="http://www.downcityfood.com/" target="_blank"&gt;DownCity&lt;/a&gt; afterward for apps, drinks or dessert from their LateNite menu. They re-opened in a new location, and if you haven't been there, it's really nice. And amazingly spacious, which is good for this group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please purchase your own ticket&lt;/u&gt; through &lt;a href="http://www.ppacri.org/show_database/spring/spring.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;PPAC&lt;/a&gt; -- online, by phone or at the Box Office. This means you probably won't be able to sit with the group, but we can all meet in the theatre lobby before the show, and then afterward to head over to DownCity together. &lt;b&gt;You may want to buy your ticket early, as the show may sell out&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are seeing the show on a different night and want to join us just for dinner on April 24, shoot me an email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;The Play&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPRING AWAKENING takes its inspiration from one of literature’s most controversial masterpieces – a work so daring in its depiction of teenage self-discovery, it was banned from the stage and not performed in its complete form in English for nearly 100 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s Germany, 1891.  A world where the grown-ups hold all the cards.  The beautiful young Wendla explores the mysteries of her body, and wonders aloud where babies come from, till Mama tells her to shut it, and put on a proper dress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elsewhere, the brilliant and fearless young Melchior interrupts a mind-numbing Latin drill to defend his buddy Moritz – a boy so traumatized by puberty he can’t concentrate on anything.  Not that the Headmaster cares.  He strikes them both and tells them to turn in their lesson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One afternoon – in a private place in the woods – Melchior and Wendla meet by accident, and soon find within themselves a desire unlike anything they’ve ever felt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more at the &lt;a href="http://www.springawakening.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Spring Awakening &lt;/a&gt;website...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby after the play  -- Look for small red Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241302335000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235858683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Awakening -- PPAC</name><id>9846930</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240617600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/9846930/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/f/d/global_7489789.jpeg</photo_url></item>