<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>120.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Living in the Love Response Workshop II&lt;br /&gt;Opening your Heart to Voice your Truth &lt;br /&gt;With Eva Selhub, MD&lt;br /&gt;www.theloveresponse.com&lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 5:00&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to discover that you are loved, always, no matter what you say, it is necessary to open your heart so that you can reconnect with yourself, others and the Divine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to center in your heart, so that when you speak, you speak from a place of integrity, dignity, grace and balance.  You voice your truth.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will combine meditation, healing and practical exercises that will help you build the skills you need to live your life in the Love Response instead of the stress response; To find your truth, speak it, and create the destiny you truly desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are constantly using your voice.  Most of the time, you speak without awareness, automatically, reactively.   Or you don’t speak at all.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When your stress response has been activated, you might react in anger, defense, offense, or your voice might freeze all together.  You might talk on and on, without noticing that others are no longer listening.  Other times, you might speak louder or scream, upset that no one is listening.  You might “shut down”, feeling invisible, and not speak again.  And other times, your voice might freeze, scared to speak lest you be judged, persecuted or exposed.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the end, you do not voice your truth.  In the end, your stress response is activated, your heart closes, old wounds take over, and you are no longer connected to your truth.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ask yourself then, “Do I really know my truth?”  and “How can I voice my truth when I am not sure what my truth is?”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because if you truly KNEW your truth, truly KNEW who you were, truly KNEW you were loved, you would be able to speak with integrity, dignity and grace always.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information go to: &lt;a href="http://www.theloveresponse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.theloveres...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272377821000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269109382000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Eva Selhub returns for another amazing workshop ~ Don't miss this one!!</name><id>12941395</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272204000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/12941395/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/2/1/global_13766849.jpeg</photo_url></item>