<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Harvard Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.334592</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.232.4343</phone><name>Abeille</name><city>Brookline</city><id>788410</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119188</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Meet and Shop with Five Talented Brookline Jewelry Artists&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenn Mason, mixed-media artist and author&lt;br /&gt;Michelle Rothman, of  Ojas Jewelry Design&lt;br /&gt;Hanne Bernstein of Danish Jewelry Design&lt;br /&gt;Sara Harding of Sara Danielle Designs&lt;br /&gt;Lisa Trachtman of Abeille&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenn Mason will be &lt;b&gt;signing and demonstrating key techniques from her latest book, Altered Paper Jewelry&lt;/b&gt;. Sara, Michelle, Hanne and Lisa will be showing their work and are available to answer questions, providing a great opportunity to learn more, support local art and get a head start on your holiday shopping. Participants in the events will be entered into a drawing to win free jewelry. Wine and cheese for all so come and celebrate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can’t make it to Thursday’s celebration, come join us for a “Girls Night” Workshop on Friday from 6pm-7:30pm. We are offering this workshop at a discounted rate of $10. Wine and refreshments will be served, of course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about the artists or the event, check our &lt;a href="http://www.abeille.us/blog/celebrate-abeilles-birthday/" target="_blank"&gt;our blog&lt;/a&gt;  or follow us &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/abeillestore" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for additional details about the event. We hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lcanale</member_name><member_id>8176022</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257637353000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Crafters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostondiycrafts</urlname><id>1301641</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Jewelry Design and DIY Crafts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255744936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE: Meet the Jewerly Artist, Trunk Show, Book Signing, Tips and Techniques</name><id>11645580</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257463800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostondiycrafts/events/11645580/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/0/1/global_8989281.jpeg</photo_url></item>