<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The 3D version of the movie starts at 7:00, so let's meet in front of the theater if it's nice out (inside the doors if it's cold) by 6:30. NOTE: The 3D version MAY cost an extra $3, per AMC's new rule. If you'd rather see the non-3D version, let me know in your RSVP so that I can take a consensus.  The NON-3D version starts at 6:15, so we'd meet by 5:45 for that one. I'm open to either -- just let me know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, please call me if you'd like to change your RSVP after 5:00 the day of the movie, if you get lost, if you are running late (so I know to wait for you).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have small popcorn and small soda vouchers for $3 each that you can buy from me before the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Tuesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;After the impending mayhem of Knowing, I think we'll need something a bit lighter. How's about a war between animated &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809918074/details" target="_blank"&gt;Monsters Vs. Aliens&lt;/a&gt;??! (The Monsters are the good guys.) This is playing in 3D and normal-vision, so I'll try to schedule the 3D when I update the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;When California girl Susan Murphy is unwittingly clobbered by a meteor full of outer space gunk on her wedding day, she mysteriously grows to 49-feet-11-inches tall. Alerted to the threat of this new monster, the military jumps into action and Susan is captured and secreted away to a covert government compound. There, she is renamed Ginormica and placed in confinement with a ragtag group of other monsters: the brilliant but insect-headed Dr. Cockroach, Ph.D.; the macho half-ape, half-fish The Missing Link; the gelatinous and indestructible B.O.B.; and the 350-foot grub called Insectosaurus. Their confinement is cut short, however, when a mysterious alien robot lands on Earth and begins storming the country. In a moment of desperation, The President is persuaded by General W.R. Monger to enlist the motley crew of Monsters to combat the Alien Robot and save the world from imminent destruction.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are always welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Monsters Vs. Aliens!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240531277000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238439924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monsters Vs. Aliens</name><id>10071716</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239748200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10071716/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>