<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>160 State St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359438</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617) 742-2286</phone><name>Black Rose</name><city>Boston</city><id>798320</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053797</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ CAREFULLY:&lt;/strong&gt; RSVPing does &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; register you for this event. You must visit the link at the bottom of the page and make your payment ahead of time to be 100% registered to attend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are teaming up with Social Fun and Boston Singles Meet Up Groups for a fun dating event&lt;/span&gt; on the 2nd floor of &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Black Rose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, running from 6 to 8 PM for members age 25-40 (approx)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; A few Meetup groups are participating, so you can't go by just one group's RSVP list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the Day of the Event:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You will arrive promptly at 5:45 PM. Matt and Biagio will meet and greet you to ensure you feel comfortable and welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You will receive a name tag with a number, your first name and the first letter of your last name, 2 numbered Date 'N' Dash forms; one labeled "Notes" and one labeled "Official: To Be Passed In", some folded paper for your own personal notes and a pen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- The numbered name tags and forms are for you to keep track of the dates you like. You will turn these in to us at the end of the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- There will be a line of tables set up with chairs on each side on the day of the event and you will sit down in a numbered order according to the number on your name tag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- At 6 PM we will explain the rules of the event to the group (please do not ask beforehand), making sure that everyone understands how the evening works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You will have somewhere between 5 to 8 minutes (depending on the turn out) to chat to your date (very important, remember to take notes!) and then we will ask the men to move to the right one spot until the end and then circle back to the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- At the end we will ask you to turn in your paper with the dates you've chosen to see again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- We will e-mail you a few days after the event has ended, noting where matches have occurred with that matches full name and e-mail address. Then it is up to you to email those potential matches to give them the information they need to establish further contact and set up a real date if both parties agree to continue onward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After The Event: Social Networking Mixer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the event we will have a Social Networking Mixer where you can socialize with all of the participants. Matt will be available starting from then onward and he can provide additional help or even suggest some of the paid classes he offers so you know there is additional help and you have options after this event has ended if you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event costs $21 per member to cover the costs to run this event. Simply click the link below for the date you'd like to attend. You will be taken to Matt's website where you will be able to make your payment and register for the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can register at the bottom of the page. We will need to collect some personal information from those who sign up, including full name, phone number and email address. We will use this information later to notify you of your matches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you for a fun night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biagio &amp;amp; Matt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.socialserendip.com/date-n-dash-events/"&gt;To Sign Up For 9/9 - CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialserendip.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/DateNDash.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px auto ; display : block"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Matt and/or Biagio on the 2nd floor of the venue</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Adams</member_name><member_id>13654210</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347238429000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346944528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Date N Dash- New Dating Event Ages 25-40</name><id>81134712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347227100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/81134712/</event_url></item>