<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>202 Burlington Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.502563</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The MITRE Corporation</name><city>Bedford</city><id>8056542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.238541</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Cross-posted with the Boston Predictive Analytics group: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Predictive-Analytics/events/72068092/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Predictive-Analytics/events/72068092/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Important** &lt;br /&gt;

If you are a foreign national, please list your name here in order to comply with MITRE's security requirements: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/NEH5Rm" class="linkified"&gt;http://bit.ly/NEH5Rm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted is one of the primary persons behind Mahout, and will be here to go into more detail as to its capabilities. Co-hosting with the Hadoop group.  Many thanks to Macy of MITRE and Jo from MapR for hosting and coordinating this event!  I copied and pasted this from a London Meetup in May which Ted spoke:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Mahout? Mahout's goal is to build scalable machine learning libraries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mahout supports mainly four use cases:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommendation mining takes users' behavior and from that tries to find items users might like.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clustering takes e.g. text documents and groups them into groups of topically related documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Classification learns from exisiting categorized documents what documents of a specific category look like and is able to assign unlabelled documents to the (hopefully) correct category.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent itemset mining takes a set of item groups (terms in a query session, shopping cart content) and identifies, which individual items usually appear together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** Please note this is in the 'burbs, and not on a direct commuter rail line, and so for folks without a car, please email me, or post a note in your rsvp, so that car pooling might help out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344097265000</updated><rating><average>3.77999997139</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonhadoop</urlname><id>1535756</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Hadoop User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>159</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334177263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ted Dunning</name><id>60176552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342738800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonhadoop/events/60176552/</event_url></item>