<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>375 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.329884</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-277-5522</phone><name>Wine Gallery</name><city>Brookline</city><id>669085</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.127210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The dynamic duo from Drink Craft Beer is hosting a FREE beer and chocolate pairing, featuring beers from Butternuts, Hoppin Frog and He'Brew. Each beer will be paired with Taza Chocolate. The event starts at 3 and wraps up by 6. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info to get you salivating:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;He'Brew Bittersweet Lenny's R.I.P.A. and Taza Mexicano Vanilla Bean Chocolate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This pairing happened almost by pure accident. We brought a cooler full of beer over to Taza and this wasn't one the pairing we anticipated to work...but oh man does it. The Taza Mexicano Vanilla Chocolate has a very interesting vanilla flavor since Taza uses the entire bean, including the pod in the chocolate. Wow! This is an awesome pairing. The vanilla works with the malt sweetness of the beer and blends with the grapefruity hops in a very intriguing flavor combination. The chocolate sweetness continues when the malt stops, helping finish off the beer. We can't do this one justice on paper, you just have to try it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Butternuts Heinnieweisse Weissebier and Taza Mexicano Guajillo Pepper Chocolate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hefeweisen and chocolate? Yup! This may just be our favorite pairing of the three. The chocolate brings out acid in the beer like a berliner weisse. The natural spiciness of the hefeweisen yeast pairs perfectly with the mellow spice of the hot pepper creating a more complex flavor than either the chocolate or the beer have alone. First you get the tart acidity and some sweet chocolate, then it moves on to the spicy yeast and earthy spiciness of the pepper, which blends seamlessly.This is a really good example of 1+1=3 in food and beer pairing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hoppin Frog B.O.R.I.S. The Crusher and Taza Mexicano Salted Almond Chocolate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Salted Almond Chocolate from Taza is simply amazing on it's own and we really needed the perfect beer to pair with this. On paper it's easy to just say an imperial stout will pair well, but we went through 7 different stouts before we found one that paired perfectly. This sweet roasty stout and chocolate go together incredibly well creating a truely decadent pairing. The result is mix of classic chocolate and nut flavors with a deep malted milk shake taste. The salt helps finish off the stout making it smoother than it is on its own. This is dessert in a glass. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While you're at it, stay in-the-know about future Drink Craft Beer events at &lt;a href="http://drinkcraftbeer.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://drinkcraftbeer...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alicia</member_name><member_id>8353321</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249326853000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248097499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FYI: Beer &amp; Taza Chocolate Tasting</name><id>10914815</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249153200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/10914815/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/d/global_9049101.jpeg</photo_url></item>