<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Building 37 on MIT Campus, near Vassar St. and Massachusetts Ave</address_2><address_1>70 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360656</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Extra-Vehicular Activity Research (EVA) lab, MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1161000</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Debora Lui, Program Coordinator of the MIT Museum, has been coordinating with a grad student to come up with a tour for our Nerd Fun group of Dr. Dava Newman's Extra-Vehicular Activity Research (EVA) lab at MIT. They have offered us eight spots on the 6:00 pm tour and eight spots on the 7:00 pm tour for Nerd Fun members. This RSVP sheet is for the six o' clock tour.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Debora Lui, Program Coordinator of the MIT Museum&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Take a tour of the &lt;b&gt;Extra-Vehicular Activity Research&lt;/b&gt; (EVA) lab at MIT.  Located within the Kavli Institute for Astrophysics and Space Research, scientists and engineers at this lab focus on human activity in space.  Learn about the design and science behind the BioSuit, the revolutionary &amp;quot;second skin&amp;quot; spacesuit being developed under the direction of MIT Professor Dava Newman.  See the hypobaric chamber for pressuring space suits, BioSuit concept prototypes, and the robotic space suit tester robot.  Learn about telerobotics research that relates to robotic arm operation aboard the international space station and about the artificial gravity centrifuge used for EVA-related research.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tours start at 6pm and 7pm, and last for approximately one hour.   Please show up at least 10 minutes ahead of time in the first floor lobby of: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;McNair Building&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Building 37 on MIT Campus, near Vassar St. and Massachusetts Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;70 Vassar Street&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Cambridge, MA 02139&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;(closest T-stop is Central Square)&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?selection=37&amp;amp;zoom=17" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Since there is very limited space, RSVPs have been set to be YES/ No. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be on the six o' clock tour. The McNair Building is a 13 minute walk from the Central Square T stop: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=central+square+station&amp;amp;daddr=70+Vassar+St,+Cambridge,+MA+02142&amp;amp;geocode=FS5yhgIdxgrD-ymTGmNaUXfjiTGSWKIeIn2vHg%3BFedfhgIdADTD-ymXGjRWqnDjiTH4GIdC2j9x1Q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.360807,-71.093248&amp;amp;sspn=0.011083,0.016544&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.362793,-71.09858&amp;amp;spn=0.011083,0.016544&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Debora Lui, Program Coordinator of the MIT Museum, will sign people in for the six o'clock and seven o'clock tours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Bio-Suit&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mvl.mit.edu/EVA/biosuit/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://mvl.mit.edu/EV...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Bio-Suit System stands to revolutionize human space exploration by providing enhanced astronaut extravehicular activity (EVA) locomotion and life support based on the concept of providing a 'second skin' capability for astronaut performance. The novel design concept is realized through symbiotic relationships in the areas of wearable technologies; information systems and evolutionary space systems design; and biomedical breakthroughs in skin replacement and materials. By working at the intersection of engineering; design; medicine; and operations, new emergent capabilities could be achieved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Bio-Suit System would provide life support through mechanical counter-pressure where pressure is applied to the entire body through a tight-fitting suit with a helmet for the head. Wearable technologies will be embedded in the Bio-Suit layers and the outer layer might be recyclable. Hence, images of 'spraying on' the inner layer of the Bio-Suit System emerge, which offers design advantages for extreme, dusty, planetary environments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Flexible space system design methods are slated to enable adaptation of Bio-Suit hardware and software elements in the context of changing mission requirements. Reliability can be assured through dependence of Bio-Suit layers acting on local needs and conditions through self-repair at localized sites while preserving overall system integrity. The Bio-Suit System is relevant to NASA's strategic plan and stated visionary challenges in the Human Exploration and Development of Space, AeroSpace Technology, and Space Science&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the EVA Lab&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mvl.mit.edu/EVA/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mvl.mit.edu/EV...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Extra-vehicular activity (EVA) is any activity that an astronaut performs outside the spacecraft, whether it be in microgravity (sometimes known as spacewalking) or on an extraterrestrial surface such as the Moon or Mars. On many microgravity missions such as those on the Space Shuttle or ISS, EVA is the sole means to accomplish certain critical mission objectives; on the Moon or Mars it will be by far the most important means by which future astronauts explore their surroundings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;At the MIT Man Vehicle Laboratory we have been pursuing EVA research for well over a decade. Our previous research has focused on quantifying the capabilities and limitations of the current Space Shuttle spacesuit, known as the Extravehicular Mobility Unit (EMU). We developed analytical models of the EMU and validated these through experiments with a pressurized EMU and state-of-the-art robotic technology (see image on left). The results have been used to enhance astronaut training, increase crew operational efficiency and optimize mission planning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;However, despite being brilliant feats of engineering design, current spacesuits would be cumbersome for use on extraterrestrial surfaces due to their considerable mass, volume and complexity. Being based on a gas-filled pressure suit concept, current spacesuits also considerably restrict the astronaut's range of motion compared to an unsuited human - particularly disadvantageous for extraterrestrial surface traversal where climbing, squatting and other such motions must be regularly performed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our current research therefore focuses on developing an EVA system that could exponentially expand the astronaut's EVA capabilities, especially on extraterrestrial surfaces, by providing enhanced mobility and life support based on the concept of providing a 'second skin' capability for astronaut performance. Known as the Bio-Suit, our system (see image on left) is a modular design based on mechanical counterpressure in which the body is pressurized using elastic tension in a skin-tight garment rather the gas in a traditional spacesuit such as the EMU. The inherent simplicity and elegance of the Bio-Suit concept has the potential to simplify life-support system design, reduce the energy expended by the astronaut in using the suit and and diminish the risk of depressurization and other EVA hazards&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Photo&lt;/b&gt;: Top Right: Prof. Dava Newman modeling a Bio-Suit mockup. Copyright 2005 Volker Steger / Science Photo Library.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>18</waitlist_count><updated>1264896855000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263407708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nerd Fun tour of the Extra-Vehicular Activity Research (EVA) lab @ MIT</name><id>12309665</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264723200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12309665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/6/global_12611046.jpeg</photo_url></item>