<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Spring St., Floor 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.366043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts (Charles River Room)</name><city>Watertown</city><id>2074041</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184196</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you're interested in meeting someone special, and would like to give online dating a try (and have it work amazingly well for you), then you're going to love this. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Online dating can be one of the best ways to find a romantic partner. Here are just some of the advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone you see on there is looking to meet someone for a potential relationship (try getting those kind of odds in a bar or even at a social event).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get a small sample of a person's looks and personality in advance without having to go up, start a a conversation, and risk rejection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's incredibly efficient (if you have a good system in place). You'd never be able to have a dozen people at various stages in the "getting to know you" process simultaneously in real life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don't have to deal with the fear of approach anxiety and the crippling pain of rejection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more. There are so many reasons to use online dating. I absolutely love it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there's a dark side of it as well. It can also be a frustrating experience if you don't know how to use it effectively. There are a lot of common pitfalls that discourage even the most enthusiastic singles, and most people end up quitting because they simply aren't getting the results that they had hoped for. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 That's where I come in. Look, anyone can show you how to meet people online. You just take a few pictures of yourself, slap up a profile, and start replying to ads. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 But to have a real chance at meeting a high quality person that could end up being someone really special to you... you need the inside secrets that you will not discover casually, on your own. The advanced, mega-powerful secrets do not appear to you magically, just because you're single and in a position to join an online dating site. You need a guide to steer you past the wreckage of dating disasters and straight to the kind of fun and joyous interactions that you've been hoping for. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Whether you're brand new to online dating, or if you're an old pro looking for some new tricks, this unique seminar is perfect for you. I'm going to teach you everything I've learned over the last ten years of using online dating to meet dozens of wonderful people. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ********************************************  &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt;

 ********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to discover what your "competition" is doing wrong, and do the exact opposite. You'll instantly stand out above the crowd and get more dates as a result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;"Secret Site"&lt;/strong&gt; you can use to get members of the opposite sex to tell you which of your pictures are the best... (its free and its fun).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The single biggest mistake people make when answering someone's ad that kills their chances of ever getting a reply back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A guaranteed way to get a phone number on the 2nd email so you can skip the endless writing back and forth and just talk in real time to schedule a date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My proven email template for breaking things off with someone you're no longer interested in that will leave them feeling good about themselves and about you (all the drama disappeared once I started using this email).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plus, I am going to teach you how to take pictures that will &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;instantly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; stand out from the crowd. People will be mesmerized and dying to get to know you better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;

 HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it?&lt;/strong&gt; The seminar is conveniently located at the Watertown Center For Healing Arts which is a beautiful facility for an event like this.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;What time?&lt;/strong&gt; Please plan on arriving by 6:45pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 7:00pm and go until 9:30pm (with a break in the middle).  There are plenty of bus lines that go to the center, and there is also lots of parking both on the street and in a big parking lot near the center.  The bottom of this page has details:  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://watertowncenter.net/directions-2/"&gt;http://watertowncenter.net/directions-2/  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How much?&lt;/strong&gt; Cheap.  If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and that's assuming there even &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a class that could offer you all this, which there isn't.    &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 No other class offers you this kind of cutting edge training that's based in real world results.  This stuff WORKS!  What if one small change is all it takes to immediately and effortlessly begin attracting high-quality friends and dating prospects into your life?  I've seen it happen many times in this group, and it can happen for you too.   &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt; Because I want to help as many people as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to.  The cost for this event is only $20, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Think about it... &lt;strong&gt;that's 67 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;.  What else do you spend 67 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt; In order to make sure I can personally help as many people as possible, the class is limited to the first 70 people who RSVP.  I'm listing this event in two groups, so there are over 7,300 people seeing this listing.  If you want in, then be sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude, and a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot.  I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Warmly,   &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366134375000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>46</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365113326000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ONLINE DATING - Proven Secrets To Finding Love On The Internet</name><id>112728772</id><headcount>40</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365980400000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/112728772/</event_url></item>