<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 Palace Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.339081</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum</name><city>Boston</city><id>8696882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098930</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>GET TICKETS &lt;a href="http://www.gardnermuseum.org/calendar/events/4734" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gardnermus...&lt;/a&gt; Gardner After Hours: Word Play Thursday, December 20, 5:00 PM Tickets $5-$15 | Purchase online or at 617 278 5156 GET TICKETS PROGRAM For December’s Gardner After Hours, we’re partnering with our friends at independent center for creative writing Grub Street for an evening of words, poetry, and mingling with artists and writers. Few people realize that Isabella Gardner’s exquisite collection began with an interest in manuscripts and rare books, and that Gardner was an avid supporter of writers in her lifetime. Join us for conversation, lighthearted activities in the galleries, and cocktails by the courtyard, of course. Featured Event: Avant Gardner: Callithumpian Consort | 7pm Tickets sold separately, but include admission to Gardner After Hours. Tonight, the Callithumpian Consort concludes its year-long celebration of John Cage with a concert featuring music by Cage, one of his contemporaries in the New York School, and a third composer profoundly influenced by Cage's discoveries. Cash wine bar around the courtyard. Café G open for snacks, dinner, and drinks. TICKETING | Includes museum admission Adults / $15 Seniors / $12 Members / Free College students / $5 Students from colleges and universities participating in the University Membership Program receive free admission. See a list of participating schools. Gardner After Hours is supported in part by The Baupost Group, LLC. Thursday evening programming is supported in part by an award from the National Endowment for the Arts. Fidelity Investments is the opening year sponsor of Jazz at the Gardner. Opening year exhibitions are made possible in part by The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts. The Museum receives operating support from the Massachusetts Cultural Council.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Txt 781-718-6203, wear name tag, we pick a spot closer to date</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maia</member_name><member_id>3083598</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356051885000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354797933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gardner After Hours</name><id>94304492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356040800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/94304492/</event_url></item>