<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After the hit that the last video night was, I decided it's definitely something I want to do again.  And thanks to JD, it's become possible!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, in August, we'll be meeting up again for an afternoon of salsa videos &amp;amp; bbq.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be showing one of JD's videos this time......A video documentary of Salsa.  Can't wait!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be potluck style again, only this time I'm listing things we need.  Please choose something from there.  If everyone has taken something, then just bring whatever else you think will be great for the potluck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are the items we need, and who has volunteered to provide them (so far):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grill (JD)&lt;br /&gt;Utensils, Plates, Cups, Towels, etc (JD)&lt;br /&gt;Hot dogs &amp;amp; buns (Ana)&lt;br /&gt;Coke (Ana)&lt;br /&gt;Salad (Matthew)&lt;br /&gt;Cookies (Leah)&lt;br /&gt;Chicken (Gabriel)&lt;br /&gt;Juice (Oscar)&lt;br /&gt;Chips&lt;br /&gt;Beef&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a BYOB event!  The limit this time is 20!  So, please be sure you can make it before signing up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1-5pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notice JD's place is off the Roxbury Crossing Station stop on the Orange Line&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND!  Join us afterward at Ryles for Wepa's Sunday Social!  I'll be a little late this time as I'll have practice first, but will join you guys there at about 9:30!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm flying in early from my trip to Atlanta specifically for this, so I'm really looking forward to it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, stay tuned for an earlier event in August!  I'm trying to figure where and when El Cantante will be playing in Boston for a meetup event to watch the film!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ana ;)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188320637000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184210528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August 26 Salsa Video Night BBQ &amp; Potluck!!!</name><id>6011400</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188147600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/6011400/</event_url></item>