<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Vassar Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Stata Center, Room 32-155 </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>6659192</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089943</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Is starting an RFID company really a good idea? That&amp;rsquo;s the essence of a question from the audience at our recent Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing Solutions Expo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;So a lot of good things have happened [in RFID] over the last 10 to 15 years. But I can also say that the RFID industry has at times been a real bloodbath. A lot of people are not here because they got laid off or they lost patience with this industry over the years. These are the survivors. For students, let&amp;rsquo;s say, what should they do after graduation? Do you recommend they go into the RFID industry? Seek jobs? Found startups? Like you did 10 years ago when we were starting?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REGISTER&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great questions. Join us for some answers as our distinguished panel of both seasoned RFID &amp;ldquo;survivors&amp;rdquo; (who&amp;rsquo;ve been there and done it) as well as some RFID hopefuls (currently in the throes of a startup) offer lessons on what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t when it comes to starting a successful RFID company. Learn what&amp;rsquo;s actually driving this industry today, where the real market opportunities lie and, most importantly, where to find some money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Got your own question for our panel?&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://fs10.formsite.com/greatwriting/form38/index.html"&gt;Ask it here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Speakers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/sean_cotter/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/sean_cotter.png" alt="Sean Cotter" width="100" height="124" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/sean_cotter/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sean Cotter, President,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.assetvue.net/"&gt;Asset VUE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;With 19 years of business development, IT leadership and entrepreneurship, Sean Cotter is responsible for the strategic direction and general management of Asset VUE &amp;mdash; whose RFID-enabled solution automatically monitors data center environments and tracks the variety of devices contained within them. Sean started his first company, a successful region IT outsourcing firm, while still in college. Selling the firm 10 years later, he became Director of IT, then CIO, at the DVL Group, one of the most respected management teams in the technology field. Sean is the founding member of the Greater Philadelphia Qlikview Users Group and the Delaware Valley Data Center Users Forum. He is also an active member of AFCOM (a leading organization of data center professionals) and the CIO Roundtable group of GPSEG (Greater Philadelphia Senior Executive Group). He holds a masters degree in business from the Saint Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Haub School of business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/diana_hage/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/diana_hage.png" alt="Diana Hage" width="100" height="132" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/diana_hage/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diana Hage, CEO,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.rfidgs.com/"&gt;RFID Global Solution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Diana Hage is building the RFID industry&amp;rsquo;s leading real-time enterprise asset management company, delivering turnkey solutions that drive measurable ROI and business value on a global scale. Since 2002, Diana has led the development of RFID industry solutions and global sales and services teams for IBM, ODIN technologies, and RFID Global Solution. Diana was named in &amp;lsquo;Top 10 Tech CEOs to Watch&amp;rsquo; by SmartCEO and profiled in Forbes&amp;rsquo; 2011 investment edition. She has been featured in the New York Times, Forbes and San Jose Mercury News and is a frequently requested public speaker. Diana holds an MBA from the Darden School of Business and a BA from the University of Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/tim_butler/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tim_butler.png" alt="Tim Butler" width="100" height="140" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/tim_butler/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timothy Butler, Founder, President and CEO,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.tegoinc.com/"&gt;Tego, Inc.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Timothy Butler is founder and co-inventor of the initial issued patent for Tego. He is an experienced entrepreneur having successfully founded and led three previous technology startups in the past 15 years, including SiteScape, Inc. a leading provider of business-to-business collaboration solutions and services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/bernd/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/bernd.jpg" alt="Brend Schoner" width="86" height="75" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/bernd/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bernd Schoner, Co-founder,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.thingmagic.com/"&gt;ThingMagic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Bernd Schoner co-founded Cambridge-based RFID company, ThingMagic, in 2000. Since the acquisition of ThingMagic by Trimble Navigation in 2010, Bernd has held the role of VP Business Development of the ThingMagic Division focusing his efforts on defining the role of RFID within the Trimble verticals, such as mobile resource management, building construction and heavy construction. Bernd holds a Diplom-Ingenieur in Electrical Engineering from Rheinisch-Westph&amp;auml;lische Technische Hochschule Aachen, Germany, and an Ing&amp;eacute;nieur des Arts et M&amp;eacute;tiers in Industrial Engineering from Ecole Centrale de Paris, France. He received his Ph.D. from the MIT Media Laboratory in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/randy_cronk/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/randy_cronk.jpeg" alt="Randall Cronk" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mitforumcambridge.org/events/auto-id-sensing-sig-event-how-to-start-an-rfid-company/attachment/randy_cronk/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATOR: Randall Cronk,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://greatwriting.com/"&gt;greatwriting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Randy is a freelance marketing writer focused on helping technology companies market complex systems, products and services in ways that audiences find clear and compelling. Since 1990 he has helped over 250 high-tech companies convey the value of what they do through white papers, web content, brochures, case studies and articles. Previously a vice president with Regis McKenna where he ran the Digital Equipment account, Randy holds an MBA from Clark University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy Cronk</member_name><member_id>465168</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337142788000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334244465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Start an RFID Company</name><id>60285552</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337032800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/60285552/</event_url></item>