<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>65 Mellen Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.655323</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sacred Heart Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>11408492</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.269974</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Maine Buddhist Gathering presents &lt;br /&gt;

Buddhist Movie Night &lt;br /&gt;

featuring &lt;br /&gt;

Amongst White Clouds &lt;br /&gt;

directed by Edward Burger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, February 23rd at 7pm (doors open at 6:30) &lt;br /&gt;

NOTE: NEW LOCATION &lt;br /&gt;

Sacred Heart / St. Dominic Parish Church &lt;br /&gt;

65 Mellen St in Portland (corner of Mellen and Sherman) &lt;br /&gt;

The film is offered free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are invited and encouraged to come early to visit and connect. Your donation of a dessert and contribution to help with expenses is greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please free free to invite friends and family. All are warmly welcome. Those interested in Buddhist practice and those new to practice are especially encouraged to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

About the film: Amongst White Clouds is a look at the lives of students, ascetics and masters living in isolated hermitages dotting the peaks and valleys of China's Zhongnan Mountain range. Director Edward Burger takes us on an unforgettable journey into this forgotten 5000 year old Zen Buddhist hermit tradition. It was widely thought that these hermitages had been wiped out by the twists and turns of history. This film shows us this is not the case. This documentary reveals to us the tradition, wisdom, hardship and joy of everyday life in these remote practice centers. With both humor and compassion, the inspiring and warm-hearted characters in the film challenge us to join them in an exploration of practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kerry Dunn</member_name><member_id>12146459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361838013000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359382782000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Movie Night</name><id>101762212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361664000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/101762212/</event_url></item>