<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Beach Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01944</zip><lat>42.574898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-525-3304</phone><name>Calas Restaurant</name><city>Manchester</city><id>500091</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.770090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;I hope everyone gets this message, it has being a change on plans for this coming Sunday Brunch, please take note&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There has being a BIG disappointment and a BIG surprise  to me to to had come back home today to a message from ITHAKI Restaurant in Ipswich, letting me know that they are canceling on us for this coming event, Sunday the third... you can only imagine my PANIC, so I call my friends from Cala's Restaurant here in my home town of Manchester by the Sea, and they will accommodate all of us to have Brunch there, this coming Sunday the third. &lt;br /&gt;I'll forever be grateful to them from saving me from this panic attack I am, still having.&lt;br /&gt;So I hope you all will be able to understand this last minute change, and I hope you all be able to get this last minute Meetup-mail.  I Apologize profusely for all the inconvenience all this changes might create. but I hope you all will be able to understand this is out of my power. I am SO saddened and GREATLY disappointed by ITHAKI by the last minute events. &lt;br /&gt;I hope you all can still make it, Cala's is a MAGNIFICENT restaurant and has GREAT food. Some of you know this already since I have hosted other events at this restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;you can check their menu at  www.calasrestaurant.com&lt;br /&gt;this will be their Sunday Brunch menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll try to get someone to park at ITHAKI in case some members don't get this last minute mail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cala's restaurant is accessible via Commuter Train from North Station. Take the Rockport line to Manchester and Cala's is located across the railroad tracks pass Crosby's Market, From here you'll see Calas across the corner, next to the Post Office. and don't worry if the train arrives a little later than 11:30, I understand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions:&lt;br /&gt;128 North to exit 15 turn right into Manchester, (School St.), go straight to the end of School St. and Central St., turn left here into Central St. and the road will go right at the corner and turn into Beach St.  Cala's is located on the right hand side #7. it is the third business from the corner where Central St. merges right into Beach st.&lt;br /&gt;Parking on the Street is available and during the winter the meter maid is not around !!!Hurray...!!! so we don't need to play musical cars as we did last summer...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again I hope you all accept my apologies for all this inconvenience &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any Q.'s call my cel... (978) 473-9358&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask at the entrance for Lettie's Reservation and someone will guide you...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lettie G.</member_name><member_id>2715523</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317748139000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><why>The food is EXCELLENT at this place... worth the trip to Manchester by the Sea and since it will be a GREAT weather we can go for a walk on Singing beach after brunch...</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199666501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Brunch Cala's Restaurant in Manchester by the Sea, Massachusetts</name><id>7048429</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202056200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/7048429/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/8/global_3116968.jpeg</photo_url></item>