<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions will follow soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to do the Cabot/Bulge/Horn hike in the less travelled Pilot Range in the North Country on&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, June 25th&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Cabot is a 4,000 footer - the Bulge and the Horn are New England 100 peaks. &amp;nbsp; Views will come from the Horn, which is a very distinctive peak in the North Country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will likely camp in the area on Friday night to get an early start - possibly in Milan State Park. &amp;nbsp;Email me if you are interested in sharing a YURT! &amp;nbsp;I have stayed here before and it is a neat experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a moderately paced hike - &lt;strong&gt;I'm not a fast hiker but I do keep moving&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the distance involved (10.3 miles) please demonstrate (via the RSVP questions) that you have been hiking similar distances recently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring plenty of water&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;We did the southern Starr King/Waumbek/Weeks climb this past weekend and there was very little water on the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared to come out in the dark if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My hikes are always dog-friendly and this range is largely unexposed and not very rocky, making it pretty easy on my "boys." &amp;nbsp;However, make sure to bring extra water for the dogs since I do not expect to find any on the trail. &amp;nbsp;I will have both dogs with me - they need these peaks too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been suggested that we take a quick dip in Unknown Pond when we get there. &amp;nbsp;If you feel like swimming and it is hospitable, come prepared with appropriate gear. &amp;nbsp;I've never been there and have no idea whether or not this is a good swimming hole. &amp;nbsp;Feedback from other Meetup hikers on this point is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will post trail descriptions from the AMC guide shortly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a loop hike, so we will not have to carpool. &amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;We will meet in the lot of the Berlin Fish Hatchery on York Pond Road at 8:30am&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cold and potentially poor weather conditions. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is dangerous especially in cool/wet weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunset on Saturday will be at 8:31 pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headlamps are not required, but strongly suggested as a safety precaution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike is not very exposed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no AMC hut along this trail, but Cabot does have a fire warden's cabin off the summit. &amp;nbsp;I do NOT believe that water is available here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you. &amp;nbsp;I require that hikers in my group wait at trail junctions and at summits to allow the group to make decisions and reset their pace along the way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I (Kate) am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. Il rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This summer, I am scheduling most of my hikes on Saturdays. &amp;nbsp;Rain dates will be on Sundays, provided the weather is expected to improve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of fabulous views and enjoying the outdoors so, if the weather looks like it will be miserable, we will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - I may delete your 'going' RSVP and/or will not take you from the waiting list if I don't see your answers. &amp;nbsp; If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning/evening of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book time is about &amp;nbsp;7 hrs 45 minutes &amp;amp; &amp;nbsp;10.3 miles depending on the route taken&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 ----------------------------------------------------------&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Copyright &amp;copy; the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bunnell Notch Trail to Kilkenny Ridge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.8 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1350 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 hr 5 min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kilkenny Ridge Trail (from Bunnelll Notch/Departure from Mt. Cabot Trail to Unknown Pond)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1300 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 hrs 15 min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unknown Pond Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.3 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1400 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;2 hours 25 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total Time/Mileage: &amp;nbsp;10.3 miles - 7 hours, 45 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER: MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY, WINTER HIKING OR MOUNTAIN RESCUE. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic, usually a Meetup Sign in the window &amp; 2 dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309095334000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308584065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH 48:  Cabot/Bulge/Horn</name><id>22837551</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309091400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/22837551/</event_url></item>