<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another &lt;span style="text-decoration : line-through"&gt;Movie&lt;/span&gt; Screening Night! Come for a&amp;nbsp;free screening at this great location! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, so please only say "Yes" if you're pretty sure you can make it. (There&amp;nbsp;should be&amp;nbsp;NO Maybe's&amp;nbsp;for this event.)&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sorry, But due to some complications with the projector I had to Close RSVP's to this event Early as we may need to deflect to an alternate location with even more limited seating.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you are to attend, I will also need your FULL NAME for the Concierge to let you in to the building. So please, when you RSVP, either place it in your comment or contact me (AJ) by meetup e-mail or text message. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I showed Coupling Season 1 a few months ago.&amp;nbsp; I got a few very good responses begging for more.&amp;nbsp; SO this time we'll be showing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0237123/"&gt;Coupling:&lt;/a&gt; Season 2 (British Comedy Show, 2000-2004)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring: Jack Davenport, Gina Bellman, Sarah Alexander, Kate Isitt, Ben Miles, and Richard Coyle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you missed Season 1, you can try and catch up on it at various places such as on &lt;a href="http://www.hulu.com/coupling"&gt;Hulu&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Most episodes stand alone well enough though, so outside of a few character jokes you'd probably be fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ's Description: Coupling is a British Comedy who's prime targets are Relationships and Sex.&amp;nbsp; It is by far one of the most hilarious Television series I have ever seen.&amp;nbsp; It is actually pretty even sided, so guys and girls alike should enjoy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each episode is about 30 minutes long (includes no commercials) so if it's not your cup o' tea it will be easy to make an early exit in between episodes.&amp;nbsp; Also do not get it confused with the US version, which is not as impressive.&amp;nbsp;Season 2 is longer, so we might not make it all the way, we'll just get to where we can.&amp;nbsp;(Starting with the Episode "The Man with Two Legs".)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event start time is 6:45 for the social portion of the evening, so you can start showing up then.&amp;nbsp; But we will not start the film until 7:30 or shortly there after.&amp;nbsp; Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list.&amp;nbsp; As the date approaches I can add people on the waiting list if someone else backs out, provided you sent me your name for the concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages.&amp;nbsp; (Just Please be careful and responsible.)&amp;nbsp;Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;instructions near&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked.&amp;nbsp; If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7pm.&amp;nbsp; If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.)&amp;nbsp; 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only at $5 daily max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday, the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the building main entrance.&amp;nbsp; Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the building door, Ring the Bell Button, Concierge will Direct you. If you have more problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307387806000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306290063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Screening: "Coupling" Season 2</name><id>19631511</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307227500000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/19631511/</event_url></item>