<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>0 Medford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.401779</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South Medford Community Room at Engine 5</name><city>Medford</city><id>6510402</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105965</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest speaker will be Mike Hruby, President of New Jobs for Massachusetts. Hruby has been a consultant to large and mid-sized technology companies for more than 20 years. During the course of over 500 projects his firm helped companies nationwide enter new markets for their products and develop new products based on the companies’ technical capabilities. He wrote an award-winning book on corporate growth strategy, titled Technoleverage. &lt;br /&gt;

 New Jobs for Massachusetts is a public policy advocate for rapid gro……wth in private sector employment in Massachusetts. Its mission is to accelerate the growth of new jobs across the state. New Jobs works with legislators, agencies, the media, voters, interest groups and think tanks to devise solutions custom-tailored to Massachusetts’ unique resources for job growth. New Jobs is non-partisan and non-profit. It is supported by voluntary contributions and accepts no government funds.(This meeting is located at the S. Medford Fire Station. If your GPS doesn't recognize the "0" enter "1 Medford Street" and just look for the fire station. It's at a triangle shaped intersection.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Morabito</member_name><member_id>10170370</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368579687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367675575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Medford Meeting</name><id>117687212</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368572400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/117687212/</event_url></item>