<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>kancamagus highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.040955</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Hancock Overlook Parking Lot</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>13254032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.523190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;*****UPDATE******&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Due to the interest in this hike, I'm going to open it up to additional members. If we end up with more than 12 on the day of the hike we will split into two groups at the trail head and meet at the top for lunch. Chris has graciously agreed to lead the second group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Its time to put the Connecticut AT on ice until the Fall and start working on our New Hampshire 4000 footer list! We'll bag two of those on this hike, Mt Hancock at 4,420 ft and South Hancock at 4,319. From the trailhead we'll take the Hancock Notch, Cedar Brook, and Hancock Loop trails. Its 3 and a half miles to get to the Hancock Loop trail, the loop is 2.6 miles and covers both peaks, then the 3 and a half miles back out the way we came. Total hike is 9.8 miles with an elevation gain of 2,700 feet. Book time (AMC White Mountain Guide) is 6 hours 15 minutes....but I'm betting we'll be closer to 8 or 9 hours. Both peaks are wooded, but there are outlooks that provide some excellent views.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Note: Please use coordinates and google map link for the trailhead location....the meetup location map is close, but not exact. This map is helpful as well, as you can see there are multiple parking lots...its the one at the end of the hairpin turn. &lt;a href="http://4000footers.com/MAP%20hancock%20south%20hancock.pdf"&gt;MAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;For more details about this hike, see:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://4000footers.com/hancock.shtml"&gt;Hancock Loop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camping Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike, being on the 93 side of the white mountains, is very doable as a day hike being a 3 hour drive from Providence. To avoid getting up at such an unpleasant hour however, I'm going to head up Friday evening and stay at a nearby campground. When I figure out where I'm staying I'll post in the comment section in case others are interested. Its usually about 20 bucks a night for a campsite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;This is an advanced hike with significant elevation gain. Please have done a hike of similar difficulty before signing up or email me directly if you're unsure.&lt;/span&gt; Please bring plenty of water (I'm bringing 3 liters) appropriate hiking attire (no jeans or cotton, hiking boots not sneakers), rain gear in case the weather turns nasty, lunch, and snacks. Some warmer layers for the peaks will come in handy as well depending on the weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailhead Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From Providence about 3 hours. Trail head is right on the Kancamagus Highway (NH rt 112) just east of Lincoln, NH.&lt;/span&gt; From I-93, take exit 32 towards North Woodstock/Lincoln, NH. Turn left onto the &lt;strong&gt;Kancamagus Highway/112 East&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and continue for 10.5 miles until you reach the parking lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;There is a parking lot, the Hancock Overlook parking area, right along the road at the trail head.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Google Map:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=44.041432,-71.524300&amp;amp;hnear=0x4cb3793196f41ec9:0xf676ac34e819c8a,44.041432,-71.524300&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=15"&gt;Google Maps Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Coordinates: 44.041432,-71.524300&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Carpool Option:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Please use the comments section to coordinate with other hikers if you want to carpool. Keep in mind that car spotting is involved!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Liability Waiver:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Hancock Overlook parking lot on the Kancamagus Highway My Cell: 508-414-8544</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370271088000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367795161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hancocks</name><id>117885442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370091600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/117885442/</event_url></item>