<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Cambridge Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362993</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 674-5151</phone><name>The Massachusetts Biotechnology Council</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836424</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086596</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>After a short hiatus to accomodate summer vacations, the Boston Biotech Meetup is back...mark your calendars for Monday, September 20 from 6:30 - 8:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to re-connecting with friends, sharing highlights of your summer vacations, and making new connections with folks throughout the biotech community, we will be fortunate enough to have a special presentation from Kevin Davies PhD, Editor of Bio-IT World, and author of the new book &amp;quot;The $1,000 Genome.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eight years ago, maverick genome scientist Craig Venter hosted a symposium in Boston showcasing half-a-dozen nascent DNA sequencing technologies that aimed to deliver “the $1,000 genome.” What seemed like science-fiction less than a decade ago is already reality. Anyone can order a full genome work-up for less than $20,000, and one company already claims it can sequence a genome for less than the magical $1,000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;British science writer Kevin Davies has chronicled the stunning advances in next-generation sequencing technologies and personal genomics in his new book, appropriately entitled The $1,000 Genome (published by Free Press). He’ll share stories and insights uncovered over the past three years of in-depth reporting and discuss some of the major challenges ahead in applying the genomic revolution to medicine.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To help us celebrate our 50th Meetup, we hope you can join us for what will certainly be an interesting conversation and a great night of networking!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Martin</member_name><member_id>10132779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297815322000</updated><rating><average>4.30999994278</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Biotechnology Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>biotech-31</urlname><id>178843</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Biotech Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>101</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281986047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The $1000 Genome</name><id>14440389</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285021800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/biotech-31/events/14440389/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/e/global_73246.jpeg</photo_url></item>