<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>185 Cold Spring Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.325967</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Church of the Redeemer</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1412346</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.915118</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : 24px"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The &lt;strong&gt;yes&lt;/strong&gt;plus workshop is a combination of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 24px"&gt;meditation, knowledge and action&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meditation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;- With a little help, anyone can meditate&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 When people hear about meditation, they almost always say either they have never tried it, or they were not able to do it. Someone may have told you that thoughts were supposed to go away, but when you closed your eyes, more thoughts than ever came up. With Sudarshan Kriya, meditation can happen effortlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sudarshan Kriya&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;- Breathing that takes you into meditation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An incredible breathing technique, which takes you into a deep state of meditation, whether or not you have any previous experience of meditation. Millions of people have done it, and the results are incredible. Most people feel deeply relaxed, renewed, as if a weight has been lifted. And anyone can do it. Sudarshan Kriya is the highlight of a series of yoga and meditation techniques you learn on yesplus to give you more energy, greater peace of mind, better focus, and so on…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;- A little self knowledge goes a long way. On &lt;strong&gt;yes&lt;/strong&gt;plus you get a lot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 It’s amazing what we dont notice about ourselves day in and day out. We get stuck in the same patterns, and we often miss simple truths. For example have you noticed that you often remember an insult more than a compliment? How about the fact that you feel so good after being sick? Sure on some level we have noticed all these things, but with a little awareness and wisdom, we can look deeper into these patterns of the mind and can be much more free and relaxed, enjoying the present far more. &lt;strong&gt;yes&lt;/strong&gt;plus brings awareness to things we have all been aware of on some level, and brings us to a whole new level of understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- yes&lt;/strong&gt;plus gives you the strength to do great things in the world.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Sometimes we have an idea that people who meditate just sit around and dont do a whole lot. They are very peaceful, but what about people who have a lot of ambition, who want to do great things in the world? yesplus is as much about action as it is about meditation. Just like to shoot an arrow forward, we must first pull the string back, to really engage in dynamic action we need deep rest. Meditation gives us this rest. Then once the mind is clear, once we are strong in our mind and emotions, we will have the courage and confidence to take on big things, and do a lot for the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medical Research&lt;/strong&gt; says it's a Good Idea&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Ongoing research has shown that the rhythmic breathing technique Sudarshan Kriya, and its accompanying practices (SK&amp;amp;P) can lead to improved physical, mental and emotional health. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 More details at &lt;a href="http://us.yesplus.org/projects/"&gt;Harvard Medical School's Health Publication&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : 16px"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance memory and concentration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliminate doubt and worry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decrease stress and anxiety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restful sleep and stronger immune system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be happy, vibrant and joyful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://secure.artofliving.org/course_details.aspx?course_id=12933</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brinda</member_name><member_id>60069742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349143534000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-542</urlname><id>1021017</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Art of Living, New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347502592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>YESPLUS WORKSHOP</name><id>82161752</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>273600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348869600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-542/events/82161752/</event_url></item>