<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come listen to game designer &lt;b&gt;Jesse Schell&lt;/b&gt; present the movie &lt;b&gt;Hackers&lt;/b&gt;, and talk about  which parts of Hackers have come true, will come true, and what will never come true. He will also be talking about what is coming up in gaming and technology. If Jesse is only half as whimsical and entertaining as his personal site at &lt;a href="http://www.jesseschell.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jesseschel...&lt;/a&gt; this should be fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hackers&amp;quot; features a young Angelina Jolie, and some other actors playing computer geeks, giving all male computer geeks everywhere hope. It's a bit over the top, with some really cheesy lines, but it's a fun little movie.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7:00 pm showtime (get in line at 6:15 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $9.75 [ &lt;b&gt;Buy tickets online&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Release Date:&lt;/b&gt; 9/15/1995 -- Movie just turned 15 years old!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duration&lt;/b&gt;: The movie itself is only 107 minutes long (1 hour, 47 minutes). The program is listed on the Coolidge Corner site as 2 hrs 47 minutes, so I am guessing that Jesse Schell will be speaking for a full hour? That can't be right. Guest speakers usually speak for twenty minutes tops for the Science on Screen program. Let me check on this... If this is true this means we will be getting out of the theater by 9:50 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, T.J. Maher will get there at 6:00 pm if anyone wants to hang out and socialize before. Rain or shine, the Coolidge Corner forms a line starting at 6:15 pm in the alleyway outside the theater, a line which quickly wraps its way down the brick wall next to the theater and turns the corner. We can all get in line by 6:15 pm, giving us more time to say hello to each other. The doors open at 6:40 pm, and the theater fills up fast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... We should be getting out of the Theater by 9:50 pm. Anybody up for the great dessert place, Finale? When you exit the building, hook a right and head to the street. T.J. will be acting like a human landmark, big ole MEETUP sign in tow, and we can decide if we want to go somewhere after or not. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about the presentation:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In this 1995 cyber thriller, Dade 'Zero Cool' Murphy (Jonny Lee Miller) is a hacking genius who was arrested at age 11 for crashing 1,507 computer systems (including those on Wall Street) in a single day, and banned from using a computer until his 18th birthday. Now of age and the new kid in a New York City high school, he meets a corps of gifted Nintendo-generation hackers, including gorgeous, tough-talking love interest Kate aka Acid Burn (Angelina Jolie), resident wild man Cereal Killer (Matthew Lillard), phone expert Phantom Phreak, and Joey, a junior hacker without a handle. These videogame-playing 'keyboard cowboys' enjoy raising some good-natured cyber havoc —until they encounter The Plague (Fisher Stevens), an evil former hacker turned head of computer security at a multinational conglomerate. When they learn that The Plague is plotting to frame them for his own nefarious crimes—including unleashing a dangerous virus and embezzling huge sums from his employer—the young computer whizzes devise a plan to bring him down ('Hackers of the world unite!'). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Game designer Jesse Schell is known for his theory of the “Gamepocalypse,” a future where games converge with reality and everything in life is a game. “Hackers is an interesting movie,” says Schell, “because its captures the growing sense that the main purpose of technology is for fun and games.” Before the screening, Schell discusses which parts of Hackers have come true, will come true, and will never come true, and some of the cool things we can expect in gaming and technology.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Jesse Schell is professor of entertainment technology at Carnegie Mellon University in Pittsburgh and founder and CEO of Schell Games. His book The Art of Game Design was Game Developer Magazine’s 2008 book of the year. For more about Schell, visit www.schellgames.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Jesse Schell:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Prior to starting Schell Games in 2004, Jesse was the Creative Director of the Disney Imagineering Virtual Reality Studio, where he worked and played for seven years as designer, programmer and manager on several projects for Disney theme parks and DisneyQuest, as well as on Toontown Online, the first massively multiplayer game for kids. Before that, he worked as writer, director, performer, juggler, comedian, and circus artist for both Freihofer's Mime Circus and the Juggler's Guild.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Jesse is also on the faculty of the Entertainment Technology Center at Carnegie Mellon University where he teaches classes in Game Design and serves as advisor on several innovative projects. Formerly the Chairman of the International Game Developers Association, he is also the author of the award winning book The Art of Game Design: A Book of Lenses. In 2004, he was named one of the world's Top 100 Young Innovators by Technology Review, MIT's magazine of innovation. His primary responsibility at Schell Games is to make sure everyone is having fun and creating beautiful things.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jesse Schell -- Our Tech Nightmare (&amp;quot;Skinner Box&amp;quot;) DICE 2010&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8FSsztwbRW0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Video of Jesse's talk at DICE 2010 (Design Innovate Communicate Entertain) a video game conference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science on Screen:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, we present a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Parking&lt;/u&gt;: Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Center St. one block from Harvard St.) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 6:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;By train&lt;/u&gt;: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287017620000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286160415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game designer Jesse Schell introduces "Hackers" now 15 yrs old @ Coolidge Corner</name><id>14990190</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286835300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14990190/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/b/global_18466027.jpeg</photo_url></item>