<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1866 Northampton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.199341</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yankee Pedlar Inn</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>1536032</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631157</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/4/2/event_174984642.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;The Utter Rudeness of Today's World: How to Combat It, One Smile at a Time &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Speaker:&lt;/strong&gt; Dianne Provost of Manners and More&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; $20 (with $5 back at the door for WBOA members who have registered in advance) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Doors slammed, horns honked, and cell phones left on ring during the movies are just a few of today's minor annoyances. When civility goes out the window, the annoyances grow.. and grow... until you're feeling like you're the last one with manners standing. (And you're annoyed and want to throw things, but as the last polite adult standing, you don't.) Join us at our November Breakfast Meeting on Thursday, November 15 at 7:45 a.m. at The Yankee Pedlar to learn how to combat incivility and restore a polite, orderly world - just in time for Thanksgiving dinner. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Throughout her career, Dianne Provost has supported senior-level executives at private corporations and has extensive corporate event planning experience. Prior to her corporate run, she was a banquet manager for 13 years, was sole proprietor of a gourmet food basket business for 10 years, and taught a gourmet basket course at Holyoke Community College. With her entrepreneurial spirit, Dianne, along with her business partner and daughter Renée Provost has brought Manners And More, Etiquette Essentials to Western Massachusetts.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Manners And More offers customized programs with a fresh approach to teaching etiquette essentials to young people in Western Massachusetts. We cover topics in Basic Manners, Communication Skills, Personal Presentation, the Art of Conversation, and Table Manners. We also offer personalized résumé writing services and interview coaching for all ages.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353016387000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351537065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November Breakfast Meeting: The Rudeness of Today's World &amp; How to Combat It</name><id>89068702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352983500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/89068702/</event_url></item>