<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us on December 3rd at the offices of our &lt;b&gt;sponsor HubSpot&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.hubspot.com" target="_blank"&gt;(&lt;a href="http://www.hubspot.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hubspot.co...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/a&gt; for some networking, food and beverages, and knowledge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presenting the case study is Boston-based cosmetic dentist Dr. Helaine Smith and B2B marketing communications consultant Dianna Huff, principal of DH Communications, Inc. Together they will discuss how to keep your marketing budget steady while increasing revenue using various search marketing strategies, including Google Local Search and building inbound links via social media and PR tactics. Business owners and marketers will learn how to cost effectively optimize a Website for local search while also building brand awareness and generating increased business. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, HubSpot will provide a review of the marketing effectiveness of your web site based on various SEO criteria.  The report will be waiting for you if you provide your URL during the registration process. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hubspot is conveniently located in Kendall Square section of Cambridge at One Broadway, &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA 02142.    For those taking public transportation, the Red Line's Kendall Square is two blocks away.  For those driving, parking is available for a fee in the One Broadway building.  Enter the building garage on the Third Street side of the building.  [url=http://www.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;q=1%20Broadway,%20Cambridge,%20MA&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;om=1&amp;amp;z=14&amp;amp;ll=42.368184,-71.083174&amp;amp;spn=0.027585,0.086002&amp;amp;iwloc=addr]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check in at the building's front desk is required before going to the  5th floor.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check in at the lobby desk is required.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Katie Donovan</member_name><member_id>6066282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1352919385000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Cyber-Founders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Startup-Pitch-Night</urlname><id>1278110</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Startup Pitch Night</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225922046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Case Study:  Same Marketing Budget - Greater Revenue</name><id>9101364</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228347000000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Startup-Pitch-Night/events/9101364/</event_url></item>