<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Pythonistas, the May meetup brings us two scientists sharing their work in Python:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Geraldine Van Der Auwera&lt;/strong&gt;: TRAPPIST is a BioPython-based     package that performs detailed comparisons of related genomic     regions and produces publication-quality vector PDF figures for     clear visualization of analysis results. It is built as a series of     functional modules that can be run separately or in pipelines.     Several pre-set pipeline scripts are provided for automated     start-to-finish processing of tasks that combine analysis and     visualization, such as producing figures of multiple alignments with     detailed similarity heat maps, identifying conserved genetic     backbones or reconstructing the differential phylogeny of mosaic     genome regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Byron Galbraith&lt;/strong&gt;: Modelling Neurons in Python.&amp;nbsp; Representing     the function and behavior of neurons in software is one of the core     activities of computational neuroscience. As neurons communicate via     electrochemical currents, this is typically accomplished through     modeling the dynamical nature of the neuron's electrical properties.     Several models treat the neuron as an equivalent electrical circuit,     with its membrane potential described by one or more differential     equations. In order to simulate the response of the neuron to     various stimuli, these equations are numerically solved over some     time interval for a given pattern of input current.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plus&lt;/strong&gt;, we'll probably have a lightning talk or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Socializing and other interactions at 6:30, formal presentations at 7:00.&amp;nbsp; See you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Batchelder</member_name><member_id>1824278</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307896413000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>101</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303000104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May meetup: Science!</name><id>17330576</id><headcount>66</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305759600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/17330576/</event_url></item>