<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Central Square</address_2><address_1>24 Pearl St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364033</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-8881</phone><name>Rangzen Tibet Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669154</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103241</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Fellow foodie, Steven David Bloomerg, says, 'the food is great at Rangzen and there's a lot to choose on the menu.&amp;nbsp;I agree and besides it has been a long time since our last lunch here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affordable family style dining in Central Square...many vegetarian dishes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For detals check out this link&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://rangzenrestaurant.com/"&gt;Rangzen Tibetan Restaurant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All you can eat luncheon buffet for less than $15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip and tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;Reservations are not accepted so please be prompt so you can be seated with us&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Green Street Garage which is diagonally across from Rangzen has parking for $2 per hour&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MBTA.com :&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Train: Central Square on the Red Line&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Bus: 1, 77, &amp;amp; 84 to name a few&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;RULES for ENGAGEMENT:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while dining.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your expenses....meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first reply, first reserved basis.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment explaining your situation.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If the meal is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged.*&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied by final update event confirmation email deadline, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as a NO-SHOW for this event.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for THREE (3) events you are removed from the group.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at 617 445-7549.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;I will arrive at Rangzen by 12:00 PM to arrange seating as well as welcome you&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a one room restaurant which makes it easy to find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298243705000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Great all you can eat lunch buffet</why><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260594632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rangzen Tibetan Lunch</name><id>12069421</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298135700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/12069421/</event_url></item>