<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>435 Bay Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01982</zip><lat>42.616276</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myopia Hunt Club</name><city>South Hamilton</city><id>636797</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.862862</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>South Hamilton, Mass. is home to the country's oldest polo match at the Myopia Hunt Club (named so because all of the original members wore glasses).  Coming from a part of the country where the saddles all have horns and the horse events are more likely to be a rodeo, David and I are very excited about attending a polo match. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gates open at 1:30 and the match starts at 3:00 (lasting generally 1h30).  We'll arrive by 2:00, and you can meet us any time between 2:00-3:00.  Bring your own blanket or chairs and food and drink, as the match is a tailgating affair.  We certainly plan to picnic before and during the match.  As you'll be in the sun all afternoon, make sure to dress comfortably and bring sunscreen.  Gone are the days of the floppy Julia Roberts hats, the club states the dress for the match is &amp;quot;country casual.&amp;quot;  Also, if you plan to &amp;quot;stomp the divots&amp;quot; make sure you have on shoes that won't sink into the grass. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is $10 (everything that I read about the club at boston.com and in &lt;i&gt;North Shore&lt;/i&gt; magazine said $10 a car, but the lady at the club said $10 a head, so we'll see when we get there what the actual charge is).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about polo, I would suggest the website: &lt;a href="http://www.sportpolo.com/default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sportpolo....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The contact number listed above belongs to David (not the hunt club) to be used to locate us at the match.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214331303000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212939021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Polo Match at the Myopia Hunt Club</name><id>8103019</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214157600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/8103019/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/8/global_4389080.jpeg</photo_url></item>