<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>All levelsbeginner to advanced-&lt;br /&gt;we can work together and become local wordpress experts-&lt;br /&gt;volunteers to bring a snack -discretely its a library :)?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;important:&lt;/b&gt; please leave a note in the rsvp&lt;br /&gt;section about your familiarity with wordpress and if you have it set up&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you need help setting up on a host server list your hosting company- &lt;br /&gt;and read this: &lt;a href="http://codex.wordpress.org/Installing_WordPress" target="_blank"&gt;http://codex.wordpres...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This way we can get situated to physically work with wordpress itself during our &lt;br /&gt;wordpress user group meetings!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Inside The Smith College Art Museum, on your left is the Hilyer Art Library.&lt;br /&gt;It is small. Walk in, on your left is a large meeting room. There is large table, computers (4) and&lt;br /&gt;projector.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking details:&lt;br /&gt;# Metered and unmetered parking is available on Elm Street, Green Street, Round Hill Road, Henshaw Avenue, Prospect Street, and other city streets close to Smith and Clarke School campuses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# After 5:00 p.m., and until 1:00 a.m., visitors may park in any white or blue-lined space on campus or in the Smith College Parking Garage, located at 42 West Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# There are also several public parking lots and a covered parking garage in downtown Northampton within 10 to 15 minute walk of the Smith College campus. Parking in these facilities is inexpensive and plentiful. The garage and largest lots are located between Pleasant and Old South Streets.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224200442000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220983094000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northampton Web Dev Meet-up WordPress Users Group</name><id>8722482</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223591400000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/8722482/</event_url></item>