<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Brewster Ct</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.317406</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-584-9903</phone><name>Northampton Brewery</name><city>Northampton</city><id>669291</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.630790</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, as always please feel free to choose one of the books to read for the discussion. If you feel ambitious you may read all of them. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/4/event_125943492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Power of Habit: Why We Do What We Do in Life and Business by Charles Duhigg&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In The Power of Habit, award-winning New York Times business reporter Charles Duhigg takes us to the thrilling edge of scientific discoveries that explain why habits exist and how they can be changed. With penetrating intelligence and an ability to distill vast amounts of information into engrossing narratives, Duhigg brings to life a whole new understanding of human nature and its potential for transformation. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Along the way we learn why some people and companies struggle to change, despite years of trying, while others seem to remake themselves overnight. We visit laboratories where neuroscientists explore how habits work and where, exactly, they reside in our brains. We discover how the right habits were crucial to the success of Olympic swimmer Michael Phelps, Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz, and civil-rights hero Martin Luther King, Jr. We go inside Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, Target superstores, Rick Warren’s Saddleback Church, NFL locker rooms, and the nation’s largest hospitals and see how implementing so-called keystone habits can earn billions and mean the difference between failure and success, life and death. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 At its core, The Power of Habit contains an exhilarating argument: The key to exercising regularly, losing weight, raising exceptional children, becoming more productive, building revolutionary companies and social movements, and achieving success is understanding how habits work. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Habits aren’t destiny. As Charles Duhigg shows, by harnessing this new science, we can transform our businesses, our communities, and our lives. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Chosen by Karen T&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Caleb's Crossing by Geraldine Brooks&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An historical fiction, set in the 1600's on Martha's Vineyard, the novel is based on the true story of the first Native American to graduate from Harvard College. The book's narrator, Bethia Mayfield, is the daughter of a Calvinist preacher. Smart and curious, Bethia is thirsty fora good education--the kind that only boys get. When she meets a Wampanoag Indian named Caleb who shares her love of learning, the two strike up a secret friendship as Bertha's father recognizes Caleb's intelligence and steers him towards Harvard. Brooks' novel is nothing less than epic. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Chosen by Elizabeth S&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Bonus Book&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power of Myth by Joseph Campbell&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/9/2/event_125946802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Among his many gifts, Joseph Campbell's most impressive was the unique ability to take a contemporary situation, such as the murder and funeral of President John F. Kennedy, and help us understand its impact in the context of ancient mythology. Herein lies the power of The Power of Myth, showing how humans are apt to create and live out the themes of mythology. Based on a six-part PBS television series hosted by Bill Moyers, this classic is especially compelling because of its engaging question-and-answer format, creating an easy, conversational approach to complicated and esoteric topics. For example, when discussing the mythology of heroes, Campbell and Moyers smoothly segue from the Sumerian sky goddess Inanna to Star Wars' mercenary-turned-hero, Han Solo. Most impressive is Campbell's encyclopedic knowledge of myths, demonstrated in his ability to recall the details and archetypes of almost any story, from any point and history, and translate it into a lesson for spiritual living in the here and now. --Gail Hudson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book chosen by: Jeanne&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Turnberg</member_name><member_id>10580891</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth Szewczyk</member_name><member_id>21666841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340890583000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335405219000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June's Discussion: The power of habit &amp; Caleb's Crossing</name><id>62172322</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340749800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/62172322/</event_url></item>