<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>276 Westminster Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822266</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Roots Cafe</name><city>Providence</city><id>1579545</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.413162</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is the 3rd Anniversary of PechaKucha Providence - the longest consecutively-run PechaKucha worldwide! Yes, Its true!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PechaKucha is a world wide phenomena with its roots in Japan, but our Providence PechaKucha has been the the only one world-wide to run consecutively without missing a month! For those that don't know, PechaKucha is a series of short presentations by anyone on any subject. Put simply: 6 minutes and 40 seconds of adult-style ...show &amp;amp; tell. (20 slides every 20 seconds). So for those with short attention spans - its great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm posting this as an FYI for the uninitiated and those that might be interested in going. This anniversary event is bound to be crowded and was HUGE last year, so if you want to get a seat be there at 7:00-7:20, grab a drink and plant yourself in a chair while they are available!. Its a great monthly event that brings out lots of people and who knows, maybe you'll be inspired to make your own presentation sometime. I was skeptical when I first heard about it 3 years ago, but it only takes one time and you'll be hooked and back for more each month! There is an intermission halfway through, so don't feel obligated to stay if its not your bag or you feel claustrophobic. Its very casual! For more info on the PechaKucha and the list of presenters this Wednesday click here:&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/254225387995919/"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/254225387995919/&lt;/a&gt; So check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the size and difficulty of meeting up during this event, each person will be on their own, please RSVP if you're planning to go so others can find you. However, its kind of guaranteed that this is so popular you're bound to see someone you know! Its Providence after all. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is posted as an FYI - if you want to go, please RSVP so other members know who to look for! I may or may not be going. If you would like to host, let me know!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333032827000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332724452000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>P-Collective FYI - PechaKucha #36 -3rd Anniversary at Roots Cafe!!!</name><id>57841922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332975600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/57841922/</event_url></item>