<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>151 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.987919</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>LuLu's Pizzeria &amp; Family Restaurant</name><city>Enfield</city><id>2150071</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.559479</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two books for this month are below. I have added the 
&lt;em&gt;'Shadow of the Wind&lt;/em&gt;' as a bonus book for those who are ambitious and would like to read it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the new members just a reminder that you only need to read one book. If you would like to read two or all three please feel free to do so.&amp;lt;/-----&lt;/p&gt;.............................. 
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Th 
&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/c/4/0/event_53527232.jpeg" width="150" height="231" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;e Secret History by Donna Tartt
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;em&gt;Richard Papen arrived at Hampden College in New England and was quickly seduced by an elite group of five students, all Greek scholars, all worldly, self-assured, and, at first glance, all highly unapproachable. As Richard is drawn into their inner circle, he learns a terrifying secret that binds them to one another...a secret about an incident in the woods in the dead of night where an ancient rite was brought to brutal life...and led to a gruesome death. And that was just the beginning...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/1/a/event_53527962.jpeg" width="150" height="232" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  The Angel's Game by 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Carlos Ruiz Zaf&amp;oacute;n&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; From master storyteller Carlos Ruiz Zaf&amp;oacute;n, author of the international phenomenon The Shadow of the Wind, comes The Angel&amp;#146;s Game--a dazzling new page-turner about the perilous nature of obsession, in literature and in love.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;&amp;#147;The whole of Barcelona stretched out at my feet and I wanted to believe that, when I opened those windows, its streets would whisper stories to me, secrets I could capture on paper and narrate to whomever cared to listen...&amp;#148;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man, David Mart&amp;iacute;n, makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of books and spends his nights spinning baroque tales about the city&amp;#146;s underworld. But perhaps his dark imaginings are not as strange as they seem, for in a locked room deep within the house lie photographs and letters hinting at the mysterious death of the previous owner.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Like a slow poison, the history of the place seeps into his bones as he struggles with an impossible love. Close to despair, David receives a letter from a reclusive French editor, Andreas Corelli, who makes him the offer of a lifetime. He is to write a book unlike anything that has ever existed--a book with the power to change hearts and minds. In return, he will receive a fortune, and perhaps more. But as David begins the work, he realizes that there is a connection between his haunting book and the shadows that surround his home.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Once again, Zaf&amp;oacute;n takes us into a dark, gothic universe first seen in The Shadow of the Wind and creates a breathtaking adventure of intrigue, romance, and tragedy. Through a dizzingly constructed labyrinth of secrets, the magic of books, passion, and friendship blend into a masterful story.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;BONUS BOOK:&lt;/em&gt; The Shadow of the Wind: A Novel by Carlos Ruiz Zafon&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/e/2/event_53528162.jpeg" width="150" height="229" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  Ruiz Zaf&amp;oacute;n's novel, a bestseller in his native Spain, takes the satanic touches from Angel Heart and stirs them into a bookish intrigue &amp;agrave; la Foucault's Pendulum. The time is the 1950s; the place, Barcelona. Daniel Sempere, the son of a widowed bookstore owner, is 10 when he discovers a novel, The Shadow of the Wind, by Juli&amp;aacute;n Carax. The novel is rare, the author obscure, and rumors tell of a horribly disfigured man who has been burning every copy he can find of Carax's novels. The man calls himself La&amp;iacute;n Coubert-the name of the devil in one of Carax's novels. As he grows up, Daniel's fascination with the mysterious Carax links him to a blind femme fatale with a "porcelain gaze," Clara Barcel&amp;oacute;; another fan, a leftist jack-of-all-trades, Ferm&amp;iacute;n Romero de Torres; his best friend's sister, the delectable Beatriz Aguilar; and, as he begins investigating the life and death of Carax, a cast of characters with secrets to hide. Officially, Carax's dead body was dumped in an alley in 1936. But discrepancies in this story surface. Meanwhile, Daniel and Ferm&amp;iacute;n are being harried by a sadistic policeman, Carax's childhood friend. As Daniel's quest continues, frightening parallels between his own life and Carax's begin to emerge. Ruiz Zaf&amp;oacute;n strives for a literary tone, and no scene goes by without its complement of florid, cute and inexact similes and metaphors (snow is "God's dandruff"; servants obey orders with "the efficiency and submissiveness of a body of well-trained insects"). Yet the colorful cast of characters, the gothic turns and the straining for effect only give the book the feel of para-literature or the Hollywood version of a great 19th-century novel.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317254148000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311613677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>September's discussion: The Secret History &amp; The Angel's Game</name><id>26961011</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317162600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/26961011/</event_url></item>