<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Bronx Zoo is a wonderful model of what zoos should be.  Animals are kept in large naturalistic enclosures which draw the visitors to learn more about conservation.  Upon entry, the Congo exhibit, a 43 million doallr exhibit, is one of if not the largest rainforest exhibits in the world and provides the visitor a slice of the Congo.  The Jungle World Exhibit is a large indoor Asian rainforest with several Languar, an Asian Monkey species alongside tree Kangaroos, Malayan Tapir, and Black Leopards.  This must see exhibit borders on the Wild Asia Monorail.  A journey on this shuttle takes the visitor through a myiad of Asian herbivore exhibits such as the Asian greater one-horned Rhino and the rare indian boved Guar.  Upon departure from Wild Asia, the visitor can enter into the Himalayan Highlands exhibit, home to the Snow Leopards and Red Pandas.  The Tiger Mountain exhibit is a vast space lush with foliage home to rare Amur(Siberian) Tigers,  the Baboon Reserve and a herd of Aodads, a sort of wild sheep.  The vast exhibit provides a copious amount of room for the animals to act as if they were in the valleys of Ethiopia, their native home. There are may more exhibits that are just as spectacular throughout the zoo.   The Bronx Zoo is the second largest zoo in the world.  Inside the zoo lunch can be purchased at many of the great of the great concession stands located around the zoo, or if the visitors desire they an eat their meal in the beautfully themed Dancing Crane Cafe, overlooking a flock of Chilean Flamingoes.  The zoo has made every effort in affording its creatures the very best life possible. Once you arrive and are inside the zoo you will be dumbfounded to find that it is smack dab in the middle of the Bronx.  You will find yourself in a whole new world.  &lt;br /&gt;   This will be a family oriented event.  Children under ten are not recommended to attend this event because of the long walking distance of the zoo and we will not leave until late in the afternoon.  The Zoo is free on Wednesdays.  The only cost is parking.  We will carpool together down to New York.  Donations to the Zoo are accepted.  Spending money should be brought for when you are in the park.  Backpacks are allowed.  In the case of the rain this event will be rescheduled.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at Barnes &amp; Noble in Holyoke, exit 15 off of 91 North, to carpool down to New York together.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>4671887</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211547866000</updated><rating><average>1.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1514</urlname><id>824401</id><group_lat>42.0999984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5899963379</group_lon><name>Single Mingle Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207017109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bronx Zoo</name><id>7645159</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211374800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1514/events/7645159/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/e/global_3300622.jpeg</photo_url></item>