<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1157 Chapel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308741</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Study Hotel</name><city>New Haven</city><id>799318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.932698</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of times a year, the Shops in downtown New Haven hold "Flights of Fancy".&amp;nbsp; Join NHCer Alina for the next Installment this Friday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You start by Registering at "The Study" hotel.&amp;nbsp; Registration is $10 and they will provide you an Event Wine Glass and a Map of all the participating Shops. (And validated parking.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there you wander around downtown New Haven to each participating shop on the map and get a Wine Sample at each!&amp;nbsp; (The Wine Thief provides the Wines)&amp;nbsp; If you chose to shop, each participating store provides a discount of 25% off for the event.&amp;nbsp; Shops are said to be in the Broadway and Chapel street districts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterward attendees can return to The Study at 8:30 p.m. for included Willoughby&amp;rsquo;s coffee, Dessert, and a grand prize drawing for a complimentary stay for two at The Study Hotel at Yale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;
  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt; The websites are a bit unclear about registration. One of them says reservations are "Recommended" the other says Required.&amp;nbsp; At the time I'm typing this, you can still pre-register online by following the link That says "Register Here" at the bottom, then again on the page it brings you to.&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;a href="https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?llr=be57c9cab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e46l499y4c8d6d11&amp;amp;oseq="&gt;Or you can see if my attempts to hyper link it work.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; They do not ask for the money at the online registration, so no worries there if you're unsure.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Alina will Host this event and can be reached at 608-432-5462 if you have trouble finding the Group.&amp;nbsp; Thanks Alina!&lt;/strong&gt; The Plan is to meet at the Bar area of the Study at 4:00 to start out.&amp;nbsp; Give us a call if you need to catch up after that.&amp;nbsp; (It is an early start for a work day for some.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like more information about the Event, you can visit the website 
&lt;a href="http://www.newhavenshops.com/2011/07/flights-of-fancy-returns-july-29th.html"&gt;HERE (Hyperlinked).&lt;/a&gt; (Included is a list of participating shops.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will Start in the Bar Area at the Study (go right after the entrance.).  Call your Host listed in the Details after that.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alina</member_name><member_id>14143337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312239828000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311612426000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flights of Fancy! - Wine Tasting in Downtown New Haven</name><id>26958051</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311969600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/26958051/</event_url></item>