<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>111 Veterans Memorial Parkway</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02914</zip><lat>41.815050</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>East Bay Bike Path</name><city>East Providence</city><id>904201</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.387184</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My meetups are just for fun and pleasure. &lt;br /&gt;Anyone and everyone is welcome. &lt;br /&gt;So don't get stressed about having to complete the whole path, just come on out, enjoy the outdoors and meet some new folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The East Bay Bike path is a 15 mile, 10 foot wide, ribbon of asphalt that provides a safe place for unobstructed cycling. From Providence to Bristol along the abandoned railroad line. For the greater part of it's length, it passes along or near the shore of Narragansett Bay.&lt;br /&gt;Users can enjoy the sights, sounds and smells as the path takes them by coves and marshes, over bridges, and through State Parks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go at your own pace&lt;br /&gt;Go as far as you want&lt;br /&gt;Stop where ever you want&lt;br /&gt;Stay for as long as you want &amp;amp; leave whenever you want.  &lt;br /&gt;NO STRESS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet us In East Providence at the 1st bike path parking lot between 9:30 &amp;amp; 10 to ride the East Bay Bike Path from East Providence to Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Bay Links&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rigreenways.org/paths/eb-data.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rigreenway...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.riparks.com/eastbay.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.riparks.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95 North and South:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 195 East to Exit 4 for Riverside-Veterans Memorial Parkway. Continue on Veterans Memorial Pkwy. to the first bike path parking area approximately 1/2 mile on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 195 West:&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 6 South Broadway. Take a left turn at the bottom of the exit onto South Broadway, then continue straight on South Broadway for approximately 2 miles to Veterans Memorial Pkwy. Turn right onto the Parkway, bike path parking will be approximately 1/2 mile on your left across from the golf course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car. We won't leave until 10 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE*****UPDATE*****UPDATE*****UPDATE*****UPDATE*****UPDATE*****UPDATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address location is &amp;quot;approximately&amp;quot; 111 Veterans Memorial Parkway&lt;br /&gt;East Providence, RI 02914&lt;br /&gt;Also, I'm going to bring a red blanket and unfold it over the hood of my car so everyone knows where I am located.&lt;br /&gt;Direction Link&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bike.meetup.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://bike.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People are asking me about a lunch option when we arrive in Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have decided to leave this up to each individual because some folks are not traveling all the way to end of the path in Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;Some are going to grab lunch at a earlier stop in East Providence, Riverside, Barrington or at the other stops along the way prior to Bristol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want everyone to feel free to go as far as they want and grab something to eat when and if they wish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't want anyone to feel obligated to do anything they don't want to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will make a point to discuss this on Saturday Morning / take a pole on how far people are traveling and who would like to eat lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3rd I'm going to be adding a &amp;quot;Poll&amp;quot; on the site so we can get an idea on who is:&lt;br /&gt;Walking the Path&lt;br /&gt;Jogging the Path&lt;br /&gt;Running the Path&lt;br /&gt;Biking the Path&lt;br /&gt;Rollerblading the Path&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This way everyone can see how many people are doing what. Click the link to let us know what you are doing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bike.meetup.com/394/polls/"&gt;http://bike.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240066771000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237140514000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Bay Bike Path - 15 Miles Long - 30 Miles Total Trip Back &amp; Forth</name><id>9959302</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238853600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/9959302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/global_5864541.jpeg</photo_url></item>