<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The area offers good trails for hiking, with short, moderate climbs in a mostly wooded environment. Dogs are permitted off leash under voice control.  Whitney &amp;amp; Thayer Woods offer the extra benefit of having a particular highlight and objective for our hike; Turkey Hill, a separate property that we can seamlessly access during our hike. Its 187-foot summit affords spectacular views of Cohasset Harbor and the South Shore. An old building is all that remains of an anti-missile radar control station sited here during the Cold War to thwart potential nuclear attack by the Soviet Union.  The trails are footpaths and carriage roads that twist and turn through resurgent hardwood and pine forests.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Though quite large at more than 800 acres, the property is easily navigated thanks to trail intersection markers. The trail network offers many combinations of various lengths, but the best option, and the one we will follow, is a complete loop across the entire property. Depending on our pace, the hike will be approximately 2 to 3 hours and covers about 10 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From Route 3, take exit 14 and follow Route 228 north for 6.5 mi through Hingham. Turn right onto Route 3A east and follow for 2 mi. to entrance and parking area on right opposite Sohier Street (there's a blinking yellow light there).  If you get to Stop and Shop (on the left) you've gone too far.  Turn around and take your first left at the blinking yellow light.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253214723000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>trail seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NE-Trail-Dogs</urlname><id>1347727</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0100021362</group_lon><name>New England Trail Dogs</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231261298000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whitney and Thayer Woods (Cohasset) *Dogs permitted off leash</name><id>9458945</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234623600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-Trail-Dogs/events/9458945/</event_url></item>