<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome, The Compass Within Series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello this is Anthony J Pasquale, Master Instructor to Mindful Wealth Thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is your chance! When Opportunity knocks, At Least Listen!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us and learn about the small steps it takes to Start YOU on the road of becoming free,,What I mean is learn how to get UN-STUCK, learn about how to begin to start to become Healthy/Wealthy/Happy. Learn to UN-Cover your talents that could be the PURPOSEFUL life you were meant to fulfill! Maybe you have an Idea or a you want to begin to learn what is stopping you from starting something? It could be about starting to look for love or a happy relationship? Maybe How to start to set the the " Buckets of Wealth" (For some of you who just reading this SCARED the daylights out of you for a moment)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen carefully, There is are basic techniques that you can learn to start you moving in the RIGHT direction to whatever you want, But if you don't know, WELL THEN, You don't know! That is where we come in!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love/Money/Career/Purpose/Goals Anything!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if it's debt you have to know basics,, LOOK, are you nervous about the future, not sure what will happen with kids college, YOUR retirement, WELL no need too! Come and learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You realize you have an idea in you that could create wealth and purpose! What if you had the time and freedom to do the things you want and what if that could turn into a passion of developing wealth, Imagine what that could do for you and your family!!! Well here is the BEGINNING!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or you are afraid of looking for that Soul mate,,, What if you learned these technique and it changed everything for you!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is what we will cover:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn to rules of Clarity (Love, Life, Career, Purpose, Financial)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn what to say to yourself everyday so you will OverCome the FEAR FACTOR in daily life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create Three Simple Daily Action Steps towards your dreams!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to create funds (Financial funds) for Your Dreams, Life Savings, College or to get out of debt whatever it maybe that you are looking to do!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to make great decisions for Health/Wealth/happiness through Mindful Wealth Thinking!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will walk away with this with the tools to BEGIN the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be part of a group of people that will walk with you every week and support your dreams, Look we are not suppose to do this alone, there are ways and people you can have someone there to ask for guidance and support towards your DREAMS, GOALS the LIFE You Were meant to Live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us,!!! Today,, Bring a friend and get your life moving in the right direction!!! Your Direction, (Read the Reviews below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the BEST Part this 3 1/2 hour workshop that could change that one dial to move you towards your Dreams/Goals and LifeStyle you deserve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony Pasquale &lt;br /&gt;

 AJP Enterprise &lt;br /&gt;

 A Mindful Wealth Group &lt;br /&gt;

 Master Instructor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Live your Life to way to were meant to, Live with Purpose and Passion Everyday"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ideal Business Center &lt;br /&gt;

 20 Locust Street, Suite 100 &lt;br /&gt;

 Danvers MA 01923 &lt;br /&gt;

 (978) 836-6501&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain "average". These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is what they are saying about this Meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 “ If you don't know what "The Secret" is or the Law of Attraction or if you do and want to start learning how to practice it in your daily life...then ATTEND this group meeting! You owe this to yourself. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Yvonne M Prince on Dec 4, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers " The Secret "Vision Board Workshop Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ Great! More group discussion would be good to help eachother and when is our next meeting? ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Terri on Dec 4, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers " The Secret "Vision Board Workshop Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ Very informative and supportive group ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Laura on Oct 17, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers " The Secret "Vision Board Workshop Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ If you want to move forward in prosperity and happiness bothe personally and professionally, Tony can help you down that road. ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Lucia on Jan 24, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers " The Secret "Vision Board Workshop Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ If they want to change their lives for the better, this is an experience to have!! ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— D on Jan 23, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers " The Secret "Vision Board Workshop Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ I will be happy to comment after I attend a meeting.....based on the ratings, people have found this meetup group GREAT!!! ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Judi V on Nov 15, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345927358000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs,Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1824</urlname><id>1133728</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>The NorthShore Business Support Network meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341944936000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bring a notebook, business cards and idea's</name><id>72763402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345915800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1824/events/72763402/</event_url></item>