<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. would like to welcome the public to our annual free Starfest 2012 star party to be held on the campus of Anna Maria College in Paxton, Massachusetts on Saturday, July 28, 2012 from 6 PM to 10 PM in Foundress Hall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc. and One Giant Leap will offer some amazing talks, door prizes and raffles as we celebrate the upcoming landing of the nuclear powered Curiosity rover on Mars! Aldrich will offer engaging presentations in Zecco Theater by speakers who will talk about the future of US Human Spaceflight and the landing of Curiosity at Gale Crater on Mars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be many outdoor activities like safe solar viewing through a hydrogen alpha filtered telescope, rocket launches in front of Foundress Hall, Walks through the Solar System, Indoor talks about Aliens by a NASA Solar System Ambassador, Seven Minutes of Terror : Landing the Curiosity Rover on Mars, a talk about the future of human spaceflight, with  Indoor telescope displays and talks about Meteorites!  There will also be great opportunities to win amazing door prizes like telescopes and space images autographed by astronauts for small donations which will help establish a new Aldrich public observatory at a dark sky site at nearby Treasure Valley Scouting Reservation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because this presentation will likely draw many interested people, we would encourage the everyone to help us plan ahead by confirming that they plan to attend Starfest 2012 by logging onto the Aldrich website and letting us know you will attend and how many would be in your party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an annual event which will introduce people to the wonders of the night sky and the science of Space Exploration in a very fun and relaxed atmosphere.  In addition to all the great indoor and outdoor activities that are planned, Aldrich members will offer public observing after the event, weather permitting.  We have a large 20 inch Obsession Dobsonian telescope and about a dozen smaller telescopes that will look at objects like Saturn, M13 and nearby Galaxies!  This event will occur no matter what the weather brings since we have access to indoor classrooms and Zecco Theater which can comfortably hold up to 300 people for talks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clear skies to all the members - hope to see many of you at the event! There is a complete listing of the event activities and times on the website of the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc.  Beginners are always welcomed - prepare to have an out of this world experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.aldrichastro.org&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;Please log in and let us know you plan to attend!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e-mail address : aldrichastro@live.com )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizer for Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President of Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter at Zecco Theater, park behind the theater. Greeters will be in front of the building.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343528095000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342669004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Starfest 2012</name><id>73980182</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343512800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/73980182/</event_url></item>