<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THE OCTOBER SATURDAY SECOND PUG MEETUP IS THE FOURTH SATURDAY IN OCTOBER!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The SATURDAY SECOND PUG MEETUP is a new venture for us! We want everyone who cannot come on the SECOND SUNDAY of each month to have an opportunity to attend a meetup on the FOURTH SATURDAY of each month, and anyone who came on the second Sunday is of course also welcome to attend on the fourth Saturday - you can never have too much fun as far as our puggies are concerned. Until further notice, the Saturday meetups will be held in King Clovis's backyard in Brockton. The yard isn't as big as Buford's and my kiddie pool is just an old black rubber horse tub, but there's plenty of shade and water, and enough room to run around in. Your organizer is short on lawn chairs, so unless you intend to sit on the grass, please remember to bring your own lawn chair!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know. We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the people attending! If you bring treats for the Pugs, please ONLY hand out treats around the central table where everyone can keep an eye on the dogs, DON'T FEED CLOVIS, and PLEASE BE SURE that nothing gets dropped - your organizer has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who has brain damage which makes it very difficult for him to swallow. I don't want Clovis to choke to death on a stolen treat, and I'm sure no one else does either.. Thank you for your consideration!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups and the South of Boston Small Breed Dogs Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend. Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis and Cletus's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226258852000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222792694000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug October SATURDAY SECOND Pug Meetup!</name><id>8864519</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224957600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/8864519/</event_url></item>