<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>34 Hillhouse Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.314384</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yale University - Luce Hall</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1339135</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924118</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We are excited to announce the very first DrupalCampCT (www.drupalcampct.org) to be held at Luce Hall, Yale University in New Haven, CT on Saturday, August 28, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drupal (www.drupal.org) is a free, open source software package that allows an individual, a community of users or an enterprise to easily publish, manage and organize a wide variety of content on a website.  A powerful and flexibility content management system (CMS) that rivals those of most commercial alternatives, Drupal is used by hundreds of thousands of people and organizations to power an endless variety of sites including community web portals, discussion sites, corporate websites, academic websites, e-commerce applications, social networking sites and personal blogs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DrupalCampCT is a full-day, no-cost event including knowledgeable speakers, informative workshops, birds-of-a-feather sessions and invaluable opportunities to network with other Drupalists in and around the Nutmeg State - as well as bagels and coffee complements of our generous sponsors!  We expect attendees to be a good mix of experienced Drupalists and newcomers to Drupal; developers, themers and content managers; and consultants, corporate professionals and academics.  In the spirit of the unconference, we are very much open to ideas and welcome any folks who are interested the opportunity to schedule a session or suggest a session.  If you're interested in presenting a session or have problems that need to be solved and you would like to see someone address those problems at a session, register for DrupalCampCT and add your ideas.  At DrupalCamp you ask the questions and the experienced users provide the answers; at DrupalCamp you discover your solutions to your most pressing problems in a variety of venues - impromptu discussions, birds-of-a-feather groups and/or prepared presentations from those who have experience on a specific topic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to seeking ideas and proposals for speakers, workshops and birds-of-a-feather sessions, we seek help with organization of the conference, individual and corporate sponsors, and general suggestions for DrupalCampCT 2010 at our recently launched website: &lt;a href="http://drupalcampct.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://drupalcampct.o...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must register for DrupalCampCT at &lt;a href="http://drupalcampct.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://drupalcampct.o...&lt;/a&gt;.  Registration through meetup.com is not adequate.  Space is limited so register today and pass on news of our event to others that may be interested in attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional information is available by visiting our website or by sending email to rsvp (at) drupalcampct.org.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dr. Mark A. Friedman</member_name><member_id>6940951</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283131686000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Web Innovators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct-web-innovators</urlname><id>1364182</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>CT Web Innovators Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281370806000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drupal Camp Connecticut</name><id>14366592</id><headcount>125</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282996800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct-web-innovators/events/14366592/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/c/global_17121964.jpeg</photo_url></item>