<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roko Belic, multi award-winning director of the Academy Award&amp;reg; nominated &amp;ldquo;Genghis Blues&amp;rdquo; now brings us HAPPY, a film that sets out to answer these questions and more, taking us to over 14 countries, from the bayou of Louisiana to the desert of Namibia, from the beaches of Brazil to the villages of Okinawa. From a scientist scanning brains in his lab to a rickshaw puller in the streets of Kolkata, we learn amazing truths about happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HAPPY is a non-profit feature documentary that deals with many of the fundamental issues we face in today&amp;rsquo;s society. How do we balance the allure of money, fame and social status with our needs for good relationships, health and a sense of contentment? Through powerful interviews and a global journey the film seeks to share the wisdom found in traditional cultures and from the cutting edge science that is now, for the first time, exploring human happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to hearing from leading neuroscientists&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; and psychologists in the field, HAPPY explores personal stories from around the world. Can Manoj Singh, a rickshaw puller from the slums of Kolkata, India, who lives in a hut made of plastic bags with his family be just as happy as the average American? In fact, he is. What about Melissa Moody, the beautiful debutant mother of three who had a &amp;ldquo;perfect life&amp;rdquo; until the day she was run over by a truck? Disabled for 9 years and disfigured for life, amazingly she is happier now than before her accident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thehappymovie.com/"&gt;http://www.thehappymovie.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/HappyMovie"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/HappyMovie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost of movie ticket: $9 at RAW&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306542266000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305939380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy  ;-)</name><id>19154731</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306538100000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/19154731/</event_url></item>