<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 S Common St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.640900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Topsfield Public Library</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>6624642</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.949593</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm not the actual "host" per-se, Bob Scherer-Hoock is, but I'm hoping to make it this month. Bob's been hosting this for years, in the past he was renting space from a Church so needed to charge to cover, but recently has moved it to a public library so no longer a cost unless you wish to donate to the library.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info cut/pasted right from Bob's email reminder:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLACE: Topsfield Public Library Meeting Room. The Topsfield Library is at 1 South Common St. in Topsfield. South Common Street is a very short arc of a street between Main Street and High Street (Route 97) that is one-way and mainly serves as parking for the library. The library is in the center of the town - you can tell it is the center because right across the street are the Town Common, original parish church, Town Hall, and elementary school, which pretty much says center of a New England Town. The library's main entrance is on the right side of the building; and the meeting room is immediately on the right as you enter the library. In fact, the meeting room comes up so immediately that you don't have to look at a book if you don't want to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIME: 1 p.m. to 11 p.m. This is one hour shorter than last year, but the later start was necessary to get the library to agree to let us use the room after hours and to allow them to schedule the meeting room for morning uses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COST: There is no charge for our game sessions at the Topsfield Library. As a public building, we have been welcomed to use the meeting room for free so long as we abide by the building rules, are not disruptive, and promote a public interest (and the current librarian sees social gaming as a public interest). IT WOULD HOWEVER BE NICE if we can make a monthly donation to the library to show our thanks. To that end, I will place a covered shoe box near the doorway for anyone to drop in donations, and at the end of the evening I will leave it behind or on the circulation desk. As a public department, the library cannot accept cash donations directly, but cash can be channeled through the Friends of the Topsfield Library (checks, if you prefer to donate that way, can be made out to "Friends of the Topsfield Library". This is STRICTLY VOLUNTARY; I will not be checking who has or has not made a donation, and I will not be soliciting donations. I will just place the shoe box near the door for those who would like to thank the library in this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the South and West: At the intersection of Route 1, Route 128 north, and Interstate 95 in Peabody, travel north up either Route 1 or Interstate 95 (they parallel each other and cross a couple of times in Peabody and Danvers until splitting off for good at the Danvers-Topsfield line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If using Route 1, just stay on Route 1 north as it crosses I-95 in the Ferncroft neighborhood of Danvers. Just after the traffic light at North Street in Danvers, Route 1 becomes a two-lane road as it crosses into Topsfield. Follow Route 1 over hill and dale until you come to a long downhill just before the Topsfield Fairgrounds. At the bottom of the hill, just past a small bridge over the Ipswich River and across from the main parking entrance to the fairgrounds, turn left on to South Main Street. Follow South Main Street as it twists and turns; after a sweeping right curve it becomes Main Street and you will pass in front of a small (very small) shopping and banking district. The library (and South Common Street) is on the right just past the last of the shops/offices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If using Interstate 95, you can either get off at Exit 50 on to Route 1 north in the Ferncroft neighborhood of Danvers and follow the Route 1 directions above, or you can stay on I-95 to either Exit 51 or Exit 52. At either exit, turn right. The right turn off Exit 51 will put you on Endicott Street at Masconomet Regional High School; the right turn off Exit 52 will put you on Topsfield Road. Both roads lead to the same intersection and become Washington Street, heading east into the center of Topsfield right across from the library at the intersection of Washington Street and Route 97.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the North: Approach from Southbound Interstate 95 and use Exit 53A, which will leave you heading south on Route 97. Follow Route 97 into the center of Topsfield. At the intersection where Route 97 takes a left turn toward Beverly, the library will be just ahead on your left. Keep going straight (i.e. let 97 go off to the left), and South Common Street will be the next left (and parking at Proctor Elementary School will be on your left).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East/Southeast: People coming from the Gloucester, Beverly, Salem areas might want to come up Route 97 north from North Beverly to the center of Topsfield. At the center of Topsfield, where Route 97 goes to the right, turn left to access South Common Street or the Proctor School Parking lot. You may also just want to just get to the Route 128/Route 1/Interstate 95 intersection and head north from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Northwest: Getting to Topsfield from the North Andover/Andover area is a pain. You have to wind your way through Boxford, one of the easiest towns in the state in which to get lost (it really has no landmarks). Best advice is find a map or GPS and get to Main Street in Boxford. Use Main Street to get to the center of Boxford Village and turn east on to Topsfield Road. Follow Topsfield Road until it crosses I-95 at Exit 52, and stay on Topsfield road heading east. It will become Boxford Road at the Topsfield line, and then become Washington Street shortly after that, which leads into the center of Topsfield. Many people avoid Boxford altogether and go south to Route 128/I-95 and approach from that direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: South Common Street is a one-way street that arcs from Main Street to High Street (Route 97). There is parking for the library on both sides. However, it would be courteous to avoid parking as close as possible to the library entrance, as we will be parking long-term and the library prefers that the spaces close to the door to be available for people making quick stops at the library. So park either towards the end of the arc, or across Main Street in the Proctor Elementary School parking lot (that's where I plan to park). There is also some parking close to the library on either side of Main Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOISE: The library will be open until 5 p.m. on Saturdays. Please keep noise levels down during that time. Please, no electronic games that make sounds until after 5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FOOD: There is no refrigerator available, so I will no longer be bringing soda. However it is OK to bring food into the room. The only stipulation is that we pack out everything we pack in. I will be bringing large trash bags, and as long as we leave no trash behind, we're OK. That means we can probably still have a snack table, but people will have to bring their own bottled water or whatever. Note that the room is carpeted, so spills will be frowned upon and may even get us disinvited (but I honestly can't remember anyone ever spilling on the tile floor in Peabody, so I think this is a pretty neat group).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DINING OPTIONS: There are four places to eat/take out food in Topsfield, all within easy walking distance of the library. (I'm not counting the Dunkin Donuts out on Route 1. From farthest to nearest: 1) Day Break Cafe, 30 Main Street, in the Village Plaza, serves typical diner-style breakfast and lunches, but is only open until 2 p.m. Still, it might be worth stopping in before heading to the library; 2) Main Street Market, 19 Main Street, is a more upscale sandwich, salad, coffee, cheese, and wine store, with a changing menu, that is open until 6 p.m. on Saturdays, www.topsfieldmarket.com; 3) Topsfield House of Pizza, 32 Main Street, open to 9 p.m. is your typical pizza and sub shop, www.topsfieldhouseofpizza.com; 4) Alex's Roast Beef, Pizza, and Seafood, 53 Main Street, open to 10 p.m., only two doors down from the library, is like Topsfield House of Pizza but with more emphasis on roast beef sandwiches and subs than on pizza, with some fried seafood added in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RESTROOMS: Yes, the library has them, adult-size, separate men's and women's, across the hall from the meeting room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WINTER WEATHER: The library remains open through all but the most severe storms, and if the library is open, gaming is on. If the library is closed, gaming is off. I live close by and can ski over if necessary, so I'll be there. If there is a question, call the library at 978-887-1528 in the morning to see if it is open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HEAT: Yes, they have it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AIR CONDITIONING: Yes, they have that too - it is a climate-controlled building&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff M</member_name><member_id>4602649</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368332451000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Gamers</urlname><id>393834</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Greater Nashua Gamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368022520000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Board Gaming in Topsfield Saturday</name><id>118355032</id><headcount>22</headcount><duration>36000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368291600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Gamers/events/118355032/</event_url></item>