<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup costs</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Household Rainwater Collection:  Why, What and How. (and a good chance of having a short presentation by Wendy Garland from Maine DEP).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready for the mud season by harvesting water for use in irrigation and other activities.  We will discuss rain barrels, cisterns and possibly a preliminary talk about ponds in your residential landscape (in anticipation of a pond workshop in the Spring).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  This is going to be held at Pam's house - about 25 minutes from the Marginal Way Park &amp;amp; Ride.  ** I am opening up a CARPOOLING thread on the message board for people to connect on rides to Pam's House**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;saddr=marginal+way,portland+04101&amp;amp;daddr=29+Serenity+Ln,+Windham,+ME+04062&amp;amp;sll=43.73767,-70.339745&amp;amp;sspn=0.176615,0.31929&amp;amp;layer=&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=12&amp;amp;ll=43.7396,-70.341682&amp;amp;spn=0.17661,0.31929&amp;amp;om=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.google.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm searching for a good data source on local rainwater collection, but it looks like Portland receives an average of about 46 inches of precipitation each year.  If you lived in a house that had 20 ft x 30 ft footprint (600 square feet) and harvested water from your roof, that means ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;46 inches rainfall x 1/12th foot per inch = 3.83 feet rainfall&lt;br /&gt;3.83 feet rainfall x 600 square foot roof = 2300 cubic feet of water&lt;br /&gt;2300 cubic feet x 7.5 gal per cubic foot = 17,250 gallons of potential collection per year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Resources will be provided on where to purchase and/or how to make rainwater collections systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To avoid carb-loading for our POTLUCK, let's breakdown the list a bit:&lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with A-G bring bread or beverage&lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with H-M bring main or side dish to share&lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with N-S bring salad or veg or dessert&lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with T-Z bring whatever you want&lt;br /&gt;We'll rotate this list each month so you won't be stuck in a rut:)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1173997860000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1165599774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Maine Permaculture March Meetup</name><id>5315438</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1173825000000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/5315438/</event_url></item>