<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389534</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Center for Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>3436492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106071</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For those who missed the earlier showing of Reel Rock 7 in Arlington, here is another chance to see it and support a good cause at the same time. Join Climb for Cerebral Palsy as they host the Reel Rock Tour to raise money for United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston. Reel Rock is an exciting cinematic event where climbers and outdoors lovers come together to celebrate ultimate adventure filmmaking. The films this year include acclaimed climbers Chris Sharma, Conrad Anker, and Alex Honnold pushing their limits as they attempt to define the future of climbing. Brian Baldeck, Austin Whipple, Jared Villemaire, and Phillip Berenz -- the Climb for CP team -- will climb Mount Kilimanjaro in February 2012 to raise awareness and funds (with a goal of $30,000) for United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston. Phillip Berenz (the team leader) has cerebral palsy and will be only the third person with cerebral palsy to successfully climb Mount Kilimanjaro unassisted. Because this is a fundraising event, a majority of the proceeds will go directly to UCP of MetroBoston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film starts at 7:30pm, but the doors will open at 6:30pm so everyone can take some time to visit the sponsor tables (sponsor list will be release prior to the event).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets can be bought here: &lt;a href="http://reelrock7.brownpapertickets.com/"&gt;http://reelrock7.brownpapertickets.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting your tickets in advance is highly recommended in case it sells out.  Feel free to drop a line or RSVP if you're looking to meet up with folks at the showing, or just grab tickets, friends and go! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Center for Arts at the Armory, Somerville MA &lt;br /&gt;

Door opens: 6:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

Film starts: 7:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

Price of ticket: $20.00 &lt;br /&gt;

Amenities: A food and drink service area (beer, wine, and snacks) and restrooms will be open during the event. &lt;br /&gt;

Handicap accessible: Yes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deb</member_name><member_id>9443907</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352525559000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349894428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reel Rock Film Tour and Benefit For United Cerebral Palsy of MetroBoston</name><id>86393402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352503800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/86393402/</event_url></item>