<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;While the Bible may be the word of God, transcribed by divinely inspired  men, it does not provide a full (or even partial) account of the life  of Jesus Christ. Lucky for us that Christopher Moore presents a funny,  lighthearted satire of the life of Christ--from his childhood days up to  his crucifixion--in &lt;em&gt;Lamb: The Gospel According to Biff, Christ's Childhood Pal&lt;/em&gt;. This clever novel is surely blasphemy to some, but to others it's a coming-of-age story of the highest order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joshua (a.k.a. Jesus) knows he is unique and quite alone in his  calling, but what exactly does his Father want of him? Taking liberties  with ancient history, Moore works up an adventure tale as Biff and  Joshua seek out the three wise men so that Joshua can better understand  what he is supposed to do as Messiah. Biff, a capable sinner, tags along  and gives Joshua ample opportunities to know the failings and  weaknesses of being truly human. With a wit similar to Douglas Adams,  Moore pulls no punches: a young Biff has the hots for Joshua's mom,  Mary, which doesn't amuse Josh much: "Don't let anyone ever tell you  that the Prince of Peace never struck anyone." And the origin of the  Easter Bunny is explained as a drunken Jesus gushes his affection for  bunnies, declaring, "Henceforth and from now on, I decree that whenever  something bad happens to me, there shall be bunnies around."&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308926896000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307020147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lamb by Christopher Moore</name><id>20664101</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308871800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/20664101/</event_url></item>