<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Monument Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.461451</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monument Square</name><city>Concord</city><id>576772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.349414</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join me for a scenic ride starting from Concord Center, heading west to out to Groton / Lost Lake, and then back.  I did this loop a week ago, and it was so beautiful.  The water levels are exceptionally high and impressive after all the recent rain, which makes for some awe inspiring vistas.  We will Hop from Pond to Pond, never going more than a few miles without seeing some body of water.  The route is entirely on paved roads, many of them back roads with little traffic.  Some small areas will have steady traffic, but I have designed the route to minimize this as much as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?hl=en&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;msid=102779203779063114278.0004832cb5b3eef96282b&amp;amp;z=12" target="_blank"&gt;Here is a link to the route&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be faster paced ride with rolling hills, and a few climbs.  You MUST be able to maintain an &lt;u&gt;overall average pace of 15MPH&lt;/u&gt;.  (some areas we will be going as high as 20+mph, and much slower for the hills... 15MPH average).  Expect the route to last approx 3.5-4.5 hours depending on how many breaks we take.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/482869/Monument%20Sq%20Meet-Up%20Spot.jpg"&gt;Monument Square&lt;/a&gt; in Concord, MA.  Be there at 9:00am, where we can say hello as I hand out cue sheets and we will be on our way no later than 9:15am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each person should bring an extra tube that fits their bike, plenty of water, and it is a good idea to have some energy snacks to keep you going.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have my brown bike with blue wheels</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Ramos</member_name><member_id>4466935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271164027000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270664096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lost Lake - 40 Miles</name><id>13115483</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270990800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/13115483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/5/global_14205189.jpeg</photo_url></item>