<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Avenue of the Arts</address_2><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9300</phone><name>Museum of Fine Arts </name><city>Boston</city><id>500439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For those of you who can get Martin Luther King Jr. day off, come join me at the Museum of Fine Arts' open house. All galleries are free admission. Special events include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Spotlight Talks, 10 am–4 pm. Join MFA staff and volunteers for 10-minute presentations about art objects in Foster &amp;amp; Partners' new Art of the Americas Wing. Each talk begins in the galleries and focuses on one work of art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Gallery Tours: Introduction to MFA Collections, meet at Sharf Visitor Center, 11 am and 1 pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• A performance by the Jelani Bauman Quartet, noon, Shapiro Family Courtyard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• MFA Teen Arts Council and Boston Symphony Orchestra Teen Council classical music performances, 12:30-3 pm, Shapiro Family Courtyard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Short Film Program, 2 and 3 pm, Alfond Auditorium, G36&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Women of the World presentation, 3:30 pm, Remis Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since I imagine there'll be a long line to get in before the museum opens at 10 a.m., I'll try to be in line by 9:45 a.m. I'll be holding a Meetup sign, and I'll meet and greet guests in the lobby as soon as I get in. Around 10:15 I'll be heading to the new Arts of the Americas wing (you should check it out if you haven't already; it's awesome!) to hear the spotlight talks, and you're welcome to join me or do something else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, call me on my cell phone at 617-692-0036. (However, I'll have to turn my phone off at 10:15 before I go into the galleries.) Hope to see you on the Avenue of the Arts!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting in the line to get in by 9:45 a.m., holding a Meetup sign, then I'll meet and greet guests in the lobby as soon as I get in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd</member_name><member_id>3530398</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295352785000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294848709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MFA Free Open House on Martin Luther King Jr. Day</name><id>16021919</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295275500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/16021919/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/1/global_20760801.jpeg</photo_url></item>