<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>across from Roxbury Crossing Orange Line station</address_2><address_1>1350 Tremont St, cor. New Dudley St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02120</zip><lat>42.331410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 541-3535</phone><name>Reggie Lewis Center</name><city>Roxbury Crossing</city><id>745528</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094400</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From Kevin:  this is a great event that has been expanded to two days this year.  Let’s try to coordinate some car pooling and get a large turnout from our local group.  You will not be disappointed!  Read on for the e-mail I received from BVS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Boston Vegetarian Society, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many new people have joined our email list since the below announcement was sent out last winter. As we enter the countdown weeks to our big Festival, we send this again, with a request to help us publicize the event, and reply if you can volunteer for the festival! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great news! We are excited to announce that we have expanded our 14th Annual Boston Vegetarian Food Festival this fall to a two-day event! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonveg....&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are thrilled to have the opportunity to enlarge the event, while staying at the Reggie Lewis Athletic Center and keeping admission free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are hopeful that expanding the Festival to two days will allow more people to attend while reducing the overcrowding experienced over the past few years. Attendance has grown each year, and some have recommended we move to a larger site or charge admission to thin the crowd. The Reggie Lewis Center has worked very well for us in lots of ways, and it's location brings us a diverse audience along with a prize location opposite a T stop, and free parking as well. Our investigation into larger sites raised issues that made us appreciate our current site all the more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our enduring ability to offer the Festival for free is part of our outreach mission. Free admission draws in curious non-vegetarians who would not pay to attend a vegetarian event. It makes it easy for veg*ns to bring non-veg guests with them to learn about the wide variety of delicious plant-based foods readily available in the marketplace, and the whys and hows of going veg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are happy that now people who cannot attend on Saturdays will have the option to attend on Sunday! We have booked some extraordinary and exciting speakers, which will be announced shortly. We hope to split the crowd by having some speakers present on both days, and to draw people to Sunday by having some stellar speakers on Sunday only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are working to provide a comfortable, enjoyable environment while expanding the educational and outreach potential of the Festival. A two-day event means we will need many more volunteers! So save the dates and hit reply to say that you can volunteer! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The BVFF Organizing Committee:Julie Correia, Kevin Coyne, Andrea Eisenberg, Maysoon Hamdiyyah, David Havelick, Evelyn Kimber, Mark Patrick, Beverly Rich, Blakely Sullivan, Jeoff Tardiff, Bronwyn Williams, Al Willis &lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonveg....&lt;/a&gt;. --Boston Vegetarian Society, P. O. Box 38-1071, Cambridge, MA 02238-1071&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin</member_name><member_id>7947968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257257657000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254970437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>14th Annual Boston Vegetarian Food Festival </name><id>11577601</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257084000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/11577601/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/2/global_9211362.jpeg</photo_url></item>