<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Friends gathered at the Peace Abbey once more, and we shared our feelings and hopes around Chapters 406 of Sack's work, The Dignity of Difference. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Sacks says, &amp;quot;I want to understand the nature of the politics of insecurity, because it is this, more than anything, that gives rise to political and religious extremism and to the kind of authoritarian populism that threatens free societies.&amp;quot; There is this sense that in the breakdown of traditional institutions and the experience of globalization, that we feel as though we are no longer in control with the destiny of our lives, that there are forces bigger than us that affect us radically and that there is not much we can do about it. In the end, it is our moral vision and the belief that we all make a difference in the face of great sweeping movements in the economy and other aspects of our lives. This is the great mission of all religions in the world today, to empower us to create a sense of social solidarity and to close the gaping gulf between the rich and poor. Our moral vision, no matter what faith, springs from compassion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next meeting we will be looking at Chapters 7-9. See you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also have a special blog for our book club you may wish to to add your own comments in between meetings as you are reading. Feel free to click comment on the first posting and let us know what are you are thinking. See it &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/912/pages/www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also have a blog dedicated to contemporary interfaith visual arts and poetry called &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/912/pages/www.sacredartpoet.wordpress.com"&gt;Sacred Bearings&lt;/a&gt;. For those who may be interested, feel free to comment on the postings. If you wish to post art and/or poetry, send them me. I will post them for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy and Fr. Joe Matteucig&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209499557000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205701343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club April Meeting</name><id>7545366</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209326400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/7545366/</event_url></item>