<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you've been using Cairngorm, the Adobe Flex framework for Flex and AIR, for any length of time. You may have wished there were some better features to the framework. Well, thankfully the folks at  Universal Mind had the same thought and developed the UM Extensions for Cairngorm. The extensions are open-source under BSD licensing and will greatly benefit your Cairngorm code.Thomas Burleson from Universal Mind will present this month on the extensions and how to use them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The project link to download the extensions and the documentation can be found at..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/flexcairngorm/" target="_blank"&gt;http://code.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Common Cairngorm myths can also be a fun read..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/flexcairngorm/wiki/CairngormMyths" target="_blank"&gt;http://code.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Burleson is a Universal Mind principal architect for Flex, Coldfusion, and Java web solutions. With over 20 years development and leadership experience, he has delivered applications and custom business solutions for numerous commerical and vertical markets. He has significant experience with user-interfaces, database and software architectures, product delivery, and technical leadership and mentoring. Most recently he lead the development efforts for the online Flex applications at Sherwin-Williams; now available for public use. He has also lead development efforts to create Flex-based CRM tools for clients in the health and manufacturing markets.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236813853000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232744660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UM Extensions for Cairngorm</name><id>9587553</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234915200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/9587553/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/f/global_5719263.jpeg</photo_url></item>