<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website. starting at Glencliff Trailhead Back to here hike 0.40 mi/17 min/+183 ft on the Glencliff Trail The trail leaves the road, passes a gate and enters a pasture, and soon crosses a small brook on a bridge. It joins a farm road that ascends from the parking area, then crosses a brook, follows a cart track along the left edge of a field, and enters the woods, where the Hurricane Trail immediately diverges right (east). to the junction of Hurricane Trail hike 2.60 mi/2 hr 42 min/+2785 ft on the Glencliff Trail The Glencliff Trail ascends moderately on a logging road that gradually fades away, crosses several small brooks, and passes a restricted outlook from a blowdown patch. Soon the trail swings right, going straight up the slope, and it becomes quite steep, passing a talus slope that offers good views to the west. At the top of the ridge, it levels and reaches the junction with a spur path (sign) that leads right, to the open summit of South Peak. In a few more steps, it enters the Moosilauke Carriage Rd.; for the summit, turn left. to the junction of Moosilauke Carriage Road and South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur hike 0.90 mi/38 min/+344 ft on the Moosilauke Carriage Road Then the Glencliff Trail enters from the left; a few steps along the Glencliff Trail, a spur trail leads left to South Peak, a fine viewpoint. The old road, now part of the AT, continues along the ridge, with a narrow fringe of trees on each side. Then it reaches the treeline and ascends the windswept ridge to the summit. to Mt Moosilauke Totals Distance 3.90 mi Time 3 hr 37 min Elev Gain +3348 ft Elev Loss -36 ft Elev Change +3312 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.90 mi/38 min/-344 ft on the Moosilauke Carriage Road The Moosilauke Carriage Road starts at the summit of Moosilauke and descends the windswept ridge down to treeline. It continues on an old road, now part of the AT, along the ridge, with a narrow fringe of trees on each side. It then reaches the Glencliff Trail which diverges to the right. A few steps along the Glencliff Trail, a spur trail leads left to South Peak, a fine viewpoint. to the junction of Glencliff Trail and South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+77 ft on the South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur Totals Distance 5.00 mi Time 4 hr 23 min Elev Gain +3449 ft Elev Loss -404 ft Elev Change +3044 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 0.20 mi/8 min/-77 ft on the South Peak, Mt Moosilauke spur to the junction of Glencliff Trail and Moosilauke Carriage Road hike 2.60 mi/2 hr 42 min/-2785 ft on the Glencliff Trail From the Carriage Road, just below South Peak, the Glencliff Trail begins. A spur path (sign) leads to the open summit of South Peak. The Glencliff trail leaves the ridge passing a talus slope that offers good views to the west, descending quite steeply. It then swings right and descends straight down the slope. It passes a restricted outlook from a blowdown patch, crosses several small brooks and begins to descend along an old logging road. to the junction of Hurricane Trail hike 0.40 mi/17 min/-183 ft on the Glencliff Trail The Hurricane Trail diverges to the left (southeast) and the trail then leaves the woods and follows a cart track along the right edge of an open field. It crosses a brook and joins a farm road that descends toward the parking area. It crosses a small brook on a bridge, enters a pasture, and passes through a gate at the road. to Glencliff Trailhead Totals Distance 8.20 mi Time 7 hr 30 min Elev Gain +3466 ft Elev Loss -3466 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>WE WILL BE IN A SILVER SUBARU LEGACY</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1336229253000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331743971000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOOSILAUKEE VIA GLENCLIFF TRAIL</name><id>56335412</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336224600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/56335412/</event_url></item>