<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Broadway </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06460</zip><lat>41.192846</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Walnut Beach </name><city>Milford</city><id>1023341</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.083772</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sun Aug 5th - 11:30 AM - 2:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

The HellCats Band- Rocking versions of your favorite tunes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sun Aug 5th - 4:00 PM - 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;

Locomotion - 9 Piece Band with 3 Horns - Top 40 and Classic Dance Tunes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Walnut Beach Where the sand meets the sky.HomeWelcome to Walnut BeachMembership ApplicationWalnut Beach HistoryWalnut Beach BusinessesWalnut Beach BoardwalkWBA Meetings2012 Holiday PartyWBA Members OnlyBy-LawsWBA MinutesWB Enhancement Boundaries2012 Arts Festival2012 Festival SponsorsFestival Sponsorship Form2012 Exhibitor Applicat'nVendor Hospitality Letter2010 Arts Festival VideoStowe Farm Arts Center2012 Summer ConcertsStudent Art ContestArt Contest WinnersPress Release for Winners2012 5K Race5K Race Route Map5K Race SponsorshipCalendar of EventsKite Day2012 Walnut Beach CleanupHalloween Pumpkin PartyHurricane Irene DamageContact UsDirectionsThe 14th Annual Walnut Beach &lt;br /&gt;

Arts Festival&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, August 5, 2012 - 10:00 AM to 5:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walnut Beach, Milford, CT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

OPEN CALL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Who: Walnut Beach Arts/Crafts Festival &lt;br /&gt;

 What: Artists and Crafters Wanted &lt;br /&gt;

Where: Walnut Beach, East Broadway &amp;amp; Viscount Drive &lt;br /&gt;

 When: Sunday, August 5, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Join us for our 14th Annual Walnut Beach Arts/Crafts Festival, Sunday, August 5, 2012 on the green across from Walnut Beach in Milford. It is anticipated that this will be one of the best years yet. In addition to our local CT artists, there will be artists coming from Rhode Island, New York, MA and further. &lt;br /&gt;

 We're seeking all types of art including but not limited to: painting, woodworking, metalwork, pottery, ceramics, clothing, jewelry, quilting, music, food products, etc. Since this is a juried festival, all arts and crafts must be original. &lt;br /&gt;

 We're pleased to offer free parking, free coffee and doughnuts for vendors, bathroom breaks throughout the day and 'fast lanes' for vendors at the food stations. &lt;br /&gt;

 To be sure we draw the crowds, the Event is being promoted in: Connecticut Magazine, Yankee Magazine, Milford Magazine, Milford Chamber of Commerce, TV channels 12 &amp;amp; 8, Radio Broadcasting, Local Billboard Advertising, CT Culture &amp;amp; Special Events Guide, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To reserve your space, complete the Exhibitor Application under the 2012 Arts Festival Link at the top of this page and return it with your check amount according to the date it is received, to the address below the application. Spaces will be given on a first-come, first-served basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Vendor and general festival questions, please call: &lt;br /&gt;

Tyyné Catapano 203-882-9453 &lt;br /&gt;

 VOLUNTEERS ARE ALWAYS WELCOME!!!! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE OF EVENTS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 AM: Registration opens for the Walnut Beach 5K Race. &lt;br /&gt;

 Join us at the WB Pavilion to register for the 5th annual Walnut Beach 5K Race. &lt;br /&gt;

 Free Ice Cream will be given to every runner/walker. There’s a free kid’s run at &lt;br /&gt;

 8:00 AM. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Where: Under the Walnut Beach Pavilion. &lt;br /&gt;

 8:00 AM: Kids Race begins. &lt;br /&gt;

 8:30 AM: Walnut Beach 5K Race begins. &lt;br /&gt;

 10:00 AM to 10:15 AM: Opening Ceremony. Winner of Wall of Art contest is unveiled. &lt;br /&gt;

 The National Anthem will be sung by Wendy Terenzio and after that a message &lt;br /&gt;

 from the dignitaries and the winner of the Wall of Art contest will be announced. &lt;br /&gt;

 The student art contest, now in its 14th year invites the winner of best in show to &lt;br /&gt;

 paint a mural to be added to our wall of art. Come see this year’s winner as well &lt;br /&gt;

 as murals from past festivals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: The Walnut Beach Green at Viscount Drive &amp;amp; East Broadway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10:15 AM to 11:30 AM: TBD &lt;br /&gt;

 10:30 AM: Antique Car Parade down Viscount Drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1:15 PM to 3:00 PM: TBD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3:15 PM to 5:00 PM (closing): TBD &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ArtFairCalendar.com: Fine Art Fairs and Craft Show Event Listings &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Free art show and craft fairs calendar and email list for art festivals across the U.S. Join our free art fair email list!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE WALNUT BEACH &lt;br /&gt;

ARTS FESTIVAL &lt;br /&gt;

WOULD NOT BE &lt;br /&gt;

POSSIBLE &lt;br /&gt;

WITHOUT &lt;br /&gt;

OUR SPONSORS &lt;br /&gt;

AND THEIR &lt;br /&gt;

COMMITMENT TO &lt;br /&gt;

OUR COMMUNITY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344252620000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343824146000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WALNUT BEACH ARTS FESTIVAL AND BANDS</name><id>75826122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344196800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/75826122/</event_url></item>