<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 East Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06702</zip><lat>41.555586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.987.7888</phone><name>Palace Theater</name><city>Waterbury</city><id>1142026</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.039742</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;HAIRSPRAY with the CT Theatre Group* Thursday JAN 7, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Winner of the 2003 Tony Award for Best Musical:&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Musical&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Book of a Musical&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Original Score (Music and Lyrics) Written for the Theatre&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Performance by a Leading Actor in a Musical (Harvey Fierstein)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Performance by a Leading Actress in a Musical (Marissa Jaret Winokur)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Performance by a Featured Actor in a Musical (Dick Latessa)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Costume Design (William Ivey Long)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Direction of a Musical (Jack O'Brien)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Performance by a Featured Actor in a Musical (Corey Reynolds) (nominee)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Scenic Design (nominee)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Lighting Design (nominee)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Choreography (nominee)&lt;br /&gt;· Tony Award for Best Orchestration (nominee)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Palace Theater&lt;br /&gt;100 East Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Waterbury, CT 06702 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's 1962, and pleasantly plump Baltimore teen Tracy Turnblad has only one desire - to dance on the popular Corny Collins Show. When her dream comes true, Tracy is transformed from social outcast to sudden star, but she must use her newfound power to vanquish the reigning Teen Queen, win the affections of heartthrob Link Larkin and integrate a TV network - all without denting her 'do! Be sure not to miss Hairspray!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You name will be added to the CT Theatre Group Will Call list &lt;br /&gt;- pick up your tickets at the Will Call window &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet before and after the show,&lt;br /&gt;join us and other Arts and Theatre Fans from the CT Theatre Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location and times will be emailed to CT Theatre Group ticket holders &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· Questions or info - Call (860) 987-7888&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· TICKETS: $65.50/ $55.50/ $50.50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· BUY ONLINE AND GET OUR GROUP DISCOUNT&lt;br /&gt;· &lt;br /&gt;· Advance Tickets Only $40 &lt;br /&gt;· &lt;br /&gt;· &lt;br /&gt;· USE CREDIT, DEBIT or GIFT CARD- you will be emailed your receipt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pick up your ticket(s) at the Will Call window&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling I-84 West &lt;br /&gt;Take the Union Street exit - Exit 22 - toward Downtown Waterbury. Turn left onto Union Street and then take the second right onto South Elm Street. At the first traffic light, turn left onto Scovill Street. The entrance to the Scovill Street parking garage will be on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling I-84 East &lt;br /&gt;Take the Baldwin Street/Downtown Waterbury exit - Exit 22. At second light, turn left onto South Main Street. Proceed straight after the first traffic light and turn right onto Scovill Street. The entrance to the Scovill Street parking garage will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rte. 8 North or South&lt;br /&gt;Merge onto I-84 East via Exit 31 toward Hartford and follow directions for Traveling I-84 East as listed above.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE HAVE A VERY LIMITED NUMBER OF TICKETS IN THE CT THEATRE GROUP SECTION&lt;br /&gt;THIS EVENT WILL SELL OUT - GET YOUR TICKET NOW &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your tickets here, visit &lt;a href="http://www.CTTheatreGroup.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.CTTheatreG...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 987-7888&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Pick up your tickets at the Will Call window, the CT Theatre Group will meet before and after the show  *  Meeting Location and times will be emailed to CT Theatre Group ticket holders </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Connecticut Theatre Group Events</member_name><member_id>8868299</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263083780000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260926479000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HAIRSPRAY * Thursday JAN 7, 2010 at the Palace Theatre with the CT Theatre Group</name><id>12093261</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262910600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/12093261/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/f/global_12264559.jpeg</photo_url></item>