<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District</address_2><address_1>184 High Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.356556</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-292-4695</phone><name>Howl at the Moon</name><city>Boston</city><id>1342099</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's Saturday night in Boston! Don't stay in with your cat and watch Lord of the Rings...Come out and mingle! (Frodo gets the ring the to Mordor, sorry).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get out and make some new friends! No age limits, no rules, just chill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Howl at the Moon is always fun and everyone had a blast last time. The music is the best and we always have a good time (you can make your own dance circles and jam to Bon Jovi, Elton John and every single other artist you've ever loved).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cover:&lt;/strong&gt; The cover stars at 6PM and it's 10 dollars. I'm getting there around 5:15ish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Line:&lt;/strong&gt; The line forms very quickly and goes around the block. I recommend getting there early and having a drink till the show stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dating:&lt;/strong&gt; This is not a singles event. It is a fun, summertime event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Texting Me:&lt;/strong&gt; A lot of you have my number by now, please do not text me to ask if people are there yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Website:&lt;/strong&gt; Please visit &lt;a href="http://www.howlatthemoon.com/locations/location-boston"&gt;Howl at the Moon's website&lt;/a&gt; to see what it's all about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Generally, we try to occupy the left corner of the bar. When you walk in, just head to the left by the windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes&lt;/strong&gt;: Please check this right before you leave the house. I might have to move the venue the day of if they inform me that the place has been rented or something (as of right now, it's on).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Posting:&lt;/strong&gt; Copy this, create an event, and post this on your FB page. Invite your friends. The more the merrier!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Enter the bar, go to the left corner by the windows</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341707994000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341002461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Night Social: Live Music and Dancing</name><id>71324712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341695700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/71324712/</event_url></item>