<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Several members suggested going back to Haveli India, since I missed it I'll be enjoyning their food for the first time.  The website is: &lt;a href="http://www.haveliindia.com/haveli_india.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.haveliindi...&lt;/a&gt;  I think we should dine and discuss affairs of state in this Haveli on April Fool's Day! So who in the state has had affairs?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I HAVE CHANGED THIS RESERVATION TO 3 TABLES OF 10 EACH (30 guests) BECAUSE IT IS SO POPULAR!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, I will collect $1.00 from each person - but will donate the money to FoodShare this time.  You may donate as much as you'd like for this worthy cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a little blurb abut it:&lt;br /&gt;Havelis developed in India in ancient times as royal houses where Royal guests would stay and be entertained. In later eras they would also become merchant homes or homes of the wealthy. But, their initial evolution was where the royal families and selected ministers got together in a congenial environment to discuss affairs of state, as they dined and were entertained. The custom was for hundreds of the best cooks and entertainers to be brought from around the state to serve the royal families and their guests. The entertainment and the food was always the best the state had to offer. And because of the number of cooks they were known to try new and creative dishes to distinguish themselves before the royal family.  It is because of this beginning that Haveli's over time became known as keepers of Indian traditions and cuisines.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation under "Meetup/Betsy"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy</member_name><member_id>3384225</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239751085000</updated><rating><average>4.82000017166</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236643624000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HAVELI INDIA  04/01/09 7:00PM</name><id>9919082</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238626800000</time><rsvp_limit>32</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/9919082/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/c/global_2456236.jpeg</photo_url></item>