<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 175</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03223</zip><lat>43.830360</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 603- 726-3813</phone><name>Campton Historical Society</name><city>Campton</city><id>1251302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.641372</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The White Mountain Huts - Past and Future Presentation&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;hosted by the New Hampshire Humanities Council&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who did not have the opportunity to attend this excellent presentation back in October, here is your chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allen Koop, Visiting Professor of History, Dartmouth College, will give a presentation about the Appalachian Mountain Club's unique system of backcountry huts.  Learn how the huts and their people have formed a world apart, a mountain society with its own history, traditions and legends.  I highly recommend professor Koops presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: no Event Organizer will be present for this Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the Old Town Hall, Campton Hollow, Campton,NH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NORTH: When traveling from northern New Hampshire The directions to the Old Town Hall are as follows- From Interstate 93 South take exit 27 Blair Bridge West Campton. Turn left at exit and proceed to intersection of Blair Rd. and Rte. 3. Continue straight crossing Blair Bridge (Covered Bridge #4 1) to the intersection of Blair Rd, and Rte. 175. Turn left onto Rte. 175N and proceed a half mile past the Congregational Church to the Town Hall on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOUTH: When traveling from southern New Hampshire The directions to the Old Town Hall are as follows: From Interstate 93 North take exit 27 Blair Bridge West Campton. Turn right at exit and proceed to intersection of Blair Rd. and Rte. 3. Continue straight crossing Blair Bridge (Covered Bridge #41) to the intersection of Blair Rd. and Rte. 175. Turn left onto Rte. 175N and proceed a half mile past the Congregational Church to the Town Hall on your left. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274150417000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271804264000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slideshow: The White Mountain Huts - Past &amp; Future Presentation</name><id>13241446</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274139000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13241446/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/1/global_11024049.jpeg</photo_url></item>