<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The 3.30pm showtime is&amp;nbsp;confirmed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Runtime: 2hr. 26 min.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Director: &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/stevenspielberg/overview/p112325"&gt;Steven Spielberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Cast: &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/jeremyirvine/overview/p683140"&gt;Jeremy Irvine&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/petermullan/overview/p51229"&gt;Peter Mullan&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/emilywatson/overview/p221329"&gt;Emily Watson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/nielsarestrup/overview/p2159"&gt;Niels Arestrup&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/davidthewlis/overview/p70493"&gt;David Thewlis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333 ; font-size : small"&gt;Written By:&lt;a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/celebrity/lee_hall/"&gt;Lee Hall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;War Horse&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reviewed by David Edelstein, New York Magazine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;In 1982, the British author Michael Morpurgo wrote War Horse, a book for younger readers that portrayed the suffering of World War I&amp;mdash;on all sides&amp;mdash;through the eyes of a horse. Joey, as he&amp;rsquo;s called, begins on a farm in Devon but is conscripted by British forces, seized by Germans after a bloody battle, adopted by a Belgian girl, taken back by Germans &amp;hellip; and on and on, through 1918, when the horse ends up amid the corpse-strewn trenches of no-man&amp;rsquo;s-land. Despite the barbarous milieu, Morpurgo&amp;rsquo;s prose is modest and uninflected. You discover, for example, that a noble officer has been killed only when Joey realizes that he is riderless. In 2007, Nick Stafford developed a stage version in which Joey was a life-size puppet with beautifully delineated musculature. The puppets, their handlers in view, added a distance that was occasionally at odds with the sentimental story. But it was terrific theater.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Steven Spielberg&amp;rsquo;s film of War Horse has no distancing devices or puppets and returns Morpurgo&amp;rsquo;s novel to its roots. To say it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;family film&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;for kids 13 and up&amp;mdash;is no slight. The horror isn&amp;rsquo;t minimized, but Spielberg pulls back from the grisly bombardment of Saving Private Ryan. He aims for a limpid, old-fashioned style that puts him firmly in the &amp;ldquo;square&amp;rdquo; category beside contemporaries with their jittery cameras and splatter (most of them imitating Private Ryan). It&amp;rsquo;s the restraint that makes War Horse remarkable. Spielberg shows you enough to understand that what you&amp;rsquo;re watching&amp;mdash;machine guns, mustard gas, bodies stretching into the distance&amp;mdash;was unprecedented. And amid the incomprehensible slaughter, it&amp;rsquo;s a horse that reminds these warriors of their humanity. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Said horse is purchased at auction by the drunken farmer Narracott (Peter Mullan) after a bidding war with his landlord, the upshot of which is that there&amp;rsquo;s no money for rent. Bloody paradoxical victory! As often happens in Spielberg&amp;rsquo;s work, it&amp;rsquo;s the sensitive son, Albert (Jeremy Irvine), who must take over for his father, and the film&amp;rsquo;s first section affirms the boy&amp;rsquo;s belief that this animal is special. With the troops&amp;rsquo; departure, the point of view passes to Joey and his new master (Tom Hiddleston), a gentleman captain who engages in a friendly riding contest with a major (Benedict Cumberbatch) atop a black steed called Topthorn. Tallyho, pip, pip, death to the Kaiser! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The British have no notion of what awaits them, and their cavalry charge through the tall wheat is both lyrical and ghastly. Spielberg proves that &amp;ldquo;aestheticizing&amp;rdquo; horror doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean cheapening or falsifying it. When two teenagers are later executed, the camera rises behind a turning windmill, one of its blades obscuring the instant of death. It&amp;rsquo;s among the most merciful depictions of murder I&amp;rsquo;ve seen, yet still unspeakable. It casts a shadow over the respite that follows in a Belgian farmhouse where a girl (Celine Buckens) lives with her embittered grandfather (the extraordinary Niels Arestrup). The old man knows he can&amp;rsquo;t protect the child, that war will take everything. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Spielberg has been ridiculed for shooting his actors from below against impossibly Spielbergian skies and a denouement that lays the love on copiously. But there&amp;rsquo;s nothing simpleminded about how he uses movie magic, as a spell to dispel nihilism, to save us from the worst of ourselves by summoning up the best. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #060606"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #060606"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll remain inside the theater after the movie holding a Meetup sign.  Afterwards, we'll go for a post-film discussion at a nearby restaurant.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caroline </member_name><member_id>10711981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326302114000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325514704000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>War Horse</name><id>46251902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326054600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/46251902/</event_url></item>