<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a film not to be missed for those interested in Bollywood films.  Reception during the intermission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cinestudio and the English Department of Trinity College are proud to co-sponsor a special event introducing Prakash Younger, Trinity's new film professor, to Trinity students and faculty and the Hartford community! After the (rare 35mm film) screening of the classic Om Shanti Om, Prof. Younger will give a short talk on the hugely popular phenomenon that is India's Bollywood. Om (Shahrukh Khan) is a young movie extra working in the 1970s' era Bollywood industry while dreaming of making it big and winning the heart of the famous actress Shanti (Deepika Padukone). While the twists and turns of the reincarnation-inspired plot are too numerous to list, we promise a wholly satisfying movie experience – including one blow-out musical number featuring 31 of Bollywood’s greatest stars.&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a reception during the intermission!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;162 min. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting outside on the bench.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273515137000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272717315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Classic Bollywood Film - Om Shanti Om </name><id>13348046</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273341600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/13348046/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>