<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>781-740-6665</address_2><address_1>Martins Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.253452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781.740.7233</phone><name>World's End</name><city>Hingham</city><id>1085516</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.871658</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As always this event is rain or shine... 90% of the time when they say it's going to rain it doesn't and when it does it's a drizzle. So just plan on going. And you live in New England for gosh sakes! Invest in&amp;nbsp;a gortex jacket, wool socks, and good footwear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we'll take a rain, snow or shine walk at Hingham's Worlds End then we'll try the&amp;nbsp;Hingham Beer&amp;nbsp;Works&amp;nbsp;for Drinks and Appetizers. Last time we did Alma Nove - let's try something new.&amp;nbsp; I will post separate events for the walk and the restaurant just in case some can can only make it to one of the other. Please respond to both so I can make accurate reservations at the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes World&amp;rsquo;s End a special place?  &lt;br /&gt;We think it&amp;rsquo;s the tree-lined carriage paths and sweeping views of the Boston skyline, only 15 miles away. The 251-acre coast-scape includes rocky shores, broad hillsides, and open fields bracketed by pockets of woodlands. The property is ideal for walking, picnicking, jogging, horseback riding, cross-country skiing, or simply enjoying nature and the outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The retreating glacier helped create the geology of Boston Harbor, including the islands and the four spoon-shaped hills (called drumlins) that comprise World&amp;rsquo;s End. This landscape also features saltwater marshes, meadows, woodlands, and granite ledges covered with red cedars and blueberry thickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a member of the Trustees of the Reservations and they have great properties. I suggest that if you like their properties please become a member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/worlds-end.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustee" target="_blank"&gt;...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustee" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustee" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hingham Beer Works - &lt;a href="http://beerworks.net/home/index.html"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://beerworks.net/home/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://beerworks.net/home/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://beerworks.net/home/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://beerworks.net/home/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to the back parking lot and look for the surly group hanging around a Black Toyota Pickup</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298834412000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's damn good fun...</why><group><who>BMers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BMSocial</urlname><id>1333853</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Metro Hike Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297535715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World's End Hike Hingham - Then Hingham Beer Works</name><id>16541171</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298829600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BMSocial/events/16541171/</event_url></item>