<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I am going to organize two events with the West of Boston over 40 meet-up group on Sat. March 6. &lt;br /&gt;First, will be an 11:00 AM Dog Walk @ Weston Reservoir. &lt;br /&gt;Next, will be a 1:00 PM Nature Walk @ Walden Pond. &lt;br /&gt;I wish dogs were welcome at Walden Pond, but they are not... ;-( &lt;br /&gt;Please join me for the Dog Walk if you are available, or both hikes if you are up for it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Weston Reservoir is located on Ash Street, between Rt. 20 and Rt. 30. There is limited parking on the street, near the begining of the trail and there are no facilities. However, dogs are welcome. The trail is about 2 miles around the fenced-in reservoir. The trail has some ice, snow, and mud, and some dry spots through the tall evergreens. Participants should dress accordingly, with proper footwear, and outerwear for the day's weather forecast. The event will happen, regardless of weather conditions, rain, snow, or shine. (We hope for shine!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a description of the place, excerpted from: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wickedlocal.com/weston/news/x1817205484" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wickedloca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Located on Ash Street, roughly halfway between Boston Post Road (Route 20) and South Avenue (Route 30) in Weston, there are two areas to park. One is along the street, directly across from the reservoir. The other is just off the road across a bridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people park along the street and cross over to the grassy area near the start of the main trail. Dogs, happy to be out and about, can frequently be seen bounding about here as their masters call them to move along. As long as they respond to voice commands, dogs are allowed off their leashes.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will depart on the dog walk shortly after 11:00 AM to be able to complete the walk in time to get to the Walden Pond Nature walk at 1:00 PM the same day. Bring trail snacks and water according to your needs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to meeting some new friends West of Boston!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeri &lt;br /&gt;857-939-0265 cell&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At large parking area near begining of trail</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268064506000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gay Women Over 40</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>lgbtfriends-212</urlname><id>1155810</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>WEST OF BOSTON OVER 40 GAY WOMENS MEET-UP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267833766000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weston Reservoir Dog Walk</name><id>12796695</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267891200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lgbtfriends-212/events/12796695/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/7/0/global_4210720.jpeg</photo_url></item>