<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here's an encore edition of the Creative Writing Workout we offered in February. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who *have* taken the Workout before: We'll continue to build on the projects you started in the first session. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who *haven't* taken the Workout before: Read on (and take a look at the feedback from the previous session) to see what you're in for! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATE/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Sunday, April 19, from 1 to 5 p.m. PLEASE ARRIVE BY 12:30 (doors open at noon) so that we can start on time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WORKSHOP DESCRIPTION:&lt;/b&gt; Creative writing is an activity that will complement--and maybe even enhance--your other artistic endeavors. In this non-threatening, low-stress workshop, we'll try several easy exercises designed to unleash your creativity and get your words flowing. Our focus is on personal expression in a supportive atmosphere, so you'll share what you've written only if you so desire, and no one (not even you) will be allowed to critique your work unless you request feedback. (Doesn't that sound liberating?) No previous writing experience is necessary, and one exercise will probably include a sketching element. You'll leave with a list of writing resources and ideas for continuing your writing practice on your own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt; Any 18+ member of the NE ATC+ Meetup or the Altered Art/Assemblage Meetup. For everyone's comfort and enjoyment, we're limiting this workshop to active participants; please leave kids and significant others at home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;VENUE:&lt;/b&gt; ArtStudio 360 in Holliston, (note: NOT at our usual venue in Wellesley). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Our bright, pleasant studio offers free parking. It has plenty of table space for writing and access to spring water, a refrigerator, a microwave and a restroom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; A couple of pens (or pencils) that you like.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; A notebook--any kind that works for you. (If possible, don't plan to write on a laptop computer even if that's how you normally write--these exercises are all about putting pen to paper.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; One ore more photographs that have meaning to you, preferably with at least one person in them.&lt;br /&gt;The photo is a tool for a writing exercise, so it doesn't have to be high-quality. But it should be a hard copy (i.e., not digital), even if it's just a printout. If it's fragile, you may wish to bring a copy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP&lt;/b&gt;: RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATION:&lt;/b&gt; If your plans change, switch your RSVP from &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; ASAP. If you need to cancel the day of the workshop, please call Anne as soon as possible--phone number will be listed in reminder e-mail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the ArtStudio team needs to cancel the workshop due to weather or for any other reason, we'll post a message here AND e-mail or call anyone who's RSVP'd as far in advance as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And if you can't make it this time, don't fret -- we'll offer this and other workshops in the coming months.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Anne</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241029108000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237120129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creative Writing Workout -- the Encore </name><id>9957501</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240158600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/9957501/</event_url></item>