<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;WWW.EASTERNMASSREIA.COM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This Thursday Febuary 12th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOLIDAY INN Rockland &lt;br /&gt;929 Hingham St.  &lt;br /&gt;Rockland, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting time is 6:00PM  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Thursday Febuary&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;EASTERN MASS REIA&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Holiday Inn Rockland   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;929 Hingham St.  &lt;br /&gt;Rockland, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next Meeting Thursday February 12th &lt;br /&gt;Frustrated with high prices, lack of response and underwriting criteria???  John Ingram, Attorney Jeffrey Sill, and other local investors who are working in the world of REO's.  This will be a straight forward no holes barred approach to what is working for them.  Learn how these investors are stealing equity and creating cash flow.  You will learn how to:&lt;br /&gt;Control the property &lt;br /&gt;Structure offers that work &lt;br /&gt;Control the closing &lt;br /&gt;Wholesale the deal &lt;br /&gt;And Much More!!! &lt;br /&gt;We'll review numbers for the last two years and analyze the opportunities in the year ahead!!!  [Pre-Register and Save]&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Mass REIA Members&lt;br /&gt; Is Your Membership About to Expire???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Renew your Membership and enroll into our Loyalty Membership Program today and get your new yearly membership for $119.00&lt;br /&gt;Our Loyalty Program is for Active members who renew before their membership expires. Click here to enroll in our Loyalty Membership Program and Renew your Membership Today!!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Individual Menbership&lt;br /&gt;Includes monthly meetings, $20 in EMASS CASH, post deals in the members only classified section, discounts on educational events and seminars. $160 yearly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;EASTERN MASSACHUSETTS REAL ESTATE INVESTORS ASSOCIATION&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The door fee for monthly meetings is $25. Pre-Register online for $15!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to www.easternmassreia.com to preregister&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Resource Providers interested in learning about opportunities for sponsorship e-mail us businessresources@easternmassreia.com  or call 1 888 588 REIA Ext.701 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;I look forward to us having a very prosperous 2009. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s. This is Our monthly networking, education, and deal making event, here at Eastern Mass REIA,  if you have a deal let us know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investors Association    &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts REIA does not claim to give expert advice in investing, nor do we endorse what featured speakers say. We do not give professional, legal, financial or tax advice. We suggest that you get competent licensed counsel before putting into effect anything you hear in our club, whether in private conversation or something said publicly. The ideas presented are only meant to stimulate your thoughts in the field of real estate investing and are not to be taken as professional advice. All investing comes with risk; therefore, as adults, it is your responsibility to exercise due diligence before making any purchase, great or small. We encourage you to be careful when ordering coffee at a McDonalds drive through window...coffee is usually hot.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek Ebrecht</member_name><member_id>4695117</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236892480000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-730</urlname><id>598232</id><group_lat>42.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>EMREIA-Eastern Mass Real Estate Investors Assoc.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231461715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investment Association February Meetup</name><id>9480665</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234481400000</time><rsvp_limit>99</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-730/events/9480665/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/e/global_3350446.jpeg</photo_url></item>