<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's that time of year again! The NEBBC will hold it's SECOND Annual Bully Parade &amp;amp; Peanut Butter PLUS Drive on Saturday, May 19th at the home of founder, Cassie-Leigh Stock, 182 Hayden Rowe Street, Hopkinton, MA! ~~~ Our first Parade last year was such a huge success, we've decided to make this a yearly event! Last year attracted over 200 attendees and their dogs, and this year promises to be bigger &amp;amp; better! ~~~ We will meet at the aforementioned address - (registration begins at 10:30a) - and walk a pre-determined route through the center of quaint Hopkinton. Walk commences at noon! Parade to meet back at the starting point for BBQ-style food, drinks &amp;amp; celebrating our amazing dogs! BBQ to last from 1:00p+/- to 3:00p! ~~~ $5 registration fee. ~~~ So what's the Peanut Butter PLUS Drive? At every event, the NEBBC tries to collect donations for a bully-friendly New England rescue/shelter. Participants are encouraged to bring donations; anything from peanut butter, toys and linens to cleaning supplies, gift cards (Walmart, BJ's, etc.) and food! (Your $5 registration fee will be waived if you bring an item to donate!) ~~~ Exactly which rescues are yet to be determined, but there will be two, and you can vote for your favorite on our online poll! Simply go to www.meetup.com/new-england-bully-breed-club, click &amp;quot;More&amp;quot; on the tool bar, then &amp;quot;Polls!&amp;quot; to cast your vote! All donation items collected at this event will be split between the top two vote-winners! ~~~ As this event promises to be even grander than last year, I will take this opportunity to review our dog/handler etiquette: 1) Avoid head-on greetings between dogs. 2) Until you are familiar with individual dogs AND handlers, contact between dogs must be kept to a minimum. 3) Prevent your dog from lunging on leash, whether it is in play or not. 4) Dog(s) must be kept under owner control at all times. 5) Do not allow your dog to surprise, or &amp;quot;sneak up on&amp;quot; other dogs. 6) A VERY important note: Just because two dogs are friendly, does not necessarily mean they are going to be friendly with each other. Make no assumptions and DO NOT LET YOUR DOG GREET ANOTHER DOG until you have asked and BEEN GIVEN PERMISSION by the owner. ~~~ No flexi/extendable leashes at this event. ~~~ All dogs must be leashed and up-to-date on vaccinations; (proof of vaccinations NOT required.) ~~~ This is a very big, very busy event, and the main objective here is to raise awareness about our beloved breeds; that means we need to be on our &amp;quot;best behavior&amp;quot; and displaying them in a positive light. No aggressive dogs at this event; email me direct at justcassie101@gmail.com if you have questions or are unsure if your dog would be a good participant. ~~~ VOLUNTEERS NEEDED for everything from bringing food, to helping man the booth, to selling merchandise, to promoting safety between dogs/handlers (&amp;quot;security staff&amp;quot; if you will), to making/distributing flyers, to soliciting sponsorship, to taking pictures and more. Again, if you can commit to something, please email me direct. ~~~ Let's make this our greatest event ever! Guests, human or canine, of ANY breed welcome! ~~~ Rain date, Sunday, May 20th. ~~~ Note: Parking is on either side of Hayden Rowe Street (Rt. 85) and down all nearby side-streets and has been ok'd with the town. No parking in apartment driveway. ~~~ Community water will be provided, but it is suggested you bring water for the walk, as it was quite warm by this time last year! ~~~ Stay tuned for more details as it gets closer to the big day!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337548254000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>60</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329170307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's HERE!!  2nd Annual Bully Parade &amp; Peanut Butter PLUS Drive!!</name><id>52222222</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337437800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/52222222/</event_url></item>