<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Kneeland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349878</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-6397</phone><name>Splash Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>1171690</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE food, No cover charge, &lt;u&gt;cash bar&lt;/u&gt;. 5 PM - 10 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please provide a firm Yes or No RSVP &lt;u&gt;by Feb. 6th&lt;/u&gt;, so we can get the correct amount of food.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is not restricted to &amp;quot;talls&amp;quot; - please feel free to bring ONE friend with you -short or tall or inbetween. All we as is that you:.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;o RSVP +1 so that we have your friend in the headcount for food,&lt;br /&gt;o Do not double-RSVP - if you have already RSVP'd thru the BBTC Meetup or Marianne's 35+ Meetup, just RSVP No here &amp;amp; indicate in the text that you've already RSVP'd on the other Meetup.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Event Guide offered both us and another Meetup Group a FREE party (excluding drinks) for 20 people  each = A GRAND TOTAL of 40 people! just for responding to their survey about their New Year’s Eve party that several of us attended. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Splash Ultra Lounge &amp;amp; Burger Bar - here we come!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nestled between Chinatown and South Station in Boston’s Leather District, Splash Ultra Lounge &amp;amp; Burger Bar is Frank DePasquale’s latest venture inspired by the posh nightlife destinations of Miami, Vegas and L.A. Located at 150 Kneeland Street, the water-themed venue boasts a picturesque roof deck in addition to a swanky ultra lounge offering state of the art billiards and after-hours dining till 2 a.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Boston’s newest swank ultra-lounge, Splash hosts nightly DJs spinning house, international, top 40’s and mash-up, serving as a chill nightlife destination for both locals and tourists who want to see and be seen. Check out their website for more details. &lt;a href="http://www.splash-boston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Splash Boston Ultra Lounge &amp;amp; Burger Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The event includes a complimentary full food buffet and free admission.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Here is the sample menu&lt;/u&gt; (Items may be updated) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;o Crab cakes, Buffalo wings &lt;br /&gt;o Marinated steak tips &lt;br /&gt;o Sliders (regular burger sliders) &lt;br /&gt;o Crab meat sliders &lt;br /&gt;o Assorted pastas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dress Code:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dressy casual is the minimum; &lt;u&gt;NO sneakers, t-shirts or hats&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;It’s a 5 or 6 minute walk from either Chinatown or South Station “T” stations.&lt;br /&gt;For additional info, check out &lt;a href="http://www.splash-boston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Splash Boston Ultra Lounge &amp;amp; Burger Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for "Marie and Robyn's" Party</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn L</member_name><member_id>3649230</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266098970000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Tall Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostontallsingles</urlname><id>1235066</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Tall Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264814654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Party at Splash Boston Ultra Lounge &amp; Burger Bar</name><id>12463491</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265925600000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostontallsingles/events/12463491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/b/global_12848539.jpeg</photo_url></item>