<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup fees</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join us for our April meetup, this time for a very permaculture-based session facilitated by our organizer, LisaF.  This session will be &lt;b&gt;useful for both [our many!] new members and those of you who have been involved for a while&lt;/b&gt;, plus we will be scouring our pantries to come up with &lt;b&gt;another fabulous potluck meal&lt;/b&gt; to share with one another!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic:  Permaculture &amp;amp; Local Resilience&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The potential of permaculture is evolving as we continue to move through interesting times in our world.  Peak oil, climate change and economic conditions are challenging us to develop as much resilience as possible (at personal, household and community levels) in our systems of food, energy, transport, building, community structures, etc.  How does permaculture fit in?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Attendees will gain insight into the origins and context for permaculture, the eithics and principles that inform permaculture design, learn about examples and applications and discuss what's happening locally to move us toward greater resilience.  To be followed by questions and discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/pages/Organizer_Bio/"&gt;Speaker Bio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Potluck + Casual Socializing&lt;br /&gt;7:15ish Announcements + Start of Talk&lt;br /&gt;8:00ish Q&amp;amp;A + Cheerful Devolution into Discussion Until We All Drift Off Home&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck Breakdown &lt;br /&gt;Last Name A-G bring a veg or salad dish &lt;br /&gt;Last Name H-M bring bread or dessert &lt;br /&gt;Last Name N-S bring beverage or &amp;quot;appetizer&amp;quot; item &lt;br /&gt;Last Name T-Z wild card ... bring whatever!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please see our Meetup Event RSVP Guidelines:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://permaculture.meetup.com/58/messages/boards/thread/5233158#20208623"&gt;http://permaculture.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your own potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/cup/napkin)! Please consider bringing your digital camera and posting up a few photos after the event!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240669319000</updated><rating><average>4.84000015259</average><count>19</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>84</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234942225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Meetup:  Permaculture and Local Resilience</name><id>9766446</id><headcount>86</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239748200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/9766446/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/3/global_255395.jpeg</photo_url></item>