<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The &lt;a href="http://www.nhliberty.org" target="_blank"&gt;New Hampshire Liberty Alliance&lt;/a&gt; is a non-partisan coalition working to increase individual freedom in New Hampshire. They do this by monitoring bills in the legislative sessions and encouraging private charity, a civil society, and citizen involvement.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many members of the NH Seacoast Liberty Meetup are also NHLA members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHLA sponsors a stretch of highway, along Rt. 4, near Durham. The NHLA will be cleaning their stretch Sunday, June 13, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at 9:30 AM near the front Radio Shack at the Lee Traffic Circle Marketplace Shopping Center, at the intersection of Rt 4. and Rt. 125.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us in demonstrating how the voluntary actions of free individuals can bring about positive results, like a nice clean stretch of highway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, there will be an informal get-together and pot luck lunch at the Puterbaugh's [to be listed as a separate event].&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring sturdy gloves. Long pants and sleeves, and a hat are recommended, as it can get weedy, buggy, and sunny. Water will be provided, but bring your own beverage, if you wish. Trash bags and safety vests will be provided as well.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for people in road crew attire.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276441316000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276043111000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Hampshire Liberty Alliance Roadside Clean-Up</name><id>13742611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276435800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/13742611/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>