<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>63 South Hampton Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.872581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Speck Residence</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>13169632</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938622</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/4/2/event_231246722.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The May meeting of the Greater Newburyport Edible Garden group will feature Windowfarming. The meeting will be held on Tuesday, May 28th at 7:00 PM at the home of Anne Verret-Speck, 63 South Hampton Road (Route 107A), Amesbury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Windowfarm is a vertical, indoor garden that allows for year-round growing in almost any window. It lets plants use natural window light, the climate control of your living space, and organic “liquid soil.” In the hydroponic system, nutrient-spiked water is pumped up from a reservoir at the base of the system and trickles down from bottle to bottle, bathing the roots along the way. Water and nutrients that are not absorbed collect in the reservoir and are pumped through again at the next interval. More information is available at &lt;a href="http://windowfarms.org"&gt;windowfarms.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne is a self-described "total non-gardener" who began experimenting with a four-pot windowfarm this year. She will show us her system and share her experience with it. She is growing and harvesting a lot of kale and lettuce and also growing thyme and basil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Edible Garden Group was formed by community members who are interested in getting together to learn and share information about sustainable food growing – veggies, fruits, nuts. The meetings are focused on building community resilience through increasing the availability of safe, nutritious, sustainably-grown local food. For more information contact Deb Carey at boiester@gmail.com or 978-388-5629.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Coming out of Amesbury on South Hampton Rd. (also Rte. 107A), we're on the right.  It's an old, charcoal grey house, set up on a slight rise, with a big, black mailbox with "Speck" handwritten on it.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dawn</member_name><member_id>8000248</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boiester</member_name><member_id>8570902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369793642000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367412961000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Experimenting with Windowfarming</name><id>117129172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369782000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/117129172/</event_url></item>