<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In June we will be discussing the third part of the Secret Book of John. Please download the .pdf from the Files section of the Meetup group and bring your questions and insights for discussion. Members of the Meetup group get a special MP3 version of the reading.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part two of our Secret Book of John discussion ended with the preparation for the creation of the first perfect man, Adam. Part three takes us through The creation of Adam, including all the demons that control his various body parts. If you thought last month was a tounge-twister then this month will pull your tounge right out of your head! However, nobody will be penalized for having no idea how to pronounce the names of the demons because it's really not that important to the understanding of the text.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what we need:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Someone to volunteer to read the reading. (Done: Fr. Norman)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Someone to bring coffee (Done: Eric)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Someone to bring a snack (Done: Pam)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll handle the printed material and the supplies for the Logos Service. Please RSVP either Yes, No, or Maybe. It really helps us plan for our meetings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And as always, please contact me with any question, comments or concerns!&lt;br /&gt;In Gnosis,&lt;br /&gt;Anthony&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Anthony Silvia</member_name><member_id>3748780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182178433000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Gnostics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>gnostic-178</urlname><id>427616</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>St. Sarah's Parish :: Gnostic Church and Discussion Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180448147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June Narthex Meeting</name><id>5827894</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182002400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gnostic-178/events/5827894/</event_url></item>