<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Coliseum Ave. (The Entrance Behind Hannaford's &amp; Chunky's)</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>42.765366</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mine Falls</name><city>Nashua</city><id>3536792</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467567</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Easy Hike Mine Falls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday Nov. 11th. 1 pm. to 3 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mine Falls Coliseum Ave. Nashua, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962 &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!      This is a dog and child friendly event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had 26 people join us, and we had such a good turn out last Sunday. I decided to do it again.  Please get there as &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/8/0/event_178084992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;close to 1pm. as possible. So, Steve ob1 can introduce you to everyone hiking with us. If you are late? Call or text me, and we will connect with you along the trail. They say it will be in the 60s Sunday. We should have a nice easy hike, with good conversation. That should made for a nice day. So, lets do it again. The trails at Mine Falls Park in Nashua are mostly paved. So, we should not any problems with the trail conditions. Please, know this is not a race. Our intent is to enjoy the views of the area, and to chat along the way. This event is meant more to have fun than to get a good workout. I thought that we would enjoy nature for about two or three hours, with a few breaks/stops along the trail. This park is easy to find and full of beautiful views and history. So, come and enjoy some fresh air, beautiful views, and all this while in good company of new and old friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 1:00 pm Sharp from the parking lot at the end of Coliseum Ave, which is off of Rte 130 and the intersection of rt. 3 exit 6 in Nashua.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: Take exit 6 from Route 3 (Route 130) and go west towards Brookline, take the second entrance to the shopping Mall area (Colliseum Ave), go all the way to the end of the road to the parking lot. Look for the meetup sign on my black van.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers so that you will be comfortable the whole time we are out on the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone cares to, we can then go grab a bite to eat or enjoy a hot chocolate, at a nearby restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 the Meetup signs on my black van.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352677296000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352383458000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy Hiking Mine Falls</name><id>90508972</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352656800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/90508972/</event_url></item>