<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is the first of the sunset paddles on the water..&lt;br /&gt;Start with a lake, maybe a river next..then do it in the moonlight...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This isnt a far distance paddle, just around the lake and beach area till it gets dark...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a flashlight just in case we enjoy the area more than we plan...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can add some other activity later..&lt;br /&gt;There is a real interesting tunnel a mile away..will make for a cool torch light tour for about 15 minutes...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN Backup Plan... i will post update if needed&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there: &lt;br /&gt;There is a easy to reach boat launch right off of rte 44 in Bolton that has plenty of parking and PortaPotties at the parking lot (they should be there by then). Further to the east on the lake is a beach area that would be an excellent place to sit on the sand to eat some snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 East to Bolton Notch &lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) rte 6 is to the right, stay on 44&lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light. &lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (across from South Road)&lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area. &lt;br /&gt;I carry my kayak on a old sailboat trailer so im easy to spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest, GPS and others use 1,000 Boston Turnpike (rte 44) Bolton to get you close enough..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182121559000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181619212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Paddle on Bolton Lake, Bolton CT</name><id>5881509</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181948400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5881509/</event_url></item>