<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 6</address_2><address_1>163 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02053</zip><lat>42.147101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 533-0669</phone><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name><city>Medway</city><id>911296</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JourneyDance™&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sunday September 9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;11:00am - 12:30pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;COST: $20 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Presented by Jessica Kozak&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jessica is a graduate of The Rhys Thomas Energy Medicine Institute.  She has been an Energy Worker for 12 years and is the owner of The Soul Purpose &lt;a href="http://www.the-soul-purpose.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.the-soul-purpose.com&lt;/a&gt; in Swansea, MA where she does Energy Healing, Soul Counseling, Spirit Communication &amp;amp; Angelic Guidance Readings, and also teaches Reiki, Metaphysical classes, and JourneyDance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;™&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.  Jessica trained with Toni Bergins the founder of JourneyDance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;™&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.journeydance.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.journeydance.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;JourneyDance™ is a grooving celebration that will have you loving your body and loving your life! Weaving simple, guided movement sequences and free exploration, JourneyDance™ reconnects you with your innate state of joyous well-being. Your mind becomes clear, free, and positive, and your body feels supple, energized, and powerful. Practiced to inspiring world music, your dance is an empowering journey to self-acceptance and transformation.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;What happens during a JourneyDance™?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;JourneyDance™ moves us through deep, personal exploration into a loving, intimate relationship with body, mind, and source energy. This sensual and exhilarating union of dance, visualization, and ritual calls us to get funky and divine!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;In a Shamanic style, we are carried through an intentional and seamless flow of simple movement sequences and free expression. We are led with exuberance and compassion to a place of authentic communication with our creative spirit, where we discover our hearts’ desires.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;We embody our physical temple, unleashing animal energies from within as we ground ourselves. We explore our inner realms, delving and diving into our ocean of emotion. We connect with our inner shaman creator to burn the mind’s clogging clutter and make space for the abundance of joy that is available to us. As we create this powerful ritual together, we liberate old cellular memories, cleanse the body and mind with sweat and breath, and elevate our vibration.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;We open to the joy of life. We are the Prayer: our body, our movement, our breath. We are the Goddess: our passion, our emotions, our sensual heart. We are the Warrior: our power, our intentions, our life’s journey.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;JourneyDance™ is a transformational experience that does not require any previous movement or dance experience. Travel this sacred and provocative journey, feel bliss, and express ourselves as soul.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Dance has transformed my life. I have found my spiritual practice through movement. My body is the church. You connect to your own prayer through this sacred movement and you heal deeply and emotionally. You also burn a TON of calories!! I dance like no one is watching. A safe and sacred space is created for the dance. All are welcome. No experience required. This is about healing and finding your own spiritual center.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please bring a towel or yoga mat, a bottle of water, and a journal to record your experience.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For more information email solsticehealing@yahoo.com or Call 508-533-0669 &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.journeydance.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Solstice Healing</member_name><member_id>9244342</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347214138000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center</urlname><id>1422661</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345138140000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JourneyDance</name><id>78027442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347202800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center/events/78027442/</event_url></item>