<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Roughly 3.5 mile loop hike of moderate difficulty near the south-central shore area in this 1,200 acre sanctuary with a complex 39 mile trail system that has a unique blaze system (&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/reading_trailblazes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt; ). North-south trails are marked with a circle shaped blaze. Square ore triangular trails weave back and forth connectin g circle trails. Crossover trails that connect two circle trails of different colors are marked with an X of the color of the circle they lead to. Complicated? Exact path will be determined at hike time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have: &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - To carry extra layers of clothing as well as trail food and water. &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water&lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay a must!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at Noon at the parking area. We would finish up at about 3 PM and head home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General directions (from a trail source):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 58 off I-95&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 77 south (toward Guilford) about 0.5 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right (west) onto Route 1 and go 0.7 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Bear left onto Peddlers Rd. and drive 1.1 miles&lt;br /&gt;* Parking area on left just past Denison Dr.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aproximate location/directions via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=540+Peddlers+Rd&amp;amp;city=guilford&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods Reserve website (with trail maps):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westwoods interactive trail map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westwoodstrails.org/inter_map.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westwoodst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guilford Land Trust (maintains Westwoods):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guilfordlandtrust.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guilfordla...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213027684000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>A fairly easy hiking experience without much difficulty! We'll explore some of the trails.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212636593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Westwoods Reserve Trails in Guilford CT</name><id>8082591</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212854400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8082591/</event_url></item>