<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please RSVP! Although we have 128 seats we still need to know who is coming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TITLE:   CAN SLIM: A FACT-BASED SYSTEM TO HELP YOU FIND WINNING STOCKS and HOW TO USE THE INVESTORS BUSINESS DAILY EACH DAY TO MORE EFFICIENTLY ACHIEVE BETTER RESULTS presented by TED LEPLAT from Investors Business Daily&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a presentation by Investors Business Daily! TED LEPLAT from Investors Business Daily is flying in from Los Angeles just for us. We have a larger room for this special event. This is our first ever presentation from IBD. Please make sure to RSVP for this meeting. If there is anyone you like to talk stocks with, bring them with you and RSVP for them!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CAN SLIM is the IBD method to research and spot emerging growth stocks that meet proven investment criteria, derived from a strategy that continues to outperform the S&amp;amp;P 500.  TED LEPLAT will show how to efficiently go through the Investors Business Daily newspaper each day to find winning stocks, and follow up with actions. He will bring current copies of the Investors Business Daily newspaper for each attendee, and show us how the paper is designed, and could be best used for better results as well as guide us through their web site: &lt;a href="http://www.investors.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.investors....&lt;/a&gt;, and show us how to use it efficiently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TED LEPLAT has been a national educational speaker with Investor's Business Daily since 1999. He presents introductory investing workshops and seminars all over the United States to individual and professional investors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the comprehensiveness of TED  LEPLAT'S presentation, the meeting will start at 7:00 pm with TED LEPLAT'S presentation and will use the entire meeting time. Again, this is not a meeting to miss! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Joanna Kim for arranging TED LEPLAT'S appearance. She has heard him at the New York group and knew we would like him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is our 4th Annual Meeting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the premeeting time (from 6:00 pm - 6:50 pm) the Tiger Financial News Network group (the Tigers Hour) will have Basil Chapman - inventor of the Chapman Wave - presenting. Basil has an Internet radio show on www.tfnn.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AGENDA:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 Premeeting hour - BASIL CHAPMAN presents during the Tigers Hour&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Meeting starts - TED LEPLAT from Investors Business Daily presents&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members value open discussion highly. We try to pack as much open discussion as possible. Expressing ideas and sharing knowledge is paramount to our members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All levels of expertise are welcome. No question is too simple - as a matter of fact the simplest question often evokes the best discussion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free meeting. There is no membership required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187996814000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>21</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>113</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185366771000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Investor's Business Daily August Meetup</name><id>6074131</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187823600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/6074131/</event_url></item>