<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Hartford Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06053</zip><lat>41.706280</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 236-3343</phone><name>Whinstone Tavern </name><city>New Britain</city><id>1148213</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.768021</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;SPEED Match Dating Singles -Social and Business Networking Events – AGES 30 -55 the best way to meet Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE CHAMPAGNE FOR THE LADIES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is better than Speed Dating? SPEED Match Dating Singles Social and Business Networking Events – the best way to meet Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating is Speed Dating combined with a Social Networking Event AND a business Networking Event – at locations throughout Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating lets you meet many new people in one evening –that greatly increases your chances of meeting someone special&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what happens if you meet someone who will make a good friend or business associate?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With regular Speed Dating, those opportunities are lost when you walk out of the door!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating lets you specify which type of relationship match is right – Dating, Friends, or Business – so you don’t have to worry about missed opportunities – and enjoy a boost in your business and social life with these NEW friends and Business relationships from local Connecticut Singles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE BEST PART – you pay for only 1 event – not 3 events&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We give you the opportunity to choose your date, choose your friends, and choose business associates and business contacts that can boost your business and success&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will be able to spend 7 minutes with each person, analyze the situation, and then decide whether they would fit in better as a dating partner, new friend, or Business Associate.&lt;br /&gt;You can choose your matches for relationships, romance, dating, friends and social relationships, business relationships and opportunities – maybe even a new job, client or employment opportunity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just choose the best match on the SPEED Match Dating form, give us the form after the event, and we will email you all of your Dating, Social and Friends and Business matches.&lt;br /&gt;SPEED Match Dating is a fun and relaxed way to meet new people. You may come to this event alone, but you will leave with new friends, business contacts, &lt;br /&gt;and maybe a new romance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get the most for your time and money with SPEED MATCH DATING &lt;br /&gt;– 3 Singles Events in 1 coming to a location near you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPCOMING EVENTS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday Jan 14 2010 at 7pm AGES 30 -55&lt;br /&gt;Whinstone Tavern 245 Hartford Road New Britain, CT 06053  (860) 827-0022&lt;br /&gt;1.5 Miles from West Farms Mall &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADV TIX $ 25 * $ 35 at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE CHAMPAGNE FOR THE LADIES&lt;br /&gt;=======================================&lt;br /&gt;Thursday Jan 28 2010 at 7pm  AGES 30 -55&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comfort Inn &amp;amp; Suites 900 East Main Street Meriden, CT 06450  (203) 440-9601&lt;br /&gt;ADV TIX $ 25 * $ 35 at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE CHAMPAGNE FOR THE LADIES&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info, call (860) 236-3343 or visit &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.SinglesCT....&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.SinglesCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE[&lt;/a&gt;/b]&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will by the front desk, look for the SInglesCT.com Party Tonight signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Singles CT .com  -Join The Party</member_name><member_id>5188478</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263686889000</updated><rating><average>2.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262110940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPEED Match Dating Singles -Social and Business Networking Events – AGES 30 -55</name><id>12169041</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263513600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/12169041/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/a/a/global_12418266.jpeg</photo_url></item>