<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This moderate to higher effort hike on a portion of the Housatonic Range Trail will be about 5.8 miles in a combination thru-hike and out-and-back style. There will be great sights, features, and adventures!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out at the Tory's Cave parking and head uphill about .4 mile on blue/yellow blazed trail past the entrance to Tory's Cave (doing that as event after this hike for those interested!). We then get on the blue blazed Housatonic Trail on the ridge of Boardman Mtn. and head south for 2.4 miles. We decend to a roadcrossing and up a steep ascent to Suicide Ledges. After that a steep descent. We eventually Cross a road near the Concord Way endpoint parking (that we will return to).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have an upward grade on the blue blazed trail for about 1.6 miles with a little climbing of rock but not bad. We'll make our way to a &amp;quot;tube&amp;quot; in the rocks we'll have to climb for 10 feet. Then on to Kelly's Slide (you need good shoe tread to not slip on this) via blue/red blazed side trail for the best views. We'll get on the blue/orange trail from there to see the Candlewood Cave, a large multi-room rockfall cave that is a blast to explore. Then on to the summit of Candlewood Mtn. with elevation of 991 ft. We then head back via the main trail to the Concord Way parking to shuttle back to the start.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at the parking area (10 - 12 cars) for Tory's Cave off of Rte. 7 at 9:00 AM. We shuttle sufficient number of cars to return our grop to the Concord Way parking area (parking for 6 cars max.) off of Rte. 37. Overall this event will last about 5 hrs. (end about 2 PM) including exploring the rockfall cave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REMINDER: There is caving at Tory's Cave after this event at 2:30 PM. You may wish to consider doing that too! Additional equipment list for that event is on that event listing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment:&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;* Hiking boots or sneakers with very good tread for traction.&lt;br /&gt;* Small backpack to keep hands free and store stuff.&lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart water.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail food for energey, plus packed lunch to eat on trail or after.&lt;br /&gt;* Wear layers to add/remove as needed to keep warm and dry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to Tory's Cave parking - MEET HERE (a &amp;quot;bit north&amp;quot; of New Milford on Rte. 7/Kent Rd., around 480 Kent Rd., New Milford, CT)&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=480+Kent+Rd&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Textual directions to Tory's Cave parking&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 7 north out of New Milford center for about 3 miles at which point you'll pass the intersection of Rt. 37 west and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;* A short distance later a gas station will be on your left. Drive 1.3 miles (passing the first street sign for the semi-circular Squash Hollow Road) and turnleft into a large dirt parking area (in two parts: a semi-circle and then a huge open field).&lt;br /&gt;* Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;* The blue trail markers can be seen at the apex of the semi-circular parking lot.   The parking lot is at an old quarry construction site.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Note:  If you see the second street sign for SquashHollow Road, you've gone too far. Drive back  about 0.4 mile.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to Concord Way trail parking (hike endpoint, pickup shuttle parking near 10 Concord Way, New Milford, CT)&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=10+Concord+Way&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Housatonic Trail&lt;/b&gt; maps can be found on &lt;b&gt;pages 55 - 57, Maps HR1a  HR-1b&lt;/b&gt; in the current 19th ed. &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Connecticut Walk Book West&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; by the Connecticute Forest and Parks Association.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Topographic map of the area centered roughly on the trailhead on Rte. 7&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?lon=-73.460755&amp;amp;lat=41.618677&amp;amp;datum=nad83" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topozone.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the trail see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirehiking.com/hikes/housatonic_range.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.berkshireh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited carpooling of up to 6 is available from Kevin S from the Hartford area and potentially available for pick-ups along the I-84 corridor heading west of Hartford, CT. Please indicate in RSVP if you would like to carpool and arrange with Kevin S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289862656000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288538518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Housatonic Range Trail in New Milford CT</name><id>15285638</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289656800000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15285638/</event_url></item>