<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Harvard Yard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Memorial Church</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>899800</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.125000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join the Greater Worcester Humanists attending Harvard's 4th Annual &amp;quot;Lifetime Achievement Award in Cultural Humanism.&amp;quot;  A few of us will be going with the possibility of dinner out before the event (details to come).  Please note:&lt;b&gt; this is &lt;u&gt;not&lt;/u&gt; a Greater Worcester Humanists hosted event, there are tickets and from what we understand, they're going fast...&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;a href="http://ofa.fas.harvard.edu/cal/details.php?ID=40871" target="_blank"&gt;BUY TICKETS HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;____________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Annual Outstanding Lifetime Achievement Award in Cultural Humanism is presented at Harvard University each year by the Harvard Secular Society on behalf of the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard and the American Humanist Association. Selected by a committee of 20-30 Harvard students each year, this award is given to a figure greatly admired by our students and community for both artistic and humanitarian reasons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in its fourth year, the HSS Cultural Humanism committee has chosen the recipients for the award, the MythBusters, based on what they feel is an outstanding contribution to Humanism in culture. The MythBusters – special-effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman – take on the task of separating truth from urban legend on their television show with the same name. In true Humanist style, the pair takes on three myths per episode and uses modern-day science to demonstrate, through scientific trials, whether or not some things we take for granted really hold any ground. The award ceremony (April 16 8:00pm Memorial Church) will feature a talk and demonstrations by the pair.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Previous winners of the Cultural Humanism Award are, in 2007, novelist Sir Salman Rushdie, in 2008, punk rock star Greg Graffin (of the band Bad Religion and the UCLA Faculty of Biology), and in 2009, writer/ director/producer Joss Whedon (“Buffy,” “Angel,” Firefly,” “Dollhouse”).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>not sure yet</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271635744000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265395819000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th Annual Harvard Secular Society Award in Cultural Humanism - The Mythbusters</name><id>12528934</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271462400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/12528934/</event_url></item>