<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Oscar Wilde said "Life imitates Art far more than Art imitates Life" (please read&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; the short &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Life_imitating_art"&gt;Wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by this observation.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; How true is Wilde&amp;rsquo;s observation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The subject intersects with the whole field of metaphor, because if life imitates art then life becomes a grand metaphor of an artistic ideal.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; And undoubtedly, in many cases this is the case.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We humans are imitators by nature.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; From the very start as we lay in our cradles we begin to imitate our parents.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Unlike most animals, we have fewer instinctual behaviors, ergo instinct is substituted with imitation.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; As adults, we continue to imitate each other.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This reality contains a multitude of questions and probably says as many good things about human nature as about human qualities that are perhaps not so good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;After all art imitates art&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Like I said, we are imitators.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Just look at popular music or iPhones or whatever you please and, of course, imitation is the surest form of flattery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And what about love?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; How much of what we know or believe about love derives from its representation in movies and other art forms. Seriously, I jest not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But &amp;ldquo;life imitating art&amp;rdquo; is also a great hyperbole.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Oh, I should mention that we humans are perhaps as prone to hyperbole as to imitation.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I do not believe that Einstein or Darwin imitated art, for example.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; But there are a lot of scientists who imitate Einstein and Darwin.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This entire subject easily leads into the question of Leader and Follower.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; There are scientific, artistic, cultural, political, philosophical leaders who, as Newton said, stand on the shoulders of giants but he and other great thinkers managed to break through the boundaries of imitation and conventional wisdom and truly create not art but new realities and/or understanding of reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly, as you can see, there is a very fine line between art and life.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; The truth is, in my view, that we are both followers and leaders, and imitators and artists.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; But have I not just created a metaphor that compares the artist to the leader?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Must not a great leader in any field be an artist who has the power to create new ideas so that we may be led from a lesser state of existence to a grander one?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; So, from my standpoint, if I am asked the question, &amp;ldquo;Does life imitate art or does art imitate life?&amp;rdquo; my answer is simply &amp;ldquo;Yes!&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Yes!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, even if my view is valid that life as art and art as life is a continuum and, as such, Wilde&amp;rsquo;s question may in the final analysis only be a literary device, there is great value in discerning and differentiating situations of&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;ldquo;art&amp;rdquo; imitating life as opposed to &amp;ldquo;life&amp;rdquo; imitating art. &lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; ****************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT FORMAT CHANGE:&lt;/strong&gt; I am going to attempt a somewhat radical change in the format of this meeting (well, not radical, it&amp;rsquo;s more imitation).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I am partial to conducting larger groups, but the problem with our current venue is that the two large round tables that can accommodate up to 13 people each tend to fracture the meeting.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Sometimes one table&amp;rsquo;s discussion seems to go better than the other and, always, the bifurcation of the group prevents social mixing so that many times folks from one table don&amp;rsquo;t even get to meet the people sitting at the other table.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Accordingly, for this meeting each table will have a designated half that will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm (the meeting will have begun at 7pm).&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This strategy will still result in 25 percent&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; of the total who &lt;span&gt;will&lt;/span&gt; not have &amp;ldquo;mixed&amp;rdquo; with people at their respective tables, but it should make a significant and positive difference,&amp;nbsp; and if there are empty seats after the switch a little more moving around can occur.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Please know this in advance&lt;/em&gt;; if you are uncomfortable with this experimental arrangement then you should opt out and not RSVP for this particular discussion.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this arrangement works, it may become the standard format for restaurants with similarly fractured seating arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt; (Green Tea Restaurant)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the big round tables in the rear of the dining room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321723879000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319050775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Life Imitating Art, Art Imitating Life</name><id>37988972</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321660800000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/37988972/</event_url></item>