<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We did not get enough people to get our group discount but we will still run the weekend.  Instead of paying the fee to the the Wedeln Club you will buy your tickets directly at Wildcat.   Some people preferred this anyway because you can pick and choose which activities to do.  Do all all3, just one or go for a hike for free - your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have updated the following with the Wildcat Mountain window price.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.$30.  Ride the famous Ziprider twice!  Wildcat's 1/2 mile long zip line ride speeds you along above trees, trail and stream.  It looks safe but fun, check the website.&lt;br /&gt;2. $23. Scenic Gondola ride to the top of  Wildcat Mountain.  Lunch included.  we may even do a short hike from the summit.&lt;br /&gt;3. $15 Frisbee golf - Wildcat has set up a 9 hole course that you play through twice.  The holes are fairly short and along the some of the most popular ski trails.   Great views of Tuckerman Ravine (Mt Washington) as you play.  Cost includes a 3 disc rental and chairlift ride to the first hole.&lt;br /&gt;4. BBQ dinner at the Wedeln Ski House will be POT LUCK.  Bring your own grill item or side dish.&lt;br /&gt;5. Sunday plans will depend on the weather - If we have a hot day the plan is to hit a mountain swimming hole, if it is too cool for swimming we will hike to the top of Kearsage North - a moderate hike we can start at the Wedeln Ski House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the Wildcat website for more info on Zip, golf course and gondola!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skiwildcat.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.skiwildcat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost to stay at the Wedeln house is $20 per person, per night.  I recommend staying both Friday and Saturday night, the house is only 20 minutes from Wildcat.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My plan is hike Wildcat instead of using the gondola but I will still ride the Zip Line and play Frisbee Golf.  People are free to join in on any of the pay activities or just join me on the hike.  I accommodate the hike I will start the day earlier then planned - I will leave Wedeln House by 8:30am on Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out our club website to find out about our house!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wedeln.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wedeln.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 21+ only, no pets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Try to come up Friday night.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251654346000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246409366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Excellent Adventure Weekend</name><id>10774243</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248534000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/10774243/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/4/1/global_9441905.jpeg</photo_url></item>