<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>240 Beaver St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.384979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UMass Waltham</name><city>Waltham</city><id>561766</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.216743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dr. Gabriel Cousens - &amp;quot;Creating Peace - Being Peace&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Waltham Raw New England Community&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 PM DVD, 6-7 PM Raw Potluck, 7-9:30 PM Speaker&lt;br /&gt;U Mass Waltham Center, 240 Beaver St., Waltham, MA 02452&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The RAW-luck buffet and lecture will be at the U Mass Waltham Center, 240 Beaver Street, Waltham, MA 02452. For directions, call (781) 891-0650 x 56. Due to limited space, prepaid reservations $5 for members (annual membership is $25) or $10 for non-members. Checks are payable to ?Waltham Raw New England Community?. Mail to Lisa Hart, 21 Williams Rd, N. Reading, MA 01864. Be sure checks have your postal address, phone number &amp;amp; email. If no time to mail checks, email Lisa at hart.lisa@gmail.com or call 978-664-0159 for reservations. All those attending are requested to bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based ready- to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people. Mark in red if not organic; many cannot eat if non-organic. Please bring serving utensils labeled with your name and a typed recipe with your name on it to display next to your dish. All are invited to our buffet and lecture! Check our website &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com&lt;/a&gt; for recipes &amp;amp; more. Questions call Betsy Bragg at 781-899-6664 or email betsy@rawnewenglandcommunity.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gabriel Cousens, M.D., M.D.(H), D.D. (Doctor of Divinity), Diplomate American Board of Holistic Medicine, Diplomate Ayurveda, a physician of the soul, teaches and lives the sevenfold peace. To the process of awakening and healing, Gabriel Cousens, M.D., M.D.(H), weaves a background as a holistic physician, medical researcher, world-recognized live-food nutritionist, psychiatrist, family therapist, homeopath, Pastoral Rebbe, acupuncturist, Ayurvedic practitioner, expert on green juice spiritual fasting and detoxification fasting, ecological leader, Reiki master, internationally celebrated spiritual teacher, author, lecturer, culture-bridger, world peaceworker, to give a unique holistic approach to nurturing the hungry soul.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226183834000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211464029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Gabriel Cousens &amp; WRNEC Buffet</name><id>7991007</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226010600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/7991007/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/f/5/global_4210853.jpeg</photo_url></item>