<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;La Femme Infid&amp;egrave;le (The Unfaithful Wife)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; directed by Claude Chabrol &amp;nbsp;France 1968, 98 min.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;La Femme Infidele&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is widely renowned as one of his finest psychological thrillers from his prime time in the late Sixties/early Seventies.
&lt;p&gt;It is a well known story: man loves woman, woman loves man, woman maybe loves other man, other man isn't sure either ... you know the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charles Desvallees (Michel Bouquet) is extremely suspicious that his wife (Stephane Audran) is being unfaithful and so hires a private detective. Once his fears are confirmed, he turns up at the lover Victor Pegala's (Maurice Ronet) apartment to meet the man his wife has been sleeping with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Confront" is the wrong word in this context. Charles seems all too calm and collected, as he proceeds to have a friendly conversation with Victor, but the utter devastation burning in the betrayed husband's eyes slowly gets the better of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tension sustained throughout the film is exceptional. Alfred Hitchcock is said to be Chabrol's main role model and you can sense his influence everywhere. &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;La Femme Infidele&lt;/span&gt; is quiet and sedated, when all is seemingly normal, but then the sinister familiar violins and twisting piano melodies creep up to warn you not to look away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a masterful atmosphere that shrouds expectation and the slightly blurred glow of the cinematography adds to the tension. The performances are what make La Femme Infidele so memorable, with superb, honest portrayals of complex characters. Eye for Film UK&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;One of 12 films the Harvard Film Archive is featuring&amp;nbsp;in their retrospective of Chabrol who passed away&amp;nbsp;Sept, 2010.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Chabrol&amp;rsquo;s reputation as one of France&amp;rsquo;s great filmmakers rests first upon his films of the late 1950s and the late 1960s. Eschewing overt visual stylization, these films favor a cool, crisp classical style that makes clear Chabrol&amp;rsquo;s admiration for Fritz Lang. His other master was Alfred Hitchcock who inspired Chabrol&amp;rsquo;s ironic distance from his characters as well as his fascination with pathology and its roots in sexual (mis)behavior. Chabrol&amp;rsquo;s ability to work quickly and efficiently, combined with his constant return to the suspense and thriller genres, allowed him to remain both prolific and popular for decades. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;After the film we will go to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Tom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a disposable MEETUP Sign  near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300050390000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This is a film and as a film group, we go to films.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297545954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>La Femme Infidèle (The Unfaithful Wife)</name><id>16542786</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299974400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16542786/</event_url></item>