<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok since everyone hates the  Sunset Social, Wino'es on the mountain top..enjoying snacks and a good selection of wine, and enlightening conversation with great people,&lt;br /&gt;I just have to do something a bit different.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new thing is a Pot Luck Dinner series of events mixed among those Sunset events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pot Luck..yeh not POT, even though you would be lucky to get it and smoke it, but i want something to eat, drink, and talk about...these events will be close to a geological feature where a grill, table, and chairs can be placed for our relaxation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hot dogs are disgusting, but since this is the first pot luck, i will get some Hebrew National Franks and Portogese rolls..and a California wine..(its my ethnic dining offering for this one)...i already got the gas grill...soooo..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring something else... and your chairs...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok what is the place...?&lt;br /&gt;Im not telling what it is you will see, ya will just have to go to find out...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: Take 91 north to exit 40 (thats rte 20 to Bradley airport)&lt;br /&gt;Pass Hamilton Standard, continue to the right to rte 20 towards New Gate Prison.&lt;br /&gt;Pass new Gate Prison sign till you get to the intersection of 20 / 202 (Granby Center)&lt;br /&gt;Stay on route 20 (west) for 3.5 miles, look left for rte 219 (Barkhamsted rd),&lt;br /&gt;Take left onto rte 219 for apx 1.5 miles look left for the park entrance of Enders State Forest.&lt;br /&gt;if you see Case rd you just past it..&lt;br /&gt;See Ya there..&lt;br /&gt;From Water town&lt;br /&gt;8 north...at the end of the exit loop&lt;br /&gt;take a left (east) onto rte 44&lt;br /&gt;then take a left onto rte 318,&lt;br /&gt;near the reserviour take a left onto 219 north&lt;br /&gt;you will intersect with 179, stay on 219 for about 2.5 miles, pass case rd, take a right into the park..&lt;br /&gt;For other start locations, GPS, and Mapquest users, use 160 Barkhamsted Road, West Granby, ct for directions and nearby roads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back up plans for bad weather...&lt;br /&gt;Heavy rain..cancelled..&lt;br /&gt;very light rain, meet at location, access situation, stay at location (set up overhead protection) or go to McLean Game preserve and party on the Cabin portch overlooking the small lake..(directions later if necessary)...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179623938000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179018876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pot Luck Dinner at a Geological Feature and short hike.</name><id>5772558</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179441900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5772558/</event_url></item>