<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Manufactured Landscapes&lt;/b&gt; by Jennifer Baichwal (Canada, 2006, 90 min.). Edward Burtynsky is internationally acclaimed for his large-scale photographs of nature transformed by industry. Photographing civilization's materials-quarries, recycling yards, factories, mines, and dams and debris- in a way often described as beautiful, Burtynsky raises questions about ethics and aesthetics without offering easy answers. Manufactured Landscapes follows Burtynsky as he photographs the evidence of China's massive industrial revolution, transforming his still images into moving ones. “A protracted exploration of the aesthetic, social and spiritual dimensions of industrialization and globalization... Raises some significant and sobering questions about the impact that we, as humans, make on our environment&amp;quot; (The New York Times).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosted by the International/Art House Film Group last year, Manufactured Landscapes was simply one of the most powerful films we've seen.  If you missed it last time, make an effort to come to this showing or a later one at the MFA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Olympics, the recent election, and the economic meltdown makes China's massive industrialization especially relevant.  You simply won't believe what you are seeing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll go to either the cafe next to the Remis Auditorium, or to the cafeterial downstairs.  The cafe is pricey with a limited menu while the cafeteria is more reasonable, but also a bit more noisy.  Probably won't be able to go outside to discuss in the Courtyard!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please indicate in your RSVP which locale you would prefer for the after film discussion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be blocking traffic by holding a Meetup Sign at the Exit</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227527705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manufactured Landscapes</name><id>9221358</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229194800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9221358/</event_url></item>