<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 Winthrop St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372213</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 491-1160</phone><name>Grendels Den</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>680291</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120634</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Happy Hour Snacks + Drinks + Harvard SQ Cambridge+ CHOCOLATE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Hour is nightly from 5:00 pm to 7:30 pm during which times all food on the menu is half price with a $3 minimum beverage purchase per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If possible, i would appreciate it if a few of you would get there early, @ 4:45 to start grabbing tables. Note if we get lots of yeses we may split up into several tables. Please try to come at or Before 5:00PM by almost 5:15PM the place is full and I doubt we can get or hold any tables if people come too late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come after 5:15 PM I cannot be sure you all will be sitting together at one table with our group, I just wanted to warn people!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grendel's Den has been serving casual gourmet dishes and international specialties in the same location for over 35 years. They have a full bar and an beer selection reknown for its high quality selection of imports,  microbrews and Hot Cider with Rum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LATER, @ 7:30 - 8:30 DESSERT !!Walk one block to enjoy French pasteries at &amp;quot;FINALE&amp;quot;, 30 Dunster Street (Holyoke Center- across the street from J. Harvard Brewery) to get a VALENTINE'S DAY CHOCOLATE FIX!!!&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;i&gt;Please indicate in your rsvp comment  if you will be &amp;quot;counted in&amp;quot; for dessert.&lt;/i&gt; I will need to hear from you &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;before 12 noon Sunday&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; in order to get an accurate head count for our reserved corner table for 8 chocolate/dessert lovin' junkies (btw- my favs are creme brule &amp;amp; chocolate mouse)&lt;br /&gt;GET READY TO SALIVATE AS YOU TURN THE PAGES   on this site below... You may choose to buddy up and share a scrumptious platter for two!!! OR  order individually one small tasty treat with a cup of cappuccino&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.finaledesserts.com/menus.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; This is an easy T accessible event. Take the RED line to Harvard Square. Parking validation is available from FINALE. Check FINALE web page for details on where to park and prices. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lauren will be wearing a rabbit fur hat</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266634700000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263409645000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GRENDEL'S DEN</name><id>12310015</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266184800000</time><rsvp_limit>33</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/12310015/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/e/global_12662670.jpeg</photo_url></item>