<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Hampshire Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.149565</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Peters Foam Dome Home</name><city>Durham</city><id>1069031</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.932807</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Energy fans, I have been very busy working on my house for the upcoming &amp;quot;National Solar Tour &amp;quot; come check out my house as well as take a tour of other house in the area&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This fun event takes place in about two weeks in some 3,000 communities across America. We invite you to join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check this web site out for locations: &lt;a href="http://www.nhsea.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhsea.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The National Solar Tour offers open-house tours to show how you can use solar energy and energy efficiency to reduce monthly utility bills and help tackle climate change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the world's largest grassroots solar event with more than 150,000 participants, taking place in nearly every state across the U.S. The National Solar Tour helps you learn how easy it is to go solar and how to save money with the latest incentives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes this event so powerful are the neighbor to neighbor discussions that can help you can gain the insight needed to make smarter energy choices.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Solar costs have decreased by close to 30% in the last year. Federal incentives have increased significantly. Now is an excellent time to go solar and the National Solar Tour is an easy way to get started.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in its 14th year, it's coordinated nationally by the nonprofit American Solar Energy Society in collaboration with dozens of outstanding partner organizations and thousands of volunteers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to be inspired! And don't forget to mark your calendar to attend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269547147000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253271184000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Green Buildings Open House Day</name><id>11404494</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254585600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/11404494/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/c/0/global_10763056.jpeg</photo_url></item>