<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Socialism and libertarianism, beyond their doctrines, are also ideals. That both ideals are embraced by millions who otherwise seem to get along quite nicely may, perhaps, suggest that these two socio-political philosophies need not be trapped in a state of fixed polar opposition. If we can escape the constraints of dogma and doctrine the argument might be made that a socialist can value “rugged individualism” and a libertarian need not bury his or her compassion. Are freedom, social flourishing and artistic perspective the exclusive properties of one side or the other? Is the desire for social welfare incompatible with the desire for less government interference? Philosophy is sometimes a display of passionate insights, but these insights can become hardened into inflexible ideals. In this discussion, we will explore examples of how these purportedly opposite philosophies express concrete complementarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I think that there a number of elements in &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Herbert_Spencer"&gt;Herbert Spencer&lt;/a&gt;’s thought, who is generally viewed as the first libertarian, that would probably (or definitely) be rejected by almost all modern day libertarians and clearly by, e.g. followers of Ayn Rand. For example, consider this quote from the Wikipedia article:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Herbert_Spencer" class="linkified"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Herbert_Spencer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;While often caricatured as ultra-conservative, Spencer had opposed private property in land, claiming that each person has a latent claim to participate in the use of the earth. He was sympathetic to Georgism,&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Herbert_Spencer#cite_note-22"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; which also took such a view. He called himself "a &lt;span&gt;radical feminist&lt;/span&gt;" and advocated the organization of voluntary labor unions as a bulwark against "exploitation by bosses", and favored an economy organized primarily in free worker co-operatives as a replacement for wage-labor."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And many socialists, I believe, have sympathy for some elements of libertarianism. It is natural that this be the case, because fundamentally intellectual desire for “human flourishing” or what Aristotle called &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eudaimonia"&gt;eudaimonia&lt;/a&gt; is, in my view, transcendent of any ideological viewpoint of politics. And, as such, this discussion concerns the deeper commonalities that unite the spirit of democracy and freedom. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!  While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).  Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348499387000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346342289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>On the Pros and Cons of Libertarianism and Socialism</name><id>80087302</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348268400000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/80087302/</event_url></item>