<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61-63 Chatham Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wild Rover Bar Boston - 1 Block from Faneuil Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>9694002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053970</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Holiday meals have been eaten, packages unwrapped, decorations placed back in storage, and toasts to the New Year have been made. As the holidays draw quickly to a close with our families and friends, our New Year’s resolutions take focus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We pull out our list made the previous January 1st, dust it off, and read through the things we hoped to achieve by the close of the year. We reflect on our past year’s accomplishments, goals, dreams, and plans that we made one year before. We ask ourselves, did I do enough? Did I check enough items off my resolutions list? What can I do to make the next year better? What can I do differently?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One resolution you can make right now, and get started with even sooner, is to make a difference in your community. Make a difference in another’s life. Make a difference by volunteering your time and talents more than you ever have before. Make 2013 the year of volunteering!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what are you waiting for? Why not make a resolution we know you won’t let go unchecked on your list. Make your New Year’s resolution now to volunteer more! Let the Boston Volunteers help make your new goals even more meaningful. We want to celebrate your New Year’s resolution to volunteer more in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us for a party to meet your fellow Boston Volunteers, discover how you can get more involved, and enjoy some refreshing spirits. This is the perfect celebration if this is your first time or you are a regular.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll meet lots of new people who share your values.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to say Hi! to the Boston Volunteer organizers.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This celebration is only $5 - please pay with a 5 bill at the top of the stairs. No $1 bills please. We also made it easier for you - you can pay our home page with your Master Card or Visa. I'll print out who else paid in advance. Everybody except the Meetup organizers who invite their groups pay $5.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our goal is to inspire people to volunteer more. We invite you to invite your Meetup group. Invited and confirmed groups include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Volunteers:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/bigenoughtodeliver/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/bigenoughtodeliver/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Fun:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Imagine Adventures:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Imagine-Adventures-Life-is-an-adventure-Will-you-join-us/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Imagine-Adventures/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be providing the extraordinary club, the DJ, and the all you can eat variety of food for you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We anticipate celebrating with you, :) &lt;br /&gt;

 Steph, Josh, Sehily, Phani, Nagina, Corey,TeLisa and Imanuela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S. Bring 4 or more friends with you and YOU get in for free! Must post on the wall how many friends you're bring with you!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 P.P.S. This is also a very popular Boston Volunteers Facebook celebration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more or discover who else is coming:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/310370685733590/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/310370685733590/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;The Boston Volunteers&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Big enough to deliver, small enough to care&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll have the whole room exclusively for us! Look for the Meetup signs. :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Josh</member_name><member_id>4450243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1357364278000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355704101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What's your New Years Resolution? New You in the New Year! Don't miss ...</name><id>95598542</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357343100000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/95598542/</event_url></item>