<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Civic Center Plaza</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06120</zip><lat>41.778091</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>XL Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>2035931</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680260</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On January 4, 2012&lt;/strong&gt; ...Highly ranked &lt;strong&gt;UCONN Women's Basketball Lady Huskies team will be hosting the West Virginia squad at the XL Center in downtown Hartford, CT.&lt;/strong&gt; I have managed to pull a few strings and got &lt;strong&gt;discounted ($10) tickets&lt;/strong&gt; to this televised event - &lt;strong&gt;CPTV&lt;/strong&gt;. I would love for many Ron Paul supporters to join me at the game to wave signs prior to game time 6pm-7pm, and inside, during the game itself, and pass out our super brochures/DVD's/bumper stickers to all that accept them....during halftime, we can canvass around civic center, and pass out info, inform the masses, and hopefully recruit some new supporters.... &lt;strong&gt;UCONN is one of the best ladies college basketball teams in the country, and usually draws 8K-16K fans to each home game&lt;/strong&gt;....This is a great way to gain exposure for Ron Paul, and watch some entertaining basketball as well..&lt;strong&gt;.Hope you all can join me. I need RSVP right away, as I must secure these discounted tickets by the end of THIS week (Friday: December 16, 2011 deadline) I need a head count ASAP (I will purchase tickets in advance, pay later)...&lt;/strong&gt;Please make this happen, or at least think of donating $10, so I can invite others to join us, or hand out to potential Ron Paul voters.... &lt;strong&gt;This event is one day after the Iowa Primary, and Ron Paul's name will be buzzing the news outlets when he takes 1st Place in the Iowa Caucuses&lt;/strong&gt; ....Let's send a message to CT voters that we got Connecticut covered as well :-) &lt;strong&gt;Thank you....Doug Weidl....call me to confirm interest in a ticket (860) 899-4818.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Douglas Weidl</member_name><member_id>25633552</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325722784000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323727205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UCONN Women's Basketball game / Sign &amp; Banner Wave and Flyer Handout Event</name><id>44247412</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325718000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/44247412/</event_url></item>