<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hope Artiste Village Mill Complex</address_2><address_1>1005 Main St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.862738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 726-2181</phone><name>The Blackstone</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>783648</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.399395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: The Blackstone on Main St. in Pawtucket (This is in the Hope Artiste Village complex - a large mill building) on the 1st floor. Park in the lot across the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blackstone has a little something for everyone. The bar is large, as is the space. They have live music most of the week as well as pool. Its located inside a really cool renovated mill complex (that houses artists studios as well) and is the location of the Winter Famers Market as well as other events throughout the year. Last summer there was an outdoor movie festival here. Park in the lot across the street. This is a place worth knowing about. If you've been, you know, and if not, come join us this Monday. So let's check it out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but you can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264648111000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264004830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - The Blackstone!</name><id>12372402</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264460400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12372402/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>