<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.376365</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-4491</phone><name>Longfellow National Historic Site</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>706336</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.126233</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the National Park Service site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/ner/customcf/apps/eventcalendar/events/longevent95237198.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/ne...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Puzzles of Dorchester Heights: Washington Ends the Siege of Boston &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date&lt;/b&gt;:  Wednesday, March 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time&lt;/b&gt;:  6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;:  Carriage House - Longfellow National Historic Site - 105 Brattle Street - Cambridge - MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Details&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Historians agree that placing artillery on the hills of the Dorchester peninsula was decisive in forcing the British military to evacuate Boston on March 17, 1776.  But why had it taken so long for either army to seize that high ground?  What was General Washington`s role in setting strategy?  And what other factors were important in the end of the siege?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Presented in the historic Longfellow Carriage House by Dr. Robert Cameron Mitchell, Professor Emeritus, Clark University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP required&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;  Please call the site at &lt;b&gt;(617) 876-4491&lt;/b&gt;.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please note&lt;/u&gt;: Calling the Longfellow House beforehand appears to be required. Showing up last-minute, dropping in, and saying &amp;quot;Oh, I'm from Nerd Fun, I RSVPed on the site&amp;quot; when they ask if you RSVPed is only going to get you a blank stare and a comment like &amp;quot;You are with &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt;?&amp;quot; ... er, we just crash events, we don't usually host them. When you RSVP to an event on the Meetup site, it's more for my benefit so I can scan the crowd and look for people, waving them to us, or helping me save seats for those who RSVPed with the people who are running the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Carriage House is in back of the Longfellow National Historic Site, on the left side. T.J. Maher should be waiting just outside the main entrance of the Carriage House starting at 6:00 pm. We can grab seats at 6:15 pm. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After we can figure out where we want to go grab something to eat in Harvard Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Longfellow House:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/long/historyculture/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/lo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The house at 105 Brattle Street in Cambridge was witness to many significant events. It was here that George Washington took command of the Continental Army during the American Revolution. The first use in the United States of anesthesia for childbirth was administered to Fanny Longfellow at the house. Famous literary figures such as Charles Dickens and Nathaniel Hawthorne were visitors, as were politicians, actors, musicians, and others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Henry Wadsworth Longfellow filled the mansion with objects reflecting his interest in other cultures. European and Asian artwork, furniture, decorative objects and books are found throughout the house. The Longfellow house was truly a cosmopolitan home&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/long/planyourvisit/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/lo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Apart from handicapped parking, there is no on-site visitor parking available.  Metered parking is available on Brattle Street and other nearby roads.  [..] From Downtown Boston by MBTA/Subway: Take Red Line (Alewife) train outbound. Exit at Harvard Square and follow signs out of station for Church Street. At intersection of Church and Brattle Streets, turn right onto Brattle and walk for 7-10 minutes. Longfellow NHS is on right hand side of Brattle St. at #105&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Map&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/long/planyourvisit/upload/Map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/lo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269038622000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267026839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Puzzles of Dorchester Heights: Washington Ends Siege Boston @ Longfellow House</name><id>12694963</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268865000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12694963/</event_url></item>