<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Pleasant Street, Suite #328</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01027</zip><lat>42.272255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Eastworks: MRW Connected, LLC</name><city>Easthampton</city><id>1568589</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.664566</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come join us! Bring your swatches.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be having a discussion about color trends. Neal and I recently went on a color trends pilgrimage on Newbury Street, in Boston, and the very upscale Natick Mall. We gathered some catalogs, flyers, took some photographs, and got a sense of what the spring colors will be. The results were fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like everyone, from their different design disciplines to bring some ideas about what they think some future color and design trends will be. Bring some swatches, or photographs, mag clippings. videos? to illustrate your idea. We will throw all the swatches on the big table and see what we get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Color Trends: Color Nazis or Collective Unconscious?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 As many designers know, color trends are forecast for as many as ten years ahead. We find this to be an interesting aspect of this discussion. Do color trends limit designers, or help them. Are color trends a recent phenomenon, or has this been the case since the distant past? Can colors be read historically as reflective of social milieus?&amp;nbsp; Across design fields, such as interior design vs fashion palettes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Color Trends Across Different Design Fields:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Do color trends vary or differ according to the differing needs of different design fields? Industrial design, interior design, photography, graphic design, architecture?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome input from members:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 If anyone has ideas that they would like to contribute to how to present on this topic, we would welcome input and participation in planning the event. Please post your ideas on this meetup page, or direct message me through the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snack Pot Luck:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We welcome your chips and dip and other tasty bits to add to the mix. Art talk goes better with snacks. Yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to MRW Connected Offices inside Eastworks:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Park in the large parking lot. go into the entrance that has the movie marquee over it. Immediately on your left, there is an elevator. Go to the third floor. Step 15 feet beyond the elevator, look for the door on the right that says MRW Connected on it (opposite the Eastworks management office).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting from 6:30 - 8:00. Come at 6:00pm for schmooze time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa and Neal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Hoag</member_name><member_id>7353473</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330105186000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329774478000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Color Trends Slam: A color trends roundtable discussion</name><id>53093222</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329976800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/53093222/</event_url></item>