<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Wattaquadock Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01740</zip><lat>42.430644</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>http://www.nashobawinery.com</phone><name>Nashoba Valley Winery</name><city>Bolton</city><id>731361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.614016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come join the fun at Nashoba Winery on Sunday, October 26 from 1-5pm for their annual microbrew festival featuring beer, wine, great foliage views, and a bluegrass band called Southern Rail. Feel free to invite as many friends/family as you'd like! (The picture is from last year's event)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's basically one outdoor party in the orchard. Picnic tables go fast, so bring beach chairs or blankets (we usually try to secure a few tables). It's family-friendly so feel free to bring your kids. Dogs are allowed but must be on a leash. You can take a 30-minute tour of the winemaking facility for $6 (includes souvenir wine glass). There may or may not be apple picking depending on how the weather is the next few weeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have a food tent set up that sells burgers, dogs, Italian sausage, pulled pork, brisket. Side dishes like cole slaw, potato salad, cornbread, and apple crisp. I recommend that you eat before 3:00 as they tend to run out of food early...You can also bring your own picnic baskets and coolers!!! They have a caramel apple stand too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their microbrews will be for sale on tap at the outdoor bar and they will also be selling wine/beer by the bottle inside the wineshop all day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nashoba Valley Winery&lt;br /&gt;100 Wattaquadock Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Bolton, MA 01740&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nasoba Winery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located conveniently off I-495 at Exit 27 (Route 117). Head West 1 mile and turn left at blinking yellow light/Coldwell Banker office. Orchard is approximately 1/8 mile up the road (just follow the traffic).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best of all its FREE - unless you tour the winery ($6)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe RSVPs allowed for now until we get closer to the event and then only YES and NO RSVPs as we approach the final date. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For Yes RSVP's I'll send my cell phone number... Come Early - it will be crowded</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226618254000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Adventurerists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak</urlname><id>1297030</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Ski, Snowboard, and Outdoor Adventurers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224195235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashoba Valley Winery - Microbrew / Bluegrass festival</name><id>8975551</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225036800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak/events/8975551/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/c/global_5969516.jpeg</photo_url></item>