<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Out of Chaos Comes Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Technology innovation and wealth creation out of crisis, disaster recovery, and reconstruction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://etffeb2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - 9:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

Location: Emerging Center at Foley Hoag the Bay Colony Corporate Center, Waltham, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managing your business risk can mark the difference between your moving ahead of your competition and failure. Your readiness to respond can determine whether your business succeeds or fails. Business Continuity, Risk Management and Resiliency &amp;ndash; with customers in Finance, Information Technology, Management Consulting and Government is not just a big market, it is also a great opportunity to help customers become agile and resilient in a time of uncertainty. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you are an entrepreneur building your business in Continuity and Risk Management or a business looking for effective strategies, getting first hand insights from leaders in the field is invaluable. Companies specializing in Business Resiliency such as SunGard earned $5.1 billion in revenues for 2011 and Iron Mountain earned $3.1 Billion in 2010. Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery represented between 6 and 7% of IT budgets for small medium and enterprise organizations in 2011. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In the February 21st EntreTech Forum, our panel of industry leaders, startups and entrepreneurs will discuss building businesses in business continuity, resiliency and risk management. We will review the growing market, the technology, earning potential, and the opportunities for entrepreneurs. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a startup in risk management and continuity, looking for tips to protect your business or interested in the technology, please join us for this informative and interactive discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panel:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Feb2012Mtg/reddish.jpg" width="100" height="125" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Debbie Reddish, CBCP, CIA, CISA &lt;br /&gt;

Vice President &lt;br /&gt;

Readysmith Advisers Limited&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debra Reddish is Vice President and part owner of Readysmith Advisers Limited. Readysmith Advisers Limited provides a SaaS application for business continuity to small and medium sized businesses. The service product is called Readiness-as-a-Service (RaaS). RaaS provides a web-hosted, wiki technology solution to assist clients to prepare for response, management, and recovery from business disruptions and disasters. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Debra has over 20 years experience in the areas of business continuity planning, information technology audit and consulting, and operational risk assessment. Debra is owner of Reddish Consulting LLC, a business continuity consulting firm. Debra was formerly Vice President and Senior Consultant with Marsh Risk Consulting. Prior to Marsh, Debra was a Senior Manager with PricewaterhouseCoopers. Debra is a Certified Business Continuity Professional, Certified Internal Auditor, and a Certified Information Systems Auditor. Her professional membership organizations include: the Northeast Disaster Recovery Information Exchange (NEDRIX), Disaster Recovery Institute International (DRII), and the Association of Contingency Planners (ACP).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Feb2012Mtg/murphy.jpg" width="100" height="114" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Sean Murphy &lt;br /&gt;

President and CEO, Lootok (&lt;a href="http://www.lootok.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lootok.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sean Murphy is President and CEO of Lootok, a specialized business continuity management (BCM) consulting firm headquartered in New York City, with a network of consultants around the world. It was Sean&amp;rsquo;s vision that led to the establishment of Lootok as a new kind of business continuity consulting company&amp;mdash;a dynamic think-tank of seasoned experts using a cross-industry approach to challenge and reinvent conventional practices in the industry. Lootok offers a full suite of business continuity services to help businesses prepare and empower their people with the education and training they need to respond at time of event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sean has managed some of the most highly regarded business continuity practices, having served as a Vice President at Marsh &amp;amp; McLennan Risk Consulting and a Senior Consultant at Ernst &amp;amp; Young prior to founding Lootok. He has worked and trained nationally and internationally, with over with 13 years of consulting experience in business continuity and seven years in military contingency planning. An avid public speaker, Sean has presented at the E&amp;amp;Y International Intern Leadership Conference, Disaster Recovery Journal Conference, and Marsh Risk Management Concepts for New Risk Managers. His most recent engagements have included the 2011 RIMS Western Conference and the 2011 Global Conference on Disaster Risk; he is slated to speak at the 2012 Continuity Insights Management conference in April.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Feb2012Mtg/morency.jpg" width="100" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John P. Morency, CISA &lt;br /&gt;

Research Vice President, Systems, Security &amp;amp; Risk &lt;br /&gt;

Gartner Research&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John P Morency is a Gartner Research Vice President whose content focus the management of disaster recovery and IT resiliency. He also focuses on compliance, security and risk management issues related to the implementation of effective disaster recovery. His IT career spans 38 years, including senior management roles in software development, IT operations management and software product marketing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining Gartner, Mr. Morency spent 14 years in technical, marketing and IT industry consulting, managing a wide range of services that included total cost of ownership, network complexity and infrastructure consolidation analyses. In addition, he is a Certified Information Systems Auditor (CISA), was a member of the Emergency Management program at Boston University, and has also served as the Training Committee chairperson for the Boston chapter of the Information Systems Audit and Control Association (ISACA). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

He holds a BS in Computer Science Magna Cum Laude from the University of New Hampshire and has done graduate work at Babson College, Boston University and Union College. His is also a US patent holder in the area of server load balancing technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etffeb2012.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329872514000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976247000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Out of Chaos Comes Opportunity – Technology innovation and wealth creation out o</name><id>qnlkbcyqdbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329867000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32004482/</event_url></item>