<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Allston  (2nd Floor)</address_2><address_1>14 Harvard Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.355206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-783-8001</phone><name>Brazilian Immigrant Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1609586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.132675</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brazilian Immigrant Center would like to announce a fall session of its Portuguese classes. There will be &lt;strong&gt;basic, intermediate and a new advanced&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; level classes. All classes are taught in Portuguese by Professor Carmem Nicoli. This is a continuation of the program that started in May 2011. The Center was so excited by the turnout and interest that we&amp;nbsp;knew that we had to offer it again. The classes will start the week of October 3rd and &lt;strong&gt;continue for 10 weeks&lt;/strong&gt;. The cost will be &lt;strong&gt;$150.00.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basic classes will be 6:30-7:30 pm &lt;strong&gt;on Tuesdays,&lt;/strong&gt; Intermediate classes will follow on &lt;strong&gt;Tuesdays&lt;/strong&gt; from 7:30-9pm.&amp;nbsp; Advanced classes will be on &lt;strong&gt;Thursday&lt;/strong&gt; from 7:00-8:30pm.&amp;nbsp; There will a full refund after the first class only. Any questions, please feel free to ask!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To assure a spot in the class we suggest you send in payment in advance. Please send all payments to the Brazilian Immigrant Center attention Lydia Edwards at 14 Harvard Ave, 2nd Floor, Allston MA 02134. Please note that the payment is for the Portuguese Basic, Intermediate or Advanced class. Also, if you find that you are in the basic and prefer a challenge or think the advanced is too much of a challenge you can move the other level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the Best Lydia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions please contact me at 617 783 8001 ext. 113 or legal@braziliancenter.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lydia Edwards</member_name><member_id>7660990</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317774382000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315868133000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portuguese Lessons at the Brazilian Immigrant Center</name><id>33291842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317769200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/33291842/</event_url></item>