<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Intervale Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01543</zip><lat>42.415409</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rutland Prison Camp</name><city>Rutland</city><id>2149101</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.989708</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, folks,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't normally schedule two meetups to the same location so close together, but we had such a great investigation the first time we went that we want to go back. Members caught some great EVPs and had good responses on equipment--high EMF spikes, good Ovulus responses, and lots of flashlight activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's time to get back there before it gets too cold :'0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be unable to attend it myself because of a conflict, but Joni Mayhan, whose idea this was, has agreed to serve as leader for this meetup. She's been there numerous times, so she knows the area pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The investigation is scheduled fairly early,&amp;nbsp;and I know it'll be hard for some people to make it. We had to do this to give people a chance to explore the location before full dark.&amp;nbsp;If you are familiar with the site, you can probably find the meetup members. If you're not, then you really do need to get there before dark so you don't get lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;In case you didn't get to read the writeup for the previous investigation, I'm enclosing it below. Have fun and happy hunting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;__________________________________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 1903 to 1933 the Commonwealth of Massachusetts ran a farm and hospital for prisoners with tuberculosis in Rutland, MA. For 30 years it was a thriving farm, worked by the prisoners. It was believed that the fresh air and outdoor exercise would help to cure them of tuberculosis.&amp;nbsp; Here's a map showing the property when it was an active farm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rutlandland.org/gallery/PrisonCampBefore/slides/map.html"&gt;http://www.rutlandland.org/gallery/PrisonCampBefore/slides/map.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, all that remains of the farm and hospital&amp;nbsp;are the cellar holes of the hospital and other buildings, the root cellar, and a small building that served as solitary confinement.&amp;nbsp; A small cemetary also existed on the property. When the state closed the prison camp, it is rumored that the grave markers were removed but the bodies remained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This property is considered to be haunted, and many paranormal groups have conducted investigations here. Now it's our turn :')&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meet at 5:30pm at the Intervale Road entrance. Intervale Road is off Route 68 in Rutland, not far from the Hubbardston line. Follow Intervale Road for a few miles. You're looking for a dirt road on the right. The pullout is marked by a bulletin board that has maps and information about the Ware River Watershed. Please park outside the entrance and wait for the rest of the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT:&amp;nbsp; Wear comfortable shoes and be prepared to walk a fair amount over uneven ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flashlight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any equipment you want to use&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insect repellent (just in case)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This needs to be a fair-weather event. If it looks like it'll be raining on the date, I'll&amp;nbsp; send out a note and reschedule it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the Intervale Rd. entrance to the park, then convoy into the site and find a place to park.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joni </member_name><member_id>8972597</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316818029000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316211684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Return to Rutland Prison Camp</name><id>33850772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316813400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/33850772/</event_url></item>