<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The topic for this class is Meditation. There are many 'methods' of meditation that are taught out there. In this class the focus is on learning spiritual meditation for the purpose of discovering and deepening in your experience of God inside yourself. Meditation is the workbench of spiritual unfoldment. Come find out what that means and how you can begin to practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a six-week class series called Meditation &amp;amp; Mysticism: Experiencing God Within Yourself. It is a powerful introductory course designed for those who are seeking an inner experience of God through meditation. Classes include teachings on the practices of the mystics and how they can be applied in the modern western world. Mysticism refers to "the practice of knowing the reality of God through direct experience." It is certainly nothing new, as it has always been at the core of every religion and represents a more inner, experiential way of coming to know God and the spiritual world. We offer this series as an opportunity for you to discover whether the mystical path might be right for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time will be spent teaching the principles of meditation that will allow you to move deeper than the body, beyond thinking and emotions, and into the reality of God's peace and presence within. Each class begins with a guided meditation that will help you begin to learn to&amp;nbsp; meditate or will help you deepen the spiritual dimension of your current practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This class teaches an introduction to mysticism in the Christian tradition, though the truths are the same as those taught in all mystical traditions. Everyone is welcome, no matter what your previous experience or religious background may be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no charge for this introductory class, but RSVP is required. Late admittance may be permissible (after the first week of the class), but check with the organizer to be sure. Completion of this series can lead into more advanced classes for those who are interested. &lt;br /&gt;

 The class is offered on six consecutive Tuesday evenings at 7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328665749000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325813793000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation and Mysticism: Experiencing God Inside Yourself - class 4</name><id>46881332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328661000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/46881332/</event_url></item>