<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>101 Churchill Hall </address_2><address_1>360 Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.339928</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northeastern University</name><city>Boston</city><id>783217</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089546</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Recent High Tech University Spin-Outs – Who is funding these deals and why?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note New Meeting Location&lt;br /&gt;Northeastern University&lt;br /&gt;240 Dockser Hall&lt;br /&gt;360 Huntington Avenue, Boston MA  02115&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Overview&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The EntreTech Forum’s October 21st panel focuses on the Forum’s core theme: Given the wealth of research and technology generated by our nation’s leading universities, how does this academic strength translate into commercial strength? Our October 21st panel includes a diverse group of company founders and CEOs leading new developments in life sciences, nanotechnology and micromachining, who will share their experiences on extracting their company’s underlying technologies out of a university environment and gathering adequate funding to launch their ideas, platforms and products into wider commercial use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey P. McCarthy, Northbridge Venture Partners  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. McCarthy joined North Bridge Venture Partners in December 1998. Prior to joining North Bridge, he was the President and CEO of New Oak Communications, a leading provider of extranet access switches. Once New Oak was acquired by Bay Networks, a Nortel Networks line of business, Jeff served as Vice President and General Manager of the Access Division. Prior to New Oak Jeff was the Vice President of Sales and Business Development at Cadia Networks, a developer of ATM concentrator products for the service provider marketplace. Prior to Cadia, Jeff spent eight years at Wellfleet Communications/Bay Networks where he held various senior management positions, including Vice President of Carrier Operations. Jeff is a graduate of Northeastern University, School of Management (Magna Cum Laude), and received his MBA (magna cum laude) from Bentley College. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aram T. Salzman,  President &amp;amp; CEO - NovoBiotic Pharmaceuticals, LLC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Salzman is CEO of NovoBiotic Pharmaceuticals, a privately held, early stage pharmaceutical company focused on the development of novel antibiotics, using a unique, proprietary method to isolate and cultivate previously unculturable microorganisms in the laboratory. NovoBiotic’s patented Cultursys® in-situ microbiological growth chamber technology was licensed from Northeastern University. The vast majority of antibiotics and many of the drugs on the market today were originally derived from soil bacteria and fungi. These microorganisms are one of the richest sources of chemical diversity and novel pharmaceuticals. The Cultursys chamber, described in Science in May of 2002, allows previously unculturable bacteria and fungi to grow in a simulated natural environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Salzman has more then 17 years of experience in Healthcare and Life Sciences Business Development, Marketing, and Sales. He founded NovoBiotic Pharmaceuticals with Kim Lewis, and Slava Epstein in April of 2003. Prior to NovoBiotic, he was employed at Cerner Corporation, the leading U.S. supplier of healthcare information technology. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rick MIcak, Founder, President, CTO - Boston Microsystems, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Mlcak is founder and president of Boston Microsystems, and leads technology development. He is a co-inventor of BMS’ novel SiC micromachining and sensor technologies, and the world expert in their combined use. With 17 years in microsystems design, development and commercialization, he has 11 patents spanning micro-fabrication technologies, advanced materials, and MEMS sensor designs and methods. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Clay, CEO Xtalic&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Clay joined Xtalic as CEO in March of 2008. Xtalic focuses on providing unique nanostructured alloys that provide corrosion and wear resistance and aesthetic benefits across a wide range of metal coating applications Prior to joining Xtalic Tom spent 10 years growing another successful MIT start up, Z Corporation, from early commercialization phase through to market leadership in the 3D printing space. Tom served Z Corporation as President, CEO and board member. Tom is a former Airborne Ranger and led reconnaissance teams while stationed at Fort Bragg, North Carolina. Tom holds a BA from Princeton University in Mathematics and an MBA with high distinction (Baker Scholar) from the Harvard Business School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tim Surgenor, President, CEO, Director - Cyberkinetics&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Surgenor joined Cyberkinetics in 2003. Cyberkinetics focuses on commercializing products based on two neurotechnology platforms: neural stimulation for tissue regeneration and neural sensing and decoding. Mr. Surgenor previously worked with Haemonetics Corporation, a medical device company where he was EVP responsibile for business development, global marketing, quality assurance and regulatory affairs. While at Haemonetics, Mr. Surgenor was an active member of the investor relations team. Mr. Surgenor was also previously President the cell therapy division of Genzyme Corporation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register Online at &lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.entretechf...&lt;/a&gt;, walk ins are welcome too&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Open to all</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Georgia</member_name><member_id>6917121</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226966944000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221608027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recent High Tech University Spin-Outs – Who is funding these deals and why?</name><id>8771489</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224628200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/8771489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/3/global_4559507.jpeg</photo_url></item>