<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's have a picnic after work on the lawn, talk, share and support each other and have fun if people want to bring games or something.  Let's make it short and simple, maybe for an hour or less, see how it goes.  Bring dinner or a snack, maybe to share or buy something at Panera, they have a nice variety of healthy food, its good and reasonable, maybe they'll sponsor us?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a large lawn at the front / end of Panera near the fountain and the theater.  Bring a sheet or chair to sit on.  There are tables outside with umbrellas and chairs on the side if the lawn is damp.  Let's meet at the lawn first so people can find us.  If the weather's bad we can meet at the fireplace inside Panera at the front / end by the fountain and decide if people feel comfortable talking there or want to go somewhere else.  There are a bunch of free parking spaces along the side of Panera and a free parking garage so parking is easy.  This is near the Arsenal Mall and Target in Watertown, at least one bus stops there for those who don't have a car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've had a couple of good, small meetups and more people are joining, which is great.  It shows how important this meetup is to people.  I'd like to see more participate in the forum here and go to the meetups to make this group a success.  This group is only as good as the people who participate by offering support to one another.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Outside Panera on the grass by the fountain at the front / end near the theater</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244062197000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242783557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picnic, talk and support each other</name><id>10451431</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243375200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/10451431/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/2/global_8675010.jpeg</photo_url></item>