<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;Sarah's cell phone is 857-453-0210 for those of you who need her that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;It seems that Friday is the unofficial NoOrg Day! 3 in a row, with this puppy here!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/members/8078853/"&gt;Sarah&lt;/a&gt; wants to see &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809883886/info"&gt;Revolutionary Road&lt;/a&gt;. I'm saving the movie for a date with my hubby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Frank and April, a married couple in the 1950s, have always seen themselves as special, different, ready and willing to live their lives based on higher ideals. So, as soon as they move into their new house on Revolutionary Road, they proudly declare their independence from the suburban inertia that surrounds them and determine never to be trapped by the social confines of their era. Yet for all their charm, beauty and irreverence, the Wheelers find themselves becoming exactly what they didn't expect: a good man with a routine job whose nerve has gone missing; a less-than-happy homemaker starving for fulfillment and passion; an American family with lost dreams, like any other. Driven to change their fates, April hatches an audacious plan to start all over again, to leave the comforts of Connecticut behind for the great unknown of Paris. But when the plan is put in motion, each spouse is pushed to extremes--one to escape whatever the cost, the other to save all that they have, no matter the compromises.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;What's a NoOrg??&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; you ask? Well, a NoOrg is a movie meetup that looks a lot like a regular Framingham Movie Meetup, but it's member-organized. There may not be an official organizer there (but if one of us shows up, you all get the discounted ticket price of $8.50), but the fun goes on without us. Whoever wants to goes out to TGI Fridays (or any other nearby restaurant) after the movie can, just like a regular FMM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP so Sarah knows who to look for. Ticket price (if George or Lesley doesn't show up) is $10.25 now, I believe. But AMC doesn't care whether you have exact change. They're more magnanimous than I yam! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah will update her RSVP or comment on the meetup a day or two before the movie, so y'all know when to show up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enjoy your picture show!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. The first person to name what movie &amp;quot;Enjoy your picture show!&amp;quot; is from gets a free drink the next time we go out. If you give me any details of the scene, you get extra credit.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Sarah looks a little like Dana, actually...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235007424000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232764414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NoOrg -- Revolutionary Road</name><id>9589390</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233360000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9589390/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>