<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please take a moment to read the ENTIRE update, as I have updated  the new meetup dates/locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEETUPS AT 1:00PM&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;HAPPY HOLIDAYS TO ALL!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope everyone is recovering from the Thanksgiving Holiday. Please note our next SUNDAY meetup will be held at Doggie Day ONLY @ 1PM!  Please feel free to dress your pup in their finest holiday gear or winter coat:) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Holiday Wish-List Drive&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefiting the Lowell Humane Society&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To our group members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I organize several dog-related meetups in Boston and each year we have a competition between our groups and other Boston dog-related meetups to see which group can donate the most to a local, dog-related non-profit.  The reason I am reaching out to you is that this year, I contacted the Animal Rescue League of Boston to be the recipient of our 'challenge' and they had encouraged me to contact the Lowell Humane Society, because with the economy the way it is, they are in DESPERATE need of help.  For a shelter to request that another shelter be the recipient speaks volume.  Eventhough they are not in my community, we are extending our fund-raising efforts to benefit their shelter this 2008 holiday season.  I am asking that eventhough they may not be in your community, please consider joining our 'challenge.'  If you chose not to join, please consider having your group donate to a shelter in your area, most of which are in need, this year in particular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what I do:&lt;br /&gt;Each meet-up group, beginning Friday, November 28, 2008 begins donating merchandise or gift cards from the Lowell Humane Society Wishlist Website.  The Wishlist is comprised of the following; gift cards to Wal-Mart, Petco, Petsmart, Market Basket, Staples, Home Depot, Agway and Target.  These gift cards are used to buy blankets, towels, office supplies, hand sanitizer, Bleach, paper towels....the list goes on and on and on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also donate any of these items yourself, but gift cards are the best so they can purchase exactly what they need.  $5, $10, $50; any denomination helps; every penny helps.  If you cannot afford to monetarily donate, go through your home and donate towels you may have not used or toys your pet may not have found interest in.  Truly, EVERYTHING will help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind there are small animals in need, not just dogs and cats; therefore, items for bunnies, ferrets, birds, guinea pigs, etc are also in demand; this is where the grocery store gift cards come in handy for fresh fruits, vegetables, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our challenge runs through Sunday, December 21, 2008.  If you are a meet-up group in the Boston area and wish to have your members drop their merchandise off at the location we use, the DoggieDay Play Center located at 400 Tremont St in the South End, all donations will be donated in your meet-up groups name.  If you wish to collect the merchandise yourselves, or drop it off at the shelter directly, donate it in your group's name.  We want them to know that our community is there for them!  We will either drop off all the donations at the shelter on Monday, December 22, 2008 or have them come pick them up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With their dedication and sacrifices to these animals 365 days each year, please join us in making this Holiday Season happy for all those volunteers, because they are all volunteers, at the Lowell Humane Society and their animals who need us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PHOTOS WITH SANTA TO BE HELD DEC. 6-7!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;are you ready for your close-up?....&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;5th Annual &amp;quot;Paws and Claus&amp;quot;, photos with Santa&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Rob Galeski p: 617-426-7387 x221  e:santapaws@doggieday.com&lt;br /&gt;  Jen Wooliscroft p: 617-426-9170 e:jwooliscroft@arlboston.org&lt;br /&gt;Where: DoggieDay Play Center, 400 Tremont Street, Boston, MA 02116&lt;br /&gt;When:  Saturday, December 6th and Sunday, Decenber 7th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Time:  10am until 4pm [each day]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Boston, MA,&lt;br /&gt;Dashing through the snow, in a one-horse open sleigh.....Santa is appearing at-----DoggieDay, [www.doggieday.com/christmas]....for his annual &amp;quot;Paws and Claus&amp;quot; photo opp's to raise money for one of Boston's most recognized shelter's, helping animals in need since 1899, The Animal Rescue League of Boston.  The donations raised will specifically benefit their CeCe Fund.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; At this time, we will resume outdoor Meetups when the weather improves in the Spring....Please stay tuned for future updates. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indoor meetup will be held at Doggie day &lt;b&gt;(1-3pm)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should anyone have any questions, feel free to contact me.&lt;br /&gt;Susana&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231700527000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226250763000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua December Meetup</name><id>9125814</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229277600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/9125814/</event_url></item>