<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>455 Highland Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01331</zip><lat>42.581253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 249-6763</phone><name>Red Apple Farm</name><city>Phillipston</city><id>395133</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.145026</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Stewardship Workshop, April 14 When: Saturday, April 14, 2012 -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:00am - 12:00pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Red Apple Farm, Phillipston&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help provide data for New England projects tracking the incidence of invasive species and the effects of changing temperatures on local habitats. Presenters Stacy Kilb and John O&amp;rsquo;Keefe will explain how to spot warning signs of invasives and tabulate data on the local environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants will be asked to note down observations they make on future hikes and report the data back to the US Phenological Network and to Beetle Detectives. Asian longhorned BeetleInvasive species pose serious threats to our landscape, as does the potential for climate change, and citizen volunteers are urgently needed to track both locally. The Asian Longhorned Beetle was introduced to the region in the 1990s and has been a serious threat to hardwoods ever since. Their calling card is the large circular exit holes they leave in tree trunks. You may also notice purple triangular boxes hanging from ash trees. These are lures for the Emerald Ash Borer, another invader being tracked locally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Citizen Stewardship Workshop at Red Apple Farm aims to train volunteers to monitor invasives and climate change. You, too, can become a Citizen Steward and help our forests by tracking phenological change and looking for invasives in your own area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To volunteer, or for more information, contact AmeriCorps Outreach Coordinator, Aja Lippincott, at outreach_americorps(at)mountgrace.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Please RSVP here and also send an email to register for this event with Aja Lippincott at&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;outreach_ameri&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;corps@mountgra&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;ce.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mountgrace.org/stewardship-workshop-april-14" target="_blank"&gt;http://mountgrace.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please indicate that you have registered for this event either in the comment section or change(update) your RSVP with this comment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Register Now Maple Sugaring 3/31/12 Stewardship Workshop 4/14/12 Volunteer Day 4/21/12&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334414286000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331688133000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stewardship Workshop(Recognize invasive insects while on our hikes)</name><id>56258522</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334408400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/56258522/</event_url></item>