<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>449 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373294</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.349.4040</phone><name>Main Cambridge Public Library</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>767569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.111112</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This lecture is part of a public lecture series that is a collaboration between the Cambridge Public Library and Grow Native Massachusetts. It is free and, of course, open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href="http://www.grownativemass.org/"&gt;http://www.grownativemass.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****Nibbling on Native Plants in Your Backyard and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lecture by Russ Cohen, expert forager and author of &lt;em&gt;Wild Plants I Have Known . . . and Eaten&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Many native "wild" plants are edible and nutritious--suitable for growing in your home landscape or found in other locales. Come learn to identify the species most suited to your culinary adventures, selecting only the edible portions of each plant. Become familiar with seasons of availability and guidelines for environmentally responsible foraging. Russ Cohen has been pursuing edible wild plants since high school and teaching others to forage for thirty-seven years. With luck, you may win a taste of his black walnut baklava, made from locally gathered nuts!*****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture will last about an hour, with about 30 minutes afterward for Q&amp;amp;A (total time about 90 minutes). Doors open at 6:30 p.m.; the lecture starts at 7:00 p.m. Seating is on a first come, first served basis. The closest T option is the Harvard Square stop on the Red Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be at the library between 6:00 and 6:15. Meet me inside the library, inside the lecture room. We may not be able to sit together because seating is based on first come, first served, but if you can't find me, my bright red backpack, *and* my meetup sign inside the lecture room before the lecture, look for me afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. I've been hearing&amp;nbsp;that a lot of people carry bright red backpacks, but how many of them are carrying meetup signs, too?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If people would like to go out in Harvard Square after the lecture, we can do that. We'll decide on Wednesday. Options for going out after the lecture:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Algiers Coffee House, 40 Brattle Street, 617.492.1557&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Harvard's Brew House, 33 Dunster Street, 617.868.3585&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you Wednesday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my bright red backpack *and* my meetup sign. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307022173000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306601074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lecture: Nibbling on Native Plants in Your Backyard and Beyond</name><id>20066961</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306966500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/20066961/</event_url></item>