<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>112 Canal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364580</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 896-2337 </phone><name>Boston Beer Works</name><city>Boston</city><id>1093898</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060198</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please join us for Blue Wave Marketing's "Integrated Marketing Strategy &amp;amp; Analytics" Event at Boston Beer Works on Canal St. in Boston (near the TD Garden and North Station). We will be featuring thought leadership presentations from two marketing strategy experts, Matt Flanagan and Victor Juri, and providing complimentary drinks, appetizers, billiards and a chance to win two tickets to see the Boston Celtics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matt Flanagan will discuss "three big ideas" for integrated marketers, and show companies looking to integrate their marketing program how to use data analytics to help them succeed. His presentation will include a quick look at some new tools on the market, how to approach visualization of complex data and ideas on how to choose - and integrate - marketing channels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victor Juri from Ayantek will show how companies can utilize social channels to run integrated campaigns through Facebook, Twitter and other social channels. How the different social campaign tools can amplify reach, how their analytics help you identify metrics &amp;amp; measure campaign success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will be held in the upstairs private function room at Boston Beer Works, and there's street parking and parking at the Government Center Garage nearby. To RSVP, for more information about the event, questions and directions, please email Max at Blue Wave at: mgrigoryan@bluewavemarketing.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350600087000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Marketing Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Marketing-Learning-Group</urlname><id>1338478</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Marketing Learning Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348612397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beer, Billiards and Business:  Integrated Marketing Strategy and Analytics</name><id>84074602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350588600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Marketing-Learning-Group/events/84074602/</event_url></item>