<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>**Note: &lt;b&gt;This group is for folks who are currently integrating Abraham teachings into their lives.  Intention is to support each other in putting into practice Abraham's teachings.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are new to the &amp;quot;Abraham&amp;quot; materials &lt;i&gt;and ready to actively integrate the teachings&lt;/i&gt;, you're welcome to join us.  We strongly suggest that you take the time to go to the following &amp;quot;free&amp;quot; resources to learn about Abraham Hicks:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) &amp;quot;About Abraham Hicks: the Teachings in Brief&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/teachings_brief.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) &amp;quot;Introduction to Abraham Hicks&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/mp3downloads.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(3) Free Video Clips on LOA by Abraham Hicks&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.abraham-hicks.com/lawofattractionsource/videos.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.abraham-hi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some light snacks &amp;amp; refreshments will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;To help keep the cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 7 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suzy Spivey and Susan Conley, BostonLOA members and &amp;quot;Abraham&amp;quot; enthusiasts&lt;/b&gt;, look forward to facilitating our continuing practice of the Abraham-Hicks materials. Come to share, have fun, raise vibration and focus &amp;quot;downstream&amp;quot; to a more joyful, fulfilling life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone who attended the Abraham-Hicks workshops in Burlington over the weekend of 6/20 &amp;amp; 6/21, we will begin by sharing thoughts and impressions of the workshop with the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, we will be picking up where we left off last month using the &lt;b&gt;Emotional Guidance System and how to better utilize it to create fulfilling relationships.&lt;/b&gt; We will listen to one question from an Abraham-Hicks workshop regarding Relationship issues and hear how Abraham guides the questioner to turn downstream and focus on the Vibrational Escrow of the relationship.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then turn the focus to each of us personally.  We will work with the process of the &lt;b&gt;“Book of Positive Aspects”&lt;/b&gt; regarding an issue in our own lives, making lists of those things we do like and do appreciate, so that our focus is downstream.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After sharing with the group what is in our Book of Positive Aspects, we will then do another exercise to move even further up the Emotional Scale and do a written &lt;b&gt;Rampage of Appreciation&lt;/b&gt; regarding the issue(s) on which we are focused.  These two exercises will leave us feeling better and thinking better feeling thoughts so that we can get more into our Vortex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(1) We ask that each participant bring your own copy of the book &lt;b&gt; Ask and It Is Given&lt;/b&gt; if you have it, since the exercises we will be doing and the Emotional Guidance Scale are all contained within that book and it can be utilized as a reference while doing the exercises.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Also, please bring a &lt;b&gt;notebook or notepad&lt;/b&gt; so that you can begin (or add to) your Book of Positive Aspects and Rampage of Appreciation.  There will be opportunity to decorate the cover of your notebook should you so desire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be molding the clay here, focusing downstream on positive thoughts that feel better and having fun with our individual desires……as Abraham says, &amp;quot;We are always evolving so you never get it wrong because you never get it done!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246135855000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244869538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Abraham Hicks Practice Group</name><id>10642071</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245884400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/10642071/</event_url></item>