<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you long to be in a relationship with someone amazing?  Someone you're &lt;em&gt;wildly&lt;/em&gt; attracted to?  Someone that totally "gets" you and accepts you just the way you are (without trying to fix, change, or turn you into someone you're not)?  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you answered "yes" to any of these questions, then you're going to love this.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;You see, 2011 is just starting, and this is the perfect chance start fresh and go for what you really want.  Would you like to get better results than you got last year?  If so, then you need to give yourself the gift of learning better tools and strategies for attracting and keeping your ideal partner.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;In this unique event, you'll learn a proven system for attracting incredible, new relationship prospects into your life anytime you want.  This is the same system I use myself, and it's proven to be highly successful (not to mention easy and fun).  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to develop an "attraction web" that automatically puts you in the way of interesting singles that are looking for a relationship.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The single most important ability you must develop in order to be interesting and attractive to other people.  Once you master this, you'll have a never ending supply of quality people wanting to spend more time with you.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 simple secrets I learned from studying the law of attraction that draws your ideal dating prospects to you like a magnet.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The "secret question" that everyone's subconscious mind is asking when you first meet them, and how this one question determines if they will even consider dating you or not.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple steps you can take right away to make yourself more physically attractive.  If you do this, be prepared to get a lot more compliments on your appearance (and you'll get a lot more dates as well).  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED  &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members.  We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, January 30th available.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that afternoon free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:15pm for registration and personal networking.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$20 cash &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen &amp;amp; notepad &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Warmly,  &lt;br /&gt;Eric  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-903-7371&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Edgemont</member_name><member_id>12651136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296533432000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295582918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Meet And Attract Your Ideal Mate</name><id>16128530</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296419400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/16128530/</event_url></item>