<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>810 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.312598</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Never Ending Books</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1433507</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.914600</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;ISTVAN PETER B'RACZ&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Uncertainty Music Series&lt;br /&gt;8pm $5.00 suggested donation&lt;br /&gt;Never Ending Books - 810 State Street - New Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     The Uncertainty Music Series is a New Haven-based creative music series run by composer Carl Testa that has been presenting concert events since September 2007. The goal of the series is to provide a venue for local and regional artists that may not have the opportunity to present their work elsewhere. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         Istvan studied composition, electronic music, and conducting at the Hartt School of Music, piano at the Yale School of Music, Franz Liszt Academy of Music in Budapest Hungary (awarded a Fulbright Grant), composition and piano at the Oberlin Conservatory, Neighborhood Music School (NMS), and the Educational Center for the Arts (ECA). He taught piano and composition as well as music technology at Central CT State University, Southern CT State University, as well as at ECA and NMS. Currently, he teaches piano, composition and theory at NMS. He also records, edits, and produces CD/DVDs of concerts and for audition. &lt;br /&gt;         His works have been performed in many venues throughout the United States, as well as Europe. He especially enjoys working with performers and composers closely, and is the Artistic Director and founder of SOUNDunderGROUND (a concert series devoted to new music, composers, performers, poets, and other artists). He composes in many different styles and mediums: electronic, avant garde, electronica, orchestral works, sound mass, tonal, atonal, creating soundtracks, ambient environments, scores for film and games, folk-music-influences, new-agey, music of the spheres, hard-core, punk. There is often some kind of aesthetic/philosophy (or a process/game) that operates as structural glue in his works. Sometimes it is not outwardly obvious. &lt;br /&gt;          In his words: “I find that the essence of ‘composing’ is in the overseeing of large-scale blue-prints of works, and delighting in detail. Its an ever-changing process which is what has me ‘addicted’ “. As a performer, Istvan performs new works for the keyboard and various electronic elements mixing styles, traditions and influences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mac.com/istvan_bracz/BRACZ_MAIN/BRACZ_MAIN.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://web.mac.com/is...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can have a drink after the show...Christopher Martins maybe?&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear the BW scarf with piano keys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295126662000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290210430000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ISTVAN PETER B'RACZ</name><id>15504285</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294533900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/15504285/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/a/global_19740954.jpeg</photo_url></item>