<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi NLPers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First of all, I need to apologize ? we are moving this month?s meeting to February 28.  Although NLP allows you to do many amazing things, being in two places at once is not one of those things, and I will be in New Orleans with Habitat for Humanity next week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Secondly, a reminder of a new feature for our meetup: we will be starting the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP (or those who want a review), and also for those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we we will get rolling with the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Main Event: Language Patterns&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had spent one meetup on language patterns last year, but the topic is so rich, we?re going to re-visit it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will briefly review some of the basic language patterns from last year (verb tenses, presuppositions, nominalizations) and then explore some new ones: likely patterns are analog/digital shifts, reversing presuppositions, and/but, and forced choice.  If those names don?t mean anything to you, don?t worry: it will all become clear by the end of the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we have time, I will also demonstrate the Fast Allergy cure.  Its a pretty elegant, very effective technique (it cured me of a wheat allergy in one session).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206130066000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200616792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming February Meetup</name><id>7139348</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204241400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/7139348/</event_url></item>