<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/4/c/event_180346412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Whoo---hoo!  Arnie is back.  Now that he stopped being governor, he can go back to being a silly action film actor.   This will be classic, lots of bad one liners and of course lots of gun play and car chases.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;Showtime is 5:30, I will be at the theater by 4:30 and we will go in for seats at 5.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; The next show isn't till 8:15 which wouldn't leave much time for an after event.   Oh well, maybe I will get home before midnight.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, I arrive at the theater an hour before the show to start gathering people, and we head in for seats about 30 minutes before the show, so we can sit together.  This also allows us to take turns getting snacks, etc., before the previews start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #9B30FF"&gt;Because the group usually sees movies opening weekend, it is a good idea to buy your tickets in advance, especially if there is a lot of buzz about the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.  We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; January 18, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt;Lionsgate &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt;Kim Jee-Woon &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt;Andrew Knauer, Jeffrey Nachmanoff &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger, Zach Gilford, Forest Whitaker, Luis Guzman, Rodrigo Santoro, Johnny Knoxville, Jaimie Alexander, Eduardo Noriega, Peter Stormare, Harry Dean Stanton, Genesis Rodriguez &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.thelaststandfilm.com/" target="_blank"&gt;TheLastStandfilm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Schwarzenegger stars as Sheriff Owens, a man who has resigned himself to a life of fighting what little crime takes place in sleepy border town Sommerton Junction after leaving his LAPD post following a bungled operation that left him wracked with failure and defeat after his partner was crippled. After a spectacular escape from an FBI prisoner convoy, the most notorious, wanted drug kingpin in the hemisphere is hurtling toward the border at 200 mph in a specially outfitted car with a hostage and a fierce army of gang members. He is headed, it turns out, straight for Summerton Junction, where the whole of the U.S. law enforcement will have their last opportunity to make a stand and intercept him before he slips across the border forever. At first reluctant to become involved, and then counted out because of the perceived ineptitude of his small town force, Owens ultimately accepts responsibility for one of the most daring face offs in cinema history.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358974251000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353102304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Last Stand (5:30 Show)</name><id>91715762</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358631000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/91715762/</event_url></item>