<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Organizer: Paul&lt;br /&gt;Contact: &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/513/members/3108784/"&gt;http://photo.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Target Audience: Anyone who is a car lover.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's not to love about classic cars - even if cars aren't your thing, who can resist the chrome, the whitewalls, and fuzzy dice. Much to consider at a Car photo shoot, light, reflection, refraction, shadow, balance and frame all in spades. These cars have so much detail &amp;amp; class that both the portrait and macro shooter will have a feast!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I shot these at a recent show there: &lt;a href="http://birdman.itsamac.com/~pmaker/musclecars/"&gt;Muscle Cars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larz Anderson Auto Museum&lt;br /&gt;Home to America?s Oldest Automobile Collection&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ford / Lincoln Day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Ford and sister company cars are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by the New England Lincolns Club, the Ford Motor Company and the Ford Dealers of New England. The Museum invites all Ford and sister marques (35 years and older) both classic and custom to celebrate the Ford Motor Company at Vintage Ford Day. The Day will feature six concours classes: Antique, Classic, Hot Rod, Custom, Racer, and Antique Truck, on one field. For those cars 34 years and younger, the museum will provide a fun field. First and Second Place People¹s Choice Awards will be presented for each of the six classes. Registration is $10.00 per car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;August 26, 2007, 10:00 AM to 2:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Admission: $10.00 per Adult and $5.00 per child&lt;br /&gt;Cub Scouts in uniform get in free, parents receive a $5.00 discount and siblings receive a $2.00 discount. &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188309844000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186972224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Larz Anderson Ford-Lincoln Day</name><id>6170216</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188136800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/6170216/</event_url></item>