<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for our regular monthly meeting where columnist Dianne Williamson from the Telegram and Gazzette will speak to the group.  Her topic will be on &amp;quot;Religion and the Press&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, Greater Worcester Humanists is having a drive to provide school supplies for needy families in the Worcester area. We were told by the staff of the food pantry that recently opened at the UU Church of Worcester that there is a real need for school supplies, and we thought this would be an appropriate need for our group to address.  Therefore we'll be taking donated school supplies at this meeting on June 9 (at our usual meeting spot, the UU Church of Worcester, 90 Holden Street, Worcester) and at our summer outing on June 27 at Rutland State Park.  Supplies would include: Pencils, colored pencils, pens, markers/crayons, notebooks, loose-leaf paper, crafts supplies, and backpacks. Thanks for helping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Public are invited to attend and admission is free.  However, feel free to make a donation at the door or even join Greater Worcester Humanists!  Membership is currently $30 per year.  Please see Don Guyton or Chris Moran for details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the formal meeting will start at 7 p.m., but doors will open at 6:30 for anyone who wants to come early and socialize.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246122282000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242238373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GWH June Meeting - Talk by Dianne Williamson of the Telegram &amp; Gazette</name><id>10403286</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244588400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/10403286/</event_url></item>