<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Volunteer-run and not-for-profit notloB Parlour Concerts approaches its sixth year anniversary of presenting local and touring old-time, traditional and revival folk, Celtic, bluegrass and country blues artists to audiences at the historic (and intimate – just 40 seats) Loring-Greenough House, 12 South Street, Jamaica Plain by presenting rising young acoustic stars Bronwyn Keith-Hynes and Catherine Bowness, supported by George Clements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BRONWYN KEITH-HYNES &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.bronwynkeithhynes.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bronwynkeithhynes.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Bronwyn Keith-Hynes is an award-winning fiddler from Charlottesville, Virginia. She began fiddling at the age of three and has studied with many wonderful musicians on the folk music scene including Beth Telford, Jerry Holland, Cleek Schrey, Matt Glaser, John McGann and Darol Anger. Bronwyn is a fluent player of Irish music, bluegrass and old time music. She has performed throughout the U.S, Ireland and France and has traveled to Ireland extensively to study with local traditional musicians. She has been featured on Irish RTE One television and the Irish Comhaltas Live Programme. At the age of sixteen she was awarded a scholarship to attend Berklee College of Music in Boston and in December 2012 graduated with a professional &lt;br /&gt;

diploma in violin performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bronwyn has won numerous fiddle contests in Irish and Scottish fiddle styles. In 2006 at the age of fourteen, Bronwyn placed third in the Open Division of the U.S. National Scottish Fiddle Championship. She holds the 2007 Virginia State Fiddle Champion title and has also won &lt;br /&gt;

at the 2008 and 2009 Mid-West Fleadh Cheoil fiddle competition. She has been a first place winner at the Lowell Fiddle and Banjo Contest 2010, 2011 and 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CATHERINE BOWNESS &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.bbbowness.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.bbbowness.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Catherine (BB) Bowness has been playing the banjo for the last ten years making frequent commutes from New Zealand to study, perform and teach banjo in the USA. In 2006 she won the Uncle Dave Macon banjo contest in Murfreesboro, Tennessee and was invited back in 2007 to tour with Colorado bluegrass band, Long Road Home. BB has performed throughout New Zealand and Australia with fellow bluegrass comrades, George Jackson and Daniel Watkins, in a banjo duet with Tenor banjoist, Alex Borwick and most recently with Cy Winstanley and Vanessa McGowan of Tattletale Saints. In 2009, BB was the first banjo student to be accepted at the New Zealand school of music where she completed a BMus majoring in Jazz Performance. Since graduating, BB has relocated to Boston, MA where she is performing, teaching and enjoying an amazing acoustic music scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GEORGE CLEMENTS &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://gwclements.tumblr.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://gwclements.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

George Clements is a guitarist and singer/songwriter from central Massachusetts. His musical influences include folk, bluegrass, celtic, classical, and jazz. He is a current student at Berklee College of Music and is an active player in the Roots Music program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is by suggested donation, with 100% of the proceeds going to the artists and to cover production costs. Coffee and pastries are provided by locally owned neighborhood businesses JP Licks and Fiores Bakery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bronwyn Keith-Hynes and Catherine Bowness w/ George Clements &lt;br /&gt;

Concert and Workshops &lt;br /&gt;

Loring-Greenough House, 12 South Street, JP &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday, March 9, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

Doors 7:30, Concert 8:00 &lt;br /&gt;

Suggested concert donation $10 plus $1 preservation fee &lt;br /&gt;

20% discount for Loring-Greenough/JPTC members &lt;br /&gt;

Separate admission fiddle, banjo and guitar workshops offered prior to the concert, $10 each - reservation required. &lt;br /&gt;

Combined concert and workshop $18 regular, $15 member. &lt;br /&gt;

Workshop info at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/261679480628136/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/261679480628136/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;notloB website - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Reservations - notlobreservations@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

Concert announcements - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== &lt;br /&gt;

notloB Folk Concerts has produced not-for-profit concerts in the greater Boston area since 2007. The series is volunteer-run; 100% of the donations go to the musicians and production expenses. Admission is by suggested minimum donation. A suggested minimum donation (varies by concert) is requested. If you cannot support the artists with dollars, please consider volunteering your time and energy. Your donations cover venue rental, sound system rental, sound engineer, publicity and other production expenses. 100% of the balance goes to the artists (many of whom travel many miles). Sometimes there are shortfalls, so extra donations are gladly accepted. If you cannot afford the suggested donation amount, consider volunteering! And please, no credit cards or checks, cash is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography, video recording, &amp;amp; sound recording. No still, video or sound recording is permitted without permission of the artist and the house. If you would like to share photos of past concerts, email the pictures and/or web link to notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In this era of pop-driven acoustic music, notloB is keeping the folk tradition alive." ~ Jack Hardy&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363196681000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360806922000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bronwyn Keith-Hynes &amp; Catherine Bowness w/ George Clements</name><id>104525772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362877200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/104525772/</event_url></item>