<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Commercial Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02188</zip><lat>42.220242</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Labor Guild</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>13169522</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.966980</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/f/a/event_209275802.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No RSVP's! Register @&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wpwkshp1.eventbrite.com/#"&gt;http://wpwkshp1.eventbrite.com/#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curious about WordPress and how it can help you build and manage a better blog or website?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WordPress is a state-of-the-art web publishing platform, developed by hundreds of community volunteers and used by over 25 million people. Best of all, WordPress is free! With thousands of themes and plug-ins available on the web, anyone can launch a feature-rich website in minutes. First, you will learn the fundamentals of how WordPress works, how to get it up and running, and how to start publishing content immediately. Then we will explore the Administrator's Dashboard, including how to organize your content and configure certain features &amp;amp; behaviors of your site. Finally, you will learn how to install themes and plug-ins to alter the appearance of your site and add additional functionality for improved social integration, search engine optimization, and backup/security. (Note: We will be working with the self-hosted version of WordPress at &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://wordpress.org"&gt;http://wordpress.org&lt;/a&gt;, not the hosted service at &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://wordpress.com"&gt;http://wordpress.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $60&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://wpwkshp1.eventbrite.com/"&gt;Sign-up for the Beginners Workshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Workshop Presenters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kurt Eng is a co-organizer of the Boston WordPress Meetup and Founding Organizer of WordCamp Boston. Kurt has been very active in podcasting and video, publishing free content to enable others to learn. Kurt focuses on people beginning WordPress and blogging, empowering them with the knowledge and enthusiasm to get started from installation to themes to writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon Bishop is a Web Developer, Public Speaker and Internet Marketing Specialist from Boston, MA. I specialize in the understanding and developing of up and coming web technologies. As a social-networking analyst, my expertise with online social patterns and the usage of interactive communication technologies allows me to provide value when discussing strategies with customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been developing websites since 1999 and developed an early fascination with interactive technologies like Flash and JavaScript. Over the years I have acquired in depth knowledge working with a variety of assorted web, mobile and software specific languages. A lot of my work is with WordPress where I maintain several plugins in the WordPress repository. In an effort to educate and enable others with WordPress, I help run the local WordPress meetup and speak at conferences and meetups.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Beach</member_name><member_id>9994469</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370102970000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368540081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston WP + Toolbox Beginner WordPress Workshop</name><id>119320632</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370091600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/119320632/</event_url></item>