<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 18 , 2008- Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Lacasse, the &amp;quot;Rehab Rock Star&amp;quot; and John Ingram, the &amp;quot;Wholesale Houdini&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Quick Nickel or the Slow Dime&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Kevin and John as they discuss when they choose to flip a property and when they choose to hold. Find out the factors they consider.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How do you assign a contract when you're buying REO's from the Bank? &lt;br /&gt;Which part of the market cycle favors which strategy? &lt;br /&gt;Which type of property should you hold? Multi's? Commercial? &lt;br /&gt;When is too much work, too much for you too? &lt;br /&gt;Tenants and Toilets - Who is dealing with them and what will it cost you? &lt;br /&gt;Which acquisition strategies favor holding? &lt;br /&gt;What are their long and short term goals &lt;br /&gt;John and Kevin are local investors working in the New England market, doing wholesaling, rehabbing, flipping, holding, residential, commercial and everything else you can think of. They don't limit themselves to any one strategy or technique, but they apply different methods as the market and their resources change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be an informal discussion, so bring your questions. If you have a deal you want to discuss and ask about, bring that too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Location: Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;Free to Boston AREIA members (please see website for details - &lt;a href="http://www.BostonAREIA.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonAREI...&lt;/a&gt;, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221946472000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219358049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association September Meetup</name><id>8594221</id><headcount>110</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221773400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/8594221/</event_url></item>