<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Central Sq.)</address_2><address_1>492 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 864-3278</phone><name>The Middle East Restaurant and Nightclub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>257177</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sat 10/10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/builttospill" target="_blank"&gt;Built to Spill&lt;/a&gt; – Night Two @ The Middle East (downstairs)&lt;br /&gt;18+, doors at 8pm, tickets $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets for Middle East Club events are available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* In person at the Middle East Box Office - 1pm to 7pm, seven days a week -- without service charge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* At all Ticketmaster locations&lt;br /&gt;    -- at www.ticketmaster.com&lt;br /&gt;    -- By phone at (617) 931-2000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For general info call the Middle East box office at (617) 864-EAST ext 221.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From last.fm:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Built to Spill is an indie rock band based in Boise, Idaho, United States. The band is best known for its catchy guitar hooks and the unique voice of frontman Doug Martsch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Former Treepeople frontman Doug Martsch formed Built to Spill in 1992 with Brett Netson and Ralf Youtz as the band’s original members. In an interview with Spin magazine, Martsch stated that he intended to change the band’s lineup for every album, with Martsch being the only permanent member. After the band’s first album, Ultimate Alternative Wavers (1993), the lineup changing idea held true, as both Netson and Youtz were replaced by Brett Nelson (not Netson) and Andy Capps for 1994’s There’s Nothing Wrong With Love. A compilation album called The Normal Years, consisting of recordings by both the first and second trios, was released in 1996. Between recording albums in 1995, the band gained notoriety by playing on the Lollapalooza tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Martsch signed Built To Spill to the Warner Brothers label in 1995. Unlike many artists signed to major labels, however, the deal the band brokered with Warner allowed it to retain a large degree of creative control over future albums. Built to Spill produced its first major label release in 1997 with Perfect From Now On. By this time, the band consisted of Martsch, Nelson, Netson, and Scott Plouf.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255568371000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250834021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Built to Spill @ The Middle East (downstairs)</name><id>11163905</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255222800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11163905/</event_url></item>