<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mountain Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.474083</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>978 464-2987</phone><name>Wachusett Mountain</name><city>Princeton</city><id>810138</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.894520</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(update 9/30)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This hike is on!&lt;/strong&gt; We are still in the 30% chance of showers area, but the sun is poking through the clouds at my house. I can't guarantee seeing an actual sunset, but maybe.  And I'd suggest bringing a rain coat, just in case!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I seem to have a fondness for sunset type hikes, I'm planning another hike up Wachusett Mountain. On September 30th the sunset is listed as 6:30pm and the moonrise is listed for 6:30pm also! The full "Harvest Moon" is listed as the 29th just before midnight, so it'll almost be full as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at the Stagecoach trailhead on Westminster Road and take the Echo Lake to High Meadow to Jack Frost to Mountain House to the summit route on the way up. We will stay on the summit until 7:00pm unless the rangers ask us to leave sooner! On the way down we will use the Administration Road back to our starting point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These trails are moderate with some steep sections, so be prepared to break a sweat! Total hiking time up should be just over an hour and hiking time down is a bit less than an hour. Estimated mileage is around 3 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking is available along Westminster Road, about a mile off of Mountain Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should be prepared for cooler weather at the summit. You should also bring enough drinks to remain hydrated, as well as snacks if you're a hungry hiker. A camera for those who want to capture the moment is also a good idea. And... A flashlight and/or headlamp that works will be useful as we hike down in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349140149000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348008049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yet another sunset/moonrise hike! With an almost full Harvest Moon, too!</name><id>83013662</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349038800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/83013662/</event_url></item>