<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>South Shore Plaza</address_2><address_1>250 Granite Street, 1st Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.219654</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-602-6149</phone><name>California Pizza Kitchen</name><city>Braintree</city><id>1475891</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.026964</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join fellow Members and Guests of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a rare Monday Night Dinner as we check out the &lt;strong&gt;California Pizza Kitchen's Grand Opening Pizza Fundraiser for the Braintree Community Youth Center&lt;/strong&gt;! &lt;em&gt;"On Monday, January 31st," California Pizza Kitchen "will donate 100% of dine-in pizza sales to support Braintree Community Youth Center." &lt;/em&gt;For more info on the Braintree Community Youth Center (BCYC) please visit their website at www.braintreeyouthcenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the primary purpose is to help raise funds for the BCYC by ordering pizza, California Pizza Kitchen has an extensive menu. Their menu is expansive, but some of the categories listed on their website include appetizers, desserts, smoothies, pizzas and specialties, to name a few. All food is made from scratch and those with food allergies need to tell the server upon arrival. You can check out their entire menu online at www.cpk.com. Their pizzas are 10" in size, perfect for sharing with a fellow diner or enjoying by yourself. If you share a pizza then you will be able to share an appetizer or entree as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is their grand opening and there is extensive advertising for this fundraiser so we can expect the restaurant to be crowded. As such, while CPK does not accept reservations, we will be able to call ahead with our party size and they will do their best to seat us at as few tables as close to each other as possible. We may have to wait a few minutes (possibly up to 15 minutes) so please arrive by 6:45pm. In addition, we will be seated at 2-3 tables very near each other. (I spoke w/ the General Manager in person and explained our Group and she is willing to work with us.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy. This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California Pizza Kitchen Grand Opening Pizza Fundraiser!  &lt;br /&gt;Monday, January 31st @ 6:30pm  &lt;br /&gt;South Shore Plaza  &lt;br /&gt;250 Granite Street  &lt;br /&gt;(1st floor in the Nordstrom Wing)  &lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184  &lt;br /&gt;781-602-6149  &lt;br /&gt;www.cpk.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Outside the main entrance inside the mall. The host station is just inside this door. We will then go in together as a Group. Otherwise, inside the Lobby. If you arrive after we are seated ask for "Angela" or the "South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: No min or max for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: 1 per Member. For exceptions please contact the Event Organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Fees&lt;/em&gt;: NONE. This is a fundraiser so we don't charge an Event Fee. We hope you will share pizza with your fellow SSDOMG members as 100% of the pizza sales will be donated to the BCYC. / You can become a 2011 Annual Member for $12 at this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 6pm on Sunday, January 30th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page. (No new RSVPs will be accepted after 5pm on Monday, January 31st.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: We will be attending whether rain, snow, sleet, clouds or shine. If severe weather is forecast this area will be updated by Friday evening. Please update your RSVP by the RSVP Deadline if weather will affect your attendance. (For full details on our Inclement Weather Policy please go to the About pages.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview&lt;/em&gt;: California Pizza Kitchen is located inside the South Shore Plaza on the 1st floor in the Nordstrom wing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Parking&lt;/em&gt;: In parking garage adjacent to the restaurant or in open-air parking lot adjacent to Target and Nordstrom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To the Mall From the Highway&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Located at 250 Granite Street/Route 37 in Braintree.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Exit 6 off Route 93.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Take a right off the Exit.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;There are entrances to the Mall at 3 lights.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Enter the Mall through one of the Main Entrances.&amp;nbsp; California Pizza Kitchen is located in the Nordstrom Wing on the first floor off the parking garage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297904607000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295479856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>California Pizza Kitchen Grand Opening Pizza Fundraiser!</name><id>16112171</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296516600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/16112171/</event_url></item>