<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Church St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02452</zip><lat>42.378204</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Unitarian Universalist Church</name><city>Waltham</city><id>3173571</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.234268</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>check&lt;11-15/$15@door</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Your Brain's Function and IQ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 How Do we Improve Cognition, Mood and Focus &lt;br /&gt;

 (as well as Developmental &amp;amp; Learning Disorders) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Using Scientific Tests and Holistic Therapies &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Is your brain functioning optimally, as well as it used to?&amp;nbsp; Would you like to keep it that way?&amp;nbsp; If you or someone you know have been suffering from mild or severe depression, anxiety, irritability, loss of focus, brain fog, memory loss, fatigue, learning disorders, hyperactivity, failure to thrive, autism spectrum disorders, senile dementia, neurological diseases, brain degeneration, or any other cognitive or mental disorders, you will be relieved to know about exciting recent advances that help us understand how environmental and emotional stressors cause neurological dysfunction. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This new knowledge can be combined with innovative and inexpensive screening tools which reveal nutritional, metabolic, and toxicological deviations that influence our brain.&amp;nbsp; We can now have effective, non-toxic treatments tailored individually to our unique situation, reducing the sources of chemical or mental stress while improved mood, and prevention of neuro-degenerative diseases, so that you and your loved ones can enjoy each other much longer! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn about nature's important wellness tools, as well as the fundamental nutrients and dietary choices that will extend and maximize your enjoyment of life.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren MD, DC, LN, CCN, DABFM, DACBN, FABDA , Nutritional, Environmental &amp;amp; Functional Medicine. Dr. T. is a sought after holistic scientist who educates medical professionals and the general public about functional medicine and disease prevention via truly natural lifestyle and dietary modification.&amp;nbsp; He is a licensed European Medical Doctor, Licensed Nutritionist and is American Board Certified of Functional Medicine, of Oxidative Medicine and of Chelation Therapy.&amp;nbsp; He is the founder of several holistic non-profits in US and Nepal, Asia, Africa &amp;amp; Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $10 if mail check payable to Optimum Health Solution, 337 Newton St.#4, Waltham, MA. Go to www.optimumhealthsolution.org after November 15 to purchase tickets on-line or $15 at door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/8/d/event_23036461.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsy Bragg</member_name><member_id>5026531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327627287000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320815205000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dr. Adiel Tel-Oren</name><id>40513822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327622400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/40513822/</event_url></item>