<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>DO SOMETHING &amp;quot;FOR THE KIDS&amp;quot;. IT WILL DO YOUR HEART GOOD AND THE KIDS WILL THANK YOU!...Hugs, Terri  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a call for VOLUNTEERS to help Rob Pudney (16th year as Chair) run the &amp;quot;Kids Fun &amp;amp; Games&amp;quot; component of the &amp;quot;Northwest Park Country Fair&amp;quot; (WINDSOR), scheduled for SATURDAY, September 25, 2010 - 10am-4pm .  There will be a nearby &amp;quot;after-party&amp;quot; ONLY for my volunteers! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: This event is being announced on &amp;quot;The Single Event&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Ira's Singles Event&amp;quot;, as well as encouraging other MeetUp organizers to post on their calendars as a “note” and forward this letter to their members.  (I'm expecting @ 20-40 volunteers, mostly singles, mostly 30's-50's but ALL WELCOME).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; To make it much easier for me to coordinate from one central location, and to cut down on redundant updates on numerous MeetUps going out to non-volunteers... even if you RSVP elsewhere, PLEASE RSVP on this, one &amp;quot;official&amp;quot; site:  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/free-summer-concerts/calendar/13573005/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;    as it's the only one on which I am an Asst. Organizer on, thus can update you directly, provide more detailed info and exact driving directions, plus, you can see who else is volunteering / partying! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rather than be assigned specific activities, to make it more interesting and allow you to mingle and meet other volunteers and still have time to check out the Fair, please feel free to “free range” monitor our various “old-fashioned” FREE activities such as: “Ye Olde Fishing Hole”, “Haystack Treasure Hunt”, “Bubble Blowing”, and the “General Play Area” (bean bag toss, stilts, jump ropes, big orange “bouncy balls” to sit on, hula hoops, etc.).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those with artistic talent and interest, please consider “Pumpkin Decorating” or “Bead Jewelry”.  For safety and due to their talent, the Bizeau family runs “Pumpkin Carving”.  (A nominal fee is charged only for these three activities, running 10-2). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, I’ll need some of you to help me run various “Contests” throughout the day: “Pie Eating”, “Sack Races”, “Water Balloon Toss”, “Three-Legged Races”, and ending with the “Tug-O-War – Over MUD PIT”! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; NOTE: I’m offering three overlapping shifts to allow you more flexibility to enjoy the overall Fair.  Of course, if you can, longer shifts and/or “all day” (still allowing you free time to enjoy the Fair) would be greatly appreciated!  It’s easy and FUN! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any questions / comments, please feel free to email me DIRECTLY (including your phone number(s) NOT via MeetUp or Single Event, so I can email you back directly, including easier to read formatted details if desired. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THANKS! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob Pudney &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YinYang2008@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"SIGN IN at the "FUN &amp; GAMES" VOLUNTEER TABLE in the open field to the LEFT of the "Big Tent"." </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285958535000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283021270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VOLUNTEER EVENT:"Kids Fun &amp; Games" @ Windsor's Northwest Park Country Fair </name><id>14573268</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285419600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/14573268/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/7/global_17513095.jpeg</photo_url></item>