<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>131 State St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358955</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 725-0100</phone><name>Kitty O'Sheas</name><city>Boston</city><id>709575</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057854</lon></venue><fee><label>Onsite Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;PLEASE RSVP YES WITH ONLY ONE MEETUP GROUP THIS ENSURES AN ACCURATE COUNT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fellow happy hourer and Social Fun organizer, Biagio, has arranged for yet another mix and mingle....which is a joint event of several meetup groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Password for entry is &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;SOCIAL FUN&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommended mode of transporatiion MBTA and or taxi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Aquarium (blue line), Haymarket (green &amp;amp; orange lines), State (orange &amp;amp; blue lines), Government Center (blue &amp;amp; green lines), and South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail) subway stations are no more than a five (5) minute walk away. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below, I've copied some details from the group for which Biagio organizes.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kitty O'Sheas is one of the best spots to host another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 160 members on Friday, June 25, 2010!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt; a Singles party. So anyone can come which means couples are also welcome. Let's get to know one another, socialize, and dance.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE BE RESPECTFUL TO EACH OTHER AND DRINK RESPONSIBLY!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will be at a medium level in the main room upstairs. The music will be tuned very low in the back room upstairs, so members can have a separate area in which to chat. AFTER 9 PM the music to be cranked up in both rooms for dancing, which means, &lt;b&gt;IT WILL GET LOUD&lt;/b&gt;. So get there &lt;b&gt;EARLY&lt;/b&gt; if you want a chance to have quiet conversation.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kitty O'Sheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kittyosheas.com/boston.asp" target="_blank"&gt;Kitty Link&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can accommodate 160 people. There are 2 bars upstairs, 4 huge comfortable couches, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor as well as its own bathroom....the makings for our own private party.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biagio is ordering $350 worth of appetizers (wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) because Kitty's Kitchen is small and it would be difficult to get enough food for 160 members, individually. The platters will be NOT be refilled with food, so get there &lt;b&gt;EARLY&lt;/b&gt;, if you want some grub.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;EVERYONE&lt;/b&gt;, whether you eat or not, please pay Biagio $5, to help cover the cost of this event, which includes renting the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders, and the DJ in addition to the food. Please find Biagio (here's a link with his photo &lt;a href="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/member/b/d/4/6/highres_1548454.jpeg" target="_blank"&gt;http://photos3.meetup...&lt;/a&gt; ), at the party to pay him. He is the ONLY person you should pay.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;AS ALWAYS YOU MUST MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon entry into the building Security will check your IDENTIFICATION, (after 9 you will also have to pay a $10 cover) then proceed to the bottom of the stairwell on your left, where you must check in with Security again. You will be able to enter upstairs by telling Security you are with the &lt;b&gt;Social Fun Group&lt;/b&gt; because that is how our party is registered.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the top of  the stairs be prepared to pay $5 to Biagio, so the line moves quickly and the stairs aren't blocked. If the line on the stairs becomes a problem, Security will make members go back downstairs.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upstairs will open at 7, so if you arrive early hang at the downstairs bar for a bit. Line for upstairs will begin forming as early as 6:30. Each Mix + Mingle has reached capacity before 7:30, so get there &lt;b&gt;EARLY&lt;/b&gt;. If you arrive after 7:30 you may have to wait in a line downstairs before being allowed upstairs. Great reason to get there &lt;b&gt;EARLY&lt;/b&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;After 9 Kitty O'Sheas charges a mandatory $10 cover to enter the building. Remember, you will also have to pay $5 to Biagio, who will be upstairs.&lt;u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The invited Meetup Groups are:    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/calendar/13583123/"&gt;Social Fun&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/"&gt;Boston Night Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FUNgirls//"&gt;Girls just want to have FUN&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.com/76/calendar/13731137/"&gt;Boston Euro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/chill-lax/"&gt;Cool Folks in the City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://diningout.meetup.com/364/calendar/13635043/"&gt;Ethnic Food Dining &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/calendar/13719298/"&gt;Boston Volunteer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There have been as many as 200 members at these Mix and Mingle cross Meetup parties. Many times there were also a few members who could not get in because when they arrived it was full. So, RSVP now and arrive &lt;b&gt;EARLY&lt;/b&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;JOIN US FOR ANOTHER GREAT TIME!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The entire second floor has been reserved under the name Social Fun</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277512895000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275992161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Mix + Mingle Part 11</name><id>13734407</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277508600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/13734407/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/1/global_4320785.jpeg</photo_url></item>