<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06037</zip><lat>41.628889</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ragged Mountain</name><city>Berlin/Southington</city><id>977436</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.796340</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mountains are considered to be sacred places in many different cultures around the world. A hike at Ragged Mountain Preserve offers beautiful scenic vistas of lakes and forests, with amazing October Fall foliage as a backdrop. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On top of the Ragged Mountain bluff overlooking Southeastern CT, we will do some light yoga stretching &amp;amp; meditation. Stretches will focus on opening the energy channels of the body, strengthening the energies of the internal organs, and balancing the 5 elemental energies of wood, fire, metal, water and earth. We will end the hike with a light lunch or snack. Please bring a blanket to practice on because the ground may not be good for mats. This is event will end at approximately 12:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A $1 donation is requested toward the community center and healing arts space at the Growing Green Co-op.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions: From Route 9, take exit to Route 71A (High Road) south onto Chamberlain Highway. About 1/4 mile past Roger's Market, turn right (westward) on West Lane. Follow West Lane about 1 mile to West Lane parking area on the right. This is located in Kensington, CT which is a suburb of Berlin. Park on the right side of the road at trailhead gate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the town of Berlin's &lt;a href="http://www.town.berlin.ct.us/filestorage/24/292/471/Town-hiking-trails%252520Model%252520(1).pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Hiking Trail map &lt;/a&gt;(Look for #5 Blue Blazed Trail over Ragged Mnt.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255471566000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250777078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking &amp; Yoga - Ragged Mountain</name><id>11156436</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255266900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11156436/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/2/7/global_10293879.jpeg</photo_url></item>