<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>836 Brooks Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.533666</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.301.0204</phone><name>Stephanie Borrelli</name><city>Middletown</city><id>1482803</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.602483</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The cards will allow you to peek into the future and understand how to heal every area of you life or others.&amp;nbsp; We will review the Angel cards and uncover the themes that they hold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also break the Tarot Cards up into the Major/Minor Arcana.&amp;nbsp; We will discuss the relation of the suits to the Elements of the earth.&amp;nbsp; We will start with the cards from the 22 Cards from the Major Arcana and begin reading the themes they have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also learn how to clear and consecrate a new deck of oracle cards, learn the more popular spreads, from single card to various card spreads and how the cards effect each other and play off each other in the spreads.&amp;nbsp; We will learn how to interpret the cards and the meanings not only of the surface picture but looking within the picture for more and feeling your intuitive inner voice help to interpret them as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the beginner can learn to conduct&amp;nbsp; wonderful and accurate readings quickly.&amp;nbsp; The experienced will learn how to develop their intuition even further.&amp;nbsp; We will work with the cards to receive messages for yourself, your famly and friends and have fun doing it!&amp;nbsp; There will be many handouts for participants to take home to continue to study and practice what you have learned.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location is to be determined in Middletown upon the amount of interest and reservations.  The cost of the program is $25.00 for approx. 3 hours.  To reserve a spot, please call Stephanie at 860-347-9145 or if you have any questions.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303047519000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Your will need to purchase a deck prior to class attendance.   Preferably Angel Cards.  We will use the oracle cards to give accurate and healing readings.</why><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300756403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Interpreting the Angel Cards &amp; Tarot Cards - How to do Readings</name><id>17006427</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302962400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/17006427/</event_url></item>