<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you sometimes find it hard to communicate your best qualities to someone you're attracted to, even though you know deep down that you really are an interesting person?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you go out to social gatherings (such as a meetup event), do you find yourself wishing that people would see through your shyness and take the time to discover the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;real&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; you that's hiding inside?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you answered "yes" to either of these questions, then you're going to love this. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this unique event, you'll learn the secrets to becoming more interesting and attractive so that you can experience the kind of effortless connections that you've been hoping for when you go out to socialize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN: *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to &lt;em&gt;instantly&lt;/em&gt; tell if someone wants you to approach them. Hint: people have been&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;hoping&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;you'll pick up on this, and you've just never noticed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple secret that makes your social life more fun and engaging, and surrounds you with an endless supply of amazing people for both friendship and dating. &amp;nbsp;And the best part? &amp;nbsp;The change happens the same day you begin using this one little "magic" idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My proven conversation starter that works 100% of the time at parties, meetup groups, and other social gatherings. &amp;nbsp;Imagine how confident you'll feel knowing that you can always walk up to someone at a meetup event and easily start talking to them, even if you think you're too shy to ever do that (I'll help you).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The #1 technique that compels people to become curious about you. &amp;nbsp;Once you master &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, you'll notice more and more people telling you &lt;strong&gt;how interesting you are&lt;/strong&gt;, and even asking YOU out on dates!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A step-by-step template for asking someone to get together with you. &amp;nbsp;Whether you're asking someone out on a date or asking a friend to lunch, this method will work for every single time and make the process much faster and easier. &amp;nbsp;(This also works for setting up business meetings with people you meet at networking events)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 PERSONALITY FEEDBACK &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that's just the first part of the seminar! Then we will go into one of the most popular activities that we do in this social skills group... &lt;strong&gt;personality feedback!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have an opportunity to participate in small group evaluations of other members, and you'll also get to experience what it's like to receive both positive encouragement and constructive feedback about how you come across to others. This is often the most revealing part of the workshop, because it's so personalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some members became aware of things they were doing for years that were turning people off, and some learned that they come across much better than they realized (which dramatically boosted their confidence in all social situations).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/span&gt; I want you to know that exercise is done very gently, kindly, and in the spirit of personal growth. We are all there to help each other. So if this section makes you a little nervous, don't let it. I promise that you will find this to be one of the most educational and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;enjoyable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; parts of the seminar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HOW TO GET INVOLVED &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line. Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Cheap. &amp;nbsp;If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and&amp;nbsp;that's assuming there even &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a class that could offer you all this, which there isn't. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No other class offers you this kind of cutting edge information plus the ability to get personality feedback. &amp;nbsp;What if one small change is all it takes to immediately and effortlessly begin attracting high-quality friends and dating prospects into your life? &amp;nbsp;I've seen it happen many times in this group, and it can happen for you too.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;Because I want to help as many people as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to. &amp;nbsp;The cost for this event is only $25, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about it... &lt;strong&gt;that's 83 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;What else do you spend 83 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In order to make sure I can personally help as many people as possible, the class is limited to the first 20 people who RSVP. &amp;nbsp;We're going to be moving around and doing lots of fun exercises, so I have to limit the size. &amp;nbsp;There are over 800 people seeing this message, so be&amp;nbsp;sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$25 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot. &amp;nbsp;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warmly, &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309188400000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308290745000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Make More Friends &amp; Get More Dates... Guaranteed! + Personality Feedback</name><id>22530901</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309116600000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/22530901/</event_url></item>