<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://plone.org/wpd" target="_blank"&gt;World Plone Day&lt;/a&gt; is a free event open to anyone interested in the benefits of a Web-based Content Management System (CMS). Coming off the heels of the annual International &lt;a href="http://plone.org/events/conferences/2008-washington-dc/" target="_blank"&gt;Plone Conference&lt;/a&gt; in Washington D.C., The Boston Plone User Group will host seminars, talks, and demos of Plone in action. Speakers include Plone contributors and developers Nate Aune, Sally Kleinfeldt, and Aaron VanDerlip of Jazkarta, Michael Trachtman of Vercadia Systems, Sid Koul of New England Wildflower Society, and Tatsu Ikeda of The Tatsu Co. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be held at The Lewis Room - Cambridge Public Library, Central Sq. Branch, 45 Pearl Street, Cambridge MA 02139 (617) 349-4010. Following the presentations, we invite the community to our après-evening social at Betahouse, two blocks away at 13 Magazine St. #2 Cambridge MA 02139. &lt;a href="http://bostonworldploneday.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;Please RSVP&lt;/a&gt; so we can get a headcount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you or your business, non-profit, school, university, government agency, or NGO uses an internet or intranet CMS today or not, Plone offers unparalleled ease-of-use and high-level sophistication at the same time for a multitude of applications. We invite members of the media to cover this free educational and community-oriented event. Non-technical people and techies alike are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[&lt;br /&gt;12:30&lt;br /&gt;- Setup, greetings&lt;br /&gt;1:00&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to Plone (Nate Aune, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;- Plone and Salesforce for Nonprofits and Small Businesses (Nate Aune, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;1:20&lt;br /&gt;- Case Study: Grantmaking with Plone - Business Process, Workflow, &lt;br /&gt;  Security and Context Sensitive Help Systems (Michael Trachtman, &lt;br /&gt;  Vercadia Systems)&lt;br /&gt;1:40&lt;br /&gt;- Making Great Websites with Plone (Tatsu Ikeda, The Tatsu Co.)&lt;br /&gt;2:00&lt;br /&gt;- Case Study: Garden in the Woods (Sid Koul, New England Wildflower Society)&lt;br /&gt;2:20&lt;br /&gt;- Plone in Higher Education (Nate Aune and Michael Trachtman)&lt;br /&gt;2:40&lt;br /&gt;- Case Study: Scientific Collaboration with Plone - Sharing Bibliographies,&lt;br /&gt;  Papers, and Discussions (Sally Kleinfeldt, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;3:00&lt;br /&gt;- Managing Images in Plone (Aaron VanDerlip, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;3:20&lt;br /&gt;- Case Study: Making Maps with Plone (Aaron VanDerlip, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;- Case Study: Managing Maps with Plone (Sally Kleinfeldt, Jazkarta)&lt;br /&gt;3:40&lt;br /&gt;- The Business Case for Content Management - Why Plone? (David Crouch, ten24&lt;br /&gt;  Web Solutions)&lt;br /&gt;4:00&lt;br /&gt;- Free Culture, Free Software, and Plone (Matt Lee, Free Software Foundation)&lt;br /&gt;4:20&lt;br /&gt;- Genius Bar (or Q&amp;amp;A ask the experts panel) &lt;br /&gt;  (Nate, Aaron, Sally, Mike, Sid, Tatsu)&lt;br /&gt;5:00&lt;br /&gt;- Refreshments, door prizes&lt;br /&gt;5:30&lt;br /&gt;- Cleanup, adjourn to Betahouse for refreshements&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonploneworldday.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;Please RSVP at the registration page&lt;/a&gt; so we know how many people to expect. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're meeting in the Lewis Room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sid Koul</member_name><member_id>2310802</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229042613000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Plonista</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonplone</urlname><id>207992</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Plone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225468702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Plone Day - free half-day conference about Plone</name><id>9067291</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226080800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/events/9067291/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/7/global_6115159.jpeg</photo_url></item>