<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>225.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;IMAGE MAKERS DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHER’S BOOT CAMP!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have you invested in a digital camera and feel you are barely using the capacity of this new technology? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you frustrated by the photos you are making and you want more control over your results?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you want to become a better digital photographer?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.testoftimephoto.com/Digital-Photographer%27s-Boot-Camp.html" target="_blank"&gt;[url=http://www.testoftimephoto.com/Digital-Photographer%27s-Boot-Camp.html]DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHER’S BOOT CAMP&lt;/a&gt;[/url]&lt;/b&gt; is a multi session workshop conducted over a period of weeks that is designed to build your photography skills and improve your image making.  The workshops will be held on October 26th and November 2nd,9th &amp;amp; 23rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workshop will feature class/lectures with photography assignments and critique of your results. &lt;br /&gt;Each session will cover  a topic of photographic technique and an assignment based on that information.   Each photographer will shoot the assigned topic and submit images (via email) prior to &lt;br /&gt;the next class.  The submitted photographs will get an individual critique and suggestions for improvement.  The following class will begin with a group review of those shots followed by a topic and new assignment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the period between classes I will be setting up appointments (10 t0 15 minutes /once a week) with each student for phone conversations.  This one-on-one call will be a continuation of the photo critique and a chance to answer your questions.  My objective is to provide guidance and encouragement that will improve your photography.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The&lt;b&gt; DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHER’S BOOT CAMP&lt;/b&gt; will require a certain amount of effort and time from those who choose to participate.  Like any endeavor in life the more you invest the greater the return.  Consider this a chance to learn new photography skills and receive.  In this class you will learn, apply the info in your shooting and then get personalized feedback on your results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUBJECTS COVERED will include the following (plus many other):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The “MECHANICS “of your digital Camera&lt;br /&gt;Establishing your digital WORKFLOW&lt;br /&gt;Observing and capturing light -taking control of your exposure&lt;br /&gt;Creative Expression- your point of view&lt;br /&gt;Displaying and sharing your images.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you need for this class:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Digital camera (point and shoot or Dslr)&lt;br /&gt;Camera Owners manual&lt;br /&gt;Email account&lt;br /&gt;Computer&lt;br /&gt;Basis photo editing software*&lt;br /&gt;Desire to learn and improve your digital photography&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*I can recommend some low cost, relatively easy platforms for photographer’s who are unfamiliar with these softwares.  I will be featuring Adobe Lightroom in the classes and would recommend this as very useful tool for ant digital photographer.  You can download a 30 day trial version at the start of the class at no cost if you want to test drive the software.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The workshop includes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Four 2.5 hour class sessions (10/26, 11/2, 11/9, 11/23)&lt;br /&gt;Weekly critique of submitted photos&lt;br /&gt;Weekly phone consultation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fee for this class is $225 and payment is required at the time of registration.  The fee includes the class sessions, photo critiques and phone consultation sessions. Class size is limited so sign-up now&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For directions go to my website -- http://www.testoftimephoto.com/DIRECTIONS.html</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288194364000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285173515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DIGITAL PHOTOGRAPHER'S BOOT CAMP !</name><id>14859099</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288134000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14859099/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/5/global_18161397.jpeg</photo_url></item>