<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>73 Tremont Street</address_2><address_1>Sawyer Library, 3rd floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358431</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Suffolk University Poetry Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>1124070</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059773</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TOM SLEIGH is the author of eight highly acclaimed books of poetry, including Army Cats (Graywolf Press, 2011), and Space Walk (Houghton Mifflin Harcourt, 2007), which won the $100,000 Kingsley Tufts Award. He has also published a translation of Euripides' Herakles (Oxford University Press, 2007), and a book of essays, Interview With a Ghost (Graywolf Press, 2006). He has received the Shelley Prize from the Poetry Society of America, a Fellowship from the American Academy in Berlin, the John Updike Award and an Academy Award from the American Academy of Arts and Letters, an Individual Writer's Award from the Lila Wallace/Reader's Digest Fund, a Guggenheim grant, and two National Endowment for the Arts grants, among many others. He teaches in the MFA Program at Hunter College and lives in Brooklyn. MELISSA GREEN'S first book of poems, The Squanicook Eclogues, published by W. W. Norton, was awarded prizes from the Poetry Society of America and the Academy of American Poets; it is currently available as a reprint edition from the Boston-based Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press. Fifty-Two, her second book of poems, was published by Arrowsmith Press in 2007. Her work has been published in AGNI, Little Star, Charles River Journal, Fulcrum, Epiphany and Ibbetson Street. Ms. Green lives in Winthrop, MA.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328232677000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327935710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry reading: Tom Sleigh &amp; Melissa Green</name><id>50217162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328227200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/50217162/</event_url></item>