<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brian Tracy's Maximum Achievements, Relationship &amp;amp; Selling Strategies&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Gain Clarity, Balance and Focus In your Business and Personal Life Wednesday - Aug 20th, 2008 in Cromwell, CT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;In this session taught LIVE by Brian Tracy himself you will learn to:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Set and achieve goals in every part of your life&lt;br /&gt;    * Develop a personal Strategic Plan that serves as a blueprint for you business and personal life&lt;br /&gt;    * Increase your income by 25% to 50% each year by focusing on your highest. value added tasks&lt;br /&gt;    * Organize your financial life so that you make more money keep more of it, invest it more intelligently and build your financial fortress&lt;br /&gt;    * Get complete control over your time an your life&lt;br /&gt;    * Develop higher levels of self-discipline, self-assured and determined in everything you do&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LEARN THE SECRETS OF SUCCESS!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS SESSION WILL SHOW YO HOW TO MKE THE NEXT 25 MONTHS OF YOUR LIFE… THE BEST EVER!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring Your Spouse, Administrative Staff, Operations Teenager, etc. ... anyone who needs to gain the FOCUS necessary to TAKE IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relationship Selling Strategies&lt;br /&gt;How to Sell More, Better, Faster And Easier in Tough Markets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this session taught LIVE by BRIAN TRACY himself, the best salespeople in the region will learn to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Make more sales, faster and easier in the market&lt;br /&gt;    * Find and focus on more and better prospects&lt;br /&gt;    * Quickly build high quality relationships’&lt;br /&gt;    * Identify exactly what the prospect wants and needs&lt;br /&gt;    * Make powerful, persuasive sales presentations&lt;br /&gt;    * Overcome any objection or resistance to buying&lt;br /&gt;    * Close the sales seven different ways&lt;br /&gt;    * Use the “Golden Triangle” of selling&lt;br /&gt;    * Take complete charge of  your selling career&lt;br /&gt;    * Man your time and double your productivity&lt;br /&gt;    * The Seven Secrets of Super Selling&lt;br /&gt;    * And much, much more...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each participant receives a complete workbook with every key point and ideas, checklists, and resources  for increasing sales and improving business results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who is Brian Tracy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Tracy is Chairman and CEO of Brian Tracy International, a company specializing in the training and development of individuals and organizations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian's goal is to help you achieve your personal and business goals faster and easier than you ever imagined.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Tracy has consulted for more than 1,000 companies and addressed more than 4,000,000 people in 4,000 talks and seminars throughout the US, Canada and 40 other countries worldwide. As a Keynote speaker and seminar leader, he addresses more than 250,000 people each year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has studied, researched, written and spoken for 30 years in the fields of economics, history, business, philosophy and psychology. He is the top selling author of over 45 books that have been translated into dozens of languages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has written and produced more than 300 audio and video learning programs, including the worldwide, best-selling Psychology of Achievement, which has been translated into more than 20 languages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He speaks to corporate and public audiences on the subjects of Personal and Professional Development, including the executives and staff of many of America's largest corporations. His exciting talks and seminars on Leadership, Selling, Self-Esteem, Goals, Strategy, Creativity and Success Psychology bring about immediate changes and long-term results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to founding his company, Brian Tracy International, Brian was the Chief Operating Officer of a $265 million dollar development company. He has had successful careers in sales and marketing, investments, real estate development and syndication, importation, distribution and management consulting. He has conducted high level consulting assignments with several billion-dollar plus corporations in strategic planning and organizational development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has traveled and worked in over 80 countries on six continents, and speaks four languages. Brian is happily married and has four children. He is active in community and national affairs, and is the President of three companies headquartered in Solana Beach, California.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=85" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't wait.  This is going to change the way you run your business!  Register right now!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224538800000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217654876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brian Tracy’s Coming to Town to Train You in Sales and Business!</name><id>8459798</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222347600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/8459798/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/1/global_5005249.jpeg</photo_url></item>