<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Boylston Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351796</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-351-2515</phone><name>Sweetwater Cafe</name><city>Boston</city><id>828107</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065987</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join Socializing for Justice at our monthly discussion series &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The Body&amp;quot; for Justice. This month's POV: Body Image&lt;/b&gt;* on Monday, November 16th at Sweetwater Cafe by Boylston T stop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To connect to &amp;quot;the work&amp;quot; and each other in more intentional ways, SoJust is hosting monthly discussion groups focused on &amp;quot;The Body&amp;quot; through various points of view (POV). This is a place for us to explore what we have in common and where we differ on topics that are important to us. This is not a seminar - there will be no presentation -  come with questions you'd like to explore. We'll creatively use the space:  smaller groups to focus on specific topics, pairing up, etc. Join us to learn more about yourself and other SoJusters!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So you know what to expect here's what we have planned:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6pm      Socializing - order dinner/drinks (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;6:30     Gather in large circle for introductions (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;7pm      Break into small groups (30 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:30     Report back (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:40     Meet in pairs (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:50     Report Back (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;8pm      Closing (10 min)&lt;br /&gt;8:10     Socializing some more (20 min)&lt;br /&gt;8:30     End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The Body&amp;quot; for Justice Discussions will be every 3rd Monday at Sweetwater Cafe.&lt;/b&gt; Possible future POV: race, feminism, gender, dating, war, abortion, safer sex, veganism, burnout and... &lt;i&gt;your suggestion&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Sweetwater Cafe is located at 3 Boylston Street. T Directions: Take the Green Line to the Boylston Street Stop. Take a right onto Boylston Street and walk 1/2 a block. They are located in the alley on the lefthand side, across from Boston Commons. Nearest Orange Line stop is Chinatown. Unfortunately this venue is not wheelchair accessible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259798755000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256010960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Body" for Justice: Body Image Discussion</name><id>11666724</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258412400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/11666724/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/0/7/global_11324567.jpeg</photo_url></item>