<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the new Mandarin/Cantonese PlayDate that will alternate in exposing our children to the Mandarin and Cantonese Languages.  It is co-hosted by MJ who is a native and fluent speaker in both Mandarin and Cantonese.  And I help provide the informal educational components in the form of a short group activity appropriate for all ages to promote the learning and use of the languages.  &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;We strive to make Mandarin and Cantonese accessible to all levels!  So don't be shy!&lt;/span&gt; We can all learn together with our kids.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week, we party!&lt;/strong&gt; We will have holiday music going on.  And order &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Dim Sum*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; again!  YUM! Our activity will be &lt;strong&gt;Handmade Red Envelopes (紅包, &lt;em&gt;hóngbāo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; And we will also do &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;"Secret Santa"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (one small gift good for a boy or a girl, $10 and under, please!)  If you're bringing more than one child, then bring an equal number of Secret Santa presents.  &lt;em&gt;PLEASE don't go crazy spending lots of money on this! It's a fun exchange for the kids.  And really, they'd be more happy with a pretty box than a fancy something-or-other.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;*Chip in for Dim Sum&lt;/span&gt; will be about $15 per person (like last time).  Please chime in with what you want!  I will arrange that &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;the entire Dim Sum Menu is available to us&lt;/span&gt; by ordering a few days in advance with Ten-Ichi Restaurant.&lt;/em&gt; :)  **Chip in for craft/activity supplies is $5 per craft.  You are not obligated to participate in our craft/activity.  But to keep the crafts and fun activities going, I'd appreciate the chip-in!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kids can always free-play as desired.  If you have DVDs to share or information on links to videos in Chinese that are appropriate for babies and young toddlers to view, please bring them to share!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a breastfeeding-friendly environment!  Bring your baby's bottle/fomula or your tots lunch if you want to stay for lunch together. (And your own lunch too.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check back often before we meet!  I will update the activity once it's been decided. And I may change our location from time to time either for variety, a field-trip or just because another member would like a chance to co-host at their home!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please also download and print the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston/files/"&gt;parking permit&lt;/a&gt; for parking on my street.  It is posted on my street and all the neighboring streets that there is no parking.  However, residents may temporarily grant parking to friends/family -- with a parking badge or permit that will distinguish you from just anyone!  Please place on dash, easily seen, to avoid a parking ticket.  And fit into my driveway first!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP, I assume you're coming with your child!  If you have 2 kids or more, please add them to your RSVP so I know how many kids will be participating.  Thanks!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;FYI for those who don't know:  &lt;a href="http://chineseculture.about.com/od/chinesefestivals/a/Chinese-Gift-Giving-What-Not-To-Buy.htm"&gt;Chinese Gift Giving - What Not to Buy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #647f4c ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****&lt;/strong&gt;The 1st deadline is early because I need to order the Dim Sum 3 days in advanced to get the weekend menu!  The 2nd deadline to RSVP just means I can only add their weekday/daily menu items to our order.  So, no worries!  The deadline is about the food!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>SMS/Call: 508-202-0097 or Comment Here on your status.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elsie Smits</member_name><member_id>17363801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357967496000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Parents &amp; Kiddies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>1371768</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Asian-American Families of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355088630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mandarin-Cantonese Holiday Party</name><id>qnhkmcyqqbjc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357918200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Asian-American-Families-of-GreaterBoston/events/94720232/</event_url></item>