<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last chance for camping this season! Come out and enjoy the fall colours! We will do some hiking and perhaps rent canoes for a few hours. Although less people go camping at this time, they have closed parts of the campground ? so please call to make a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Less than 40 minutes to the coastal beaches to the east and to Manchester to the west, Pawtuckaway State Park Campground is well located for easy access to a variety of attractions and activities. All sites are wooded and many provide views of the lake. Each of the campsites has an open fireplace, picnic table, flat area for a tent, and a parking space. Although there are no hook-ups, recreational vehicles are welcome in sites where they fit. Running water, flush toilet facilities, a camp store, boat launch, and canoe and paddle boat rentals are available. Coin-operated showers are accessible 24 hours a day. Please remember that pets are not permitted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 195-site campground includes 180 sites available by reservation only, 4 of which are for youth group reservations; and 15 for first-come/first-served campers. Reserved camping with full staffing and facilities will be available starting May 25 through September 3, then weekends only until October 8, 2007. Reservations for campsites may be made by calling the Reservation Office, Monday through Friday, from January through the end of the season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pawtuckaway State Park offers a variety of landscapes, with something to do and see for everyone. There are many opportunities for hiking, with trails leading to many special points of interest, including a mountaintop fire tower; an extensive marsh where beavers, deer, and great blue herons may be seen, and a geologically unique field where large boulders called glacial erratics were deposited when glacial ice melted near the end of the Ice Age. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The campground sites line the shore of beautiful Pawtuckaway Lake. The park includes a large family beach on the lake with a bathhouse, a group picnic area, a playground, park store, and a group shelter with a ball field available by reservation only. Other activities in the park include biking, fishing, snowmobiling, and cross-country skiing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pawtuckaway State Park&lt;br /&gt;128 Mountain Road&lt;br /&gt;Nottingham, NH 03290&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reservations: 603-271-3628&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 101 east to Exit 5 and follow signs to Pawtuckaway State Park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/ParksPages/Pawtuckaway/Pawtuckaway.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191289319000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188833691000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping Weekend</name><id>6289811</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191016800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6289811/</event_url></item>