<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1851  Post Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06824</zip><lat>41.141064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wilson's Barbeque</name><city>Fairfield</city><id>1511399</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.264351</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Fairfield now has its own authentic, Southern-style, take-out barbeque joint with the opening of the new &lt;strong&gt;Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Barbeque&lt;/strong&gt; at 1851 Post Road, Fairfield. Drawing on experience as both a competitor in and a judge of national barbeque contests, local entrepreneur and barbeque pit master Ed Wilson is as he says, &amp;ldquo;bringing the South&amp;hellip; North.&amp;rdquo; The new restaurant&amp;rsquo;s menu includes the most popular Southern barbeque favorites. All are slow cooked in the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s own hardwood pit. In fact, all the items on the menu are made right on the premises from original Southern recipes. Ready to take out, the barbeque can also be enjoyed in the restaurant when there&amp;rsquo;s an open stool.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Wilson's Barbeque menu reads like an eating tour of the South: Eastern Carolina Pulled Pork, Memphis and St. Louis Style Ribs, Texas-Style Brisket and Sausage that actually comes from Texas. Lighter fare includes smoke-cooked, free-range chicken and a variety of salads. Pulled Pork, Brisket or smoked Sausage sandwiches are also listed and all barbeque is also available by the pound. In keeping with the Southern motif, the side dishes offered are such classic favorites as: collard greens, baked beans, mac &amp;amp; cheese, corn bread or biscuits. In addition, an unusual side named Mimi&amp;rsquo;s Jag, for Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Mother, is a traditional Portuguese style rice and bean dish called Jagacida that goes remarkably well with barbeque.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Wilson is quick to point out that he first learned his love for cooking and spices from his Mother. &amp;ldquo;Nobody left my Mother Mimi&amp;rsquo;s kitchen hungry. And Mimi loved spices. That&amp;rsquo;s how I learned. Most important, she taught me that real satisfaction comes as much from serving great food as it does from eating it."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Wilson's Barbeque hours are from 11:30am till closing on Thursday, Friday, Saturday and Sunday. The new restaurant is conveniently located near Exit 21 off I-95 at 1851 Post Road across from Hemlock Hardware and can be contacted by phone at: 203-319-7427 or 319-RIBS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call Me</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301182876000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Texas style Brisket, Ribs, Smoked Sausage, Pulled Pork, collard greens, baked beans, mac &amp; cheese, corn bread or biscuits. In addition, an unusual named Mimi’s Jag, is a traditional Portuguese style rice and bean dish called Jagacida - "YUM, YUM, YUM</why><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297308480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Diners, Drive - ins and Dives lll "Did anyone say " BBQ"  finger lickin good :-)</name><id>16512639</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301178600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/16512639/</event_url></item>