<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For more than 30 years, the Ryles Jazz Club has continuously entertained us with an outstanding line-up of great local Jazz musicians. And, the club’s reasonable prices for music and food have made it one of the premiere Jazz venues in the Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ritmo Masacote is a 13-piece Salsa &amp;amp; Latin Jazz band comprised of some of the Berklee School of Music’s most talented alumni and students. They're also some of Boston’s finest musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This charismatic band's performances are full of spirit &amp;amp; energy that bridges the divide between music and dance, and are often coupled onstage with dancers from Masacote's Dance Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There'll be ample room to dance at this event, which is modestly priced at only $15 per person. Please bring the exact amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To listen to Ritmo Masacote on Youtube, click &lt;a href="http://video.search.yahoo.com/search/video?ei=UTF-8&amp;amp;p=youtube+ritmo+masacote"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3987cb"&gt;http://video.search.yahoo.com/search/video?ei=UTF-8&amp;amp;p=youtube+ritmo+masacote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For dinner prior to the musical performance at 9pm, we'll dine @ 7pm at the S&amp;amp;S Restaurant, just steps away from Ryles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although there are other great restaurants in Inman Square, the S&amp;amp;S has an unbeatable combination of good food, reasonable prices, ample seating, quieter ambiance for group discussion, and 3 FREE parking lots on Hampshire Street close to the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've already made a reservation at the S&amp;amp;S @ 7pm under my name for us, and will change the number if others join us or cancel between now and then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ritmo Masacote is EXTREMELY popular, and Rick the Manager at Ryles told me that it's going to be difficult to get in. Worse yet, Ryles doesn't accept reservations. But, luckily, I pulled some strings and got Rick to agree to hold a reservation until 8:30pm. His rigid requirement is that we pay him before 7:15pm that night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I plan on being at the S&amp;amp;S early @ 6:30pm to meet all of you, collect all of the ticket money, then run across the street to purchase the tickets at Ryles by 7:15pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be sure to allow yourself enough extra time to park your car and arrive at the S&amp;amp;S no later than 7pm, preferably earlier, and make sure you bring the exact amount of cash for the tix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339449418000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338261377000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Latin Jazz &amp; Salsa - Ritmo Masacote @ Ryles</name><id>66728362</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339282800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/66728362/</event_url></item>