<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;JREX- Open Event - Interview series #1 - Photographer- Keitaro Yoshioka&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody who is over 21 is welcome!( You don't have to be in business) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;June 19th Friday - The door will open at 6:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;We'll be serving a light meal, drinks, and desert including alcohol. &lt;br /&gt;$15/person  JREX member $10/person &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The place is right near Lechmere T station on Green-line.(3min walk from the station) &lt;br /&gt;There is a public parking next to the station($5.50). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google My Map         &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/dgeemn" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/dg...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please RSVP(yoyaku) directly at&lt;/span&gt;       www.jrex.us &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOSHIFOTO &lt;br /&gt;Keitaro Yoshioka &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keitaro Yoshioka was born and raised in Tokyo, Japan. He came to Boston in 1982 and attended the School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston. He majored in photography and studied with Bill Burk, Jim Dow, and Elaine O’Neil. &lt;br /&gt;While he was in school, he won the Boston Globe Photo Contest Award, Best of American College Photography Annual Award, and his work was exhibited at the New Wave International Photography Exhibition in Paris, France, as well as galleries in New York.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the completion of both undergraduate and graduate programs at the Museum School, Keitaro started working at the Polaroid 40”x80” room-sized camera studio at the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, as lead photographer. He has worked with Chuck Close, Evergon, Marie Cosindas, Ulay, and many other established artists with this camera. He has also photographed well -known art collections of the Boston Museum of Fine Arts and has traveled in the United States and Europe photographing well -known works of art. He was involved with Picasso’s Guernica exact size photographic reproduction project in Madrid, Spain, as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After nearly 10 years of working at the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, Keitaro went on his own. He has been working as a commercial/fine art photographer. His corporate clients include Cisco Systems, Dentsu, Genzyme, Google, Fidelity, Harvard University, Hitachi, IBM, The Italian Trade Commission, Lotus, Microsoft, P&amp;amp;G, Winn Company, Wise Construction, and Segway. He does annual reports, architectural photography, portrait, and product photography for his clients. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keitaro has won the Epson Color Imaging Grand Prix Award four times in the past, and his winning images have been exhibited throughout Japan. &lt;br /&gt;He had a solo exhibition at the Bumpus Gallery in Duxbury, MA last year and received the Conant Award (best exhibition of the year) from Bumpus Gallery this year. &lt;br /&gt;Also, he received a grant from Genzyme Corporation and had a group show at the Genzyme Corporation in Cambridge, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to commercial/fine art photography business, he is a faculty member of the photography department at the Massachusetts College of Art and Design,  &lt;br /&gt;Boston Architectural College, and New England School of Photography.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From: &lt;a href="http://yoshifoto.zenfolio.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://yoshifoto.zenf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a name-tag.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tamami</member_name><member_id>4015329</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245625362000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243908343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>JREX interview series #1 - Photographer- Keitaro Yoshioka</name><id>10550943</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245452400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/10550943/</event_url></item>