<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>DONT use the Map Link, its wrong</address_2><address_1>165 Adams Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.774002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Look on a different map or somet</phone><name>Adams Mill Restaurant Upstairs Pub</name><city>Manchester</city><id>367588</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.550224</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Today: A chance of showers, with thunderstorms also possible after noon. Cloudy, with a high near 74. Light northeast wind. Chance of precipitation is 40%. New rainfall amounts between a tenth and quarter of an inch, except higher amounts possible in thunderstorms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight: A chance of showers and thunderstorms. Patchy fog after 3am. Otherwise, mostly cloudy, with a low around 65. Calm wind. Chance of precipitation is 50%. New rainfall amounts between a tenth and quarter of an inch, except higher amounts possible in thunderstorms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancels the event...if its raining around 6 or so..i dont think its good to go hiking here...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Adams Mill Trail (1.93 mile loop) Park at restaurant, 165 Adams Street. Trail starts to left of restaurant, follow along dike to river, up river to railroad trestle, across trestle, go along tracks for 200 feet, go down steps and downstream on Eighth Utilities property, along river section on very narrow ledge to Adams Street, along sidewalk to parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there:&lt;br /&gt;Use 165 Adams street, Manchester ,ct for your gps or mapquest..&lt;br /&gt;its about a mile south of the Buckland hills mall..and the restuarant is on the left if heading south on adams st..on the left of the restaurant is the trail sign..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOW, Adams Mill Restaurant is a special place for us, There is  a trail back there that i have heard is pretty good..and i have never hiked there before..but we park next to an entrance to the trail for our evening after party events.. time to see where the trail goes...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would simply like tohave uus take our  time, go carefully , look around, and check out this trail with a few persons..(Non Complainers of course)..maybe if we decide, stop in at the restaurant for an appetizzer, say hi to the night manager, (Rob did this the other day..Thanks)..Then sit out back and realax a bit drinking our Diet Caffiene Free Beverages..the Coke kind...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189637395000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189353372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Adams mill hike trail....Rain Today ???? Lets See...</name><id>6324704</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189464300000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6324704/</event_url></item>