<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't forget to vote in the special senate election on January 19 before coming to Hennessy's!&lt;/b&gt;  Then come on out to watch the results with us! &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The monthly meetup at Hennessy's is a casual gathering to give us lonely MA Republicans an opportunity to meet one another.&lt;/b&gt; The recent crowds have included a great mix of long-time members and first-time attendees!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come whenever you can (we're usually around till at least 8:30)&lt;/b&gt; for a drink or dinner, or simply for the conversation. &lt;b&gt;There's no agenda&lt;/b&gt;, so feel free to talk politics, current events, jobs, sports, vacation plans, movies...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**********&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetups are very informal and generally there is no agenda with the exception of announcements around 7:00. &lt;b&gt;If you have something to share about a campaign, an event, a website, an organization, here’s your chance to tell the group&lt;/b&gt;. ** If you have an announcement, please let me know when you arrive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**********&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can&lt;b&gt; find us in the back section by the TV and fireplace&lt;/b&gt; or tell the hostess you're with the Meetup group. We're usually there for a few hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is no event at the Garden, parking is $10 at the Government Center Garage.  Haymarket and Govt Center are the nearest MBTA stations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/b&gt; Invite your friends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't be discouraged by the small number of RSVPs on this site; we usually have 20-30 attendees!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: &lt;/b&gt; This meetup event is cross-posted at the Boston Republican Party Meetup Group and on Facebook.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk to the back section near the fireplace &amp; TV.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amanda</member_name><member_id>4385831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264115200000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Republicans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>republican-94</urlname><id>131129</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Republican Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260967874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Republican January Meetup</name><id>mvkvyncbzb</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263942000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/republican-94/events/12095906/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/f/global_8964575.jpeg</photo_url></item>