<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Approximately 1/4 mile you will see the Eastman Cross Country sign on your left which is Clubhouse Lane.  </address_2><address_1>Greensward Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03753</zip><lat>43.497826</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>More info: (603) 863-4500  </phone><name>Eastman Nordic Center</name><city>Grantham</city><id>860362</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.120610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Trails at Eastman Cross Country Ski Center offer something for everyone from the novice to the most experienced cross country skiing and snow shoe enthusiast. They offer winter fun for the entire family--cross country skiing, lessons, snow shoeing, sliding, and ice skating at an affordable price.  &lt;a href="http://www.eastmannh.org/ski/trails/" target="_blank"&gt;trail map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.eastmannh.org/ski/images/DSC00684.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The physical amenities at the Eastman Cross Country Center include:&lt;br /&gt;• 36+ kilometers of groomed ski/ snow shoe trails&lt;br /&gt;• A warming hut located in the &amp;quot;John's Glen&amp;quot; area&lt;br /&gt;• A 75 foot diameter skating pond with warming hut&lt;br /&gt;• A groomed sledding area&lt;br /&gt;• Lessons by ski professionals&lt;br /&gt;• Restaurant and meeting center&lt;br /&gt;• Retail, rental, gift shop and repair center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastman Cross Country Center is open seven days a week from 9 AM to 4 PM from December 1st through March 31st. Our visitors describe our trails, other amenities and their experience at Eastman as &amp;quot;world class.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;The location of our facility is easily accessible to the Upper Valley of New Hampshire and close to additional winter attractions such as the Sunapee Ski Resort. Our facility is well situated close to a major interstate, I-89, which makes us easily accessible from outside the region&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day Pass &lt;br /&gt;      Adult $12.00&lt;br /&gt;      Junior $8.00&lt;br /&gt;   Day Pass After 12:30pm &lt;br /&gt;      Adult $10.00&lt;br /&gt;      Junior $6.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an Official Rossignol Demo Center and Tubbs Snowshoe Center we offer a full selection of cross country ski and snow shoe equipment for both sale and rental. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All skiers, snow shoers, sledders and skaters must check-in with the cross country center. This will be our meetup point to start our afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Boston: I-93 North to Concord, NH. In Concord take I-89 North to exit 13. At the end of the ramp, turn right. Turn right at the next right which is the main entrance to Eastman. Turn right at the next right which is Greensward Drive. Approximately 1/4 mile you will see the Eastman Cross Country sign on your left which is Clubhouse Lane. &lt;br /&gt;From Vermont: I-89 South to exit 13. At the end of the ramp, turn left. Turn right at the next right which is the main entrance to Eastman. Turn right at the next right which is Greensward Drive. Approximately 1/4 mile you will see the Eastman Cross Country sign on your left which is Clubhouse Lane. &lt;br /&gt;From Maine: I-95 South to Portsmouth. Prior to the toll booth, take RT 101 North into Manchester. In Manchester, take I-93 North into Concord. In Concord take I-89 North to exit 13. At the end of the ramp, turn right. Turn right at the next right which is the main entrance to Eastman. Turn right at the next right which is Greensward Drive. Approximately 1/4 mile you will see the Eastman Cross Country sign on your left which is Clubhouse Lane.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Gold Honda CRV  phone 603-477-5116  walkie talkie channel 8, red Fisher skis</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233411427000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232760338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Afternoon X Ski and Beginner Snowshoe, Grantham, NH</name><id>9589041</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232903700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9589041/</event_url></item>