<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Is there a better way to spend a Wednesday night? Probably. But climbing is so much fun and good for both body and spirit. So join us and meet some new climbing partners or belay some familiar faces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: you will need to pass a belay test if you are an experienced climber but new to the gym. You can take a belay test when you get there. If you have never climbed before at all, you should take a class at Metrorock. Please call the gym in advance to make arrangements to take the class. You can use the message board on this meetup to find other people that want to take the class. Metrorock will charge you $16 for a daypass if you are not already a member or a punch card holder. For more information see:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.metrorock..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gym also has a shuttle to the gym from the T - Wellington Station on the Orange Line if you don't have a car.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;Brendan (plagirized from Kevin:)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. I'll be around the picnic table until about 7:30 pm, after that you'll have to come find me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metrorock is hard to find for first time visitors. So if you find yourself going in circles here are some hints:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the traffic circle near Wellington Station take Santili Highway towards Best Buy and Mellon:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If Best Buy is on your right and the Mellon building is on your left as you are going away from the circle, you are on the correct road. Then, take a left when you see a sign that says Metro rock. This sign is very very easy to miss as it is quite dark at night. Also, the road is full of potholes so drive slowly. Then take the next left to Metrorock.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be around the picnic table until about 7:30pm. Else, check the whiteboard.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brendan Sever</member_name><member_id>4538459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237644794000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237298743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wednesday Climb</name><id>9972340</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237419000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/9972340/</event_url></item>