<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>To subscribe to our list-serve, email me: sggoodale@yahoo.com&lt;br /&gt;Apologies for  late posting. We'll meet in Living Room of  &amp;quot;Dakin House&amp;quot;,a dorm/office complex right near Franklin Patterson Hall. There are two brick buildings with a white tent and patio furniture between them. The Dakin living room is the one of the right, enter on the side.&lt;br /&gt; At first crossroads after entering Hampshire College from Rte 116,take a left. Drive 1/3 mile to right entrance to Franklin Patterson Hall. Parking lot on left.  Contact (if you need help ) : call Serena (cell) 773-513-9693&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This  Meeting's  Agenda: &lt;br /&gt;1. Preparations &amp;amp; outreach for a major  film screening of &amp;quot;9/11: Press for Truth&amp;quot; at Hampshire College the evening of Tuesday, October 10th, which will include the producer, Kyle Hence. Outreach will be planned to bring community residents and students from the other colleges and high schools&lt;br /&gt;2. Plans for setting up other screenings in the Valley, or presentations, that include Kyle Hence, a long-term 9/11 Truth activist. He is available for events on Monday, Oct. 9, through Wednesday, Oct 11th&lt;br /&gt;3. Preparation of strategies, including handouts, signs and perhaps banners for promoting &amp;quot;9/11 Truth&amp;quot; at Amy Goodman's event at Mt. Holyoke College the evening of October 4, a Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;4. If time allows, developing outreach strategies into the community, including media publicity, tabling, and offering presentations to various community and special interest groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, Steve Goodale&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540470000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1156291413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Western Mass 9/11 Truth Alliance</name><id>5091611</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1159302600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/5091611/</event_url></item>