<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Cliff St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.333027</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgerton Park</name><city>New Haven</city><id>333949</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.915660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I think this is a great idea for a meetup, made by Catherine. Let's do the lawn chair, small snack to share and drink of your choosing routine and enjoy a late summer evening together. Check out the details here: &lt;a href="http://www.elmshakespeare.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=123&amp;amp;Itemid=118" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.elmshakesp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Imaginary Invalid (French: Le Malade imaginaire) is a three-act comedy by the French playwright Molière. It was first performed in 1673 and was the last work he wrote. Molière collapsed during his fourth performance as the hypochondriac on 17 February and died soon after. The original play included dance sequences and musical interludes that Marc-Antoine Charpentier composed. &lt;br /&gt;Summary: &lt;br /&gt;The play is about a miser, Argan, who imagines himself sick when he is not. He dutifully sticks to any instructions given to him by his doctor. His doctors milk his hypochondria for all it is worth, which leads eventually to their demise. Argan wants his daughter Angelique to marry a doctor so he can get free medical care, even though she is already in love with Cleante. Together with Argan's maid Toinette, his brother Beralde attempts to cure Argan of his fixation on doctors. Together, they convince him to play dead, in order to find out who is really loyal to him. As it turns out, Argan's second wife is only after his money, whereas his daughter really loves him. After the revival of the supposedly-dead Argan, Angelique is free to marry whomever she chooses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there are questions or suggestions please call me at 802-233-9060. Thanks guys,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the purple and yellow balloons! They'll be right next to the Arts and Creative Cultural Events' flying piano scarf.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nanette</member_name><member_id>4729277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253641782000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249340418000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shakespeare in the Park - The Imaginary Invalid</name><id>11026824</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252106100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/11026824/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>