<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lucky enough to have your birthday in the beautiful month of January - or want to celebrate with those who are? Then please join us at   &lt;a href="http://www.maxbrenner.com/home.aspx"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Max Brenner&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in Boston's Back Bay for a very fun evening which will of course include great food, drinks and the usual laughs that accompany our events. Max Brenner is highly recommended by several Social Fun members; they offer some of the best burgers and Mojito's this side of the Atlantic. Want more? Get ready for chocolate inspired drinks and desserts that will make you feel like your spoiling yourself just a little - even if it isn't your birthday! If the mood suits us after dinner we can venture out to one of the many other venues in the area for even more birthday fun - including some music and dancing. The restaurant manager has arranged for us to do checks by groups of 4 and will be able to seat us at one table. I'll send out more details as we get closer to the date, but in the meantime, please let me know if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks and see you then!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the host and look for the Social Fun Meetup sign at our table...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul</member_name><member_id>10877649</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358782895000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354747904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Birthdays Celebration Dinner</name><id>94228462</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358641800000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/94228462/</event_url></item>