<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Dunster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-441-9797</phone><name>Finale Dessert Company</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>796663</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119213</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meeting #2 of the Theoretical Computer Science Meet-Up Group will be on Fri. 8/28/09 at 7PM (supper at 6PM) at finale at 30 Dunster Street in Harvard Square, Cambridge  &lt;a href="http://www.finaledesserts.com/locations-cambridge.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.finaledess...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit the red line Harvard Square subway stop next to Out-of-Town News.  Dunster Street is on the right of the big Au Bon Pain behind the escalator and finale is one block down on the left, corner of Dunster and Mt. Auburn.  There is parking underneath the block that Au Bon Pain is on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be in the big dining room but we can move to the small meeting room or outdoors under umbrellas.  Topics for which members have shown interest include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Artificial Intelligence: Strong AI (Joel, Alex), Natural Language Processing (Parasuraman), Connectionist Models (Robert).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Programming Language design and selection (Emmsey, Erik).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Analyzing, paradoxes &amp;amp; puzzles, applying formal methods to problems at work and play, Axiomatic basis for Computer Science (Navnet, Orville, Natasha, Charlie and all of the other members who joined the Puzzle Olympiad at our 1st meeting).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Perhaps we can start with the overdue promised survey of Theory of Computation (Turing), Incompleteness in Logic (Godel, Rosser) and any other branches of Computer Science.  There will be at least one and probably more attendees qualified to give a little talk.  After that I would merely say “formalize”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But mostly expect lots of puzzles, problems, ideas, inspirations, theories and fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the large dining room with a notice on the table.  Later we can move to the meeting room or outdoor tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie</member_name><member_id>2078145</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254240869000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Theoreticians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving</urlname><id>1340773</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Theoretical Computer Science Problem-Solving</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250692538000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Theoretical Computer Science Meeting # 2 Fri. 8/28/09 7PM at finale Harvard Sq</name><id>11147478</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251500400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Theoretical-Computer-Science-Problem-Solving/events/11147478/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_9894127.jpeg</photo_url></item>