<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  If you are wondering why there so few RSVPs, take a look at this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a lot of wordsmiths in this group.  I think it is time to have a little competitive fun with a Scrabble Tournament.  :-)  It will be free and there will be a few small prizes to be given out but mainly this is just for bragging rights in the group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP and own a standard Scrabble set, please consider bringing it along.  Thanks. :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tournament Rules:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The competition will be point based.  Unlike elimination competitions, this ensures everyone can continue playing throughout the event and not get bored.  Furthermore, it puts the emphasis more on the strategic aspect of the game where players can focus merely on how well they can play their letters rather than who knows the most obscure words.  This I hope will be more enjoyable for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players will play in 2 games each, with each game lasting no longer than 2 hours.  Each player will compete against one other player each game.  The objective is to score as many points as possible during the game.  Each player's turn will be timed.  Each player will have a certain amount of time to think of a word and then they must play a word when the time is up.  Players will alternate back and forth until they run out of letters or the 2 hours is up, whichever comes first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Word challenges will be permitted.  If a word is challenged, the person who played the word must give the definition.  If their definition accurately reflects the meaning of the word based on our official dictionary, the challenger loses the amount of points that word is worth.  If a word is challenged and the player doesn't know the meaning of the word, than the player removes the word from the board and loses that turn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The winners of the tournament will be decided by each player's average score across both games.  Each player's score will be recorded which will allow us to transition to an ongoing ladder if people enjoy this format and want to continue more of these tournaments in the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, this is meant to be a friendly tournament.  :-) While this is set up like a competition, this is still just a game where the point is to have fun so please don't throw chairs across the room if the only word you can play during a turn is C-A-T. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Food theme:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The food theme for this Mini-Meetup will be foods with letters, numbers or faces on them.  (Examples: Alphabet soup, M&amp;amp;Ms, Animal crackers, etc.)  Feel free to bring or make something that fits the theme otherwise we will have some default finger food snacks on hand.  If the tournament goes long, we'll organize a meal as a group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the location:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pickman Street is located between the Commons and the water.  Parking on Pickman can be tight, but there should be ample parking along either Pleasant Street (by the Commons) or Collins Street (by the water)&lt;br /&gt;It will take place on the third floor unit.&lt;br /&gt;Note: there will be two cats present that will be very very sad if they have to get locked up.  They are very polite however.  If anyone would like to attend but has allegeries please send me a private message.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289261999000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287415558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Scrabble Tournament</name><id>15146429</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289066400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15146429/</event_url></item>