<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello, Java Meetup members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our next Meetup, David Thomson, creator of an open source messaging application called SupraSphere, will give a presentation about SupraSphere and technologies involved: digital identity, electronic currency, database &lt;br /&gt;filesystem, rfid, rss, semantic web, distributed authentication, privacy, and personalization. If you were ever wondering what the connection between all these concepts might be, this will hopefully be a place to start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More than a presentation on technical matters such as particular encryption algorithms, which can be covered if there is adequate interest among those present, it will be primarily an exploration of the nexus between different emerging trends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anybody who plans to attend could bring a portable projector - it would be great! Please, let us know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be hosted in the SupraShere office space (thanks, David!) at 87 Wendell St. in Post Office Sq., Boston. The closest T stations are South Station and Government Center. It's &lt;br /&gt;about a five minute walk from either Faneuil Hall or South Station. &lt;br /&gt;From South Station in particular, you must walk up High St. toward the water, and the office is adjacent to International Place in between Franklin and High St. at the intersection of Batterymarch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=151+2nd+street+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;spn=0.021942,0.042160&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.suprasphere.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.suprasphere.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.supraspher...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kaj Kandler</member_name><member_id>1142521</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1119312564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Java July Meetup</name><id>4724767</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1121727600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/4724767/</event_url></item>