<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Washington &amp; Hyde Park Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.299938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forest Hills subway stn.</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>183700</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113548</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will walk from Forest Hills to Chinatown, where we will have Dim Sum. After lunch hop on the Orange line to get beck to Forest Hills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a pay parking lot ($4) at Forest Hills and some free on street parking nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ksgaccman.harvard.edu/hotc/displayplace.asp?id=11436" target="_blank"&gt;http://ksgaccman.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The linear Southwest Corridor Park follows the Orange Line rapid transit system from downtown Boston to Forest Hills station in Jamaica Plain. In its entirety, the Southwest Corridor Park is 4.7 miles in length with a total of 52 acres of parkland. Twenty-seven of these acres are in the Heart of the City. Three of the nineteen Orange Line stations lie in the Heart of the City. Stonybrook and Green Street are neighborhood stations accessed primarily by people on foot, while Forest Hills is a regional transportation hub that connects to parking lots, buses, and a commuter rail. Three sets of railroad tracks extend from downtown Boston to the community of Forest Hills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The southern sections of the Southwest Corridor Park include tennis courts, basketball courts, expansive open areas, five tot-lots, fountains, three community gardens, passive sitting areas, and paved biking and walking paths. Portions of the Orange Line are covered with decking to provide space for parkland and playground facilities. Interruptions to the flow of the park occur at Williams Street, Green Street, and Boylston Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The designers of the Southwest Corridor Park referred to the park as a &amp;quot;new strand of the Emerald Necklace.&amp;quot; They designed the park to minimize maintenance costs. Original discussion about the plan revolved around supplemental support for maintenance from community organizations. The design incorporated low shrubs, high visibility, and an open, flexible landscape.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emperor Garden&lt;br /&gt;690 Washington St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02111-1614&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (617) 482-8898&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside the subway station, in front of the donut shop.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol T</member_name><member_id>3564111</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234022677000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232893577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Southwest Corridor trail and Dim Sum (2/1 is Chinese New year)</name><id>9596539</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233500400000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9596539/</event_url></item>