<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 East Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.684003</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-356-2431</phone><name>Ipswich Inn</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>878537</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.835260</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello Ladies, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trying to get back into the swing of things as life has finally settled down a bit.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am hoping that there will be a lot of participation in some excellent workshops that are designed for us to feel healthy, and happy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the description: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Why do I feel so lousy and what Can I do about it? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We subject our body to toxic substances every day simply from the air we breathe and the food we eat.  Add to that the unhealthy things we choose to put into our bodies like caffeine, alcohol, and fast foods, and you can begin to see how toxins build up quickly in our system.  Now consider the medications we ingest from birth control to high blood pressure medication to Tylenol and it’s no wonder that many of us feel lousy on a daily basis.  If you constantly feel lousy, chances are you’re toxic!   In this workshop the doctor will discuss how to identify if you’re toxic and discuss the various methods for removing toxins from your body to restore it to optimal health. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be charging a $10 REFUNDABLE fee for this meet-up, only refundable after you attend.  I unfortunately have to do this due to some difficulties I have had in the past with last minute cancellations that has made it difficult on myself, and the venue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no cost for Dr. Jennah's presentation.  We will be having this at the Ipswich Inn, in Ipswich MA.   Regular Breakfast/Lunch menu available at very reasonable cost!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please call me, or email with any questions.  978-998-9353 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laura&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>8371260</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260646478000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Women Supporting Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Women-Social-Network-Group</urlname><id>1379831</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journeys</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247148220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wellness Workshop with Dr. Jennah Dieter</name><id>10838198</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250352000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-Social-Network-Group/events/10838198/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/9/global_7285529.jpeg</photo_url></item>