<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you every felt left out or ignored?&lt;br /&gt;Does it feel like the event somehow is never over?&lt;br /&gt;Are you living with the residual emptiness that brings up sadness and anger in your life?&lt;br /&gt;Would you like to learn how to finally leave these experiences behind?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feeling of being left out is a devastating experience especially if it happens when we are children. The event may be over, but somehow it never feels like it is really over.  &lt;br /&gt;Not only because it hurts deeply. It actually leaves you feeling empty.  Literally energetically EMPTY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The emptiness brings up sadness and anger. &lt;br /&gt;Both initial emptiness and the energy subsequently lost to this trauma often create a state of adrenal exhaustion.  It makes you feel like doing anything is too much effort.  The life becomes limiting in so many ways. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many ways in which we have stopped feeling &amp;quot;whole!&amp;quot; And it takes a lot of courage to acknowledge the places where we were wounded as children or adults. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If all this sounds true to you, come and join us!&lt;br /&gt;During this meetup you will lean how to bring healing to your body, mind and spirit by learning to actually fill up the emptiness inside you.  Discover powerful principles and learn techniques of energetic re-integration that will enable you to satisfy the full extent of your earning for what has been withheld from you.  Most importantly, you can do this without actually being dependent on changing the person or circumstances that caused the neglect. &lt;br /&gt;-------------------&lt;br /&gt;I want to share with you what one of my students wrote to me:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I don’t remember the exact moment that this began, but it continued throughout my childhood and early adult life, long enough for me to recognize the pattern of neglect. I was always told to “shut up,” “be quiet,” “mind my own business,” “I’m doing something wrong,” and “children should be seen and not heard.” If I asked a question, I was given a smart-ass answer instead of being taken seriously. I was not validated as a human being with an inquiring mind nor was I nurtured by any communication with my parents. My parents were not good at teaching life skills, communicating, praising, or encouraging us kids.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To put closure on this trauma, I used techniques that you taught me. Using one of the techniques - I closed myself in my energy field. Then, I pushed away all the times that he told me to shut up and all the times he gave me a stupid answer to a question. Afterward, I felt lighter or maybe I should say enlightened. Now that I’ve investigated this past trauma, I understand that he didn’t know any better or have the necessary parenting skills to raise well-rounded children. I don’t blame my father for treating me this way. I have forgiven him for being so ignorant. He learned his mistakes from his parents. He wasn’t nurtured or encouraged as a child so he had no role model to learn from.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have also reclaimed the energy that I lost from childhood. I have evaluated what I lost, I’ve learned how it weakened me; and I’ve overcome the emotional negativity from it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our relationship now is good. I’ve readjusted how to communicate with him. Our energy is now able to connect without being shut out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do not miss the chance to heal your wounding and create a new reality by joining us to-night at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/calendar/14314371/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blessings on your healing journey&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281732167000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280910046000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healing the Invisible Wounds of Neglect</name><id>14314371</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281654000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/14314371/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/0/global_16206976.jpeg</photo_url></item>