<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Mass. Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>530797</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Bookish Ball is Harvard Square's celebration of books held on Shakespeare's birthday and featuring performances, readings, and sales! Harvard Book Store will be participating by holding a Shakespeare Sale, in honor of Shakespeare's birthday and the Bookish Ball. On April 28th, all books by or about Shakespeare will be 20% off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE OF EVENTS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10:30am - Chalk artists begin drawing on Palmer Street &lt;br /&gt;

11:00am - Banner and hat craft activity - Whale Room at the Cambridge Public Library &lt;br /&gt;

11:55am - Reading by Toni Bee, Poet Populist of Cambridge at the Cambridge Public Library &lt;br /&gt;

12:05pm - Sidewalk Procession departs the Cambridge Public Library; AfroBrazil Boloco and activities on Palmer Street including face painting, balloon artists, and Open Air Circus Workshop &lt;br /&gt;

12:30pm - Sidewalk Procession arrives in Harvard Square and assembles for the ribbon cutting at The World's Only Curious George Store Harvard Square, 1 JFK Street &lt;br /&gt;

12:45pm - Toasts, Common Text Reading, performances and cake and ice cream on Palmer Street &lt;br /&gt;

1:00pm - Performance by Zumix on Palmer Street &lt;br /&gt;

1:15pm - Performance by AfroBrazil Boloco on Palmer Street &lt;br /&gt;

2:00pm - Shakespeare Pub Talk - moderated by Dr. Nick Walton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard Square is home to over a dozen book and printed word shops. Many will be holding events, book readings and promotions to celebrate the Bookish Ball.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335627707000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335040004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fifth Annual Bookish Ball &amp; Shakespeare Birthday Celebration</name><id>61553562</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335623400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/61553562/</event_url></item>