<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>539 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.353896</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 259-3400 for tickets</phone><name>Boston Opera House</name><city>Boston</city><id>746686</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062154</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>88.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's Wicked in Boston!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The musical, that is.  The Tony Award winning (2004 - Best Actress, Scenic Design, and Costume Design) musical comes to Boston's Opera House this fall.  Tickets to the show are a bit steep, but if we get a group of 20 or more together, we can get a discount.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Wicked&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Long before Dorothy dropped in, two other girls meet in the Land of Oz. One, born with emerald green skin, is smart, fiery and misunderstood.  The other is beautiful, ambitious and very popular.  How these two unlikely friends end up as the Wicked Witch of the West and Glinda the Good Witch makes for the most spellbinding new musical in years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;WICKED, the untold story of the witches of Oz, features music and lyrics by Stephen Schwartz (&lt;i&gt;Godspell&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Pippin&lt;/i&gt;, Academy Award winner for &lt;i&gt;Pocahontas&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;The Prince of Egypt&lt;/i&gt;) and book by Winnie Holzman (&amp;quot;My So-Called Life,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Once And Again&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;thirtysomething&amp;quot;), and is based on the best-selling novel by Gregory Maguire. With musical staging by Tony Award winner Wayne Cilento (&lt;i&gt;Aida&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;The Who's Tommy&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;How To Succeed...&lt;/i&gt;), WICKED is directed by 2003 and 2004 Tony Award-winner Joe Mantello (&lt;i&gt;Take Me Out&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Frankie and Johnny in the Clair de Lune&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Glengary Glen Ross&lt;/i&gt;.).&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;a href="http://www.wickedthemusical.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wickedthem...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE THE FOLLOWING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Group pricing for the show is $82 (orchestra seating).  With service fees, the total per person is $88.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;We need a minimum of 20 people to get group pricing.  &lt;i&gt;If there are less than 20 sign ups in one week, this meetup will be canceled.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will be collecting payment for the event through PayPal.  If/when we reach 20 or more sign ups, I will contact you with payment information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sign up by getting on the wait list - after payment is confirmed I will move you to the &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;NO REFUNDS unless the performance is canceled or you can find someone to take your place!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am also trying to get a tour put together for Nerd Fun if we have enough people.  Look for that in a separate meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;EDIT: These tickets were purchased months in advance, so we can't get any more now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wing</member_name><member_id>3393735</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1284065774000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270698412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Wicked" at the Boston Opera House</name><id>13121414</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283727600000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13121414/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/b/global_14213339.jpeg</photo_url></item>