<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>You're invited to my fund raiser!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On April 20, 2009 I'll be running in the 113th Boston Marathon...  I've been training very hard because this is the first time I'm running the Boston Marathon, and my third marathon overall.  I'm very excited because Boston is also where I was raised and grew up.  Boston is very rich in history and tradition and running the city's marathon allows me to be a part of the history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever more importantly, by running the marathon I'm able to raise funds through my running team, Team Brigham which supports Brigham &amp;amp; Women's Hospital.  Team Brigham raises money for essential BWH community health programs to improve the quality of life for those less fortunate. These programs provide jobs for young people interested in health care, offer programs for domestic violence victims,  make available compassionate services for women with breast cancer and support community health centers - all addressing the serious needs of our community and beyond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thursday April 16th, 2009 starting at 8pm I will be hosting a fund raiser at Fuji 1546 in Quincy, MA. Food will be provided along with prize give aways for gift certificates, Red Sox or Patriots tickets, and a brand new Nintendo Wii gaming console.  100% of the proceeds from the fund raiser will go to Brigham &amp;amp; Women's Hospital health programs.  To view the official invitation, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/p.php?i=691391060&amp;amp;k=35CTXZRSPW4M51F1XKW4XU" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not able it make it to the fund raiser but would still like to donate to a worthy cause, please visit my fund raising website at &lt;a href="http://www.rubenrunsboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rubenrunsb...&lt;/a&gt;.  I appreciate anything you can donate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make it a great day,&lt;br /&gt;Ruben&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a name tag</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250194192000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>realestateinvestor</urlname><id>596743</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>InvestorsBeat.com - Massachusetts Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238022501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Real Estate Solutions April Meetup</name><id>10036170</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239926400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestateinvestor/events/10036170/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/8/global_7853928.jpeg</photo_url></item>