<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 138</address_2><address_1>909 E Main Rd</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02842</zip><lat>41.529285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.848.5161</phone><name>Newport Vineyards</name><city>Middletown</city><id>247043</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.273540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;October 11, 2009 Newport Vineyards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I called today about this event - I was told this is a laid back walking open house type event. &lt;u&gt;I changed the time to 1:30 since there were a lot of reservations at 12:30 and it was suggested by the Winery.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entry is &lt;b&gt;$10 per person - it includes wine tasting, an open house tour, live music, and a logo wine glass &lt;br /&gt;(case club members complimentary).&lt;/b&gt; &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;I was told the event accepts CASH only only for its Festivals.[/&lt;/b&gt;u]&lt;br /&gt;Food station and hay ride tickets can be purchased for $5.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They would like some RSVP's therefore I changed the RSVP date to Thursday so we can get an updated count. If you would like to RSVP after that date please email me. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvest Open House &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wine tasting, live music by local Beatles' tribute band &amp;quot;Abbey Rhode&amp;quot; (I have heard this tribue band play in Bristol they are fun!), and a selection of locally grown gourmet bites. Food stations from McGrath's Fine Catering including burger &amp;quot;sliders&amp;quot; from Aquidneck Farms grass fed beef, chowder and stuffies, local cheese, and more. Fatulli's will have mouth watering offerings. Stop in and treat your senses.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check the Meetup site the morning of this event in case of cancellation due to low participation and/or severe weather.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will  meet/greet at 1:30 by large wooden barrel to the right facing front door, after that call my cell 401-829-8516.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lonnie</member_name><member_id>6911660</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255477799000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newportfriends</urlname><id>429443</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>Newport Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254580634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Celebration at Newport Vineyards - Wine, Live Music, &amp; Food.</name><id>11536215</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255282200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newportfriends/events/11536215/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/2/global_3972658.jpeg</photo_url></item>