<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>294 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.551907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-922-0004</phone><name>Organic Garden Cafe</name><city>Beverly</city><id>598589</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.879082</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Memory of a Place: A Seaweed Harvester Reflects on 40 Years of Play and Work&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday morning, September 26th, at 9:30AM to 11AM. If possible, please call 978/922-0004 to RSVP for this FREE event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larch Hanson will be at the Organic Graden Cafe (294 Cabot St. Beverly, MA &lt;a href="http://www.organicgardencafe.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.organicgar...&lt;/a&gt;) to tell stories and show a video about the work he has done on the coast of Maine for the past 40 years, harvesting seaweeds for food and medicine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to integrate seaweeds into your life, this presentation will be very helpful, very strong and beautiful ocean medicine for your body and soul. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larch is thoroughly at home working and playing in small boats in the surf at the same time that he is totally at home in his deepest spiritual core which is in sync with the energies of ocean, blue and lavender light, and the life in the sea and beyond the veil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larch runs his business like a CSA (community supported agirculture), and he refers to his customers as &amp;quot;A Circle of Friends&amp;quot;.  Members of this circle are welcome to visit Larch on the coast of Maine, six hours from Boston, an hour's drive beyond Bar Harbor and Acadia National Park.  His house sleeps 20 people, and there's no charge for an overnight stay!  His websites are www.theseaweedman.com and &lt;a href="http://www.alcasoft.com/seaweed/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.alcasoft.c...&lt;/a&gt; and you will find his contact information there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those of you who bring a laptop will have an opportunity to get Larch's website, video and stills on your personal laptop screen.  Larch will also have some of his wild harvested seaweed for purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is a rare opportunity in this day and age to share such a moment with an individual so genuine, caring, interesting and wise. I am very excited to see Larch again this Sunday and share this time with any of you who can make it!   Hope to see you here - Rawbert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The photo was taken last month of 64 year old Larch harvesting digitata from the wildest surf locations he can find for seaweed harvesting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seeking the Wild Exception ---Larch Hanson &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There are unseen patterns,&lt;br /&gt;Afloat in the Universe,&lt;br /&gt;Anchored to the Earth by mineral salts,&lt;br /&gt;That determine the Form of each plant.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A plant is but a condensation of a Pattern, or Thought,&lt;br /&gt;Expressed in transformation of minerals, water and sunlight,&lt;br /&gt;Yearning to return,&lt;br /&gt;through evolution,&lt;br /&gt;to its true home,&lt;br /&gt;In Infinity.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A human body, also, is a condensation of&lt;br /&gt;a Pattern,&lt;br /&gt;And the human body is anchored to the earth,&lt;br /&gt;Through the minerals of plants,&lt;br /&gt;And the human Spirit is aided in its return&lt;br /&gt;to Infinity&lt;br /&gt;By the Essences of plants, arising, lifting,&lt;br /&gt;upwards toward the Light.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The sea plants were the first ones to truly anchor themselves&lt;br /&gt;To the earth, through concentrating minerals&lt;br /&gt;at their lower end,&lt;br /&gt;And then floating, upwards, lifting, back toward&lt;br /&gt;the Light.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We all had to go down into the depths with dark&lt;br /&gt;and salt,&lt;br /&gt;Before we could lift, upward, toward the Light.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I ask my daughter:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If we destroyed all the daisy plants,&lt;br /&gt;(like the ones in the vase on the table)&lt;br /&gt;And all the daisy seeds ....&lt;br /&gt;Would there still be a chance for daisies?&lt;br /&gt;Would the world again evolve through daisies?&lt;br /&gt;Does the Pattern still hold?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I have sent her into the Darkness,&lt;br /&gt;to ponder on the Light.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;She knows that her Pattern is anchored&lt;br /&gt;and uplifted&lt;br /&gt;By the Patterns of kelp, alaria, dulse, nori,&lt;br /&gt;Buckwheat, oats, rye, wheat, millet, rice, com,&lt;br /&gt;Carrot, kale, onion, bean, burdock, cabbage&lt;br /&gt;and broccoli,&lt;br /&gt;To name a few.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The thought of losing any link in the&lt;br /&gt;Chain of Being&lt;br /&gt;Troubles her ....especially in this precarious age.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The human family is asleep to this Awareness,&lt;br /&gt;This Knowing:&lt;br /&gt;Destroy the plant patterns,&lt;br /&gt;Or interfere with them,&lt;br /&gt;In the name of &amp;quot;improvement&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;And you will distort the human pattern.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A sea harvester seeks the wildness of the&lt;br /&gt;outermost islands,&lt;br /&gt;In hopes of capturing the unspoiled patterns...&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;And when he grows old,&lt;br /&gt;He roams in fields of waving grain&lt;br /&gt;Seeking the Wild Exception.&lt;br /&gt;---Larch Hanson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's been thirty years since I wrote Seeking the Wild Exception, and the young daughter mentioned in the poem is now an ecologist candidate for her PhD.  At age 64, I still push toward the wildest surf locations I can find for seaweed harvesting, and in my garden, there are many plants that simply reseed themselves, volunteering because they have adapted to the seaweed-rich soil that I've created for them.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rawbert</member_name><member_id>11144266</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285792028000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285218765000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Larch Hanson (FREE Talk!) @ Rawbert's</name><id>14867812</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285507800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/14867812/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/4/global_18177604.jpeg</photo_url></item>