<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Many people harbor deep and secret feelings that there is something inherently wrong with them. This results in people feeling 'less than' others or having to make themselves feel 'better than' others. In fact, if you could see yourself as your Creator sees you, you would know thoroughly that you are completely loved and accepted. This doesn't mean there's not work to do on yourself, but it does mean your heart can rest in the knowing that while you are doing the work, you are supported by the God of Love. Come and learn how to begin the journey toward love of God and yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;lunch is included with the seminar cost&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the presenter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Father Peter Bowes has served as a Priest and Christian Master Teacher for over 20 years. Though he has had much other life experience, having owned a restaurant and a construction business, had a thriving psychotherapy practice, written three books on spirituality, been married for many years and raised two daughters, his primary focus in life has been his devotion to serving God and teaching others how to come into a real experience of God inside themselves.  Currently, Father Peter serves as Co-Director of the Order of Christ/Sophia, teaching and ministering to his spiritual students, and guiding fifteen Centers of Light and their ministers around the country. He travels between these Centers year-round, teaching and lecturing, as well as performing his music as a singer-songwriter of Mystical Christian folk rock. Many of the elements of the Mystical Christian teachings can be heard and experienced in Father Peter's music, encouraging the listener to seek and discover the Truth within. Listen to his music on Sophia Radio. When not traveling, Father Peter lives at the Center of Light in Chicago, IL.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347686000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241307553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Learning to Love Yourself</name><id>10322212</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242482400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/10322212/</event_url></item>