<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Property Description  695 acres | Established 1984&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noanet Woodlands features many miles of shady trails and woods roads for walking, cross-country skiing, snowshoeing, and horseback riding. A hike up Noanet Peak leads to a view of Boston's skyline above the forest canopy. The Reservation is named after a chief of the Natick Indians, who camped, fished, and hunted along Noanet Brook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During settlement, Noanet Woodlands was cleared for timber, firewood, and a few small homesteads. In the early nineteenth century, Samuel Fisher, Jr. used Noanet Brook to operate a sawmill, producing boards, planks, and joists for the construction of buildings in burgeoning Dedham. Fisher's business boomed throughout the 1820s and 1830s. Later, the Dover Union Iron Company built a large rolling and slitting mill that made barrel hoops, wheel rims, nail plates, and nail rods from forged iron. Today the mill's twenty-four-foot-high dam and twenty-foot-deep wheel pit are preserved, but visitors will have to imagine the towering thirty-six-foot overshot wheel that powered the mill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1923, Miss Amelia Peabody purchased Mill Farm on Dedham Street. Over the next sixty-one years, she acquired thirty additional parcels of land stretching south to Powisset Farm. Her diverse interests included outdoor recreation, sustainable agriculture, architectural experimentation, and land conservation, all of which shaped the landscape today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails&lt;br /&gt;17 miles of trails. Moderate hiking, strenuous in places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a trustee reservation.  Donation from non-trustee members are welcome but not necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For trail map and more info please see &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/pages/341_noanet_woodlands.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need a ride please say so in your RSVP..if you can give a ride please do the same.  The most convenient train station to be picked up at is newton highlands.  I can pick a few people up from there at 9:45.  Please email Luba directly if you have questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will dine at&lt;br /&gt;Fresh City:&lt;br /&gt;241 Needham St&lt;br /&gt;Newton MA 02464&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182264088000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180874498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Noanet Woodlands</name><id>5847285</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182090600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5847285/</event_url></item>