<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Guys!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're trying something new for the June Meetup Event!  We're planning a salsa video &amp;amp; potluck night.  Hong, one of our meetup members, has kindly opened up his place (and HUGE TV) to us in June for a get together.  We'll be watching a salsa video compilation of various salsa dancing in NY, Paris, and various salsa congresses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to hang out and get to know one another outside the dance scene.  Plus, if you're new to the scene, you'll get to see what salsa dancing around the world is like.  Or, maybe some of  you are looking for a little inspiration? :)  I know videos always helped me get out of ruts or just plain motivate me in the past.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And the best part.....Hong lives right aroung the corner from Ryles (no joke).  So, after the video night, you can decide to head over to Ryles at 8:30 for the lesson, or with everyone else at 9:30 for the dancing at Noche Latina's Tuesday night at Ryles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been wanting to do this for a while, so I'm reallly excited about it!  Only problem....THE MAX IS 12 PEOPLE, so make sure that you are definitely coming if you sign up.  Then, bring your dance shoes, a dish to share with everyone else, and some energy for the dancing later that evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm   Meet at Hong's place to watch videos, hang out, and have some finger food&lt;br /&gt;8:30pm   Some people can leave to attend the lesson at Ryles.  Others can stay for more movies (cover is $13 with lesson)&lt;br /&gt;9:30pm   We all head over to Ryles for the dancing  (cover is $8)&lt;br /&gt;12:30am Time to Go Home :( &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you guys can join us!  Sign up to the right if you can come, and please mention what you'll be bringing in the comments so we don't have 20 boxes of cookies and nothing to drink.  ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ana :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182468867000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179362446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa Video &amp; Potluck Night (June Meetup Event)</name><id>5786407</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182295800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/5786407/</event_url></item>