<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I need the excersize so if you want you can join me on the walk ( i am going to do this with or without a group) or meet me at the Park later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wind is too high for a paddle event today, but cooling for a walk-hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Sunny, with a high near 65. North wind between 10 and 13 mph. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;As the paddling season winds down, my other group starts  up doing walking events and other activities during the cold season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i invite the new kayakers to meet the other group members on this event from my FY group and enjoy another method to stay fit and active both mentally and physically as best i can come up with throughout the season untill its paddling time again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Above map link is correct for your specific directions, or use your GPS, general driving directions at bottom of page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the return to some walking events as i pick the remaining good days for kayaking as i find them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its too soon to know the exact weather, but usually after a frontal passage of rain the wind tends to be up there and makes kayaking not pleasant, but lets see if Sunday is more fitting for a paddling event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather :  (as of Tuesday) its usually a bit different ? &lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 65  wind unknown.  I will update as the week progresses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear some good boots Cobalt Goblins are kind of squishy when ya stomp on em and its also muddy in their swamp but its only a few BIG feet wide and miles deep...most of us can jump over the chasm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first part is a walk through an old torture Camp then up a LITTLE HILL (apx 20-30 minuts) A snack at the top, the &amp;quot;Feature&amp;quot; is enjoying the sun looking out over a nice lake &amp;amp; countryside, up there you will be able to converse with our group members &amp;amp; anyone else at the top.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It depends how windy it is up there on how long we stay..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At The bottom, the next &amp;quot;Feature&amp;quot; is to explore for some Deep Lurking GOBLINS and maybe a special guest coming up from the under world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we cook some Goblins in the fire place @ Hurting Park for the last &amp;quot;Feature&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hurting Park is just south of the intersection. Directions supplied if necessary at the walk location when we are done or just follow us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some water &amp;amp; snacks for the top Look Out, Bring some Pot Luck food &amp;amp; your faviourite Bugg Juice for the Barbie-Q and Goblin Boil Up at Hurting Park just minutes away for after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some old wood also for the fire in one of the 4 fireplaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info on the Resident Goblins:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Hiking HERE Beware Of Goblins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;Peter Marteka | The Hartford Courant    January 4, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Beware of the goblin who haunts the deep dark forests of Cobalt. A goblin ? an old legend says that prevented generations of miners from finding the main vein of a mineral that once produced some of the most brilliant blue colors humankind has ever known.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Along the banks of the aptly named Mine Brook is the entrance to the old cobalt mine. Located off Gag Poutch Road in the aptly named Cobalt section of East Hampton, there are plenty of vestiges of the mine that was worked in the 18th and 19th centuries, from huge stone foundations to fenced-in mine shafts. Big pieces of quartz boulders lie in the brook's bed outside the entrance ? the tailings of centuries-old mining operations. Icicles hang from the moss and fern-covered hillside. A stream rolls down from the mine entrance, creating a brown, rusty outflow in the brook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Like the miners who searched for gold in the far-off Klondike a century later, men came to the forests of East Hampton in the middle 1700s in search of a strike. But there were no shouts of &amp;quot;Thar's gold in them thar hills.&amp;quot; It wasn't gold these prospectors were searching for, but cobalt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Cobalt is extremely rare in the United States, with the only mineral ever produced in the country of measurable quantity coming from the East Hampton forests. Rocks containing the reddish-gray mineral produce a greenish-yellow stain on the surface and emit a sulfurous and arsenic odor. The mineral was exported and used to give chinaware and pottery a brilliant blue color.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Cobalt is the Anglicized German word, Kobold, meaning a goblin or gnome. German miners once believed that cobalt was a demon in the mines, bringing them bad luck and cave-ins. The string of bad luck continued in Cobalt during the 18th and 19th centuries. Over that period, five successive mining companies, starting with John Sebastian Stephauney in 1762 and ending with the Chatham Cobalt Mining Company of Philadelphia in the 1850s, came to Cobalt and tried to make mining the ore profitable. But little cobalt was found in the rock and miners never discovered the main vein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Prior to the search for Cobalt, gold had been discovered in the mid-1600s. The township of Middletown, which owned the land, granted Gov. John Winthrop permission to mine it. Excavation began in 1661 around the stream beds and rocky valleys of what is now known as Great Hill Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;It was rumored that he had found gold from which he cast gold rings,&amp;quot; according to the publication &amp;quot;East Hampton Bicentennial 1967.&amp;quot; The hill became known as &amp;quot;The Governor's Ring.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    To some, Cobalt Mine is just a hole in the ground. To others, it sits in silent testimony to a bygone era when men toiled and struggled to mine a mineral protected by a goblin that ended up breaking their hearts and spirit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    To reach Gag Poutch Road, take Route 66 to Cobalt. Turn North on Depot Hill Road. (directly across from Route 151). Follow Depot Hill Road (North Direction) to Gag Poutch Road.&lt;br /&gt;    Take a right onto Gag Poutch Road and follow it till it turns into a dirt road, you will cross a small bridge but keep going till the second bridge or park at the old HAUNTED CCC camp drive way right before the second bridge, There are a few places to park in the area ( maybe 12 cars or so) so you may have to jockey to get one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I WILL PUT OUT A FEW ORANGE STRIPED CONES TO HELP IN FINDING US.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;    See ya there,&lt;br /&gt;    al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;############################################################################&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hurting Park Directions for the after party:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Hurd State Park: From Hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use 50 Hurd Park Road East Hampton ct for GPS and maps, its close enough but look for the real entrance nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I 91 South to rte 9 South, (exit 22 left side on 91 S)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right for the Aragooni Bridge, (rte 17/66 East direction, go over bridge and get onto rte 17 / 66), &lt;br /&gt;follow 17/66 (stay on 66) to Cobalt center, take a right onto 151 South,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;go 2.6 miles to the intersection of 151/Hog Hill Road/Hurd Park Road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear right onto Hurd Park Road, go apx 0.75 miles then the main park entrance is on the right, &lt;br /&gt;Follow the paved road apx 0.75 miles then there is a sign that says &amp;quot;BALL field and SHELTER&amp;quot; on the right, &lt;br /&gt;take that right and go to end of the twisty road to the big parking lot, &lt;br /&gt;We will be at the shelter at one of the fireplaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see you all soon.. &lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for ORANGE STRIPED TRAFFIC CONES @ the old Torture Camp and ORANGE Hunting HAT</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286218407000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285685171000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WALK @ COBALT HILL + Visit to Hell Gate &amp; Fireside POT LUCK BBQ @ HURT ST PK aft</name><id>14924181</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286035200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14924181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/7/global_18329447.jpeg</photo_url></item>