<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Long Wharf Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.299412</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sports Haven: Information</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1523453</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.911964</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bike New Haven on a leisurely, 10 mile group ride in support of New Haven's &lt;a href="http://www.downtowneveningsoupkitchen.com" target="_blank"&gt;Downtown Evening Soup Kitchen!&lt;/a&gt; We'll ride city-endorsed bicycle routes past some of New Haven's finest green spaces in honor of DESK's sustainability campaign, and end with a celebratory BBQ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.ridetoendhunger.com/bicycle.php5" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ridetoendhunger.com/bicycle.php5" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ridetoendh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for full info on parking and registration, and detailed maps.  Registration is $25 for single rider, $35 for double (i.e. tandem bikes or child seats).  Register the morning of the ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consider downloading a pledge form (see &lt;a href="http://www.ridetoendhunger.com/bicycle.php5" target="_blank"&gt;ride website&lt;/a&gt; above) and collecting donations of $5 or more to turn in at registration. DESK has been serving record numbers of people as operating expenses continue to increase, and every bit helps to support our critical mission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't have a bicycle? You can still support DESK by joining the entire group (motorcyclists, bicyclists, and supporters) at the &lt;b&gt;BBQ lunch after the ride--starting at 1pm--at the Elks Lodge (522-524 State St.) for just $10 (BBQ is free for registered riders, with cash bar).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact for this event is Michelle.  I'm also the ride organizer, so I should be easy to identify on ride day, and easiest to get in touch with before 10am on the morning of the event!  Meet with me at the AT&amp;amp;T Parking Lot on Grove and State Sts. at 10am to park and ride down with a group to registration, or meet us at ride registration/start at Sports Haven (600 Long Wharf Dr.), where you can park as well.  Registration is 9-11am (with free coffee and donuts); ride start is promptly at 11am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll email my cell phone to &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's a couple days before.  You can also RSVP on &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=115379484039#/event.php?eid=115379484039" target="_blank"&gt;facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253027506000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249756681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ride the 1st annual BICYCLE LEG of the Ride to End Hunger for D.E.S.K.!</name><id>11065875</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252854000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11065875/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/9/3/global_10084499.jpeg</photo_url></item>