<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hickory Hill Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03053</zip><lat>42.873618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Musquash Conservation Area</name><city>Londonderry</city><id>1178579</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.403379</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Host: Claire P. cell @ 603-247-0897 &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather permitting, I think it would be fun to go hiking or snow shoeing on the Musquash Conservation Area trails in Londonderry NH. Please know that my intent is to enjoy the view of the area, and to chat along the way.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This event is meant more to have fun than to get a workout.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I plan on hiking for approximately two hours, while taking many small breaks along the way.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 2:00pm &lt;strong&gt;sharp&lt;/strong&gt;, at the Hickory Hill Dr, entrance. Please follow these directions: From the Nashua area: Take NH 111 East turn left on NH 102 East, drive 5.9 miles then turn left on Parmenter Rd, drive 0.4 miles, take a slight right onto High Range Rd, drive 2.5 miles, turn left on Hickory Hill Dr.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Drive to the end of the road for the entrance. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;From the Manchester area: Take NH 128 South (Mammoth Rd), drive 4.0 miles, turn right on Shasta Dr, drive 1.2 miles, turn left on High Range Rd, drive 0.3 miles, take first right on Hickory Hill Dr.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Drive to the end of the road for the entrance. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Look for a white Toyota or a Meetup sign.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers for comfort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is at no cost! I hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP or call my cell @ 603-247-0897&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Do not RSVP no.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Musquash Conservation Area, Londonderry, NH &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claire P</member_name><member_id>7906902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332717065000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331467640000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking or snowshoeing at Musquash in Londonderry</name><id>55870872</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332698400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/55870872/</event_url></item>