<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One other update, Morse's Pond's rules for dogs is &amp;quot;Off leash, up to two dogs per person, must be under control&amp;quot; so... DOGS WELCOME! (Tory likes to play!)  Dogs must be leashed on the Wellesley College campus and should be on leashes on the town paths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On October 31, 1999, renowned allergist Dr. Dirk Greineder brutally murdered his wife while walking their dog through the woods of Morses Pond in Wellesley. We'll retrace the murder by walking to where they parked their car, follow the same wooded path they took, we'll pause where he claimed she stayed behind because of a hurt back, we'll find the area where the body was found and then hike to where the evidence was found.  For more information about this brutal crime, see &lt;a href="http://www.courttv.com/trials/greineder/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.courttv.co...&lt;/a&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After walking through the woods, we'll follow the beautiful wooded paths through Wellesley College and around the town. We'll start and finish at the Tailby Parking Lot, adjacent to the Wellesley Square Train Station. After the walk, we will have a group lunch at a nearby restaurant. Most of this walk will be on paved or hard pack trails. A few areas will be rougher trails, but that is only a small area of the Morses Pond woods.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the walk we will have lunch at Captain Mardens seafood restaurant.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map of Morses Pond area is here: &lt;a href="http://wellesleyma.virtualtownhall.net/Pages/WellesleyMA_Trails/mpmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://wellesleyma.vi...&lt;/a&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;Wellesley Trail maps are here: &lt;a href="http://wellesleyma.virtualtownhall.net/Pages/WellesleyMA_Trails/gistrailmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://wellesleyma.vi...&lt;/a&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking in this lot is free on Saturdays. The Framingham/Worcester Line train leaves South Station at 10:50 AM and arrives to Wellesley Square at 11:22 AM, so we'll meet around that time. This is a Zone 3 trip and they charge extra if you buy your outbound ticket on the train, so be sure to pick one up at South Station or Back Bay. The return trains leave Wellesley Square at 3:02 and 3:47.           &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions? Call Joanna at 781-956-2099         &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196095232000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194272118000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greineder Murder Scene Walk - Morses Pond and Beyond</name><id>6680129</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195921800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6680129/</event_url></item>