<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 Bradford Street </address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 751-4812</phone><name>Camilles Roman Garden</name><city>Providence</city><id>978518</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422015</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Providence Collective Monday Meetup series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar and restaurant scenes in Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Camilles - in Historic Federal Hill!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P-Collective member Michele has graciously offered to host this week's MNM and picked a place we've haven't been to yet!  - yes, it really is true!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camilles on Federal Hill is a classic. Renowned for its location and fabulous food, it seems that there is also a lovely patio terrace in the back that offers beautiful al fresco dining and also seems to have a large bar area for mingling and chatting the evening away - but we wouldn't know anything about that, would we...... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if you haven't been, where better to spend a warm summer evening than in the Roman Garden patio at Camilles socializing with friends. This one is worth knowing about, so let's check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michele will be wearing a white skirt with a pink polo shirt and glasses. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Michelle is hosting, please look at her picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michele S</member_name><member_id>8570259</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281394487000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280459235000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Camilles!</name><id>14260123</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280786400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/14260123/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>