<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for meetup fees, etc.</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Anyone who is available on Saturday December 16th is invited to join together for a bit of holiday/yule/solstice cheer while seeing a living breathing permaculture home at the same time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Note that space is limited so it's important to RSVP at this site as soon as you are able ... Thanks! *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles &amp;amp; Julia Yelton welcome us to their very own Humastacia Permaculture Gardens (less active in December...but still very wonderful) for a potluck lunch followed by a brief discussion of cosmology (an area of interest for them which forms some of the underpinnings for their approach to permaculture) and then a tour of the home inside and out.  This event will offer something for the strictly practical-minded amongst us as well as for those interested in the &amp;quot;connectedness of all things&amp;quot; as we write our own stories of sustainability into the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING:  A dish/beverage/snack to share.  Comfy warm clothes for the outside part of the tour and/or hanging out near the outdoor bread oven (which will be fired up that day).  Optional:  A written intention for the new year (for your eyes only:) that we can send up in the firing of the oven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CARPOOLING:  Anyone who would like to carpool from Portland is encouraged to meet at the Marginal Way Park-and-Ride lot (Next to Franklin Arterial and across from Bally Total Fitness; NOT across from Wild Oats) at 10:00 am on 12/16.  We will organize ourselves into the fewest number of vehicles and leave by 10:15 am.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone not carpooling with us can meet us there at 11:30.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166459668000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163871392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Potluck Lunch &amp; Permaculture Tour of Yeltons' Home</name><id>5276808</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166286600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/5276808/</event_url></item>