<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sam Spade, Dashiell Hammett's archetypally tough San Francisco detective, is more 
&lt;em&gt;noir&lt;/em&gt; than 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;a&gt;L.A. Confidential&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and more vulnerable than Raymond Chandler's Marlowe. In 
&lt;em&gt;The Maltese Falcon&lt;/em&gt;, the best known of Hammett's Sam Spade novels (including 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;a&gt;The Dain Curse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;a&gt;The Glass Key&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; ), Spade is tough enough to bluff the toughest thugs and hold off the police, risking his reputation when a beautiful woman begs for his help, while knowing that betrayal may deal him a new hand in the next moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spade's partner is murdered on a stakeout; the cops blame him for the killing; a beautiful redhead with a heartbreaking story appears and disappears; grotesque villains demand a payoff he can't provide; and everyone wants a fabulously valuable gold statuette of a falcon, created as tribute for the Holy Roman Emperor Charles IV. Who has it? And what will it take to get it back? Spade's solution is as complicated as the motives of the seekers assembled in his hotel room, but the truth can be a cold comfort indeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you only know the movie, read the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Maltese Falcon is not only probably the best detective story we have ever read, it is an exceedingly well written novel.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; 
&lt;em&gt;The Times Literary Supplement&lt;/em&gt; (London)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hammett&amp;rsquo;s prose [is] clean and entirely unique. His characters [are] as sharply and economically defined as any in American fiction.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; 
&lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313514025000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312314624000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hammett: The Maltese Falcon</name><id>27995131</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313359200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/27995131/</event_url></item>