<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02180</zip><lat>42.479187</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-279-7885</phone><name>Stoneham Theatre </name><city>Stoneham</city><id>1248388</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100259</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us at a special group rate for a presentation of &amp;quot;The Cutting&amp;quot; at this small, not for profit, professional theater....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this show, Judith is in prison under suspicion of killing her mother. She is also in the prison of her own silence. From the moment the police came to question her she has not spoken a word. As a last resort, a specialist who has had great success with mutism in children, is called in to make a psychiatric assessment. The psychiatrist battles against her entrenched and lonely silence until at last the dam is broken and an extraordinary story pours out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe we will have some of our own stories to tell as well after the show. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are available in a reserved group block for the  &amp;quot;Merrimack Valley Meetup&amp;quot; and may be purchased directly. &lt;br /&gt;Pay by check:&lt;br /&gt; Stoneham Theatre&lt;br /&gt;Attn: Kelly Walsh, Group Sales&lt;br /&gt;395 Main Street, Stoneham, MA 02180&lt;br /&gt; OR&lt;br /&gt;Credit cards: Call Kelly at 781-279-7885 x 105&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyone who reserves before March 3rd is assured of seating with the group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the theater for the show. I am also planning a before show gathering for drinks and a bite to eat so please reply to both events separately. Knowing our group..we will probably go some place after as well! :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205534740000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>10</count></rating><why>Seating is reserved for our group. Please do not reserve a seat unless you are certain that you will attend. You may reply "maybe" but please confirm by March 5th. If we exceed 25 people we might be able to add more seats but may not all be together.</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203102502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stoneham Theater Event</name><id>7337548</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1205022600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7337548/</event_url></item>