<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I forgot the movie's link! Oops! &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810025226/info" target="_blank"&gt;(500) Days of Summer&lt;/a&gt;. There you go!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:40, so let's meet outside the theater BY 7:10. I wait for people for less time on the weekends, seeing as how it's more crowded. So I'll be heading in to buy tickets AT 7:20 sharp. Please keep your RSVP up-to-date and call me with any &amp;quot;I'm lost&amp;quot;s or &amp;quot;I'm late&amp;quot;s!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you tomorrow!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This romantic comedy looks cute (well, we've done all the action movies so far!). (500) Days of Summer stars Joseph Gordon-Levitt (of &amp;quot;3rd Rock from the Sun&amp;quot; fame) and upcoming -- and currently omnipresent -- star Zooey Deschanel (you may have seen her in Yes Man or Almost Famous).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This is a story of boy meets girl, begins the wry, probing narrator of 500 DAYS OF SUMMER, and with that the film takes off at breakneck speed into a funny, true to life and unique dissection of the unruly and unpredictable year-and-a-half of one young man's no-holds-barred love affair.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the theater doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup with a specific time a few days before, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for 500 Days of Summer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250636556000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248919064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>(500) Days of Summer</name><id>10990277</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250290800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10990277/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>