<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>355 Hope St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.835983</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 751-6777</phone><name>Tortilla Flats</name><city>Providence</city><id>690516</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.401337</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Tortilla Flats on Hope st. over on the East Side&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tortillaflatsri.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://tortillaflatsr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tortilla Flats is another East Side institution - yup, its been around 30 years now. Located in an old firehouse on the corner of Hope St. and Olney St. and caddy-corner to Hope High School, its situated north of the Thayer St. shopping area and is somewhat its own neighborhood spot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the food has received mixed reviews by the standards of the very decerning and highly-evolved palettes of most PVD diners, people like it for the warm, casual and friendly atmosphere. Its basic Mexican food served best with their highly regarded Margaritas. Its been around forever and any time we talk about going to a Mexican place, Tortilla Flats always comes up as a place to go. So, if you haven't been in awhile, or you haven't been yet, let's check it out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but you can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265629747000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264528292000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Tortilla Flats!</name><id>12429051</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265065200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12429051/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/b/global_5889099.jpeg</photo_url></item>