<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DEADLINE HAS PAST, SORRY NO NEW RESERVATIONS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How Does the Wedeln Ski Club celebrate President's day weekend??  Eat chili and ski, of course!  The fun will start Friday night of the holiday weekend.  Friday is usually a casual BYOB at our club, hang out in front of the fire, meet other skier/riders.  We will hit the mountains on Saturday, Sunday and maybe even Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The real highlight of the weekend is our 8th annual Chilifestival, starts right after skiing on Sunday.  Club members and guest are welcome to enter their own secret recipe, yes fabulous prizes for the winners.  Vote, eat and enjoy the atmosphere.  Last year we had over a dozen chili-chefs and almost 150 taste testers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President's day weekend is an ideal time to come up and check out our ski house.  Cost to stay is only $20 a night.  Please bring your own sheets, pillows, blanket and towels. The Wedeln Ski Club is a not-for-profit club that owns a large house (former country inn) with 19 bed rooms.  Beds are available for full members or guests.  As always the Wedeln Ski Club is 21+ only.  More details to follow if you sign up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the house by 8pm friday night</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298332423000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295646992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>President's Day Weekend - Ski and eat chili!</name><id>16136842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298077200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/16136842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/3/global_10297043.jpeg</photo_url></item>