<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1084 Shennecossett Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06340</zip><lat>41.317254</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-405-9052</phone><name>Alexey von Schlippe Gallery of Art</name><city>Groton</city><id>933288</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.063891</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/d/7/c/event_92564412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Paintings and Mixed Media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opening reception-6 8pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frank Bruckman ~ Scott Kahn ~ Rick Silberberg ~ Native American Art/Adornment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill Morrison &amp;amp; Kent Hewitt Jazz Duo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be there at about 6:30...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/b/event_38459131.jpeg" width="55" height="52" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Many of you may know Frank Bruckman from shows we have been to at Kehler Liddell in New Haven.&amp;nbsp; Come join us at this wonderful Gallery&amp;nbsp;in Groton; a lovely estate with&amp;nbsp;beautiful ocean side grounds and an interesting sculpture path.&amp;nbsp;The represented artists are tops and the jazz performance at the reception always makes for an enjoyable evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The&amp;nbsp;Gallery&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

The Alexey von Schlippe Gallery of Art was founded in 1992 by Julia Pavone and David Madacsi, at the University of Connecticut's Avery Point Campus, which occupies the Long Island Sound Gatsby-era estate of industrialist Morton Freeman Plant. The Gallery is located in the Branford House Mansion, a 19,000 square-foot granite Tudor mansion built by Plant at the turn of the century, which itself is a treasury of carved, chased, sculpted, cast, molded and inlaid works of European craftsmen in oak, mahogany, walnut, onyx, marble, sandstone, bronze, iron and plaster.The mansion, a registered property in the National Register of Historic Places, which was renovated and restored, has become the focal point of this seventy-three acre, seaside campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Gallery provides four separate but contiguous &lt;a href="http://www.averypointarts.uconn.edu/exhibitions.htm"&gt;exhibition&lt;/a&gt; spaces.One of these spaces is most often dedicated to the exhibition of works from what we regard as a unique treasure--a permanent collection of paintings by the late Alexey von Schlippe (1915-1988), an innovative and accomplished painter of international reputation, and former Professor of Art at the University of Connecticut's Avery Point campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The additional gallery spaces are used for exhibits of regional, national and international artists as well as for student exhibits. It is a policy and purpose of the Alexey von Schlippe Gallery of Art to offer significant exposure to artists from across the complete spectrum of artistic expression, especially those doing innovative work. We believe this policy will afford the public (and -- especially importantly -- students) access and exposure to an enhanced diversity of creative works of art, particularly by regional artists.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the reception area where the music is performed</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330888327000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328971298000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paintings &amp; Mixed Media</name><id>51944522</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330731000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/51944522/</event_url></item>