<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 White Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.388901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Porter Square Shopping Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12742462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119186</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear BA Members,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE post if you can drive or if you need a ride. We need to make sure we have enough drivers and that riders have one if they need it. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come hike with fellow BA members! Meet in the Shaws parking lot near the Porter Square T stop. Contact me at 857-236-5631 if you can't find us. Remember your bag lunch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for drivers for all those who wish to attend this trip, so post a message if you are available to drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Franconia Notch is a popular hiking destination for many who live in New England. It is a intermediate level challenging hike with typical New Hampshire terrain (rocky and steep), 2.5-3 hours drive from Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Franconia Notch is one of the most frequented series of peaks in New Hampshire and part of the White Mountain range, noted for its varied hiking trails and great views (e.g., &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/IesTwk"&gt;http://bit.ly/IesTwk&lt;/a&gt;). This hike is recommended for intermediate hikers, as the summit is over 4,000 feet. The notch is located primarily in the town of &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franconia,_New_Hampshire"&gt;Franconia&lt;/a&gt; but extends south into &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lincoln,_New_Hampshire"&gt;Lincoln&lt;/a&gt;. It is bordered to the east by &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franconia_Ridge"&gt;Franconia Ridge&lt;/a&gt;, comprising &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Lafayette"&gt;Mount Lafayette&lt;/a&gt; (5,249 feet/1,600 m), &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Lincoln_%28New_Hampshire%29"&gt;Mount Lincoln&lt;/a&gt; (5,089 feet/1,551 m), and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_Haystack_Mountain_%28New_Hampshire%29"&gt;Little Haystack Mountain&lt;/a&gt; (4,780 feet/1,460 m), and to the west by 4,080-foot (1,240 m) &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannon_Mountain_%28New_Hampshire%29"&gt;Cannon Mountain&lt;/a&gt; and the sheer face of Cannon Cliff. &lt;strong&gt;For more information: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franconia_Notch"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franconia_Notch&lt;/a&gt;. And: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.franconianotch.org/things-to-do/great-outdoors/hiking.aspx"&gt;http://www.franconianotch.org/things-to-do/great-outdoors/hiking.aspx&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check out the &lt;strong&gt;weather report on the top of the mountain&lt;/strong&gt; in the following link for Franconia Notch before attending this hike. This page will help prepare you for the weather conditions you will face and the type of clothing, footwear, and gear you will need. Check out this site and refresh for the correct date to check weather conditions: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Lafayette/forecasts/1603"&gt;http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Lafayette/forecasts/1603&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Mt. Lafayette is representative of the weather we will encounter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the Mt. Monadnock weekly report for updated information on weather and trail conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring a windbreak, sweater or fleece for the summit (yes it gets down to 40 degrees sometimes even in summer) at that elevation,&lt;/strong&gt; an extra pair of hiking socks for stream walks, hiking boots, layers, warm jacket, rain jacket, &lt;strong&gt;two liters of water&lt;/strong&gt;, lunch, snacks, first aid kit, trail map, and compass if you have one, smartphone trail gps apps are great if you can download them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a one day trip with the sole purpose of hiking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;The Franconia Notch loop beginning with The Old Bridle Path and ending with the Falling waters trail.&lt;/strong&gt; At a minimum, we require that anyone signing up have a basic fitness level &lt;em&gt;comparable&lt;/em&gt; to walking 3 miles daily or running 3 miles three times per week. The hike will be about 6 miles round trip and take an estimated 5-6 hours on the trail, including lunch. This trail is often busy with hikers and rated a 3 out of 5 in difficulty, meaning it can be noticeably steep at times, you’ll be breathing in deeper and faster, and you’ll probably need to step up onto or over rocks, tree roots, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Old Bridle Path - Franconia Notch State Park&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.franconianotch.org/things-to-do/great-outdoors/hiking.aspx"&gt;http://www.franconianotch.org/things-to-do/great-outdoors/hiking.aspx&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Distance: 4 miles round trip &lt;br /&gt;

 Rating: Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;

 Great views of the Notch.  Start at Trailhead parking lot on the right on I-93 north between Exits 34A &amp;amp; 34B, or park at the Lafayette Campground and cross under the Interstate. This is one of the most popular trails in the area. At .2 miles the Falling Water Trail goes to the right; the Old Bridle Trail goes straight. At 1.9 miles you will emerge on the first of two spectacular open ledges. The next is 100 feet further. The rest of the trip up Agony Ridge to the Greenleaf hut is very difficult. We will take Falling Waters trail back down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be hiking at a moderate to brisk pace, and we will want to keep all members together for the safety of all our hikers. So, cooperation to this end is important.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Note: For safety, anyone in not wearing hiking boots or similar footwear (exceptions for very experienced hikers who have come before) and those not carrying water will not be allowed to carpool with the group Franconia Notch.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Need To Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 All summits are potentially hazardous due to high winds and unpredictable weather. Please bring appropriate provisions and hiking gear in preparation. Note it tends to be colder than average New England temperatures at the summit. Please be sure to bring the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: Franconia State Park day use fee&lt;/strong&gt;: $5 per person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking Equipment&lt;/strong&gt; recommended by Hike Safe: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;2 Liters of Water&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hiking boots &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt; No vibram 5-fingers or barefoot/light footwear as trails are expected to be wet and potentially snowy/icy. Wet/ cold feet mean turning back to the car &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweater or Pile Jacket &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long Pants (wool or synthetic)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shorts- wicking only&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;T-shirt- wicking only&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bag lunch (we will be on a mountain and driving for 8-9 hours, so bring lunch and snacks)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;extra socks &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;(a welcome treat for the feet at mid-hike, or if you inadvertently step in a stream or snow. They also double as mittens…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flashlight or Headlamp (required) Dark falls quickly below tree-line on this hike!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;high energy lunch and snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;winter jacket and shell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Aid Kit/Repair Kit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whistle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rain/Wind Jacket &amp;amp; Pants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pocket Knife&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hiking poles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;map&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;compass&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Notice&lt;/em&gt;: Pets are not allowed on the mountain! &lt;br /&gt;

 No Camping or Fires except at campgrounds!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Text/ call me at 857-236-5631 if for some reason you have trouble locating us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;NOTE: HIKING HAS INHERENT RISKS. DO NOT ATTEND THIS MEETUP IF YOU ARE UNSURE IF YOU ARE ADEQUATELY PREPARED. AS A GROUP WE CAN DECREASE RISK BY BUDDYING UP AND LOOKING OUT FOR EACH OTHER BUT NOBODY IS LIABLE FOR YOU. THIS IS A VOLUNTARY HIKE. IF YOU ATTEND, YOU ARE ASSUMING THE RISK.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368933699000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367959209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Franconia Notch!</name><id>118229802</id><duration>41400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368880200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/118229802/</event_url></item>