<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per season</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi All: Just a quick update. We have 40+ people signed up already.  If you havent already done so, please email &amp;quot;bh_vball@yahoo.com&amp;quot; if you are interested.  We will send you an application and answer any questions you may have. You can also see our ad in Craiglist:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston.craigslist.org/gbs/act/1172026212.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://boston.craigsl...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great time and includes three weeks of drills and basic instruction with coach Sean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration for the Brettl-Hupfer's Coed Outdoor Volleyball League is now open!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginner and Intermediate Players&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$60 for the volleyball season.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every Wednesday night from 6:15pm - 8:30pm beginning June 3 the Brettl-Hupfers will be playing volleyball at Artesani Park in Boston.  The league runs for 10 weeks and ends with a FREE weekend at the Brettl-Hupfers house in Bartlett, NH from August 21-23 for Championship weekend.  Prizes for the winning team and a cookout for everyone are also on the schedule for the weekend as well as hikes and swimming in the Saco River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New to volleyball?  Never played before?  No problem - for the first 3 weeks we will have a professional volleyball instructor to do drills and work on team skills.  Each group of 2 teams will work with the instructor for a 45 minute session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Nets and Equipment will all be Tournament grade&lt;br /&gt;• Must be 21 Years of age&lt;br /&gt;• Minimum of 3 Men and 3 Women per team maximum of 8 players&lt;br /&gt;• Scoring will be Rally Point Style&lt;br /&gt;• Play the whole time (No sitting out - No working)&lt;br /&gt;• Registration will be taken on a first come first serve basis&lt;br /&gt;• Players must play in at least half of the regular season games to be eligible to play in the playoffs&lt;br /&gt;• Teams must have a minimum  of 2 Men and 2 Women for games to count towards standings &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register using the PayPal link above or contact one of the organizers to mail payment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have 3-4 nets set up. We will be close to the canoe rentals area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dan</member_name><member_id>8253363</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Fogel</member_name><member_id>8569503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247880535000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242264762000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volleyball Registration</name><id>10407542</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244067300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/10407542/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/8/global_6726632.jpeg</photo_url></item>