<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Yeh They are back....&lt;br /&gt;Bring a good Flaviour, some snacks, and a little head lamp or flashlight...&lt;br /&gt;Somehow these events go a little past the sunset..NOT exactly sure why..but i like it...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where : MOUNT HIGBY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Preview: From Pinnacle Rock one has the best viewpoint of the surrounding countryside: Hartford and Mount Tom to the north, Meriden toward the west, and a far-reaching view to the south, including Beseck Mountain, with Black Pond at its base. On a clear day Long Island Sound and New Haven are also visible. The Connecticut State Police Academy (YEH THEY HAVE BINOCULARS..dont do anything stupid) and a memorial tower can be seen at the base of the mountain, below Pinnacle Rock. Notice that the cedar and chestnut oak trees are stunted and blasted from exposure on the mountain peak. Views of Black Pond and New Dam, as well as East Peak and the lone stone tower of Castle Craig to the west (look for an array of martian antennae that sprout from the ridge behind the castle), are visible on a clear day. &lt;br /&gt;If the wine is not good we are pouring it off the edge..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;From the north:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Interstate 91 south to exit 17, this exit is for 5/15 and East Main street...bear toward the  lanes to east main street..not 5/15 ( if i remember correctly its bear to the right) at the exit end take a left (east) on east main street....go about 2.25 miles to the intersection of 66 (meriden  rd) and 147..Guida's Icream and food is on the left (north)&lt;br /&gt;pull into the back area where we will meet before going to the little parking area before the trail entrance way just a bit west of Guida's heading towards 91.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For mapquest and GPS users...guida's is 484 Meriden road, Middlefield ct..&lt;br /&gt;I know you are going to get strange directions from these programs..just look at the roads first.... I gave you the least goofy directions...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the west...691 to rte 66...meet at intersection of 66 and 147 like above...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180047152000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179596183000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Observation Wine Tasting Social Event</name><id>5795729</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179873900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5795729/</event_url></item>