<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>417 Hixbridge rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02790</zip><lat>41.570974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-993-9695.</phone><name>Westport Rivers Vineyard</name><city>Westport</city><id>1044102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060021</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/b/1/event_8127057.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;New improved agenda for this meetup! I spoke with the winery today and learned that their special event is most likely going to be rescheduled and will definitely not interfere with the 3 pm winery tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also learned that there are a number of nice picnic locations on the premises and that people are welcome to bring food and complement it with a bottle of wine. Sounds like a plan to me!! There is no food for sale at the winery's store, but they highly recommend a sandwich shop/cafe that is less than 2 miles from the winery. Follow this link to it and you will see why:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://partnersvillagestore.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://partnersvillagestore.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we can meet there to buy food for a late lunch, we can bring our own picnic fare, or we can try for a combination. Please let me know your preference when you RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've also confirmed that there is no charge for the group tour and that the tasting fee is $8 per person and includes a wine glass to take home. If you are old enough to drink wine, you are old enough to take care of this on your own, so the usual RSVP reservation fee is not required. Just&amp;nbsp;note that the RSVP deadline is TWO NIGHTS before the event so we will have a better idea of the head count and be able to make any last minute adjustments to the time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For directions to the winery,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.westportrivers.com/directions.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.westportrivers.com/directions.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Partners Village Store is at 865 Main Road, Westport.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please update your RSVP or email me with your thoughts about lunch. Best to have some food in our tummies before we drink too much wine!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details will be sent to participants</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315075688000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313171442000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picnic, winery tour and tasting at Westport Rivers</name><id>29261391</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315071000000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/29261391/</event_url></item>