<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 West Main Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06451</zip><lat>41.538148</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-235-6386</phone><name>Meriden YMCA (Gymnasium)</name><city>Meriden</city><id>1016436</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.806376</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets face it, working out can be healthy, rewarding, beneficial ...working out can be lots of things, but it's never been known to be much fun UNTIL NOW!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zumba® fuses hypnotic latin rhythms and easy to follow moves to create a dynamic fitness program that will blow you away. The goal is simple:  to want to work out, to love working out. Zumba® Fans achieve long term benefits while experiencing an absolute blast in one exhilarating hour of caloric-burning, body-energizing, awe-inspiring movements meant to engage and captivate for life!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The routines feature interval training sessions where fast and slow rhythms, and resistance training are combined to tone and sculpt your body while burning fat. Add some Latin flavor and international zest into the mix and you've got Zumba®!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the past years Zumba® has become nothing short of a revolution. Coining the concept of fitness-party™ and making fitness fun, Zumba® has spread like wild-fire, and has positioned itself as the single most influential movement in the industry of fitness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why? Because it's the best party around. Come join the party!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BTW...there will be door prizes, refreshments and a drawing for cool stuff the night of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S THE INFO...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zumba Dance Party - all proceeds to benefit the Meriden YMCA&lt;br /&gt;Friday, July 31, 2009 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Meriden YMCA Gymnasium&lt;br /&gt;110 West Main Street, Meriden, CT  06451&lt;br /&gt;Tickets:  $10 in advance&lt;br /&gt;$15.00 at the door&lt;br /&gt;For additional information call YMCA 203-235-6386 ...OR...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sandy (of our group) has very graciously offered to purchase tickets, in advance, for those who wish to go. But please be definite about it and be certain to PAY her if you order and do not go. This is coming out of her pocket...we do not want her to lose money!!! IF YOU WISH TO GO AND WANT HER TO GET YOU A TICKET...SEND HER AN EMAIL ON THIS SITE!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LAST INSTRUCTION...HAVE A BLAST, ZUMBA STYLE !!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup Partiers!!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249251171000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248116996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Do It !!!   Zumba Dance Party!!!</name><id>10917229</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249077600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/10917229/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/3/global_9775219.jpeg</photo_url></item>