<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Another in a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines! Hikes will be taken at a slower pace, with gains of 1000 feet or less and most will be 3 - 4 miles and take about half a day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A not-too difficult hike for about 1.5 miles leads you to the highest natural waterfall in NH!  Path may be muddy and steep at times, and a bit slippery if the weather is wet.  We have the option of visiting Bemis Brook and Coliseum Falls either on the way in or as we come out, depending on how we feel.  (We will &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; be doing the loop to the Frankenstein Cliffs...at least, not this time!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounting the seasonal waterfalls, our research indicates that Arethusa Falls is the single longest drop in New England. However, its height is of great controversy. We have come across sources stating that Arethusa is anywhere from 125 feet tall to “well over 200 feet in height.” Several other sources believe the falls to be about 160 feet, with which we agree. This multi-tiered plunge appears to fall from the sky. From the trail and the bottom viewpoints, you cannot see anything above the falls, aside from a few trees on the side of the river. What you do see is a peaceful and heavenly expression of Bemis Brook. The streams of water range from extremely powerful during high water run off times to hundreds of trickles during prolonged draughts. The gracefulness of the falls for the most the summer is what makes this waterfall a must-visit. Over the years, we have seen many inexperienced hikers struggle on the trail just to have the chance to see Arethusa Falls. They may be exhausted along the trail, but we have never seen anything short of a relieved smile at the waterfall. Everyone appears deeply content when they finally reach the falls. Arethusa falls becomes, in a nutshell, a job well done for all who witness its elegant beauty. This is also one waterfall you will not want to miss during peak fall foliage. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Get There:&lt;br /&gt;    From Conway, NH take Rt. 302 North. The Arethusa Falls road is on the Left 6.1 miles North of the White Mountain National Forest sign, and immediately after the Crawford Notch State Park sign.&lt;br /&gt;    From the North on Rt. 302, the Road is 3.4 miles past the Willey House, on the Right. There is a parking lot and the trailhead is clearly marked.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the trailhead by 9:45am.  I have a bright orange backpack and a big smile.  My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283165149000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281403643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It Hike to Arethusa Falls</name><id>14373318</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283090400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14373318/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/f/global_17087839.jpeg</photo_url></item>