<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Brattle St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373447</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvad Square (Pit) and also Gap store near</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>13213742</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120186</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Vigil &amp;amp; Picket&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Bangladeshi workers killed in the April 25th Rana factory collapse&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, May 4th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4:00 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard Square&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4:00: Vigil at Harvard Sq. T Station (Pit)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4:30: Picket outside Gap store (15 Brattle St. Cambridge)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of April 28 over 350 workers are confirmed dead and more than a thousand are trapped in the rubble of concrete slabs for over four days in the aftermath of a garment factory building collapse in Bangladesh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the early 1990s, more than a thousand people, mostly teenage girls, lost their lives in different garment factories in Bangladesh from fire, collapse of factory buildings, secret killing by goons or in police shootings. These crimes recur with rising death tolls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us to express your thoughts, sorrow and outrage at the ongoing tragedy. Is the global supply chain that enforces work in the cheapest conditions responsible for these tragedies? Is there connivance between Bangladesh government and the factory owners? Do we as consumers have a role? We will also picket outside Gap to pressurize it to join the Bangladesh Fire and Building Safety Agreement to make immediate safety improvements in supplier factories. Gap is one of the global retailers (along with Walmart) that refuse to sign this agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Facebook - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/586265954730691/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/586265954730691/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Alliance for a Secular and Democratic South Asia co-sponsors this event with groups including Massachusetts Interfaith Worker Justice, International Labor Rights Forum, IWW and MA Jobs with Justice. To be part of the campaign please write to workersNov25@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>swapna</member_name><member_id>8664561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367708494000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367583952000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vigil for Bangladesh Workers - Sat, May 4, 4 pm, Harvard Square</name><id>117519942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367697600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/117519942/</event_url></item>