<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Goethe-Institut Boston and the Coolidge Corner Theatre are pleased to present new films from Germany highlighting young directors who, with their first or second features demonstrate that there is more to New German Cinema than&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;The Lives of Others&lt;/em&gt;. Sunday Matinees showcase a sampling of new and award-winning German films rarely shown outside Europe. All films in German with English subtitles. And still only $5!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;About the film:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;On a hot summer day, a bicycle is found in a wheat field - the exact scene of a crime committed 23 years ago. This time 13 year-old Sinikka is missing. While the investigator of the unresolved case and a young colleague start their inquest, for Sinikka&amp;rsquo;s parents an agonizing period of waiting and uncertainty begins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style="font-size : 10px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The summer heat lies over the modest family homes like a bell jar and, behind the doors, once intact worlds begin to fall apart. Is history repeating itself? 23 years ago, a young girl named Pia was raped and murdered at this exact spot. Has the same thing happened now to 13-year-old Sinikka? Krischan, the retired police inspector who led the first investigation, is convinced that there&amp;acute;s a connection between the two crimes. His efforts to capture the killer back then were unsuccessful; this time, he is determined to bring him to justice together with his younger colleague David. While Sinikka&amp;acute;s parents are trapped in an agonizing period of waiting and uncertainty, their daughter&amp;acute;s fate rips open old wounds in the heart of the first victim&amp;acute;s mother.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 10px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;In his strikingly commanding debut feature, Swiss-born Baran bo Odar confirms his status as one of the most promising and talented young directors of today. His exceptional directing skills and distinctly cinematic language give this screen adaptation of a bestselling novel its unmistakable signature.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 10px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Germany 2010;&amp;nbsp;118 min, 35mm &lt;br /&gt;Directed by Baran bo Odar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Lisa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-size : 10px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the exit holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298900073000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298131496000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Silence</name><id>16624027</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298822400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16624027/</event_url></item>