<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>84 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Campus - Julius Adams Stratton Building </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>438442</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093750</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join a free on going Spanish study group for advanced beginner to intermediate level Spanish learners. Together we will use various strategies such as games, presentations and short conversations to learn and practice the basics of spanish grammar and vocabulary.  Future sessions will focus on learning about cultures where Spanish is spoken. All levels of Spanish speakers are invited to attend this group, as it would be nice to have native Spanish speakers and others fluent in the language to help facilitate meetings.  Also come to this next session to enjoy the delicious and reasonably priced food in the Mexican restaurant Anna's Taqueria after about 1 1/2 hours of studying.  Please RSVP.  My cell phone number will be sent out to all who plan on attending. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Materials:  Bring a pen, pencils and paper.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet just inside the building's main entrance that is closest to Massachusetts Ave., in the vicinity of the MIT Federal Credit Union and the restaurant Anna's Taqueria.  &lt;br /&gt;We will then together find a place to sit down in one of the lounges or food court areas.  It is fine with me if you can stay for only 1 1/2 of the 2 hours allotted for this event. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;PUBLIC TRANSIT: &lt;br /&gt;MBTA: &lt;br /&gt;Kendall Square Red Line - Walk on Main Street in the direction opposite Longfellow Bridge. Take a left onto Vassar Street (no sign for Vassar Street) at the sign that reads Danny Lewin Square. Walk to the other end of Vassar Street and cross over to the other side of Massachusetts Avenue. Take a left and walk a short distance. You will see the concrete Stratton Building on your right. &lt;br /&gt;Hynes\ICA Green Line Boston, transfer to RT 1 Harvard\Holyoke Gate bus or walk toward Cambridge.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buses: RT 1 Harvard\Holyoke Gate; or RT1 Dudley Station via Mass Ave. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karin B.</member_name><member_id>1270087</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196954728000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonspanish</urlname><id>145862</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196042511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spanish Language and Culture Study Session </name><id>6802542</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196625600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonspanish/events/6802542/</event_url></item>