<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Albany Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01105</zip><lat>42.120143</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gasoline Alley Foundation</name><city>Springfield</city><id>1152356</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.574804</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>All night party, free accommodations. ManFort @ Gasoline Alley, Springfield, MA- 250 Albany St. Contact rthomas@socialk.com for more info. [url=&lt;a href="http://event.pingg.com/HumanRevolution]http://event.pingg.com/HumanRevolution[/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://event.pingg.com/HumanRevolution]http://event.pingg.com/HumanRevolution[/url&lt;/a&gt;]

Continuing in the tradition of the great folk artists and writers before him, Human sings the songs of the American heart and soul. Backed by The Human Revolution, an impressive rotating cast of master musicians, Human has been leading the way for politically, socially, and ecologically charged performers and songwriters for almost a decade. Past members of the lineup have included: Roger Fritz (Sheryl Crow, Shelby Lynn), Jeff Pevar (Ray Charles, Crosby Stills and Nash, CPR), Donny “Divino” Smith (Willie Nelson), “Uncle” Don Lopez (Willie Nelson, Willie K), Gene Parsons (The Byrds, Steven Bates Band), David Mayfield (Andy Griggs, Cadillac Sky), Jessica Lea Mayfield, Alice Di Micele, Kailen Yong (Boulder Acoustic Society) and MC Radioactive (Spearhead) to name a few. Their performances tie in contemporary themes with nods to historical events, and boast an eclectic mix of styles with a definitive foundation in that roots-rock country style of music known as Americana, they call it Mystic Americana. Songs transition gently from ecstatic dance beats to tearjerker ballads, from modern political laments to positive roots reggae, carrying the audience on a journey which changes, often with the band, from show to show.

In April of this year, Human released his sixth studio album “Love Always Prevails,” featuring a more rootsy-folky sound than his previous endeavors. Though born in the economic crises of the past few years, the album reveals a positive and refreshing outlook and encourages the listener to remember what is truly important in life. The all acoustic project was recorded at Peter Temple Studio in Albion, CA and features some of Northern California’s finest acoustic musicians including Sam Frey on upright bass, Oliver Jacobson on fiddle, and longtime Human vocalist Brockell Briddle singing sweet harmonies with guest artists Lee Rider on dobro, Mike Ehlers on guitar, and Anton Mizerak on harmonica.
 
Human recently relocated to the small mountain town of Ashland, OR after 8 years on the Mendocino Coast of Northern California. He continues to perform and tour locally and nationally.

[url=&lt;a href="http://www.thehumanrevolution.org][b]www.thehumanrevolution.org[/b][/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thehumanrevolution.org][b]www.thehumanrevolution.org[/b][/url&lt;/a&gt;]

&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/0m6ayLGiWf0&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

(posted by [url=&lt;a href="http://essenic.com]essenic.com[/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://essenic.com]essenic.com[/url&lt;/a&gt;])</description><how_to_find_us>Please contact other members via messages to meet and carpool. Enjoy!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283086985000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279718304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Human Revolution Concert: Springfield, MA</name><id>14167724</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282967100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/14167724/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/d/global_16604285.jpeg</photo_url></item>