<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Cranberry Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.839191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-2526</phone><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>727813</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.691455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ok this is a Hike or Bike - whichever you would like to do. Each trail I have mapped out takes about 60-90 minutes.  So whether you have a bike or want to hike - you choose. If it rains we all could do the hike. As the group builds I would like to make these a bit more challenging or at least longer treks. But for now let's try to get as many people there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can all meet at the Ranger Station parking lot. Both trails start there. The hike is an easy trail going around a pond. Approx 3-3.5 miles. . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Depending on who comes and skill level we have one of two choices on the bike. Both are about an hour. One is beginner to intermediate the other definitely intermediate. If you have a mountain bike – that is preferred. The paved trails aren’t perfect and there are a few spots where you have to cross unpaved trails and roads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the “Hike or Bike” we could have a picinic or go to a local establishment.  Send me an email if you have a preference and I will update the MeetUp as we get closer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring plenty of water and snacks if you need them. If you are biking please make sure your machine is in good working order and you have all the appropriate safety gear. See you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Black Toyota Tundra - Red Band on Antenna</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223333049000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221859121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Myles Standish Bike or Hike - Rain or Shine !</name><id>8792768</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1222621200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/8792768/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/3/global_5489923.jpeg</photo_url></item>