<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>210 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.345224</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Church of Christ, Scientist</name><city>Boston</city><id>935261</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086745</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Along Huntington Avenue stands a dense concentration of Boston's most venerable cultural institutions. From McKim, Mead &amp;amp; White's Symphony Hall to Guy Lowell's Museum of Fine Arts this tour will showcase the establishments dedicated to the fine arts, music, theater, education, religion, and sports.  We'll start at the &amp;quot;Mother Church&amp;quot; (The First Church of Christ Scientist), wander down Huntington Avenue and through Northeastern University, and end in front of the Isabella Stewart Gardner museum.  This tour was created by Nerd Fun's own Megan Murphy, and if we're lucky, she'll be leading our group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet on the front steps of the First Church of Christ Scientist (the one with the giant reflecting pool) at the corner of Mass. Ave and Huntington Ave.  The church is located near the Symphony stop of the Green Line E train or a couple of blocks up Mass Ave from the Mass Ave station on the Orange Line. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $15 per person ($5 for Boston By Foot card holders - membership information at their &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; (BBF membership gets you free admission to other nerdy events that aren't announced to the general public))  Purchase tickets in cash on site.  The 90-minute tour will run in rain or shine, so please check the weather and come prepared.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for me, Amy, wearing my Boston By Foot hat and my Meetup button.  The tour starts promptly at 2:00pm.  I listed 1:45pm so that everyone has time to pay and get organized.  If there are too many of us we'll have to split up into smaller groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the tour, some of us will be visiting the Isabella Stewart Gardner museum.  If you got the Groupon (or was it BuyWithMe) a few weeks back, this might be a good time to use it. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for people with Boston By Foot badges - mine says "amy!"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280197972000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278780258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston By Foot Walking Tour: Avenue of the Arts</name><id>14060428</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280079900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14060428/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/5/global_16304917.jpeg</photo_url></item>