<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday's High is 41 in the Bowl.  Bring Sunscreen as the forecast is for a Sunny day.  Sherburne Trail is ski-able until 3/4 mile from the base.  We'll see how far the sleds will get us.  Sledding in Tuckermans is a go only as high as you want to sled down.  I usually go up a ways do a test run then determine how high I can go and still feel comfortable that I can make it to the bottom.  You don't have to sled as there will be plenty of action to watch.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: John Lagasse (978) 973-5022&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is simple - we are going to hike up to Tuckerman Ravine and do some sledding. If you just want to tag along and watch things you can do that too. If the weather cooperates we can spend the day sledding and lounging around so bring your sled and some type of inflatable camp chair. We will finish the day by sledding down the John Shurburne Ski Trail - there are some long straights, a few sweeping s-turns, and lots of bumps at the bottom.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The top speed two year's ago was 42.2 MPH!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Here are a couple of videos and some pictures from years past...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/MzeRvAnkxzk"&gt;2010 Tuckerman Ravine SledFest Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/photos/2030971/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/rqCL5uQw2yM"&gt;2009 SledFest Events Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;you don’t bring a sled you will miss out on the fun. The most popular choices are:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zipfy Sled - &lt;a href="http://www.ems.com/product/index.jsp?productId=3655510" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ems.com/product/index.jsp?productId=3655510&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Slidy Sled - &lt;a href="http://www.ems.com/product/index.jsp?productId=4450226" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ems.com/product/index.jsp?productId=4450226&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOR SOME REASON THESE EMS LINKS WON"T WORK OFF THE PAGE SO YOU WILL NEED TO COPY AND PASTE INTO YOUR BROWSER.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Be sure to have a way to secure your sled to your pack for the snow shoe up and your snow shoes to your&lt;/span&gt; pack for the sled down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you want to sled on this trip &lt;strong&gt;you must bring a helmet&lt;/strong&gt; - the slopes are steep so the speeds will be fast, there are exposed rocks that won't be all that forgiving if you hit them, and there will be skiers and snow boarders all around us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The US Consumer Product Safety Commission publishes a pamphlet titled "Which Helmet for Which Activity" which provides useful information covering a broad range of helmets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While there isn't a helmet specifically designed for sledding, they recommend that wearing a ski helmet (ASTM F2040; CEN 1077; Snell RS-98 or S-98), a bicycle helmet (ASTM F1447; Snell B-90/95 or N-94), or a skateboard helmet (ASTM F1492; Snell N-94) is preferable to wearing no helmet at all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted on this hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; out and back trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 6 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 1,900 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. If the weather is nice plan to be out all day. People will be able to come and go as they please.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;MODERATE&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Mount Washington Observatory)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet inside the Pinkham Notch Visitors Center near the fireplace by the front door. According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 154 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 10 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=361+New+Hampshire+16,+Gorham,+NH+03581+(AMC+Joe+Dodge+Lodge+at+Pinkham+Notch)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.261106,-71.250801&amp;amp;sspn=0.006823,0.019205&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFU9TowId8sbA-yEz_vuuYdAtpylz_sOp9pGzTDEz_vuuYdAtpw&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;z=7"&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(google.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Zipfys</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John (LAG) Lagasse</member_name><member_id>2667639</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367413212000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365684930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tuckerman Ravine SledFest  - Part Duex - Fun In The Sun</name><id>113815402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367067600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/113815402/</event_url></item>