<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What is involved in acquiring and protecting intellectual property? And why is this important to the overall success of your company? Does the intellectual strategy change as a company grows from idea to start up to a company with marketable products? Come to a panel discussion of seasoned professionals and find out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Crossing Boundaries series continues with our latest event: Crossing boundaries on the road to innovation: Avoiding IP pitfalls along the way on September 22, 2011. This program will consist of two parts - a brief introduction to patents followed by a panel discussion. The first part will describe the form, function, and future of patents. The second part will be a panel discussion surrounding the issues and pitfalls associated with IP as one moves from innovation to marketed product, including: IP capture; tracking and triage; IP transfer; and IP commercialization. Learn how what you do (whether scientist or accountant) matters to intellectual property and understand how to protect it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the link to register: &lt;a href="https://netforum.avectra.com/eweb/DynamicPage.aspx?Site=HBA&amp;amp;WebCode=EventDetail&amp;amp;evt_key=7E561C7E-A6D0-4429-A609-53EA88D11B79" target="_blank"&gt;https://netforum.avec...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316789489000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Biotechnology Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>biotech-31</urlname><id>178843</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Biotech Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315926882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HBA Boston event on avoiding IP pitfalls along the value chain</name><id>33368012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316727000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/biotech-31/events/33368012/</event_url></item>