<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello Everybody,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's meeting will be held at the Coolidge Corner Branch Library at 31 Pleasant Street in Brookline.  There is only one conference room; we're listed as &amp;quot;Who Moved My Cheese?&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is limited parking behind the library, but finding on-street parking should be easy on a Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For you first-timers or you newbies, we'll have a table set up just for you.  Russell will lead this table and will help guide you through the cards and the gameplay and shed some light on how the game works, and how what may not seem like a great deal might actually be phenomenal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The times also changed due to the hours of library.  &lt;b&gt;We will meet from 1:15 pm to 4:00 pm.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note &lt;b&gt;there IS parking&lt;/b&gt;.  PLEASE BE ON TIME.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rules:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE SAY &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY IF YOU ARE SURE  &lt;br /&gt;PLEASE ARRIVE 10 MINUTES EARLY.  GAME STARTS ON TIME  &lt;br /&gt;GAME TIME IS 2 HOURS.    &lt;br /&gt;EACH TEAM IS ASSIGNED A COMMENTATOR.    &lt;br /&gt;AT THE END OF EACH GAME, WE HOLD A COMMENTATOR SESSION FOR 15 MINUTES FOR EACH TEAM.  &lt;br /&gt;COMMENTATORS DISCUSS THE RISKS AND REWARDS TAKEN BY EACH TEAM MEMBER  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE DO HAVE A WAITING LIST.  &lt;b&gt;THE GAME WILL END AT 4 PM&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;b&gt;GAME FEE IS $5 PER PLAYER&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;THANK YOU  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EDAN BARSHAN  &lt;br /&gt;ORGANIZER&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is only one conference room at the Coolidge Corner Branch Library.  Ask for "Who Moved My Cheese?".</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Russ</member_name><member_id>3610750</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205255982000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Kiyosaki's CASHFLOW101 challenges the players' current ways of thinking about money and opens their eyes to how the RICH see it.  It's exhilarating to see the AHA! moments dawning on the players as the game progresses.  What a rush when it's YOU!</why><group><who>Will-Be Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCashflowMeetup</urlname><id>302998</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Cashflow Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203880747000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Metro Boston Cashflow March Meeting</name><id>7398740</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205082900000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCashflowMeetup/events/7398740/</event_url></item>