<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Made in the USA: the state of American inventions.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Scott Keeley, Obvia Design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What types of U.S.-invented products show promise in the global economy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Which products are successfully manufactured and marketed in the U.S. and not overseas?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Which inventions are making it in the post-crash market?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can American inventors do to maintain their intellectual margin?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In this presentation Keeley looks at recent market trends and gives advice, based on recent experiences with manufacturers and inventors, on how inventors can benefit by adjusting to the &amp;quot;post-recession&amp;quot; paradigm. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;He will also talk about promising industries that so far resist outsourcing, one of which is medical-industry products. He also will talk about previously successful inventions and products that, for better or worse, have lost viability in this new-world marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keeley runs Obvia, a Rhode Island small business that helps inventors get their products produced and marketed. He is an industrial designer/engineer who develops prototypes and works with manufacturers in the U.S. and China to get products to market. A recent specialty is intellectual property and alternative-energy engineering. His biggest client is FloDesign Wind Turbine Corp., for whom he is second-in-command for IP and engineering design. He has been in the business for nine years now, and have been featured in Inventors' Digest (January 2009), on Fox News Boston (2007), and he has presented at the Inventors' Association of New England, Brown University, and the New London and Cross Mills' public libraries. Keeley holds a patent for the Ovation guitar and has developed solid, selling products.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For more information about Keeley and his work, please see &lt;a href="http://www.obvia.biz" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.obvia.biz...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Downstairs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275598558000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274283900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June Meeting</name><id>13531343</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275518700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/13531343/</event_url></item>