<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>280 The Fenway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-566-1401</phone><name>Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum</name><city>Boston</city><id>698253</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.098228</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finish off March in style! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Third Thursdays&lt;br /&gt;5:30-9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us After Hours every third Thursday for a new kind of night out, September through June…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Hours is live music, art, conversation, cocktails and more in an inviting atmosphere. Linger around the courtyard bar and listen to live music or sample the tasty menu in the Gardner Café. Experience something different each month – from impromptu gallery talks to cutting-edge contemporary performance – and spend time in the galleries exploring what the Gardner is all about. Members and Isabellas get in free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Art, music and atmosphere: what will you discover After Hours? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members: entry is FREE&lt;br /&gt;Nonmembers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Hours Tickets&lt;br /&gt;Members: free | Adults: $12 | College Students: $5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy After Hours Tickets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Hours Plus Tickets (Includes admission to After Hours)&lt;br /&gt;Adults: $23 | Members: $15 | College Students: $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buy After Hours Plus Tickets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Box Office: 617 278 5156&lt;br /&gt;Tickets also on sale at the door, subject to availability. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artful Flavors @ After Hours&lt;br /&gt;Artful culinary offerings are also being served up After Hours! Indulge in all-new specialty cocktails and snacks at The Courtside Bar adjoining the interior garden, or sit down for dinner and drinks at the award-winning The Gardner Café featuring a full menu of sweet and savory dishes to fulfill your culinary, as much as your cultural, appetites!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Courtside Bar&lt;br /&gt;Indulge in “Courtside Cocktails” and all-new “Courtside Bites” offerings at a Courtside Bar adjacent to the interior garden, open 5:30 to 9:15 pm. “Courtside Cocktails” include “THE MADAME GAUTREAU” (an all-new specialty cocktail inspired by one of Isabella Gardner’s favorite paintings), along with wine, beer, and non-alcoholic alternatives. And a changing array of “Courtside Bites” (available for just $1) will adequately sustain you to explore the galleries and art activities that await.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Courtside Bar accepts cash and all major credit cards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;View full “Courtside Cocktails” and “Courtside Bites” menu offerings&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“COURTSIDE COCKTAILS”&lt;br /&gt;THE MADAME GAUTREAU $8.00&lt;br /&gt;THE MADAME GAUTREAU (non-alcoholic version) $4.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Hours signature cocktail&lt;br /&gt;A refreshing and harmonious specialty cocktail – sparkling wine, a blend of grapefruit and pineapple juice, and a splash of grenadine – the perfect toast for a summer evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Madame Gautreau cocktail is named for John Singer Sargent’s painting, Madame Gautreau Drinking a Toast (1882-83) – one of Isabella Gardner’s favorites – depicting the ravishing beauty, charm and vitality of Paris socialite Virginie Avegno (“Madame X”). Indulge in this all-new specialty cocktail alongside the court; and then go pay Madame Gautreau herself a visit in the nearby Blue Room gallery!&lt;br /&gt;Wine  $8.00&lt;br /&gt;Beer | Stella Artois  $6.00&lt;br /&gt;Sparkling and still water  $2.00&lt;br /&gt;Variety of juices  $2.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“COURTSIDE BITES”&lt;br /&gt;New this year, creative snacks will also be offered up at the Courtside Bar for $1. “Courtside Bites” offerings will vary each month, and range from a Japanese rice cracker mix to spiced nuts and dried fruit and served up in an artful paper box.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Courtside Bites $1.00&lt;br /&gt;Offerings differ each month.&lt;br /&gt;The Gardner Café&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gardner Café is also open during After Hours, serving up sweet and savory dishes, cocktails and other culinary offerings from 5:30 to 9 pm. Tables are available on a first-come, first-served basis. Reservations are available for museum members only by calling 617 566 1088.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Must RSVP first</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243118143000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235165331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Third Thursdays - Gardner After Hours is live music, art, and conversation...</name><id>9785720</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242945000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9785720/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/b/global_7613403.jpeg</photo_url></item>