<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>AMC Auditorium &lt;br /&gt;4 Joy Street, Boston MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM potluck, 7:00 PM slideshow&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Japan is a unique combination high technology, ancient traditions, elegant temples, meticulous gardens, and varied landscapes forming an exciting place to travel and experience the outdoors. Join David Loutzenheiser, one of the leaders and organizers of the first AMC Major Excursion trip to Japan on a discovery of this fascinating country.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traveling entirely by foot and public transportation throughout the country, explore the world's most extensive high speed rail system, and buses that climb narrow mountain roads. See varied accommodation from mountain huts, to temple lodging, ryokans, hostels, and hot spring towns.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Highlights of the trip will be shown:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;climbing 8,000 foot high volcanoes  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;visits to temples and shrines large and small  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;tours of the worlds largest and oldest wooden buildings over 1,000 years old &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;climbing 2,446 stone steps to a sacred peak &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;summiting two of Japan's five highest peaks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Witness a day-long trek up ladders, along ropes and chains through the Daikiretto, or &amp;quot;big cut&amp;quot;, that makes the Knife Edge seem like an easy walk in the park!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you plan to attend, please RSVP to Julie at AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail.com.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30 PM, feel free to use the following guidelines: &lt;ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last names beginning with A-L bring an main dish or side dish &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last names beginning with M-Z bring an appetizer or dessert &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Homemade dishes are great, store bought goodies, and takeout are equally welcome.  Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (stovetop, oven, microwave, sink, fridge, etc).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294843382000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294372933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Japan's Temples, Mountains and Gardens  (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>15954239</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294788600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/15954239/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/6/3/global_20644195.jpeg</photo_url></item>