<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7900 Mystic Dunes Lane</address_1><state>FL</state><lat>28.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(407) 396-1311</phone><name>Mystic Dunes Resort &amp; Golf Club</name><city>Celebration</city><id>1016833</id><country>us</country><lon>-81.590905</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Event will take place at the Mystic Dunes Resort and Golf Club during the month of October. There will be time trials, race and prizes the night of the 30th and an open reception Halloween “Monster” Bash, sponsored exclusively by City Beverages and Monster Energy Drink the night of the 31st.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Criterium or short course bike race, includes an all terrain course totaling 4.2 miles of beautiful scenery, gravel, dirt, sand, and paved sections that which combined make a course to entice the most extreme rider.&lt;br /&gt;This event offers an exciting platform for the best-in-the-world of bicycles. It is a venue to showcase the rider’s technical and athletic skills, and win significant cash prizes and titles that will further enhance their development and amusement of this sport. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will create precedence for many more rides already on the agenda. It will be a great opportunity to experience avant-garde mountain bike racing. The Central Florida Criterium Cup includes a time trial, various levels of racing and, the celebratory culmination of the one night competition and Monster Energy Drink sponsored Halloween holiday bash on the 31st. There will be winners in each category, and many prizes. The event is sanctioned by the United States Cycling Federation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The competition is also open to all of the 7 Central Florida County Police departments and international visitors.  Cash &amp;amp; prizes will be awarded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For sponsorship opportunities or for more information visit www.cflcriteriumcup.com or call 407-353-0013&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Felix Hernandez</member_name><member_id>4930754</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herfel</member_name><member_id>8086452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257108072000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bikeandsocial</urlname><id>1526849</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7900009155</group_lon><name>The Bike and Social Club (Worcester &amp; surrounding areas)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253463954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CFL Criterium Cup THE RACE!</name><id>11419355</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256934600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bikeandsocial/events/11419355/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/global_10800073.jpeg</photo_url></item>