<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/7/event_21781175.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Toad's promotion: "Rohn Lawrence is an incredibly accomplished musician. So accomplished in fact that he has toured or recorded with: Najee, Alex Bugnon, Will Downing, Freddy Jackson, Pieces of a Dream, Brian McKnight, Boney James, George Duke, Marion Meadows, Regina Belle, Norman Conners, Rick Braun, Diane Reeves, Angela Bofill, Phil Perry, Jay Rowe, Nelson Rangel, Andre Ward, Bread and Butter, Maysa, Nestor Torres, Roger Ball, Glenn Jones, Miki Howard, Lamone Andrews and Club 1600. ROHN HAS MOST RECENTLY BEEN ADDED AS A PRINCIPAL MEMBER OF "PIECES OF A DREAM" AND HAS BEEN KEEPING BUSY TOURING WHILE STILL MANAGING TO HIT US EVERY MONDAY DOWNTOWN NEW HAVEN AT TOAD'S PLACE!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know he's good and has been around SOCT area for a long time.&amp;nbsp; Talked to Tom and the group about&amp;nbsp;Rohn&amp;nbsp;at the wine social last week and people wanted to go.&amp;nbsp; Yes, it is later in the evening on a MONDAY night and at TOAD's no less (upstairs at Lily's pad).&amp;nbsp; After the New Haven Collective meetup&amp;nbsp;slide over to Toad's and listen to great music for $5 at the door.&amp;nbsp; Doors open at 9pm, show starts at 9:30-till.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out Toad's listing: &lt;a href="http://www.toadsplace.com/wp/shows/2622"&gt;http://www.toadsplace.com/wp/shows/2622&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure.  Haven't been to the pad.  Someone will leave word with the bar keep.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299554041000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Smooth Jazz and Blues by one of the best in the area!  Need I say more?</why><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299127168000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Night of Smooth Jazz with Rohn Lawrence &amp; Friends</name><id>16778574</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299549600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/16778574/</event_url></item>