<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bridge Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.360770</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Boyle O’Reilly statue</name><city>Boston</city><id>731094</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609630</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>National Park Service Announces &lt;b&gt;Walking Tour of the Back Bay Fens&lt;/b&gt; On &lt;b&gt;Tuesday, August 19 th&lt;/b&gt; at &lt;b&gt;5:00 p.m&lt;/b&gt;. a National Park Service ranger from Frederick Law Olmsted National Historic Site will be conducting a &lt;u&gt;free, two-hour guided walk of Boston’s Back Bay Fens&lt;/u&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting place is the John Boyle O’Reilly statue located at theintersection of Boylston Street Bridge and the Fenway, across the street from Boston Conservatory. It is within walking distance of the Hynes Convention Center Auditorium Green Line “T” station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This walking tour entitled “The Back Bay Fens: Vision and Revisions” will examine the multifaceted history of the Fens focusing on its transformation from “the foulest marsh and muddy flats to be found anywhere in Massachusetts” into an urban oasis of greenery. It will explore the design of this significant “emerald necklace” park created by Frederick Law Olmsted, the visionary landscape architect who was our nation’s premier parkmaker. Stops will include Mother’s Rest, the Richard Parker Memorial Victory Gardens, the Aggasiz Bridge and War Memorials area, and the James P. Kelleher Rose Garden. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk will be held rain or shine and is free and open to the public. No advance reservationsare required. For general information about the walk, please call Frederick Law Olmsted National Historic Site at 617/566-1689, extension 216 Monday through Friday. -NPS-&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a park ranger, Mark Swartz, leading. Meet at the Statue!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alyson</member_name><member_id>5616452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219353137000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218119818000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walking Tour of the Back Bay Fens</name><id>8496589</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219179600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/8496589/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/9/6/global_5067990.jpeg</photo_url></item>