<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Knipe Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01835</zip><lat>42.745752</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-521-7550</phone><name>Evenfall</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>907331</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109486</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Spain…Espana..No wonder Hemingway fell so passionately in love with the place. &lt;br /&gt;Unlike Hemingway, you won’t have to hop a flight to experience the wonderful culture of Spain. &lt;br /&gt;Evenfall Restaurant in Haverhill, MA will host a” Celebrate The Taste of Spain” dinner featuring Spanish cuisine, music and culture. A sizzling night awaits you with a live Flamenco Dance show and dinner experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The “Celebrate The Taste of Spain” dinner will take place on Friday April 23rd and the Evenfall Restaurant will have you stomping your feet to the beats of traditional, powerful flamenco music. Enjoy the heart racing music of world renown Spanish guitarist Juanito Pascale as Sabrina Aviles gives a one hour Flamenco dance performance. Great music, and culture, fiestas and more fiestas!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The night will begin at 7:15 pm with mouth watering flavors of Spain that include Ajo Tomate(tomato salad), Tortillas de Camarones(crispy shrimp fritters), succulent  filet mignon and fresh local haddock . A glass of wine from Spanish vineyard Pereles Estate will be served with dinner. The flavorful menu will make you will feel like you are dining on the streets of Spain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Celebrate The Taste of Spain” event will occur at Evenfall Restaurant on Friday, April 23rd at 7:15 PM. Doors will open at 6:30 PM. Evenfall is located at 8 Knipe Road (Route#125) in Haverhill, MA. Tickets are general admission and cost $55 per person.  They can be purchased online today at www.drinkwaterproductions.com or at Evenfall Restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272237639000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Men and Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-527</urlname><id>501015</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Cocktail Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269975567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate The Taste Of  Spain!</name><id>13039222</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272064500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-527/events/13039222/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/9/global_4160137.jpeg</photo_url></item>