<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1273 Queen Street (Rt. 10)</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06489</zip><lat>41.648497</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-747-1100</phone><name>Jitters Coffeehouse</name><city>Southington</city><id>1091950</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.871628</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new Meetup for The CT Meetup to Enhance Humanitarian Knowledge and Action!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: May Day for Haiti!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday, May 1, 2010 12:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt;Jitters Coffeehouse&lt;br /&gt;1273 Queen Street (Rt. 10) &lt;br /&gt;Southington, CT 06489&lt;br /&gt;860-747-1100&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a wonderful time at Haitian Happy Hour.  That cozy evening at La Paloma, with snow falling outside, was so much fun, and we raised $800.00 for CHO and GHESHKIO!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, you know what?  It left us wanting more!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Announcing a new MAY DAY FOR HAITI celebration!  And don't worry:  It is NOT going to be an exact replication of the Haitian Happy Hour.  We have made this event an original, changing some things, adding some things.  But it still comes from the desire to help this struggling country. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I looked up May Day in Wikipedia.  It says: &lt;i&gt;May Day marks &lt;b&gt;the end of the uncomfortable winter half of the year&lt;/b&gt; ... and it has traditionally been an occasion for popular and often raucous celebrations, regardless of the locally prevalent political or religious establishment. &lt;/i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think this is very fitting for this event!  Let's come together in the hope that Haiti will move beyond this very very uncomfortable winter in its history.  Let's celebrate in the hopes that a new season, a Springtime, will come for the Haitian people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, Wikipedia lists the traditions of different countries on May Day, and it describes Haiti as &lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;the only predominantly Francophone independent nation in the Americas. It is one of only two independent nations in the Americas (along with Canada) that designate French as an official language.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;  The French tradition mentioned is the tradition of giving a &lt;b&gt;Lily of the Valley&lt;/b&gt; (taken directly from Wikipedia):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;On May 1st, 1561, King Charles IX of France received a lily of the valley as a lucky charm. He decided to offer a lily of the valley each year to the ladies of the court. At the beginning of the 20th century, it became custom on the 1st of May, to give a sprig of lily of the valley, a symbol of springtime. The government permits individuals and workers' organisations to sell them free of taxation. It is also traditional for the lady receiving the spray of lily of valley to give a kiss in return. Now, people may present loved ones with bunches of lily of the valley or dog rose flowers.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, after having read all of that, I hope you will be excited to join us at this celebration of Spring in honor of new life and hope for Haiti! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will take place at Jitters Coffeehouse in Southington.  This is a wonderful place worth checking out if you have never been there.  Jitters offers live music on Friday and Saturday nights, but that is just the beginning.  Shirley, the owner, offers all kinds of classes such as Yoga and Tai Chi.  She is involved in a food coop, green energy, and nutritional programs.  Next door is a great used sporting goods store also owned by Shirley and which will be open for browsing during this event.  For all the details on everything Jitters has to offer, see the great website: &lt;a href="http://www.jittersclub.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jittersclu...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event will be from 12 to 4 p.m.  This is different from the Happy Hours, and it allows us to use the wonderful outdoor deck at Jitters.  There will be complimentary refreshments served, but Shirley also has a great selection of soups, salads, snacks and FABULOUS desserts and coffees available for purchase.  There will be a fun raffle, a silent auction, and several great performers, including both presentations and live music!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So PLEASE mark your calendar now and come join us...come drop by for a short stay or a long visit!  Suggested donation is $5.00, with raffle tickets and silent auction items separately. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO - if you want to donate and raffle or silent auction items, food, or your time and help, please email Kelly or Erin!  It will be greatly appreciated! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to see you!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272902903000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270331553000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May Day for Haiti!</name><id>13078562</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272729600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13078562/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/global_14106051.jpeg</photo_url></item>