<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>**Sunset variation** This is a moderate 2.5 mile hike that includes a relatively scenic western view at SUNSET from the summit of Lookout Mountain (a.k.a. Case Mt., 744 ft.). Portions of the trail include the Shenipsit Trail. The start of the hike from the parking lot is somewhat steep but after that it is much easier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike is anticipated to last 2 hours and rise 350 feet. Overall the hike should start at 7:00 PM and be done by about 9:00 PM. We'll meet in the parking lot and head to the pond first and explore the trails. Then we'll wind up at the peak in time for the 8:30 PM sunset. After that we head for the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map can be found as hike #6 in the &amp;quot;50 Hikes in Connecticut&amp;quot; book by the Connecticute Forest and Parks Association. There is no meal planed for after this one given the late hour but we could head out for ice cream after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this hike is Kevin S so please direct questions on the hike to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-84 E to I-384&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 4 off of I-384 (Highland St.)&lt;br /&gt;* From the end of the Exit ramp, right onto Spring St.&lt;br /&gt;* Go about 0.2 mile and make a sharp left and you'll see a small parking lot at the bottom of the hill on your left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1151190603000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1150466350000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Highland Springs and Lookout Mountain in Manchester CT</name><id>4982442</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1151017200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4982442/</event_url></item>