<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;GO MAINE, MaineDOT, The Turnpike Authority and the Bicycle Coalition of Maine are throwing a party!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bike to Work Day will be celebrated in grand style this year! Activity will be taking place all day at Lobsterman Park, corner of Middle and Temple, in front of the Nickleodeon movie theater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interested in riding with others? See times and meeting places for bikepooling from Westbrook, South Portland, Falmouth, or Yarmouth into downtown Portland &lt;a href="http://gomaine.org/05/btwdayriders/" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• 7am – 10am: Radio van, commuter rides coming in, food, media, exhibits, etc. &lt;br /&gt;• 11am – 2pm: demos, lunchtime traffic, food discounts, media driven traffic, exhibits, etc.&lt;br /&gt;• After hours: Sebago Brewing Company will offer discounts and maybe a bike movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many details are yet to be worked out, but activities are planned to include:&lt;br /&gt;• Breakfast and lunch incentives and giveaways. After work food/beverage specials and possibly a movie at Sebago Brewing. &lt;br /&gt;• T shirt and Prize item giveaways.&lt;br /&gt;• At least three volunteer bicycle commuter groups arriving from different locations by 8:00-8:30. &lt;br /&gt;• A Radio Remote Van.&lt;br /&gt;• Demo Bike Rides at noon and perhaps after work using Summer Feet Bicycle Tours.  &lt;br /&gt;• Maintenance, Commuter, Safety and Gear presentations from GO MAINE and/ or local bike shops.  &lt;br /&gt;• GO MAINE Van and Carpool info. &lt;br /&gt;• Bicycle Coalition of Maine, Portland Bicycle Commuting Meetup, and other local transportation alternative/ bicycle groups displaying their wares/ messages.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276637009000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Bike Commuters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Bike-Commuting</urlname><id>225788</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Bicycle Commuting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270914573000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Bike to Work Day</name><id>13142892</id><headcount>200</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274439600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Bike-Commuting/events/13142892/</event_url></item>