<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>North Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.853680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lippitt Memorial Park</name><city>Providence</city><id>720951</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.391617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join the Providence Collective for a fun day with some special Fall treats:  Farmers market, art fair, and leaf peeping!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at &lt;b&gt;11:00 am&lt;/b&gt; on the Southeast corner of Lippitt Park, at the corner of North Ave. and Blackstone Blvd.  This will give us a chance to say hi and meet each other, especially if there are new faces in the crowd.  Then at about &lt;b&gt;11:15&lt;/b&gt; we'll make our way into the park to enjoy both the food and art markets.   Feel free to split up and wander around and see all of the delicious and beautiful items offered by local farmers and artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we will reconvene back at our starting spot at about &lt;b&gt;12:15&lt;/b&gt;.  We will take this time to welcome any additional people into the group.  You can also show off your great finds to everyone else.  I'm sure more than once we'll hear &amp;quot;Oh, I love that, where did you get it??&amp;quot;  We'll leave a little extra time to run back and make any additional purchases, as well as time to put our new treasures in our cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then at &lt;b&gt;12:30&lt;/b&gt; we will walk to Swan Point Cemetery to take in the fall colors.  What?  You think it's morbid to have an enjoyable walk through a cemetery?  Well, it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; time to gear up for Halloween, after all.  And Providence's own horror writer, H.P. Lovecraft is buried there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But, beyond the Halloween spookiness, Swan Point is a gorgeous Providence treasure.   It has trees imported from around the world, great views of the Seekonk River, and it is also a great place for bird watching.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow a pre-set course for this walking tour, and each Collective member will be provided with their own maps and literature.  We will hit the highlights of the imported trees and of the residents.  I estimate the walk will last about an hour, but that will depend on our speed.  The materials will be yours to keep and use for further exploration that afternoon, or even to plan a return trip at another time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All are welcome to enjoy part or all of these fun events, so bring your friends, neighbors, and kids.  Please note that there will be some steep hills during the Swan Point tour, so please be sure you are able to enjoy the whole tour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional links and information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.farmfresh.org/food/farmersmarkets_details.php?market=11" target="_blank"&gt;Hope Street Farmers Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RI farms - veggies, fruit, bread, etc.&lt;br /&gt;Open from 9:30am - 12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Lippett Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.providenceopenmarket.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Providence Open Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Art, clothing, crafts, etc.&lt;br /&gt;Open from 10:00am - 4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Lippett Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lippett Park is located inside the triangle of Hope St., Blackstone Blvd., and North Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://swanpointcemetery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Swan Point Cemetery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;585 Blackstone Blvd.&lt;br /&gt;Providence, RI 02906&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a bright red wool coat on.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephanie</member_name><member_id>8926850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287353132000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287001077000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Local food, local art, and leaf peeping.</name><id>15099699</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287241200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/15099699/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/2/global_18721314.jpeg</photo_url></item>