<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>207 Wickenden St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.819340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>273-1198</phone><name>Coffee Exchange</name><city>Providence</city><id>435109</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.399147</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be a sort of walking tour of this side of Providence. It is not really downtown, but more the College Hill, Wickenden Street and surrounding area. It is a more laid back, social walk to get to know this area of Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've never been to the famous Thayer Street, then you will see it on this "sorta" tour. I say "sorta" because I can't really give any history about any of the places we will visit. I can only guide you on the walk, and let you wonder aimlessly behind me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting point will be at the popular Coffee Exchange on Wickenden Street. There is plenty of street parking and parking on side streets of Brook St, Alves Way (Pike Street), and Traverse St. There's some parking back there behind Coffee Exchange on Alves Way, but beware of the signs for resident parking. Meet out in front of the shop, do not go inside. The place is too small for everyone to be standing around waiting inside unfortunately. Once we have all gathered, we will begin the walk. We will walk on Wickenden Street, head to Benefit Street, continue on Waterman St, walk up Thayer St, go back on Hope Street, and return to Wickenden. We will return to Coffee Exchange, for a total of - I'm taking a guess here - 2 to 3 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, if anyone would like to socialize, we can go inside Coffee Exchange... try to scrounge up enough tables, sit and chat for a bit over coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully weather won't be awful and we won't get a freak snow storm. If we do, I will cancel this meetup. I'll keep an eye on the weather.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Standing outside of Coffee Exchange to begin the walk. This is where we will end up after the walk.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300020568000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Walking is fun, and it might be nice to see this side of Providence. It's not downtown, but more the college area and it's surroundings.</why><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299210745000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walking Aimlessly around Providence College Hill and Wickenden</name><id>16792274</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299949200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/16792274/</event_url></item>