<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Parking Lot</address_2><address_1>2 Avenue A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01376</zip><lat>42.600845</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-863-3221</phone><name>Great Falls Discover Center</name><city>Turners Falls</city><id>289039</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.564000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Click and Shoot: Turners Falls&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Great Falls Discover Center at 11 AM. We will head out in what ever groups you want to start shooting by 11:30am. I'd suggest packing a sandwich and snack, and have a drink with you...There is no agenda other than meeting up again for dinner together and lecture that night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the Great Falls Discovery Center and learn about the Connecticut River Watershed's rich natural, cultural, and industrial history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Center is fully accessible and is housed within a complex of old mill buildings and includes open habitat exhibits, fish tanks, and a multipurpose program room. Exhibits highlight various habitats found in the watershed, timelines put perspective on today's view of the threats to habitats and what we can do to safeguard them. But We'll more than likely be outsides wandering about...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The four-acre park that surrounds The Center has butterfly gardens, native plantings views of the canal and river as well as safe play areas. This park is linked to a railtrail that runs from Turners Falls to Deerfield, a walking tour through downtown Turners Falls, and the watchable wildlife areas of Barton's cove and along the canal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission to the Great Falls Discovery Center is free!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we'll meet for dinner. Chat. Eat. Then visit the Museum and attend Lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A forty-year retrospective of photography by Ron Rosenstock HYMN to the EARTH Reception &amp;amp; Artist's Talk - Saturday, July 7, 2007 Evening Talk at Hallmark Institute of Photography, Industrial Boulevard Turners Falls, Massachusetts 01376&lt;br /&gt;Hallmark Museum of Photography&lt;br /&gt;85 Avenue A&lt;br /&gt;Turners Falls, MA 01376&lt;br /&gt;413-863-0009&lt;br /&gt;info@hmcp.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;From North &amp;amp; South: I-91 to Mass. Route 2 East Route 2 East to Gill-Turners Falls Bridge. Cross Gill-Turners Falls Bridge to traffic signal; Museum is on left at intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From East &amp;amp; West: Mass. Route 2 to Gill-Turners Falls Bridge. Cross Gill-Turners Falls Bridge to traffic signal; Museum is on left at intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***I'd recommed we car pool. If folks from Worcester want to gather at the 70 Webster Street Parking lot at 9:30am we can figure out a good way to travel together. Please post locations for other to meet and car pool.****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~Also~~ Please bring Sunblock, Drinks, Cash for Meals, Hat, Sunglasses, Hiking Shoes + Camera Gear. I'll be sure to have a first aid kit in my car.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183993530000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180097109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turner Falls Click and Shoot- Rosenstock Lecture</name><id>5817498</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183820400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/5817498/</event_url></item>