<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Woodridge Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.187100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-551-3307</phone><name>My Personal Residence</name><city>Westwood</city><id>787702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Watch SuperBowl Game:&lt;/b&gt; 5:30-10:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mission of our group: Three fold &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Feel good and have fun!! Watch Superbowl!&lt;br /&gt;2. Welcome and develop new valued friendships with both men and women of our age group. &lt;br /&gt;3. Develop a mutually respectful and fulfilling long-term monogamous relationship. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We utilize private House parties or Dance parties as a vehicle to meet other singles -45 plus age group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host-Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;House Party &lt;br /&gt;Sunday Feb. 1st &lt;br /&gt;5:30PM --10:30PM &lt;br /&gt;44 Pickman Drive &lt;br /&gt;Bedford, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Values: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We cooperate as a team to be successful by inviting other 60 plus professional people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We demonstrate a respectful/ nonjudgmental: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. By saying Yes to someone who asks us to dance. (once) &lt;br /&gt;B. By offering positive solutions or alternatives if you disagree with someone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Men and women bring healthy food selections &lt;br /&gt;Make it a festive celebration. Bring a small pizza-Pizza Party&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have an Open bar/wine/beer/soda/water/- $10.00 fee &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer/Host- Richard Tosti &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &amp;quot;Time of party: 5:30-10:30PM &lt;br /&gt;2. &amp;quot; Dress code- &amp;quot;business casual&amp;quot; - No shoes, jeans, or sneakers- stockings good, slippers great! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group was formed on the principle of synergy. We must take responsibility for inviting people. My personal goal is to have an equal ratio of men and women. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Direct friends to this website. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are perfect the way you are. Someone is searching for you right now. Help me, help you find a life companion, lover, friend, husband, or wife. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be ready to feel inspirational scars in your body and mind that will change your life forever through our association. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A woman who invites a man for another woman to meet will return the favor. It's called the Law of Psychological Reciprocity! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very important we have fun and feel joy in the process. Only when we are feeling joy are you in the receptive state of allowing love to enter in our lives. Learn more in my Law of attraction classes in my home. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.meetup.com/RichardTosti-LawofAttraction/ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check out www.Maximum-Overdrive on meetup. Also-This is part of the process of sustaining this feeling of joy- if you go to a health club, instead please consider joining this aerobic exercise dance party weekly- I would like to sponsor it Tuesday and Thursday for you- we need a minimum quota- strictly fast dancing. It will take discipline, commitment, time, most important loyalty to this club that is focused on preparing you to receive your life partner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only thing we have control over is ourselves. Take care of yourself, improve, accept yourself as an imperfect changing, growing human being. How is your heart? Take care of it. Do you feel a lower energy level? Movement will remedy that- do something that is fun-dancing! Are you like me, when I turned 50- my metabolism slowed down and I started getting a roll around my stomach? Exercise- I value myself now-then I will be able to value someone else in my life. This is called healthy self-esteem. Happiness is inside out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The adolescent mindset says: I need a younger woman to validate me, or that I am still appealing to younger women. Today, I am a mature adult. I have the self-esteem and self-confidence in myself. If I love me at 63, then I will love a women of similar age. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I accepted myself that means I can accept you. Particularly someone of a similar age. Men, I pray you understand what I'm talking about. Your happiness!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location and Directions -You will see open house signs-simple &lt;br /&gt;My Home &lt;br /&gt;44 Pickman Drive &lt;br /&gt;Bedford, MA &lt;br /&gt;128- Exit route 4/225 toward Bedford, 3.9 miles (stay right at two forks in road- Rt. 4 &lt;br /&gt;-left on Dudley (Huckins Farm sign lite up) and left on Pickman &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best is yet to be! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Tosti&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1339201545000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Dancing and Mingling Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dance-party</urlname><id>635019</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Singles Dance Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231962737000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>45 Plus -Super Bowl Party Fans</name><id>9523368</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233525600000</time><rsvp_limit>45</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dance-party/events/9523368/</event_url></item>