<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;em&gt;Another in a series of Meetups with Boston's De-Cluttering group.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this beautiful summer winds down, you might be noticing papers peeking out from under piles on your desk, dated from last April and May (and September?).... &amp;nbsp;Is there ANY way to dispatch all those papers 
&lt;em&gt;expeditiously??&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As evidenced by our Meetup's polls that have been conducted over the years, 
&lt;em&gt;paperwork&lt;/em&gt; is one form of clutter that especially challenges many of us around Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will bring handouts on sorting papers to share, and Kevin Martin also will offer for our consideration some insights gleaned from neurolinguistic programming (NLP).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us to share your SUCCESSES in Taming the Paper Tiger - as well as any particular challenges for which you still seek solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-And perhaps come away with a Decluttering Buddy to help you steer into September with a cleared-off desk!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;**We're trying a new venue! If you come by car, be sure to allow extra time to find parking around Central Square, Cambridge&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;nbsp;And do l 
&lt;em&gt;et us know i&lt;/em&gt;f you have other ideas for possible venues (see Our Venue Wish List below)--**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;When we can see something from a different perspective, often we notice new things that might serve us better.&lt;/strong&gt; This is certainly true regarding old papers, which involve blockage of sorts- metaphysical (thoughts) as well as physical (manifested thoughts).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of our members have made profound discoveries together over dinner while learning about NLP and experimenting with its techniques to change feelings at a deep level. While our achievements might be longer-lived if followed up by more neurolinguistic programming work,&amp;nbsp;alternative&amp;nbsp;approaches could require months, if not years, of much more expensive therapy and drugs - for possibly no greater benefit. And while clutter&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;be vanquished through sheer determination alone, most of us have experienced difficulties with such: "discipline" is easier said than done ... which is why clutter confounds so many of us. So, we welcome opportunity to meet periodically, celebrate progress, and consider next steps to consolidate and increase our gains. We welcome&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;thoughts on clutter and NLP, however diverse the viewpoints might be: do bring them to the table for us all to consider their basis in truth and results, to respond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having facilitated many positive changes with NLP, Kevin knows with certainty that neurolinguistic programming offers great value to many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;/strong&gt;, a practicing certified hypnotherapist and neurolinguistic programming (NLP) Master Practitioner, is back to offer more pointers and frameworks for QUICKLY (on a scale of MINUTES- NOT months or years ... so, practically magic: like a "Gestalt switch") "reprogram" our lives to surmount cluttered thinking for more successful, satisfying living. As organizer of several Boston-area NLP Meetups, Kevin originally envisioned his groups to help people learn self-help tools. He often looks for resources, tools, and groups outside the fields of hypnosis and NLP to mesh with that vision -and fortunately has found that our group does!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;If you plan to eat, please arrive by 6:30 pm&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to order; otherwise, by 7 pm will be fine. While no purchase minimum for refreshments is specified, participants are encouraged to order something to support the business in appreciation of Management's permission to meet in their space. PLEASE ALSO BE ADVISED: Commercial eating establishments generally do not permit on-site consumption of refreshments brought from elsewhere, due to liability concerns.)&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;AGENDA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Approximate)&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;6:30 pm- Order refreshment or dinner: $2.10 (for coffee) or upward ... PLEASE BE ADVISED THERE IS A WAIT LINE at the counter, so allow some time to order prior to our meeting at 7 pm
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm- Intro to neurolinguistic programming (NLP)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:15 pm- Roots of Information Clutter
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:30 pm&amp;ndash; NLP technique(s) described
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;7:45 pm - Demonstration(s)
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm- Q&amp;amp;A
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;8:45 pm- Wrap-up
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Notepad &amp;amp; pen or other note-taking device, calendar to schedule Action Items (next steps). Dress in layers (e.g., wear a sweater in case the restaurant is cooler than you'd prefer) and comfortably, as Kevin sometimes has us do NLP/EFT physical exercises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;OUR&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;VENUE WISH LIST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;We welcome your suggestions for alternative Venues&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;especially quieter, preferably free spaces under friendly, fairly flexible management, with ample free parking nearby and public transportation that runs on a frequent schedule until at least 9:30 pm (permitting our participants to linger and converse after meetings). ...OR we might meet outside in a public park (with shelter nearby in case of rain) during warm weather, perhaps over a potluck dinner, since group members have said they especially like to be out in Nature- where we don't have to feel too responsible for how everything looks, and maintenance! (...I also noticed recently that a Travel Meetup group might meet in a restaurant at Logan Airport- neat idea: such&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;relevance!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Might we do something similar?&amp;nbsp; I welcome ideas!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;VIDEO PREVIEWS&amp;nbsp;
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Bandler: NLP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8vlcsFJyEXQ&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;S. Andreas: Compulsion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwxvUofenC4&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: EFT/procrastination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UegIujmGUiY&amp;amp;feature=channel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R. Smith: Tapping&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PBNoefm5_i4&amp;amp;NR=1&amp;amp;feature=fvwp&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;RECOMMENDED READING&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Hung by the Tongue: What You Say is What You Get&lt;/em&gt;, by Francis P. Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Biology of Belief: Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter, &amp;amp; Miracles&lt;/em&gt;, by Bruce H. Lipton&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Get the Life You Want&lt;/em&gt;, by Richard Bandler&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Richard Bandler's Guide to Trance-formation&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;- EXCERPTS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...there is a magic moment when it all comes together, without effort."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...if you learned to do something one way, you can learn how to do it totally different and better. Learning is the way to personal freedom. Hypnosis and NLP are tools to make this easy and fun."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...when we know how something is done, it becomes easy to change. We're highly programmable beings ... we can program ourselves to change. That's not being a robot; that's becoming a free spirit."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...three steps to making enduring change:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. People must become so sick of having the problem that they decide they really want to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. They have to somehow see their problem from a new perspective or in a new light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. New and appealing options must be found or created, and pursued.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...since time distortion is a characteristic of the phenomenon we call "trance," just as it is of dreaming, we can lead people through choices very rapidly. The learning tool of altered states permits us to familiarize the subject with a new experience in a fraction of the time it would take for them in an ordinary waking state."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I noticed that when they made the change, they switched to 
&lt;em&gt;watching&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;themselves doing the behavior. ...they'd discovered how to disassociate from the problem experience."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...I had some people...apply what I had learned. I had them "step out" of their bodies.... And it worked. They got rid of their [problems] really quickly. Their brains simply shifted the way they perceived their situation, and their problems went away."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Suddenly, without actually realizing it, something happened that switched off the problem and turned on the solution."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Each of us creates a representation of the world in which we live--that is, we create a map or model which we use to generate our behavior. Our representation of the world determines to a large degree what our experience of the world will be, how we will perceive the world, what choices we will see available to us as we live in the world."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"it's often much more productive - and a lot easier - to change the map someone has been using rather than the territory in which the person is functioning."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If we build feed-forward loops so we're moving toward pleasure rather than away from pain, we're walking toward something we want, and we know in which direction we're going."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If we have only one response, we're stuck. If we have two, we can oscillate backward and forward. If we have three or more, it starts to feel a lot better."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The pattern is simple: white out the image you don't want, and then immediately replace it with something you prefer."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I work by accentuating people's desires, hopes, and dreams, and making them absolutely irresistible."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've told people not just to listen to what their clients are saying, but also to notice what they're not talking about, because what's 
&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;there is what they need."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I'm always looking for the shortest route to get people where they want to be, comfortably and with the greatest degree of enjoyment...."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"the right mental strategy ... means that it works and you enjoy it, and therefore you'll practice it more and more...."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...recognize the value of simplicity."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"if you give yourself bad commands, bad things happen."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"procrastination is not a psychological problem; it's just a matter of mental organization."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"there's nothing wrong with easy."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Repeat this thought and action several times, making it faster each time, until you feel yourself being pulled to your feet by the vividness of your image."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I consider the model of submodalities to be probably the most significant thing I've done so far. It allows us to create maps that show with tremendous precision how consciousness functions to produce wanted and unwanted results. The strategy model shows us how to work sequentially; the model of submodalities explains how things work simultaneously."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"find out what they're certain about and start to give them doubt about their limitations and certainty about the things they want."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Often, one or two submodality changes precipitate a systemwide shift."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"how quickly the brain learns if we learn to communicate with it in a language we understand."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In a third column, write down in some detail how your life would be better for making these changes."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I said, 'Maybe you guys should have seven hundred people in the audience and then it would be a lot easier, because if people are scared, they retreat into deep trances.'"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The other important thing you need to remember when making this sort of change is speed. The brain learns quickly; ...if the information is presented too slowly, the brain won't learn because it can't detect a pattern."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...'entrainment.' There are certain distinct signs of developing trance that people unconsciously pick up on and follow, until they, too, go into trance."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"...keep your eye on what you want to achieve, which is to put people into wonderful, relaxed states, and then have them face their problems with all the resources they didn't know they had.&amp;nbsp; Then, ... the waking state will never be the same... that's called learning."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Success Is An Altered State"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;CLARIFICATION FROM KEVIN--&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Misconceptions&amp;nbsp;about hypnosis&amp;nbsp;abound- formed through TV, movies, and staged entertainment. The most prevalent misconception is that hypnosis is a form of mind control - that a hypnotist can make someone rob a bank or do terrible or absurd things. This is absolutely false! A hypnotist cannot make anyone do anything against their values. No one will do anything they would not normally do or that they have not wanted to do. Onstage, a hypnotist provides a 'safe' atmosphere for people to have fun and act on things they may not normally do socially; however, if they have never wanted to do some particular thing, they will not do so under hypnosis. In a clinical offfice session, people under hypnosis do only what they feel safe doing, and no more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hypnotist is only a guide; the person under hypnosis is actually doing the work by following suggestions. That is why we say that all hypnosis is self-hypnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another general misconception is that someone under hypnosis is sleeping. This is far from true: Most people are totally aware of what is happening around them, and can remember everything. Most&amp;nbsp;hypnosis&amp;nbsp;sessions are experienced as deep relaxation - approximating the state of awakening in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;MEETING FEE&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;The $10-per-person meeting fee (payable via PayPal, preferably, or in cash to Judy Stitt at the event&amp;nbsp; 
  &lt;em&gt;before presentation&lt;/em&gt;, please) helps to compensate (1) the presenter for his time, training, and specialized knowledge so generously shared with us, and (2) the organizer(s) for time spent planning, administering, and coordinating events - also to defray Meetup.com's charge assessed organizers for this Meetup Web site and other resources to serve our group.)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lower level - probably under the stairs. I will set a Meetup tent sign on our table (at least until the formal meeting begins at 7 pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312490825000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311878758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Clearing the Decks" of Papers for the Upcoming Work Season - FAST !</name><id>27388381</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312239600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/27388381/</event_url></item>