<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Mercantile Wharf Building</address_2><address_1>101 Atlantic Ave (Richmond Street intersection)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.361656</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-723-5101</phone><name>The Living Room</name><city>Boston</city><id>238389</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051994</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's your chance to dine in your pajamas or sweats in relaxing surroundings. You're welcome, even if you don't wear pajamas, but please be advised you must wear clothes. :) Our last gathering here was such a great experience, it was inevitable we would return to enjoy another reasonably priced and delicious brunch. When I make the reservation I will make sure they are prepared to have crab cakes for the poached eggs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thelivingroomboston.com/brunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;Living Rooom Brunch Menu Link&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10 minute walk from Aquarium MBTA station on the Blue Line &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearby garages and parking on street  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REMINDER of MEMBER GUIDELINES:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive promptly and bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a no-show.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members who miss/no-show three meals for which they have RSVPd &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot;, are removed from the group. If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No shows and last minute cancellations impact everyone; from the organizer to the person on the wait list (which could or has been you), to the restaurant's who staff based on reservations. Please be considerate by RSVPing YES only if you plan on attending. If you're not sure and think you want to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187068281000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183185256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Living Room Pajama Party Brunch</name><id>5955529</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185118200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/5955529/</event_url></item>