<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>NATALIE ANGIER discusses The Canon: A Whirligig Tour of the Beautiful Basics of Science&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome Pulitzer Prize-winning science journalist Natalie Angier to discuss her new book The Canon. With the singular intelligence and exuberance that made her bestselling book Woman an international sensation, Angier takes us on a &amp;quot;whirligig tour&amp;quot; of the scientific canon. She draws on conversations with hundreds of the world's top scientists and on her own work for the New York Times to create a thoroughly entertaining guide to scientific literacy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angier's sparkling prose and memorable metaphors bring the science to life, reigniting our own childhood delight in discovering how the world works. &amp;quot;Of course you should know about science,&amp;quot; writes Angier, &amp;quot;for the same reason Dr. Seuss counsels his readers to sing with a Ying or play Ring the Gack: These things are fun and fun is good.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;The Canon is a joyride through the major scientific disciplines: physics, chemistry, biology, geology, and astronomy. Along the way, we learn what is actually happening when our ice cream melts or our coffee gets cold, what our liver cells do when we eat a caramel, why the horse is an example of evolution at work, and how we're all really made of stardust. &lt;br /&gt;It's Lewis Carroll meets Lewis Thomas -- a book that will enrapture, inspire, and enlighten. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets cost $5.00 and are available at the store or over the phone with a credit card at 617-661-1515&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179009567000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178150096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NATALIE ANGIER discusses "The Canon" ...</name><id>5735227</id><headcount>75</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178836200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/5735227/</event_url></item>