<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Where: Wentworth Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;550 Huntington Avenue &lt;br /&gt;Boston &lt;br /&gt;Willson Hall (Building 7) Room 102&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Contact: Doug Fuda&lt;br /&gt; Antiwarleague.com&lt;br /&gt;617 331-1491 (cell)&lt;br /&gt;dougfuda@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Meeting Description: Tom Eddlem, Doug Fuda, and Larry Lepard, members of Antiwar League and the Ron Paul meetup, are calling this meeting to give people a chance to reflect on recent events and to meet other Ron Paul supporters. The first part of the meeting will be a wide open discussion of the Ron Paul Revolution, with an opportunity to evaluate its significance and its future and compare notes with others.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the second part of the meeting we would like to discuss what to do next in the Boston area, and especially to think about what to do after the conventions and the election. In particular we would like to focus on the question of empire vs. republic, which is our specialty, and what can be done to challenge the warfare state and &amp;quot;creeping totalitarianism&amp;quot; right in our backyards.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Topics: how to oppose the empire and big brother in the local area, and how to get established on the college campuses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Possible actions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oppose Real ID.&lt;br /&gt;Oppose Homeland Security ( federal ) infiltration of local institutions.&lt;br /&gt;Invite speakers (from across the spectrum, like antiwar.com) on war and empire (like Tom Woods, Justin Raimondo, Chalmers Johnson, Ray McGovern, etc.)   &lt;br /&gt;Target the media for its complicity, especially the Boston Globe. &lt;br /&gt;Demand that the governor challenge the federal takeover of the Massachusetts National Guard for use in an unjust war of aggression.&lt;br /&gt;Add your own suggestions to the agenda.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;________________________________ &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Wentworth is next to Northeastern, one block south of the Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Plenty of parking. Turn off Ruggles street and drive past the guard booth into the West Lot. Park near the far end of the lot, right near Willson Hall (Building 7) See the campus map:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wit.edu/pop_campusmap.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wit.edu/po...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions to Wentworth:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wit.edu/pop_directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wit.edu/po...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Doug Fuda&lt;br /&gt;Antiwarleague.com&lt;br /&gt;14 Fletcher Street&lt;br /&gt;Roslindale, MA 02131&lt;br /&gt;USA&lt;br /&gt;617 331-1491 (cell)&lt;br /&gt;dougfuda@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ureneck</member_name><member_id>4211251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210459249000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209549505000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul Revolution-Open discusssion and long term plans </name><id>7841422</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210285800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/7841422/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/7/global_1551159.jpeg</photo_url></item>