<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Newton st</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.309955</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Larz Anderson  Park</name><city>Brookline</city><id>856405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.137877</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event:&lt;/b&gt;We will be holding our 20th Anniversary at the Larz Anderson Park. Since this is a special year for our Club we want to celebrate this event with a party among friends that includes deli &amp;amp; vegetarian platters and a Birthday Cake provided by Mosaic. We are also planning on some live entertainment. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt; RSVP IS REQUIRED BY JULY 7TH:&lt;/b&gt;   Send your email to: mosaic_mass@yahoo.com  and include an email address (preferred) or phone number for us to contact you and include the word Picnic in the subject line because if it looks like rain we have arranged an indoor alternative and we would contact people who have signed up to let them know of a change in location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt; - If you’re a full member of Mosaic Mass the picnic is Free! however a &lt;b&gt;Meetup membership&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;is only an introduction&lt;/b&gt; and the directions for membership are below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Membership&lt;/b&gt;: If you have not been a member or would like to renew the membership cost for membership is $25 for an individual (see other prices on the membership form at our web site) and then you can come as a member and attend the Picnic at no charge.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For Membership:&lt;/b&gt;  Send a check with the form and the correct amount made out to “MOMC of MA” to: MOMC of MA, P. O. Box 1821, Brookline, MA 02446. If you have a Paypal account, you may also pay us on www.paypal.com.  Send the money to mosaic_mass@yahoo.com. Opening a Paypal account is easy and free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guest Fee&lt;/b&gt;: $15.00 which can also be paid by Paypal.&lt;br /&gt;There is a direct link to Paypal for the charges for this event and the membership option on the “Schedule Page” at our website and if you choose to pay for your membership online then print out the Membership form and bring it with you on the 11th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Mosaic will have tables set up in the Picnic area and futher details will be provided when you rsvp</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278879044000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277169040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOSAIC OF MASS ANNUAL Picnic – 2010 </name><id>13870221</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278874800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/13870221/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/0/global_1883520.jpeg</photo_url></item>