<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Last Year at Marienbad&lt;/b&gt; directed by Alain Resnais (Hiroshima Mon  Amour, Muriel, Private Fears in Public Places) France 1961 93 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remains one of cinema's glorious enigmas, endlessly compelling and intriguing.  L A Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be prepared for an experience such as you've never had from watching a film when you sit down to look at Alain Resnais' &lt;b&gt;Last Year at Marienbad&lt;/b&gt;, a truly extraordinary French film.  NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A highly seductive parable about seduction, it?s set in and around a baroque European chateau/hotel, where the nameless hero (Giorgio Albertazzi) tries to persuade the nameless heroine (the wonderful Delphine Seyrig) that they met the previous year. Shot by Sacha Vierny in otherworldly black-and-white 'Scope, it oscillates ambiguously between past, present, and various conditional tenses, mixing memory and fantasy, fear and desire. The overall tone is poker-faced parody of lush Hollywood melodrama: an entire scene from Gilda is restaged shot by shot, a life-size blowup of Hitchcock can be glimpsed in a corridor, and a recurring match game played by the hero and his creepy romantic rival (Sacha Piteoff) is as mordantly ritualistic as a western showdown. Yet the film's dreamlike cadences, frozen tableaux, and distilled surrealist poetry are too eerie, too terrifying even, to be shaken off as camp. For all its notoriety, this masterpiece among masterpieces has never really received its due.  Chicago Reader&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Alain Resnais from a 1962 interview: 'For me [ &lt;b&gt;Last Year at Marienbad&lt;/b&gt; ] represents an attempt, still crude and primitive, to approach the complexity of thought and of its mechanisms. But I stress that it is only a small step forward compared to what we should achieve... In reality we don't think chronologically; our decisions never conform to an ordered logic. We all have factors which determine our being but are not successions of logical acts following a perfect sequence.' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what Strictly Film School has to say: &lt;a href="http://www.filmref.com/directors/dirpages/resnais.html#marienbad" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmref.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should make for a compelling discussion afterward. Hope to see you there- Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203205876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Resnais' Last Year at Marienbad</name><id>7345016</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204396200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7345016/</event_url></item>