<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston, MA 02215</address_2><address_1>537 Commonwealth Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.348770</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-437-1868</phone><name>NESOP</name><city>Boston</city><id>498558</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096530</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please note this event is with the Boston Photography MeetUp! Please sign up through thier site or email Banafsheh directly at Marmoolac@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Creative Directions in Fine Art Photography:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During our first hour with Steve Maka, we'll hear him discuss how he is overcoming the odds of his studio fire and is finding new and innovative ways to keep on creating. Come spend an evening with Steve as he discusses the new directions his work is taking after the devastating fire at the Uxbridge Mill. He'll speak about what it is like for him to use his brand new 44? large format printer, scanning for detail, and learning to play in PhotoShop. &amp;quot;I see PhotoShop as an amazing art tool, not just a way to process my photographs.&amp;quot; says Steve. Come see some of his amazing kaleidoscope imagery, and hear him discuss his process on creating these unique photographs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The difference between a great image verses a mediocre one: &lt;br /&gt;During our second hour with Steve, please fell free to bring in one of your very own images and have him take a look. He?ll give you an honest and fair critique about what he see and what kind of impact the image has on him on an intuitive level. He asks that if you bring a print - please make it at least 11x14 or larger, so sharing the image with everyone in the room will be easier. He'll encourage an open discussion of ideas and dwell a little while in the the world of creativity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details&lt;br /&gt;www.makaphotography.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this fabulous workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, February 13, 2008 at 8:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;NEW ENGLAND SCHOOL OF PHOTOGRAPHY&lt;br /&gt;537 COMMONWEALTH AVE. ROOM 1 AND 2&lt;br /&gt;Boston , MA 02215&lt;br /&gt;617-437-1868&lt;br /&gt;Info/Map&lt;br /&gt;Expected Attendees&lt;br /&gt;28 people ? 28 Yes, 0 Maybe&lt;br /&gt;There's still room for 12 more.&lt;br /&gt;Organized by&lt;br /&gt;Banafsheh ehtemam (PHOTOGRAPHER AND FOUNDER)&lt;br /&gt;Event fee&lt;br /&gt;USD30.00 (exact change please)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;One of the best I have done was to purchase two of Maka's Prints &amp;quot; . Banafsheh&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if you wish to pay with paypal please $32.50 . or email me for the address and simply send me a check Banafsheh&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203123944000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201833230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steve Maka Fundraiser/Lectrue: Creative Directions in Fine Art Photography</name><id>7237825</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202950800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/7237825/</event_url></item>