<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Holden St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01606</zip><lat>42.305233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>UU Church of Worcester</name><city>Worcester</city><id>707867</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.817561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us at our November meeting where we will be joined by actor Richard Clark who will be performing as Mark Twain in celebration of the 100th anniversary of Twain's death.  Mr. Clark will be giving us a look at Twain's philosophies and a glimpse of early turn of the 20th century Humanism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Clark is an actor with over thirty years of experience in New England regional theater, New York Theater and television.  He is a graduate of Clark University and studied at the American Academy of Dramatic Art, The Actor’s Connection, and the Actor’s Loft in New York City. His Keeping History Alive series brings historical figures such as Mark Twain, Andrew Carnegie, Clarence Darrow, John Barrymore, Ernest Hemingway and William Shakespeare back to life. His shows are based on biographies, autobiographies personal letters, books and the works of various playwrights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program is scheduled to start at 7 at the UU Church of Worcester, with doors opening at 6:30 for socializing and conversation. Please watch this page for updates and changes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290365292000</updated><rating><average>3.56999993324</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287542660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Richard Clark performs Mark Twain: A Humanist Perspective</name><id>15166924</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289347200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/15166924/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_18904665.jpeg</photo_url></item>