<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>CGIS South Building Tsai Auditorium</address_2><address_1>1730 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375269</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tsai Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>748933</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.112774</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Science and Democracy Lecture Series &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Ulrich Beck, Professor of Sociology at the University of Munich, and the British Journal of Sociology Professor at the London School of Economics and Sciences.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His interests focus on 'risk society', 'individualization' and 'reflexive modernization'. He is the director of a research centre at the University of Munich (in cooperation with three other universities in the area), Sonderforschungsbereich - Reflexive Modernization, financed since 1999 by the DFG (German Research Society). He has been a fellow of several scientific institutions, among others the Institute for Advanced Study Berlin in 1990-1991. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Science and Democracy, a lecture series aimed at exploring both the promised benefits or our era's most salient scientific and technological breakthroughs and the potentially harmful consequences of developments that are inadequately understood, debated, or managed by politicians, lay publics, and policy institutions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is co-sponsored by:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seas.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;The Harvard University School of Engineering and Applied Sciences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://environment.harvard.edu/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;The Harvard University Center for the Environment &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;in conjunction with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hks.harvard.edu/sts/" target="_blank"&gt;The Program on Science, Technology and Society &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Harvard University's John F. Kennedy School of Government&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Program on Science, Technology and Society at Harvard University's John F. Kennedy School of Government is dedicated to enhancing the quality of research, education, and public debate on the role of science and technology in contemporary societies. Through integrated, cross-disciplinary initiatives in research, teaching, training, and public outreach the Program seeks to develop foundational, policy-relevant insights into the nature of science and technology, and the ways in which they both influence and are influenced by society, politics, and culture. Among the fields that significantly contribute to the STS Program's core mission are science and technology studies, anthropology, comparative politics, history, government, law, and sociology. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is free and open to the public.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296255959000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219971885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sonderforschungsbereich!</name><id>8643959</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226527200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/8643959/</event_url></item>