<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>312 Litchfield Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06524</zip><lat>41.414001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethany Music and Dance</name><city>Bethany</city><id>4567382</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.973019</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bethany Music and Dance (BMAD) parties are held once a month on a Friday night, beginning at 7:30 PM (please do not arrive before 7:30 PM). Contrary to popular opinion, BMAD is not held on the same Friday each month but is planned around the schedules of the occupants of 312 Litchfield Tpke. The date of each month's party will be posted thier websites (see below) approximately two weeks in advance. Bring a dessert or beverage to share. There is a lot of music and dance happening at each party, but you do not need to be able to play an instrument or sing or dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos will be hosting this meetup, and can be reached at 215-206-9381 if you need him.  Thanks Carlos!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music parties are acoustic; please leave your amplifiers at home. For the benefit of others who attend, please apply fragrances lightly. Smoking is not permitted anywhere in the house. Thanks for your cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill has been calling dances for over thirty years, starting out in New Haven, Connecticut with the contra dance series that has been a fixture of the folk music and dance scene since 1976. In addition to contra dances in and around the northeast, he has called at various dance camps regionally and nationally. Much of his calling activity centers on special occasion "barn" dances including the monthly musical event BMAD at his home in Bethany, CT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info, check out the website: &lt;a href="http://www.billthedancecaller.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.billthedancecaller.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carlos Moya</member_name><member_id>31366462</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364862211000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364491251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bethany Music And Dance Festival</name><id>111510392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364599800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/111510392/</event_url></item>