<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Unquowa Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06824</zip><lat>41.141869</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>yoga for everybody</name><city>fairfield</city><id>3796832</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.256554</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What you put into your body physically is just as important as what we put in emotionally and spiritually. Our bodies may not digest things properly and this is when it is time to work on those other aspects of ourselves, and if we are digesting just fine, the Chinese have been using Qi Gong for several thousands of years as preventative medicine, to keep everything flowing. Qi Gong is described as the art of effortless power. It's a form of exercise that combines deep stretching, graceful flowing movements, and mindfulness through motion. Being in the flow is the exquisite place where life happens with ease and effortless power. Athletes describe it as being in the &amp;quot;zone&amp;quot;. We can all tap into our own unique &amp;quot;zone&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;qi flow&amp;quot; where life happens with ease, relaxation and joyful abandon. In this workshop, participants will delve into the magic of Qi Gong through a combination of gentle stretching, flowing movements, and postures of power. The retreat will be a wonderful balance between movement, lecture and meditation. Inner Peace is an energetic state of harmony and balance. Lee Holden is an internationally known instructor in meditation, tai chi, and Qi Gong, as well as a licensed acupuncturist, herbalist, and author. His popular library of Qi Gong DVDs have made him a regular fixture on PBS. Lee has worked with Deepak Chopra as well as Mantak Chia, a widely revered QiGong expert. Holden is also a stress management consultant to top Silicon Valley corporations like Apple, 3Com and Cisco, and has been the on-set wellness consultant for several Hollywood film productions. Lee is a graduate of U.C., Berkeley, with a BA in Psychology. Lee , a &amp;quot;Doctor of Chinese Medicine,&amp;quot; is a graduate of Five Branches Institute in Santa Cruz, a leading acupuncture college in the U.S. Each workshop is $35 in advance, $45 1 week before. 2 locations in connecticut October 14th 6:30pm-8:30pm Yoga for everybody 27 Unquowa Rd, Fairfield, CT 06824 203-254-YOGA October 15th 3-5pm Yoga Space 777 Federal Road (Route 202) Brookfield, CT 06804 (203) 775-6220 oct 14th with yoga for everybody &lt;a href="https://clients.mindbodyonline.com/ASP/home.asp?studioid=5.." target="_blank"&gt;https://clients.mindb...&lt;/a&gt;. oct 15th with yoga space &lt;a href="https://clients.mindbodyonline.com/ASP/home.asp?studioid=1.." target="_blank"&gt;https://clients.mindb...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318636319000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317642451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Qi Gong Flow and Tao Yin w/ Master Lee Holden Oct 14th or 15th </name><id>35914282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318631400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/35914282/</event_url></item>