<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>City Hall Plaza</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.359197</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston City Hall Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>950175</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058038</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's enjoy munching on tasty fresh traditional Japanese food this Sunday! And in the process support ethnic festivals in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's start by enjoying Japanese Flower Arranging at Boston's 2nd Annual Japanese "Haru Matsuri" ("Spring Festival" in Japanese). It will be held on Sunday May 19th from 10am--6pm. The venue is Boston City Hall Plaza. Admission is FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the Japanese Spring Festival there will be an "Ikenobo Ikebana" Flower Arranging Booth. Teachers of the Ikenobo style of Japanese Flower Arranging will be on hand to demonstrate the art of Ikenobo and to answer any questions about this style of Japanese Flower Arranging. Essentially this style of Japanese Flower Arranging is very important, as all Ikebana (Japanese Flower Arranging) originated from this style. It began in Kyoto, Japan as a Buddhist floral offering. This will be a great opportunity for you to acquaint yourself with this style of Japanese Flower Arranging and an opportunity for you to find future classes if you so desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there is MORE!! There will be Japanese Exhibits/Shows/Vendors and Food booths. There will be about 34 food booths and about 80 non-food booths PLUS live stage performances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Stage will include: Chorus performing Japanese traditional songs/Kid's dances/traditional Japanese dances/Japanese Pop music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food booths include traditional Japanese food: Yakisoba (fried noodles)/Okonomiyaki (Japanese-style pancake)/Ramune (Japanese soda) and tea/ Udon noodles with toppings/Ukon spice drink/Beef bowl with rice/ Green tea ice cream/ Rice balls/ Ramen/ Curry Rice/Grilled Squid/ Mochi (rice cake)/Seaweed salad&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus many booths selling and promoting Japanese culture and Arts &amp;amp; Crafts. For example: Origami/ Kimono/Calligraphy/Martial Arts/Buddhism/Anime and Manga/Japanese healing arts/etc... Please see &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.JapanFestivalBoston.org"&gt;http://www.JapanFestivalBoston.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be there to guide us. I am the Organizer of a brand new Japanese Flower Arranging Meetup. See &lt;a href="http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please meet me at 10:30am at the Starbucks with the Steaming Kettle at 63 Court Street (next to the Government MBTA station). This is the Starbucks with the giant, golden steaming tea kettle hung over the front entrance. (See &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.celebrateBoston.com/strange/giant-tea-kettle.htm"&gt;http://www.celebrateBoston.com/strange/giant-tea-kettle.htm&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring a friend or more! Let's enjoy a leisurely Sunday immersed in Japanese culture! Please remember to RSVP! See you there! Stay as long as you like! Remember it is FREE! I will be there from 10:30am until the event finishes at 6pm. If you can not meet me at 10:30 am please let me know. I could rendezvous with a later group at 1pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP to: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/Events/119288212"&gt;http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/Events/119288212&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there! Kim&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Starbucks with the Steaming Kettle at 63 Court Street (next to Government station). This is the Starbucks with the giant, golden steaming tea kettle hung over the front entrance.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369005247000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368678206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enjoy traditional Japanese Food at Boston's Japan Spring Festival and MORE!!</name><id>119652532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368973800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/119652532/</event_url></item>