<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up.&lt;br /&gt;********************************************* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As practice-tioners of Law Of Attraction, we know how important it is to have a consistent practice, keeping our thoughts and emotions in a happier, higher vibrational place, so that we attract more of what we want. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, these days, even the most &amp;quot;disciplined&amp;quot; of us might be getting drained mentally and emotionally, given the current economic climate where we are &amp;quot;bombarded&amp;quot; by other people’s fearful emotions, anxiety and loss of hope. On top of this, some of us also have to deal with personal fears and concerns too (e.g. experiencing job and/or financial loss). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This sense of frustration, fear and/or disempowerment causes loss of energy. This drain can make it challenging to remain in a happier, joyful place day in and day out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on her system of Energy Restructuring, &lt;b&gt;Yuliya Cohen, energy healer and BostonLOA member,&lt;/b&gt; will share with us some simple and powerful ways that quickly and efficiently connect you to the Universal power contained within your own body so that you can...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- disengage immediately from negative thoughts and emotions in the moment they are happening,&lt;br /&gt;by taking back all the energy lost to negative thoughts and emotions in areas of your life like health, relationships, financial, job/business or spirituality, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- strengthen your personal “good vibe space ” to ward off negative vibes,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and the Best Part! – You don't have to be in control of the process – The Universe will do it for you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By enhancing your LOA practice with these powerful tools of Energy Restructuring, you can get yourself to a more hopeful and energetically empowering &amp;quot;inner&amp;quot; place that allows you to deal more effectively with the &amp;quot;outer&amp;quot; realities of a world that's fear-based.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The added bonus is that you can get to this better place faster without requiring extensive 'digging' into underlying problems and beliefs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us, volunteer to get some &amp;quot;mini-coaching&amp;quot; with Yuliya&lt;/b&gt; where she demonstrates how to use the Energy Restructuring tools  that will guide you to a place of empowerment and authentic wholeness. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;*********************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Yuliya Cohen:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; www.yuliyacohen.com&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya is a trained energy healer, medical intuitive and therapist, and the creator of the Energy Restructuring™ System. She received her training from the HLCC &amp;quot;Crucible&amp;quot; program, directed by Rev. Rosalyn Bruyere, a world-renowned healer, scholar &amp;amp; researcher in the field of Energy Healing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yuliya was formerly an engineer &amp;amp; computer science researcher (including work at Siemens Research and Technology Laboratories) and holds degrees in Civil Engineering from the Kiev School of Civil Engineering &amp;amp; in Computer Science from Brandeis University.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240176761000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>63</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236142603000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonLOA Meetup - IN PERSON, 7 - 9 pm</name><id>9877055</id><headcount>63</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239145200000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/9877055/</event_url></item>