<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>84 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359476</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Stratton Student Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>920739</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093974</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ok, I am finally going to set up a Contra Dancing meetup.  I have no idea what I am getting myself into, but I am sure that a lot of laughter will be included in the event.  This is a limited number event, so please do not rsvp yes unless you are pretty sure you can attend and keep it up to date so that if someone else can take you place if you can't make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is Contra Dancing, well it is the precurser to Square Dancing and you end up moving around the floor and dancing with everyone throughout the dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT has Contra Dancing on Tuesday evenings a few times a month.  They charge &lt;b&gt;$6 per person&lt;/b&gt; to join in the fun.  Please bring cash, there are cash machines in the student center.  They do have regulars already and asked that I keep the attendance to 10 people or less.  They also say we do not have to worry about gender as partners can be changed frequently.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dances run from 8-10:30 and begin with some basic instruction.   The people who run the event said we would be welcome to show up at 7:45 and get some extra instruction.   Please wear comfortable clothes and appropriate shoes.   This is a very fast moving dance and rigorous so keep that in mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I plan on going over to the food court on the second floor of the Student Center at 6 to grab a bite to eat before hand, anyone interested can join me.  We will head upstairs to the 4th floor at 7:40 for our special introduction to the dance.  If you don't join us for the pre-event, meet us at room 491 at 7:45.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking and Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Stratton Student Center (Building W20). It is located at 84 Mass. Ave., directly across the street from the main entrance to MIT.   Campus map:  &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=W20" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The number 1 bus runs along Mass Ave and can be caught at Harvard or Central Square.    It stops right in front of the building.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule for Bus 1:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/schedules_and_maps/bus/routes/?route=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com/s...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also walk from either Kendall or Central Square to the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walking from Kendall Square (11 minutes):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=84+Massachusetts+Ave+Cambridge+MA" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walking from Central Square (12 minutes):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=84+Massachusetts+Ave+Cambridge+MA" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See a schedule for the #1 bus which runs along Mass Ave.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking&lt;br /&gt;Free parking is available in the West Annex Lot (on Vassar Street west of Massachusetts Avenue, next to the West Garage), or on the street. The lot behind the Bank of America ATM at Mass Ave and Vassar Street is closer, but it often fills up on weeknights.  No parking permit is required at these lots after 5 pm or on weekends. Metered street parking is free after 6 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the food court on the second floor of the building at 6.  I will have a meetup sign and a meetup pin.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1291919272000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290185869000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Contra Dancing</name><id>15500539</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291768200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15500539/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/8/global_19736408.jpeg</photo_url></item>