<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE JULY MEETUP IS THE SECOND SUNDAY IN JULY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the July meetup, it's back to Buford's Puggy wonderland in Carver, otherwise known as Ron and Shar's yard.  This yard is HUGE, securely fenced, and always nicely mowed for the meetups.  There's shade and water and even a kiddie pool for the amphibious Pugs, and for lazier folks like your organizer - me - there's plenty of room to set up a lawn chair in the shade to sit and sip soft drinks, eat snacks, and watch the Pugs run wild.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know.  We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host, and we'd certainly like to give Shar a break every now and then.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OUR LAST MEETUP?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a beautiful day it was, hot, but not too hot for the Pugs to run around and play, and play they did!  We were hosted by our Puggy wannabe, Jack Russell Terrier Wizzar and his family, Dave and Shari, in Middleboro.  Wizzar was beyond thrilled to have so many fuzzy visitors all at once, and he spent the afternoon delightedly running around and around his yard, pursued by relays of Pugs.  If any Pug got a little overheated, there was a &amp;quot;dipping station&amp;quot; and a hose to cool them off, although most of them weren't very appreciative of the attention!  Thanks especially for new member Alex for taking over my dipping duties and keeping my French Bulldog Cletus nicely cooled off.  I didn't even get wet!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had quite a few brand new members attend who had just joined in the previous week, thanks to the marvelous coverage we got from the Brockton Enterprise.  I hope that we were able to make the new folks feel welcome, certainly, their Pugs had a marvelous time!  We look forward to having them all come back, Pugs, kids, babies, and all!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Dave and Shari for opening their non-Puggie home to all their Puggie friends, and for being so aware of the extra safety precautions that Pug owners have to take for their Pugs in summer weather, especially for the hose and the dipping station!  Thanks to Shari for her rice krispies squares (I think your organizer - me - ate most of them), and to the folks who brought the cookies and the brownies. Even though our monthly host provides the soft drinks and the paperware, we depend on our members to bring the snacks for all the pugaholics attending.  They haven't failed us yet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your baby. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the adults!  Please don't bring treats for the dogs, without prior approval - one of our long term members has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who could very easily have a fatal reaction to dog treats.  Thank you for your consideration!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. We want everyone to have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups and the South of Boston Small Breed Dogs Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend.  Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis, Cletus and Stoney's faces when Puggie Sunday rolls around.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>33</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216523598000</updated><rating><average>4.92999982834</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213470709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston Pug July Meetup</name><id>8142965</id><headcount>38</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215972000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/8142965/</event_url></item>