<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Great Path</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.762273</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 512-3000</phone><name>Manchester Community College</name><city>Manchester</city><id>184492</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.567017</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This FREE event is held at Manchester Community College (MCC) in Manchester, CT. You must register online (&lt;a href="http://www.mcc.commnet.edu/signup/global.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mcc.commne...&lt;/a&gt; ) with MCC for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;We have called together leading scientists, policy makers, and citizens to discuss the complex issue of global climate change. This is your invitation to question, consider, and examine the root causes and consequences of climate change on a global and a local level. The conference will provide background information that is scientifically derived and examine management strategies that affect us all. Come find out what is being done in CT and how this connects with regional and global strategies to minimize human impact. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come develop your awareness and understanding of this pressing issue and explore policy and management implications. This conference will be of wide ranging interest and relevance to all concerned citizens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 21, 2006&lt;br /&gt;9:00 AM - 1:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SBM Charitable Foundation Auditorium&lt;br /&gt;Manchester Community College&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free and Open to the Public&lt;br /&gt;***Register Online (&lt;a href="http://www.mcc.commnet.edu/signup/global.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mcc.commne...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;or call 860- 512-2691&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speech Itinerary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:30 AM - 10:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Climate: How Did We Get Here?&lt;br /&gt;And Where On Earth Are We Going?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Anji Seth&lt;br /&gt;Assistant Research Professor of Geography&lt;br /&gt;University of Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:30 AM - 11:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Changing Environments&lt;br /&gt;of Long Island Sound&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Johan &amp;quot;Joop&amp;quot; C. Varekamp&lt;br /&gt;Harold T. Stearns Professor of Earth Science&lt;br /&gt;Wesleyan University&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30 AM - 12:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Policy Implications of&lt;br /&gt;Global Climate Change&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Bryan Garcia, Director Energy Market Initiatives&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut Clean Energy Fund&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also at MCC:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Global Warming: The Signs and the Science&amp;quot; * &lt;br /&gt;A PBS Film&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday October 17 at 11 AM and 7 PM&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 21 at 2 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* No Preregistration Necessary for Attening the Film &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Filmed in the United States, Asia and South America, this wide-ranging, compelling and accessible documentary brings the reality of climate change to life and offers viewers an inspiring example of people who are making a difference in their own communities. Is it possible to avert disaster? Can a paradigm of progress built on fossil fuels be altered significantly in time? Will changing the way things are done mean economic ruin or new opportunities? These are some of the questions the documentary poses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Global Issues Conference&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The goal of the Global Issues Conference is to improve the public?s understanding of international issues by presenting a program of distinguished, internationally known speakers. The conference provides a forum to introduce and to examine issues that affect international relations in areas such as politics, economics, history, religion, art, culture, and law.&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership is planned at this event. Just mingle with other members and the others who go to the conference.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540627000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1160767339000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MCC Global Issues Conference - Global Climate Change (free)</name><id>5196223</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1161435600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5196223/</event_url></item>