<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you had clients ask you how to send &amp;quot;those emails that look like a picture&amp;quot; and you didn't know how to respond? Have you wanted to send them for yourself? Do you know some things about HTML email, but want to learn more? Scott Carson, Director and Owner of Noble Desktop will show how to create and send HTML Email in a variety of ways. You might learn that you already have some or all of the needed tools, and just didn't know it. Scott will also briefly discuss using an email marketing service such as Constant Contact. Details covered will include:&lt;br /&gt; • How do I get started?&lt;br /&gt; • Should I do it myself, or use an Email Marketing Service?&lt;br /&gt; • Dos and Don'ts — tables, frames, animations, etc.&lt;br /&gt; • Using Cascading Style Sheets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott will tailor his presentation to the interests of attendees. Those with some HTML knowledge will be able to ask for more in-depth information, but Scott's presentation will help even novices leave with a better understanding of the options available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Carson runs two email lists, one for his business, Noble Desktop (21,000 emails) and one for his hobby website (12,000). He will share all of his secrets! You can check out the Noble Desktop website at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nobledesktop.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nobledeskt...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TO RESERVE YOUR PLACE: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;- Go to: www.paypal.com and select the &amp;quot;Send Money&amp;quot; tab&lt;br /&gt;- Insert &amp;quot;kolkdesign@usa.net&amp;quot; in &amp;quot;Recipient's Email&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;- Type in the amount you wish to send. ($24 per person)&lt;br /&gt;- Select &amp;quot;Service&amp;quot; for &amp;quot;Type&amp;quot; (of money sent).&lt;br /&gt;- Put ICC meeting-May 7 in the &amp;quot;Subject&amp;quot; box.&lt;br /&gt;- Note: Use the PayPal message box to type in your meal preference. This time our meal choices are: Basa Sole Picatta; Chicken Marsala with Mushrooms; or Penne Roberto with Sundried Tomatoes and Artichokes (vegetarian).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OUR RESERVATION DEADLINE is Monday, May 4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tell them you're there for the Independent Creative Club.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ginger LaBella</member_name><member_id>5838547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245798024000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Network Marketers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>networkmarket-792</urlname><id>818489</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4400024414</group_lon><name>Independent Creative Club of Greater Hartford</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240434845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creating and Sending HTML Email</name><id>10245501</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241733600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/networkmarket-792/events/10245501/</event_url></item>