<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>732 S Undermountain Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01257</zip><lat>42.088855</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass AT: Race Brook Falls Trailhead</name><city>Scheffield</city><id>1600742</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.411130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/8/c/event_22546220.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part 1 of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail! Join us on Sunday April 17th to do the first part of a series of hikes that I will be scheduling to do the entire length of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail. We will meet at the Race Brook Falls Trailhead, which will be the ending location of our hike.We'll then leave half the cars and drive down rt 41 to the Undermountain Trailhead in Salisbury, CT. Because we there is no easy entrance to the AT right at the Massachusetts border, we have to hike through about 3 and a half miles of Connecticut to get back to the Mass border and then start our Mass AT journey. We'll hit some great scenic spots including Bear Mountain, Sages Ravine, Race Mountain, and Race Brook Falls (pic to the left). Total hike is 10.5 miles through challenging terrain with a total elevation gain approximated at 2500 ft (1500 up to Bear Mountain, another 1000 on the AT between Bear and Race Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a lengthy hike over difficult terrain with some decent elevation gains. We will have to move at good pace because of the length of the hike so I ask that only experienced hikers in good physical condition sign up. I'm limiting the numbers on this hike so please only sign up if you are sure you can make it (which really always applies, but its worth calling out). Please bring plenty of water (I'm bringing 3 liters) appropriate hiking attire (no jeans or cotton, hiking boots not sneakers), rain gear in case the weather turns nasty, lunch, and snacks. I spoke with a ranger at Mt Everett Reservation on Saturday the 9th and he said the snow was just about gone and they are expecting weather in the 70s this week which should melt the last of it. He said he didn't think traction devices would be necessary. That being said, I'm bringing my micro spikes just in case (better to be safe!) and I recomend that you do as well. Do expect some muddy trails though....not getting out of this one with clean hiking boots!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Trailhead Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Providence 2 hours 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Newport 3 hours 10 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note the address given above is approximate...it is an intersection of rt 41 that is close to the trailhead...but no the actual trail head address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google maps recomends different routes based on newport (across CT) or providence (up to the mass pike) so take a look and pick you best route based on your location. But you want to end up on rt41 in Salisbury CT or Sheffeild MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;From CT: The entrance to Race Brook Falls is a few miles over the border of Connecticut in Sheffield, MA. From the center of Salisbury take Route 41 north. Go over the border and a few miles later on the left side will be a paved cutoff from Route 41. It almost looks like a tiny rest area. (If the parking area is full, you can park along Route 41 but just make sure your car is really off the road and on the grass.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;From MA:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;access is on MA Rte. 41, 5.5 miles south of South Egremont, MA, on the right side of the road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Route&amp;nbsp;Information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;1.9 miles on the Undermountain Trail to its junction with the Appalachian Trail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;.9 miles to Bear Mountain summit(2,316 ft). Great views from the top of Connecticut's highest mountain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;.7 miles to the MA/CT border.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;3.9 miles to Race Mountain summit(2,372 ft). 360 degree views!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;1.1 miles to the intersection with the Race Brook Falls Trail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt;2 miles down to the parking area along a series of waterfalls&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444 ; font-size : 14px"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be in Worcester MA the night before, but please use the comments section to coordinate with other hikers if you want to carpool. Just remember that we do have to carspot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Massachusetts Appalachian Trail Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/8/4/a/event_22547178.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Most hikers are a little in awe of the Appalachian Trail, which runs 2,179 miles from Georgia to Maine, and secretly wonder/wish they could hike the whole thing...and I'm no exception. Since hiking the whole thing isnt an option....I figured I would start hiking sections of it starting with Massachusetts. The Massachusetts section runs through the western part of the state through the Berkshires from Sages Ravine at the CT border (near Salisbury, CT) up to the southern end of the Green Mountains in Vermont. So throughout this hiking season I'll be posting various chunks of the trail, in order going from South to North. The trail runs 90 mile in Mass....so it will probably be about a dozen hikes. A few of them will be single hikes but some will be weekend hikes where we hike both Saturday and Sunday to get the most miles under our belt since its a bit of a drive to get up there. It can be challenging to find access points to the trail to properly divide up the sections so if you sign up for these please be patient and keep in mind that there are some logistical issues to car spotting and finding appropriate parking areas (and I have never hiked most of these trails)....we will end up hiking far more than the 90 miles since we will have to hike on connecting trails just to get to the AT. (The first hike is a great example....4 miles of connection trails hiked, plus 1.5 of CT AT....meaning we only get through 5 miles of actual Massachusetts AT on section 1!). I'm going to limit the numbers for these hikes and I will try and give preference to those that are doing multiple sections and not just one. That is, if you have gone on the first two sections I will try and make sure you get into the third section before someone who hasnt done any so far. Depending on how it goes we may increase the limit. We'll see if we even get much interest given the length of the car ride up to the Berkshires. I hope to see some of you out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Race Brook Falls Trail Head, look for my bright yellow Ford Escape. Cell: 508-414-8544. Above address is approximate, see directions below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303210632000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Part 1 in a group of hikes I'll be posting all year to section hike the entire 90 mile Massachusetts part of the Appalachian Trail. Please see note at the bottom for information about the group of hikes.</why><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302377361000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massachusetts Appalachian Trail: Part 1</name><id>17245466</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303047000000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/17245466/</event_url></item>