<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>* Use Dirt Road on River Side*</address_2><address_1> 64 Tariffville Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06081</zip><lat>41.896631</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Curtis Park River Put In</name><city>Tariffville</city><id>353334</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.778124</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; MONDAY Memorial Day: Mostly sunny, with a high near 72. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is posted on www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Just a note to all regarding getting to Curtiss (yes, it does have 2 &lt;br /&gt;esses in the name) Park on Monday:  Simsbury has a big Memorial Day &lt;br /&gt;parade in the center of town along Hopmeadow Street (Rt. 10) midday &lt;br /&gt;that will snarl traffic trying to get through from Avon and west. Best &lt;br /&gt;to plan the route through Granby and down Rt. 189 to Tarifville.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see lots of paddlers there. It is a really pretty section of &lt;br /&gt;the river, and one that my wife and I always tried to include in the &lt;br /&gt;canoe trips we ran for the Farmington River Watershed Association (back &lt;br /&gt;when dinosaurs roamed the Earth).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bill Pratt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is for everyone, Beginners to seasoned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Kayak  Put In area is easy to drive up to, seems secluded enough for a dinner and rest event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location is called Curtis Park, a socker, baseball fields and that kind of place, but on the river side there is a dirt road leading towards the river where there is a put in area..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will get to see the beginning of the Tarriffville George..and paddle upstream if time permits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;bring some pot luck food and favourite beverage...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford direction:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;91 north to exit 36,&lt;br /&gt;Take left (west direction) on to 178 (park ave) toward bloomfield for 1.6 miles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At intersection take right onto 187 (north direction) (Blue Hills Ave) for about 5 miles heading toward Tariffville direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will meet rte 187/189,&lt;br /&gt;Stay on 189 to Tarriffville..at the end of the nice paved part you will end up in Tariffville, take a left at the light onto rte 315 (Elm st) follow it to the end at the stop sign take the left into Tarrifville Road (the street sign says Withrop rd, thats the road to the right though)..continue on 315 for about 1.2 miles, take a right into Curtis Park (right side) and go to the river via the dirt road..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ok if you use Mapquest, GPs or other..there is 2 Tariffville roads in the town and the numbers dont match right....so be careful and use the map and compare it to the directions given.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best GPS address i can get is 64 Tariffville Road, Tariffville CT and the MEETUP MAP LINK ABOVE is correct.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a secondary landmark: its near rte 315 and 202 intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;other info and map picture:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://connecticut.quickcityinfo.com/Poquonock/Parks/377680/Curtis_Park" target="_blank"&gt;http://connecticut.qu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drive Carefully,&lt;br /&gt;I may get there a bit later, or earlier..depends on traffic and kayaks and how they hold on..LOL&lt;br /&gt;This is the second trip and now with new bearings and even more updates to car and trailer..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have 5 kayaks available but would like a rental doughnation of 15 bucks for each one.&lt;br /&gt;Pleas know the kayak type and its quirks before reserving.&lt;br /&gt;Pfd, Paddle and other accessories included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. The Brown Homless Persons Bathtub= Pungo 12' with F/R floataion bags installed=  Durelle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper &amp;amp; Dipper= Riot Tourlite 15'= AL-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna Snake= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', = Bill &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Wild Dancer= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'= Alex&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Flat Boat= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= Nancy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to end of road, look for the orange striped cones.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243824567000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242915251000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAK EVENT &amp; POT LUCK DINNER*   in Tarifville on the Farmington River  MONDAY</name><id>10462246</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243270800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/10462246/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/c/global_3264476.jpeg</photo_url></item>