<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Haven't seen this in years - and it's one of the greatest movies ever made - and as relevant now as it was in 1954 - maybe more so.  The movie's at 7:00.  After, we'll go to one of the usual suspects in Harvard Square.  The directing is superb, the acting is gifted, and the score is riveting.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Elia Kazan. &lt;br /&gt;With Marlon Brando, Karl Malden, Lee J. Cobb &lt;br /&gt;US 1954, 35mm, b/w, 108 min. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kazan and Bud Schulberg's devastating portrait of mob controlled corruption and grinding working class struggle within the New Jersey longshoreman community was a landmark both in terms of its politics and its showcasing of Method acting—embodied by Marlon Brando as an intuitive yet carefully controlled mode of gestural performance. Rejected for fear of controversy by all the major studios, Kazan was forced to independently produce his hard-hitting and risky project, cutting costs by working with upcoming Group Theater actors such as Brando and Kazan regular Karl Malden. Featuring one of Leonard Bernstein's most accomplished scores and fabulous black-and-white cinematography by Soviet legend Boris Kaufman, On the Waterfront defines a beautifully moody and spontaneous updating of the Ash Can School that captures the hard-bitten poetry of cold water flats, lonely cafeterias and lives broken by years of hard, unhappy labor.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll try to sit in the exact middle of the theater.  Also, at the end I'll be in the front left, where we can gather.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248630167000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>On The Waterfront</name><id>10961153</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249772400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10961153/</event_url></item>