<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>suggested donation</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We will be discussing &amp;quot;Reading Lolita in Tehran: A Memoir in Books&amp;quot; by Azar Nafisi.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the back cover: Every Thursday morning for two years in the Islamic Republic of Iran, a bold and ispired teacher named Azar Nafisi secretly gathered seven of her most committed female students to read forbidden Western classics.  As Islamic morality squads staged arbitrary raids in Tehran, fundamentalists seized hold of the universities, and a blind censor stifled artistic expressio, the girls in Azar Nafisi's living room risked removing their veils and immersed themselves in the words of Jane Austen, F. Scott Fitzgerald, Henry James, and Vladimir Nabokov.  In this extraordinary memoir, their stories become intertwined with the ones they are reading.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note new location.  The Creamery is located near BC and is T-accessible via the green line- last stop on the B train.  This establishment does not sell coffee or tea but there's a Dunkin Donuts right next door and a nice (but very small) coffee shop- French Press a few doors down.  The Creamery doesn't mind if you bring a drink into their shop.  Thanks in advance for your flexibility and patience and we find a suitable location for our group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, I would like to continue this group after June so we need to decide which books we'd like to read and discuss.  Please bring a list with you to the next meetup or post your suggested titles on the message board.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!  &lt;br /&gt;-Sabina&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sabina</member_name><member_id>1638720</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179860982000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Brookline Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brooklinereads</urlname><id>332113</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Brookline Book Club Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177877472000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Brookline Book Club May Meetup</name><id>5722399</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179687600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brooklinereads/events/5722399/</event_url></item>