<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Friend Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The North Star</name><city>Boston</city><id>6465492</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060905</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT INSTRUCTIONS:  This is a cross-listed event hosted exclusively by RED SOX NATIVES.  To attend this meeting, you must go to the Red Sox Natives MeetUp group, join and RSVP there.  There is a $10.00/per person charge for this event. Red Sox Natives people will be handling ALL payments.  Ticket to event will enter you into the 50-50 raffle. PLEASE SEE THE RED SOX LISTING FOR ALL INFO (same as below).  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/72774032/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/72774032/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to contact me if you have any questions, but all information is below.  Thanks! Isabel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===================================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's get ready for The 2012 New England Patriots Season with a 2012 RED SOX NATIVES EXCLUSIVE EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives organized weekly Patriots viewing parties last year with guests from several other invited groups attending. We had a blast with up to 80 people attending at various locations in Boston, Woburn and Wakefield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star will be our Primary Home for watching 2012 New England Patriots games (as well as hosting Trivingo).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will introduce you to The North Star with a RED SOX NATIVES EXCLUSIVE EVENT, a 2012 Patriots Season Kickoff Party on Friday, August 24 at 7:00pm to watch the Patriots take on the Tampa Bay Buccaneers in the third Pre-Season Game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff and The North Star has kindly reserved a large section of the venue for the Red Sox Natives. Come early by 7:00pm to get yourself a prime seat and enjoy some pre-game socializing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff will welcome you to The North Star with Cornhole to add to the Tailgate feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff at North Star will provide a spread of appetizers appropriate with the number of on-line Pre-Paid YES RSVPS. Pre-paid Event fee to reserve your space is $10.00. Ticket sales close 24 hours before the event. Tickets at the door are $10.00 per person, if available, and will not include entry into the 50-50 Raffle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives will announce our plans for the 2012 Patriots season. We have a couple of Special Guest Event Hosts lined up. Would you like to be a Guest Event Host for a future Game Watch? Are you ready for a SURPRISE or two this season?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets start with this Kickoff Party. Any Red Sox Native who buys a $10.00 ticket on-line in advance 24 Hours before the event will be eligible for the 50-50 Cash Raffle Prize as well. So RSVP, purchase your ticket, invite other fans, friends, guests, enjoy the food, learn about North Star and maybe you will take home some cash too! Great odds for a small party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game time is 7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Star is super conveniently located next to the TD Garden and on the Green and Orange Lines and Commuter Rail at North Station. The Red and Blue Lines are within a 10 minute walk and street parking is also available if you arrive early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is responsible for their own drinks. PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO AND TIP YOUR SERVER.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Sox Natives Team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTES:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On-Line ticket sales close 24 hours before the event ( at 7:00pm Thursday,August 23)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to be eligible for the 50-50 Raffle you must purchase your $10.00 ticket in advance and on line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no ticket refunds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$10.00 tickets purchased at the door are not eligible for the 50-50 raffle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$10.00 tickets may not be available at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any Native purchasing a ticket must have a recognizable face photo as their main profile photograph to be eligible for the 50-50 raffle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeff has reserved a large section for us. Ask the hostess to direct you to our sign-in table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345860950000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344368210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CROSSLISTED Patriots Season Kickoff &amp; Viewing Party - Patriots @ Tampa Bay</name><id>76742052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345849200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/76742052/</event_url></item>