<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join List Visual Arts Center Public Art Curator Patricia Fuller on a tour of MIT's public art collection. This walking tour focuses on notable sculpture and architecture on MIT's campus. Just as MIT pushes at the frontiers of scientific inquiry, it is the mission of the List Visual Arts Center to explore challenging, intellectually inquisitive, contemporary art making in all media.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The collections distinguish themselves from conventional museum holdings not only by the focus on contemporary art, but also by public visibility. The Institute itself has become the museum, with works of art sited either outdoors or in offices, lobbies, libraries, corridors, and conference rooms, thus becoming integrated into daily life and working situations of those affiliated with MIT and of MIT's many visitor populations-visiting scholars, students, parents, alumni, and friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://listart.mit.edu/node/468" target="_blank"&gt;http://listart.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT Public Art Tour&lt;br /&gt;Location: List Visual Arts Center Date: October 11, 2008 Time: 12:00 pm - 2:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;LVAC Public Art Curator Patricia Fuller will lead a tour of MIT's public art collection.  This walking tour focuses on notable sculpture and architecture on MIT's campus.   Group meets at the List Center, Wiesner Building, 20 Ames St.  Raindate for this tour is Sunday, October 12 at 12:00 PM.  Check the website for weather updates. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For More Info: &lt;br /&gt;617-253-4400&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223914289000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222398148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MIT public art tour</name><id>8836135</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223740800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/8836135/</event_url></item>