<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here's what's on the agenda for the April Meetup: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DOORS OPEN:&lt;/b&gt; 11 a.m. If you'd like to help set up -- and we can always use the help -- please arrive at 10:30 a.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LUNCH: &lt;/b&gt; Order will be called in at noon for delivery at 12:30-12:45 p.m. (To plan ahead, see &amp;quot;Ty's Pies&amp;quot; menu in the Files section; add 20 percent to the prices listed to cover your share of tax and tip). You're also welcome to bring your own lunch (microwave and fridge on site) or to step out between 12:30-1 to pick something up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THEMED CARD SWAP:&lt;/b&gt; 1 p.m.--deadline to receive cards; about 2 p.m.--packets redistributed among participants. To participate, see the instructions in the Messages section.&lt;br /&gt;Coordinator: Anne, with 1 add'l volunteer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MONTHLY CHALLENGE: &lt;/b&gt; 1 p.m.--deadline to receive contributed elements; by day's end--packets redistributed among participants. To participate, see instruction in the Messages section. Coordinator: Lori. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ARTISTS' PAPER/ATC BACKGROUND SWAP: &lt;/b&gt; Ongoing activity. To participate, see the instructions in the Messages section. Coordinator: Martha&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ENCORE ACTIVITIES: &lt;/b&gt; Several people told me how sorry they were to miss the demonstrations on making transfer images and using Shrinky-Dink (shrink plastic) images on ATCs. So we're repeating BOTH activities at the April Meetup. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About 1:30 p.m.--Transfers (Martha and others)&lt;br /&gt;About 2:30 p.m.--Shrinky-Dinks (Ellen) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OTHER ACTIVITIES: &lt;/b&gt; Please bring anything you'd like to put on display, share, swap or sell (we have tables for all those purposes). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CLEAN-UP: &lt;/b&gt; Begins 4:15 p.m. ; out the door by 4:45. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A FEW IMPORTANT REMINDERS:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVPs&lt;/b&gt;: As always, please RSVP soon even if your answer is &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot;--this helps greatly with planning. And remember, you can always update your RSVP as your plans change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; COSTS: &lt;/b&gt; Please plan to pay your $5 Meetup fee &lt;i&gt;in full at the event&lt;/i&gt; (you may also pay beforehand via PayPal). And if you're in on the group food order, please bring enough to cover your share of lunch plus tax and tip.  Please, no IOUs -- it's getting too hard to figure out who owes what after the fact. Also GREATLY appreciated: Small bills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks much. See you on Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a blonde with a black apron and a name tag--or just yell "Who's Anne?" Feel free to use our self-service check-in table to sign in, pick up a name tag and pay--then just find a seat and start making stuff.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210023646000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><why>This is a creative, lively and generous group that loves to share supplies, technique and information--and is always open to trying new things.</why><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202179019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April ATC+ Meetup in Wellesley</name><id>7265163</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209308400000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/7265163/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/f/d/global_2986349.jpeg</photo_url></item>