<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;**If the RSVP is full, please put yourself on the wait list, as I will be opening up more spots as the event date approaches**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We are excited to have our next night life event at Felt!  All members are welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Has the weather gotten you down?  Don't let winter get in the way of having a great time this Saturday night!  We are hitting up Felt, which has a great bar and dance scene, along with 2 floors of billiards.  &lt;b&gt;This will be a solid night for meeting people and getting your groove on!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8:30pm at the SECOND FLOOR BAR at Felt (533 Washington St).  &lt;b&gt;I encourage everyone to arrive early as the lines will get more crowded as the night progresses.&lt;/b&gt;  Please look for me to find the group.  We will head up to the 4th Floor dance area around 10pm to beat the lines.  Cover:  None for the bar area, but expect to pay $10 to get into the 4th floor dance area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. &lt;b&gt;For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please dress appropriately as this is an upscale venue.&lt;/b&gt;  If traveling by T, Boylston is the closest T stop on the green line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>11</waitlist_count><updated>1234482061000</updated><rating><average>4.44000005722</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>50</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233635871000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Night Life Mixer and Dancing at FELT, This Saturday, Feb. 7!</name><id>9660499</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234056600000</time><rsvp_limit>52</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/9660499/</event_url></item>