<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Law of Attraction, the basis by which the entire Universe operates, affects physical as well as non-physical experiences.  In essence, thought draws in other thoughts of a similar vibration, &lt;b&gt;and the same applies to what surrounds you from the moment you wake up until you say good night.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feng Shui&lt;/b&gt; is the art &amp;amp; science that concerns itself with what &amp;amp; how we interact with our environments...&lt;br /&gt;- to understand what we have attracted and &lt;br /&gt;- make the necessary adjustments &lt;br /&gt;so that we can &lt;b&gt;harmoniously vibrate with what we allow in our world and thus claim the life that we want.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that LOA is the core of six millennium of Feng Shui practice? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so... &lt;b&gt;Can Understanding and Changing Our Environments Attract Better Relationships?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JOIN US at our February meetup when we celebrate LoVE in ALL relationships, and hear &lt;b&gt;Lidia Scher, Feng Shui expert and BostonLOA member&lt;/b&gt; introduce us to the ancient Feng Shui principles, to help us analyze &amp;amp; revamp key areas of our homes...&lt;br /&gt;- to provide clarity, &lt;br /&gt;- align our thoughts with our desires &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;- allow the right relationships to enter &amp;amp; flourish in our lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prepare to allow meeting up with the special someone, &amp;amp;/or enhance your current relationships with yourself, your significant other, your family &amp;amp; your friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you very much, Lidia, for your gift of time, expertise and facilitation at our February meetup!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Lidia Scher&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Award-winning interior designer, sculptor and Feng Shui expert, Lidia Scher is a native of Argentina, who has earned a bachelor of fine arts degree in sculpture and architectural design, and holds a Master of Art degree from the Mass College of Art. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition she has studied professional level training in Feng Shui with Stephen Devine and Grandmaster Professor Lin Yun, and holds a certificate of Advanced Feng Shui Studies from Shanghai, China.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lidia is the recipient of numerous sculpture and interior design awards, is a much sought after speaker with teaching credentials from DeCordova Museum, the University of Lowell, and Newbury College, and has authored several articles on Feng Shui, art education and interior design. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lidia is the owner of LAS Associates, a 21 year old Arlington, MA based interior and architectural design practice specializing in dental/ medical design.  &lt;b&gt;www.lasassociates.net&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She is on sabbatical as the Program Director for the Boston School of Feng Shui.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lidia Scher</member_name><member_id>4022049</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202431195000</updated><rating><average>4.36000013351</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>62</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199880932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Law of Attraction February Meetup</name><id>7070372</id><headcount>61</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202256000000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/7070372/</event_url></item>