<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>350A High Hill Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.497585</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mountain Ridge</name><city>Walingford</city><id>5858682</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.751846</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice: Due to a low RSVP, time running short, and other events scheduled this day we've decided to cancel the Sunday event at this show and just do Saturday.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This a 250 table gun and knife show. We tried to get a table and were told "no political groups", but we are moving forward none-the-less. The show starts at 9am, the plan is to get there early and pamphlet the parked cars with Ron Paul's 2nd Amendment slim jim. This won't take long if we have enough people. I know some of us are planning on paying the $10 entrance fee so we can peruse the show in our Ron Paul gear and it should cover us if parking becomes an issue for some of our meetup members. The worst they can do is tell us to leave. Judging by satellite maps of the area, I'm not sure how a successful a sign-wave would be here - if we want to do an afternoon wave we might have to move out a mile or few to find a busy intersection. If we have a location we can sign wave (from around noon to 2pm) - and then hit the afternoon cars that have cycled in afterwards - the show runs till 5pm Saturday. If not maybe we grab some lunch and head back for an afternoon pamphlet drop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$1 Off coupon for those who wish to peruse the show:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://users.erols.com/fasttrack/library/all-coupon%20w-background.gif"&gt;http://users.erols.com/fasttrack/library/all-coupon%20w-background.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This also allows for two groups, an am and pm. Some will stay most of the day but if you can't make it in the am, you can still come up for the afternoon and participate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always please feel free to call &lt;strong&gt;860-730-3RON&lt;/strong&gt; to get in contact with us the day of and during the meetup if you've arrived but cannot locate us..&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334414284000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329872748000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wallingford Gun and Knife Show Saturday</name><id>53263532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334408400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/53263532/</event_url></item>