<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>157 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.306068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>O'Tooles Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>New Haven</city><id>3876912</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.923782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join Andrew playing Trivia on Wednesday at O'Toole's! You can text him at 508-524-9988 if you have any questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O'Tooles is an excellent establishment with great food and delicious beverages, holding Trivia every Wednesday Night! Come join the excitement as we take first place with your help! Or you can just come to hang out and drink some good Irish beer. Either way, please show up to Register at 8:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew will host this meetup, so look for him. You can text him at the number supplied above if you have trouble finding the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for Parking? &lt;br /&gt;

 Street - Orange, Court, and Chapel have metered street parking with some also on State and Elm an extra block over. (~$1.50/hr, until 9 PM... there is an 11pm rumor, however that has not yet been substantiated by the city in any way I can find online or in local signs.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garage -The Garage at 360 State Street is very close, enter down the ramp on State between Court and Chapel. If you pay close attention to how you are leaving then there is an exit directly out onto Pitkin Plaza, which O'Toole's borders on. Otherwise it's just around the other side of the block. (It's pricier, though I don't remember how much.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're up for a longer walk, some Yale lots in the area also go free after 5 pm.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text Andrew at 508-524-9988.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew</member_name><member_id>32462702</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359002898000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358558542000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivia at O'Toole's</name><id>qsdsffyrcbfc</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358989200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/100316112/</event_url></item>