<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>258 Thayer St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.828827</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Antonio's Pizza</name><city>Providence</city><id>489053</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.400734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Juan Williams from NPR is going to be speaking about &amp;quot;Election 2008&amp;quot; at the Central Congressional Church at 7 PM, and I was hoping maybe some of you would be interested in coming with me to hear him.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's meet up at Antonio's at 5:45ish&lt;/b&gt;, get dinner (they have fantastic and very unusual pizza there -- its menu features pizzas like avocado black bean, pesto tortellini, barbeque steak burrito...), and then &lt;b&gt;walk over to the church at about 6:45&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feel free to meet us for the lecture and not dinner, or vice versa.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is information about Juan Williams and the free lecture: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;National Public Radio's JUAN WILLIAMS will speak about &amp;quot;Election 2008&amp;quot; in the next Religion and Politics Lecture held at Central Congregational Church at 7 p.m., Thursday, January 31, 2008.  The church is located at 296 Angell Street in Providence , Rhode Island , at the corner of Cooke and Angell Streets.  The lecture is free and open to the community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Williams is senior correspondent for NPR's &amp;quot;Morning Edition&amp;quot; and the host of &amp;quot;America's Black Forum,&amp;quot; a nationally syndicated weekly news program.  He also is a featured political commentator for Fox News.  He is widely regarded as one of the nation's leading political writers.  For many years, he was an award-winning columnist for the Washington Post, and he also served as host for National Public Radio's &amp;quot;Talk of the Nation.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He is the author of six books, including Thurgood Marshall:  American Revolutionary; This Far by Faith:  Stories from the African-American Religious Experience; My Soul Looks Back in Wonder; A Tribute to Historically Black Colleges and Universities, and Eyes on the Prize:  America's Civil Rights Years, 1954-1965.   His most recent book, published by Crown Publishers in 2006, is entitled &amp;quot;Enough: The Phony Leaders, Dead-End Movements and Culture of Failure That Are Undermining Black America and What We Can Do About It.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll have a small, discreet "Meetup" sign at Antonio's. Also, when you RSVP, I'll email you my telephone number and you can give me a call if you can't find us. Antonio's is pretty small though, so it shouldn't be too difficult.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202008602000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201117246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pizza Dinner and "Election 2008" Lecture with NPR's Juan Williams</name><id>7180166</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201819500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/7180166/</event_url></item>