<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>269 Millway Road</address_2><address_1>Barnstable Harbor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02630</zip><lat>41.718259</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 362-6088 </phone><name>Hyannis Whale Watch</name><city>Barnstable</city><id>990592</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.309285</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since 1981, Hyannis Whale Watcher Cruises of Cape Cod has been offering whale watch adventures as a platform for conservation and education to people of all ages from around the world. Throughout your whale watching adventure, our expert naturalists will share an intriguing look into the &amp;quot;wonderful world of whales&amp;quot;. They will also provide commentary on the local ecology and history of this unique area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each whale watch cruise is approximately 3½ to 4 hours in duration and guided by our expert naturalists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For your comfort and optimum viewing, the Whale Watcher has two climate controlled interior cabins with cushioned seating and three exterior viewing decks. Located in the main cabin, the Galley offers a variety of hot &amp;amp; cold entrees, snacks, alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages. Feel free to bring your own snack/lunch! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each woman is responsible for paying for her own ticket. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are sold on a first come-first serve basis. It is possible to make a reservation, but only by emailing us at whales@whales.net. We will confirm by return email and then you will need to pay on your departure day at the ticket office. Tickets can only be purchased ahead when sailing on the same day. Be sure to print out our cruise coupon and present it at time of purchase. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Prices &lt;br /&gt;Adults $45.00 &lt;br /&gt;Seniors (62+) $40.00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet by the ticket office and get on board together. See you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barbara will be wearing her Girls Just Wanna Have Fun pin!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281377650000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277239334000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hyannis Whale Watch</name><id>13878823</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281270600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/13878823/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>