<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>99.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We will gather for a luscious live lunch served by Alchemy Cafe at noon (included in fee) followed by three informative talks by Dr. Clement from 12-5pm:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTER BY SEPT 19 and save $20 off the $99 fee! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“SUPPLEMENTS EXPOSED”-THE TRUTH THEY DON’T WANT YOU TO KNOW ABOUT VITAMINS, MINERALS, AND THEIR EFFECTS ON YOUR HEALTH- (Brian’s new book just came out in October).&lt;br /&gt;Brian Clement, PhD, NMD, CN, will reveal one of the most precarious misunderstandings of today. His objective is to shine a bright light on the importance of good nutrient intake and squelch the stereotypical belief that all nutrients are created equal. You will learn how these and many other cherished ideas we hold about nutrition are a dangerous collection of myths and half-truths based on adherence to a synthetic belief system that has led our culture far astray of nature’s promise and potential for bestowing health and healing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;LONGEVITY &amp;amp; VITALITY: CREATING A DISEASE-FREE FUTURE Dr. Clement will explore 50 years of clinical research and human experience on the subject of disease prevention and life extension. He will explain how each of us can lengthen our life span and increase the quality of our health and well-being. His clinical research as Director of Hippocrates Heath Institute offers him a private understanding of how all people can prevent pre-mature aging, disease, and resulting unhappiness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“ENJOYING LIFE WITHOUT LIMITS”: Brian will discuss foods for Optimum Energy, Achieving Vitality, and Natural Anti-Aging.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Brian Clement, Ph.D., L.N., N.M.D.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Brian Clement, Ph.D., N.M.D., L.N. has spearheaded the international progressive health movement for more than three and one-half decades.  By conducting daily clinical research as the director of the renowned Hippocrates Health Institute, the world’s foremost complementary residential health Mecca, he and his team have developed a state of the art program for health maintenance and recovery.  His Florida (U.S.A.) center has pioneered a program and established training in active aging and disease prevention.  With hundreds of thousands of people participating in this program over the last half century, volumes of data have been accrued giving Clement a privileged insight into the lifestyle required to prevent disease, enhance longevity, and maintain vitality and stamina.  Among Dr. Clement’s many contributions are “Living Foods for Optimum Health”, “Longevity”, and Lifeforce”, which Dr. Colin Campbell called “One of the most important books ever written on nutrition”. His latest book “Supplements Exposed”, will change America’s perceptions about nutritional supplementation. This landmark publication will expose the pharmaceutical fraud rampant globally in the sales, production, and distribution of worthless and harmful vitamin pills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Clement is first and foremost a devoted husband and a caring father of four.  In addition to daily counseling and research studies, Clement conducts conferences worldwide on attaining health and creating longevity giving humanity a roadmap for redirecting, enriching, and extending their lives. Dr. Clement is a licensed Nutritionist. He graduated from the University of Science, Arts, and Technology where he earned his Ph.D and N.M.D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285434974000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282882807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop Intensive with Brian Clement from Hippocrates</name><id>14558834</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285430400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/14558834/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/4/global_17491044.jpeg</photo_url></item>