<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Temple Pl</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.355240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 542-8111</phone><name>MANTRA</name><city>Boston</city><id>668995</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>THE PRE-EVENT IS A FREE EVENT AND WILL LEAD INTO MAIN EVENT!!! BiotechTuesday, Boston's premier networking event for biotech professionals, is having a special Pre-Event this month from 5:30PM to 7PM before our main networking event. This event will focus on cultivating leadership skills and other career building activities with a panel discussion, breakout sessions, and networking. Take this opportunity to learn how to best position yourself for career advancement. Topic: How to Build Leadership Skills to Move Your Career Forward Registration: &lt;a href="http://www.acteva.com/booking.cfm?bevaid=220868" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.acteva.com...&lt;/a&gt; A moderated panel discussion with Q&amp;amp;A: Jill Dietz, Director of Human Resources, Merck Nancy Kohl, Head of Research, Center for Novel Experimental Therapeutics, Dana Farber Jocelyn Dunphy, Adjunct Faculty, Graduate Programs in Biopharmaceutical Leadership, Emmanuel College Following the panel discussion, you can attend one of the following breakout sessions for additional dialogue and Q&amp;amp;A: 1.Key leadership skills and how to get your employer to help you obtain them- Jill Dietz 2.When and how to position yourself for a promotion/career transition- Jocelyn Dunphy and Nancy Kohl 3.Overview of Emmanuel College Biopharmaceutical Programs- Marjorie Bell and Jay Coggeshall 4.Managing the competing demands of work, education, and social life- TBD 5.How to use mentorships as a career development tool- Lauren Celano, Propel Careers Please select which panel you wish to attend from the pull down list below. Schedule of activities: 5:30PM - 6:00PM Check-in and Networking 6:00PM - 6:30PM Discussion Panel 6:40PM - 7:00PM Breakout Sessions 7:00PM - 7:15PM Emmanuel College Presentation and Raffle This pre-event is sponsored by Emmanuell College Graduate Programs in Biopharmaceutical Leadership. There will be complementary hot appetizers for this Pre-Event. There is also validated parking offered at the Lafayette garage located under the Hyatt hotel right around the corner from Mantra. It is a flat rate of $10 after 5pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308702075000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308527000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Biotech Tuesday Pre-Event and Main Event</name><id>22778141</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308697200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/22778141/</event_url></item>