<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;What Makes a Life Significant?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(William James panel discussion)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little over a century ago, the Harvard psychologist and philosopher William James gave a public lecture entitled “What Makes a Life Significant?&amp;quot; In honor of the hundredth anniversary of his death and to celebrate his enduring influence, we have invited a panel of distinguished scholars to revisit the question posed in that lecture from a mix of disciplinary perspectives. What do we, in the 21st century, think &amp;quot;makes a life significant&amp;quot;? What can the academy contribute to an exploration of that question? Jim Kloppenberg (Warren Professor of American History) will introduce and moderate a star-studded panel that includes philosopher Sissela Bok (Senior Visiting Fellow, Harvard Center for Population and Development Studies), Luke Menand (Bass Professor of English), and Cornel West (Class of 1943 University Professor at Princeton). The panel will begin at 6:00 pm, but we invite you to join us at 5:00 pm for a reception and an opportunity to view an exhibit of rare materials belonging to James from Harvard's archive and collection of historical scientific instruments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is free and open to the public, but seating is limited and on a first-come, first-served basis.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Event &lt;br /&gt;Date: April 26, 2010 &lt;br /&gt;Time: 5:00 pm - 7:30 pm &lt;br /&gt;Location: CGIS South Building, 1730 Cambridge St., Tsai Auditorium (Room S010) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The panel discussion will be recorded and archived on the website (&lt;a href="http://socialscience.fas.harvard.edu/)" target="_blank"&gt;http://socialscience....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link: &lt;a href="http://www.wcfia.harvard.edu/node/5701" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wcfia.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272489239000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272123408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What Makes a Life Significant? (William James)</name><id>13276956</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272315600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/13276956/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/7/global_6176535.jpeg</photo_url></item>