<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Market Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.811623</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Firehouse Center for the Arts</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>7989882</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.869919</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;ARTWALK Newburyport is a self-paced / self-guided tour of several galleries and studios throughout downtown-and beyond Newburyport. They open their doors 3:00 pm - 7:00 pm with special exhibits, discussions, painting demos, live music, refreshments, and more- all in a casual reception environment. Maps can be found online @ &lt;a href="http://www.artwalknewburyport.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.artwalknewburyport.org/&lt;/a&gt; or at the visitor's center when you arrive. This event is FREE. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

A quote from someone that has attended in the past years; “ARTWALK has always been great! Some of the galleries go all out with refreshments, entertainment, and appetizers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be advised that this is a walking tour and we will be doing a lot of that. There is no set plan when finished with the tour- perhaps; Waterfront Park, the new self-serve ice cream parlor, the quaint lounges and restaurants, a walk along the water with some new friends, or take the 10 min drive to Plum Island and enjoy the beautiful sunset from the beach (whoooo).....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS IS A SHARED EVENT with other meetup groups. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

* WE WILL MEETUP  between 3:00 and 3:15 pm In front of The Firehouse Center For The Arts. If facing the center, the bench to the left- by the shady tree, myself or someone will be wearing a meetup.com pin or have a sign. MY CONTACT # IS: 978.289.7679 after 1PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; **Parking can be tight - so try to plan accordingly. Please consider carpooling with other members. It’s a great way to get to know someone new or travel with a friend. Just post your comments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will all meetup on a bench outside The Fire House Center- more details are in event description</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350824843000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346883921000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ARTWALK NEWBURYPORT- Last Of The Season</name><id>81024302</id><headcount>37</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350759600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/81024302/</event_url></item>