<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>46 Columbia Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02339</zip><lat>42.106266</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cafe Eleganza</name><city>Pembroke</city><id>1613797</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.806885</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;An Italian restaurant. A strip mall. Sounds promising, no?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you answer, let us give you a hint: This is a case where the cover &amp;ne; the book! Once you're inside Cafe Eleganza in Pembroke, you can see that the &lt;em&gt;Eleganza&lt;/em&gt; in the name is not just an affectation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and the food... Well, have a look at the &lt;a href="http://www.cafeeleganza.com/Restaurant%20Menu.htm"&gt;online menu&lt;/a&gt; and consider that this restaurant is an easy drive from some other Italian places - it's a stone's throw from the much-hyped Orta - and has been holding its own against them for more than a few years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How it's been able to do so is a question best answered with fork in hand, and that's just what we plan to do on Thursday, April 28th at 7:00 pm. Please join us around the table for a touch of &lt;em&gt;Eleganza&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cafe Eleganza&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;Columbia Park&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; 46 Columbia Rd (Route 53) &lt;br /&gt; Pembroke, MA 02359 &lt;br /&gt; (781) 826-0700&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.trattoriasanpietro.com/index.html"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cafeeleganza.com/"&gt;Cafe Eleganza&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer:&lt;/strong&gt; Mike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. Two per member allowed. For questions about exceptions, please contact Mike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price Range:&lt;/strong&gt; Many dishes are offered in more than one size in order to fit various appetites and budgets. Quite a few dishes are $15.99 or under, with dishes over $20.00 being rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Annual Members - None, Group Members - $2.00, Guests - $2.00; $12 to become a 2011 Annual Member&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over four years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Wednesday, April 27th 29th @ 7:00 pm. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer. Changes to "No" after the deadline will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Cafe Eleganza (and its sister takeout business, Pasta Eleganza) is located on Columbia Rd (Route 53) in Pembroke, just alittle south of the Hanover - Pembroke line. The restaurant sits in a strip mall called Columbia Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304206584000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Quite awhile ago, this restaurant was not the top finisher in a poll, but it did draw the interest of several members after Mike suggested it. Here's to second chances.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303185721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Touch of Eleganza!</name><id>17355596</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304031600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/17355596/</event_url></item>