<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Afterwork Mixer this Thursday June 28th at Rattlesnake on the Roof! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For young professionals alike in the heart of Boston's Back Bay neighborhood 6:30-9:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4th of July weekend  is approching, while many of us will be traveling this weekend and some staying around the city, there is still time to come and hang with the Boston Nightlife Group as we kick off the weekend in style! This time we are taking the party to Rattlesnake Bar  a premier afterwork hotspot among the Boston nightlife scene. Rattlesnake is one of my favorite outdoor venues in the city, last years event at Rattlesnake was a blast, I'm sure this Thurs will be the same!  Better yet the weather is looking to be around  75 degrees which is  a nice cool down from the 90 degree weather approaching Tues and Wed.  So come and join the group for a few cocktails as we kickoff the start to a wonderful holiday weekend! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also if you have not been to any or a few of our events whether an Afterwork Mixer, New Member meetup, or even a nite on the town in the city with the group, I encourage all of you to come this Thursday and meet many of our wonderful members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Details: We will meet on the roofdeck (hence the title) near the bar area. Please look for me upon arriving my picture is on the left hand side of the website under the Assistant Organizer section. I HIGHLY RECOMMEND coming early as possible, with a holiday weekend approaching,  this venue is guaranteed to fill up fast!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also my phone is 617-671-5310. Please make note prior to arriving. Look forward to seeing you all there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation &lt;br /&gt;Green Line to Arlington&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line to Back Bay station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Show full description&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183242738000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182742332000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Party on the Roofdeck!!    Afterwork Mixer 4th of July Kickoff Party!</name><id>5931935</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183069800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/5931935/</event_url></item>