<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2935 Main Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06033</zip><lat>41.723628</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-657-4527</phone><name>TANGO RESTAURANT</name><city>Glastonbury</city><id>831704</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.614992</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>MARK YOUR SOCIAL CALENDER, UPDATE YOUR BLACKBERRY               &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       CALENDER SECTION WITH THE DATE BELOW.   THURSDAY JANUARY     28.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  LAST THURSDAY OF THE MONTH HAPPY HOUR &lt;br /&gt;  WITH   THE IRA!                               &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;TANGO THURSDAY ( How cool is this?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Important Question:  What was the last time you did the Tango??  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, now you have the chance. When you ask? See Details Below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:  JANUARY 28. Thursday Night.  4:30 PM  to ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Tango (But, of Course) 2935 Main Street, Glastonbury, CT 06033. 860-657-4527. (Very easy to find, so please do not panic) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                               DETAILS/SMALL PRINT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Simply Stated - Tango is AWESOME, FRIENDLY, FUNKY, GREAT FOOD AND AND  MOUTH-WATERING  COCKTAILS. HAPPY HOUR SPECIALS ROCK THE HOUSE!!!!  (And it is not EXPENSIVE)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SEE:  WWW: CTTANGO.COM FOR PICTURES AND DESCRIPTION.  The Web Site has Color and Flash!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; DRINK SPECIALS: For happy hour are $2 bud light drafts, $3 amstel light and Sam  Adams seasonal draft beer, $4 white and red wine, $5 red and white sangria, $5 Smirnoff drinks, $ 5 House Martinis.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD SPECIALS:  Buy One item from the Tapas menu and Get One FREE. Yes, Free!!!!  I was there this past Monday, and the Tapas were delicious and plentiful.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Above Specials are till 7:00PM. We will have our own area in the Funky Bar Reserved for The Ira’s Singles Group.  We can stay as late as we want!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R.S.V.P:  Please let me know if you are joining on or before January 27, Wednesday  so I may keep the Restaurant informed how many Happy Hour Playful folks are joining. If you say yes, please do come, if you change your mind, please let me know. This is only fair to me and the Restaurant. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R.S.V.P:  Mistrchrming@aol.com. Subject Line, Tango Happy Hour. Questions:  Ira- 860-604-5792. ( A $1.00 suggested donation for Meet Up-More is okay as well. LOL)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND FOR CURIOUS MINDS, WHAT IS EXACTLY IS A TANGO, YOU ASK? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tango is a style of syncopated ballroom dance music in 2/4 or 4/4 time that originated among European immigrant populations of Argentina and Uruguay (collectively, the &amp;quot;Rioplatenses&amp;quot;). It is traditionally played by a sextet, known as the orquesta típica, which includes two violins, piano, doublebass, and two bandoneons. Earlier forms of this ensemble sometimes included flute, clarinet and guitar. Tango music may be purely instrumental or may include a vocalist. Tango music is well-known across much of the world, along with the associated tango dance.&lt;br /&gt;The most famous and recognizable tango song is the La Cumparsita tango by Uruguayan Gerardo Matos Rodriguez&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the back of Bar Area. Will be a Singles Event Sign </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1265244810000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263567284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira's TANGO Happy Hour Thursday  January 28. </name><id>12327522</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264716000000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12327522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/9/global_12631161.jpeg</photo_url></item>