<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This joint presentation of Boston Area Philosophy  Discussions and the &lt;a href="http://buddhism.meetup.com/625/"&gt;Eastern  Philosophy Group&lt;/a&gt; is&amp;nbsp; a repeat appearance of a meeting we had back on January 10, 2010. Like many topics in philosophy, the questions relating to the nature of Self and Other are endless, and inquirers are rewarded more deeply with each return.&amp;nbsp; This is the nature of philosophy! There will be an introductory talk of ten to  fifteen minutes and then we will launch into the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concepts of the self and its denial or abnegation are central in both Eastern and Western philosophy. We will engage in a comparative discussion of some of the major perspectives in both traditions. Schopenhauer and Nietzsche were influenced by Vedic philosophy, and Nietzsche&amp;rsquo;s rejection of absolute dualisms, if it was not actually inspired by Lao-tzu is in important respects complementary. Indeed, the dualism of Self and Other--perhaps the most basic of all dualisms--is arguable. Are Self/Other and Self/Selflessness illusory distinctions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key issues will be broadly considered and could range from Ayn Rand&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;virtue of selfishness&amp;rdquo; to Buddhism&amp;rsquo;s transcendence of the self. What is the basis of morality? Ego and selflessness may both play a role. What do you think? Here is a special question that I would like to pose for this meeting:&amp;nbsp; "Is selfless self-interest possible?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concept of reincarnation, which is pervasive in Eastern religious and philosophical traditions but also common in the Western traditions may have important implications for our discussion. What is the relationship between soul and self? And what are the ethical implications of beliefs concerning the existence or nonexistence of the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eastern and Western philosophers and philosophy aficionados of all persuasions are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt; (Green Tea Restaurant)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lizbeth</member_name><member_id>8197391</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1308613770000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304200415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Self and Selfless: East/West Perspectives</name><id>17492995</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306537200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/17492995/</event_url></item>