<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At our October meetup, Marilou Seavey, Master Trainer of NLP (www.mindbridgetraining.com) set the framework of turbo-charging the Law Of Attraction with NLP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During our November meetup, Tom Maloney, BostonLOA member &amp;amp; Essential Mind Power Trainer, will facilitate a more in-depth discussion of how we can use an NLP-based questionnaire powerfully to springboard us to develop a more well-formed outcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A well-formed outcome allows you to ...&lt;br /&gt;** align your core beliefs with your true desires,&lt;br /&gt;** propel towards manifesting what you really want&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us, plan on being actively engaged in learning and using the questionnaire &amp;amp; other NLP-related exercises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you very much, Tom, for your gift of time and facilitation at our November meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Tom Maloney:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom has been actively pursuing the study of the power of the mind since 1973 when he took his first Silva Mind Power class. He is a Master NLP Practitioner, NLP Coach and Essential Mind Power Trainer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to contact Tom: TAAM2@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NLP (Neuro Linguistic Programming) is the science of studying success, &amp;amp; then &amp;quot;reprogramming&amp;quot; the software of your mind to produce immediate &amp;amp; positive change in all areas of your life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Combining the thinking of LOA with NLP skills offers you powerful &amp;amp; practical tools available for changing limiting beliefs, behaviors, &amp;amp; for achieving rapid results in your personal, professional &amp;amp; spiritual development.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194662981000</updated><rating><average>4.30000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>48</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191369916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AGENDA for BostonLOA November 6th Meetup</name><id>6474548</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194393600000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/6474548/</event_url></item>