<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Rowe Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.615200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-283-6776</phone><name>Cruiseport Gloucester</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1225971</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.654700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Empty Bowl Dinner 2010 &lt;br /&gt;Cruiseport Gloucester &lt;br /&gt;6 Rowe Square &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, May 13 &lt;br /&gt;4 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an evening of food and hospitality. Park your car at Good Harbor Beach and enjoy a complimentary trolley car ride along the backshore to the event site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a minimum donation of $12 you may choose a handmade bowl crafted by artisans from the community, and fill it with delicious soup. The meal is simple;soup, bread and a cookie, but the message goes home with your bowl as a reminder that somewhere someone's bowl is always empty. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Empty Bowl Dinner raises both hunger awareness and money to support our services to these families, which include an after-school snack program, a Summer Food Service Program, and Food Stamp application assistance, as well as our hot meals and free groceries at The Cape Ann Food Pantry. This year we are using proceeds from the event to support our summer lunch programs and Mobile markets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at Good Harbor Beach parking lot (free parking), Thatcher Road, Gloucester (in front of the entrance to the Snack Bar building) and taking the free trolley to the event.  Please include in your RSVP whether you will be meeting us at Good Harbor Beach parking lot or at the event location.  We will only wait 15 minutes after the meeting time prior to leaving for the event, if you are meeting us at Good Harbor lot and are running late, please call the meetup phone at 978-304-2811.  Note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Vicki&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Good Harbor Beach parking lot (Thatcher Road, Gloucester), in front of the snack bar building entrance, and we'll go to the Cruiseport by Trolley</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vicki</member_name><member_id>4058114</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273846041000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270512428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Empty Bowl Dinner</name><id>13097090</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273785300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/13097090/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>