<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The next meeting of the Greater Boston Stop the Wars Coalition will be on&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, April 6 at 6:30 PM at&lt;br /&gt;Encuentro 5&lt;br /&gt;33 Harrison Avenue, 5th Floor&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;(Chinatown Stop on the Orange Line T and Boylston Stop on the Green Line T)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming out of the marches on the Pentagon and on Wall Street we have some important opportunities to carry the antiwar campaign forward in the next period. On July 10-12, the National Assembly to End the Iraq and Afghanistan Wars and Occupations will be held in Pittsburgh, PA and we need to begin discussing what proposals we would like to bring there. In the weeks ahead we also need to have a discussion of our overall strategy and tactics moving forward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next meeting of the New England United regional antiwar network will be held next Saturday, April 11 in Hartford, CT. where we will all have the opportunity to discuss collaboration region-wide. Conferences in Boston and Connecticut will be held in 3 weeks and we are also looking forward to May Day which is being organized in Everett this year.  With less than 3 months into the Obama Administration, folks in Massachusetts are already organizing a petition campaign to Bring the National Guard Home. We also need to take a look at our finances and consider the possibility of doing a fundraiser. All are welcome to this meeting and we are looking forward to your participation.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Schaich</member_name><member_id>4406518</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Harris</member_name><member_id>5188497</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suren Moodliar</member_name><member_id>5714882</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239453306000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People for Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>stopthewars</urlname><id>708558</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Antiwar</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236038706000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Antiwar Meetup</name><id>9864580</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239057000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/stopthewars/events/9864580/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/b/global_6761595.jpeg</photo_url></item>