<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update: Make like the original Dawn of the Dead&lt;/b&gt; T.J. Maher will be in the Prudential Center Food Court at 111 Huntington Ave, in Boston, MA. &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/food-court-at-the-prudential-center-boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; starting at 1:00 pm, sitting in the back near the patio entrance. He'll reserve some tables with table tents. Feel free to drop by anytime from 1:00 pm to 2:30 pm to socialize, eat, or use the public restrooms to put on your costumes. At 2:30 pm we can all shamble through the Prudential Center itself in a circuitous route, following that with a screening of &lt;b&gt;Zombieland&lt;/b&gt; at AMC Loews Boston Common.( &lt;b&gt;See the Details&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/boards/thread/7879530/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; ] ) since it will be too cold, too wet, or both. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't wanna dress up, but wanna participate?&lt;/b&gt; Heck, make a protest sign saying &amp;quot;Zombies are people, too!&amp;quot; I'm sure that should be fine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Upcoming.com:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://upcoming.yahoo.com/event/4233568/"&gt;http://upcoming.yahoo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston Zombie Walk 2009&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Saturday October 17, 2009 at 3:00pm &lt;br /&gt;Copley Plaza, Bolyston St&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join Boston Masquerade and several local zombie march groups for a shambling good time in downtown Boston! We'll meet up at Copley Square around 3 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tell all your undead friends, this event is free and open to everyone!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... This looks like fun! I've always wanted to participate in a Zombie March, but who is Boston Masquerade?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Boston Masquerade:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonmasquerade.com/about.html"&gt;http://bostonmasquera...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Boston Masquerade is a not-for-profit group that presents fun, free events in the Boston area. It was founded by local members of Anonymous, an online group opposed to the illegal and abusive practices of the Church of Scientology. All events are open to the public. Contact us by email to find out about how you can help contribute ideas, talents, materials and help us cover our expenses to keep the free entertainment rolling! [...] To find out more about our founders, visit whyweprotest.net &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Um... can't you be a zombie for being a zombie's sake? Eh, they also seem to have fun simply holding a pleasant Pirate Picnic on George's Island, and a free Masquerade Ball back in May ... maybe this will just be your normal everyday apolitical zombie march? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;But what is a Zombie March?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zombie_walk"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A zombie walk (also known as a zombie mob, zombie march, zombie horde, zombie lurch, zombie shamble, zombie shuffle or zombie pub crawl) is an organized public gathering of people who dress up in zombie costumes. Usually taking place in an urban centre, the participants make their way around the city streets and through shopping malls in a somewhat orderly fashion and often limping their way towards a local cemetery or other public space (a series of taverns in the case of a zombie pub crawl).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Promoted primarily through word of mouth and online message boards, zombie walks are an underground activity. During the event participants are encouraged to remain in character as zombies and to communicate only in a manner consistent with zombie behavior. This may include grunting, groaning and slurred, moaning calls for 'brains'. It should be noted that zombie behavior is a hot topic of debate. Purists who draw their definitions from the original Living Dead films will claim that a zombie would never have the ability to call for 'brains' and furthermore that a zombie needs only living or freshly killed flesh for its sustenance, and not the brain in particular&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... ah! The next Great Schism! The eternal struggle between fast and slow zombies. When will the madness end? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear your best zombie outfit (makeup, old clothes that look torn, that you don't mind getting fake blood on) and meet up by 2:30 pm at the Prudential Center Food Court. At 2:30 pm we can shamble as a group to Copley Square. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with blue eyes, short brown hair, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is Lunch&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to a black messenger bag. T.J. Maher will getting there by 1:00 pm. Feel free to stop by, socialize, grab lunch, then use the public restrooms to put on your costume. We can start shambling at 2:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information, from Crawl of the Dead.Com&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.crawlofthedead.com/crawls/info/boston_zombie_walk_2009"&gt;http://www.crawlofthe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our shambling horde will be assembling at Copley Plaza in downtown Boston around 3pm on the third Saturday in October. Bring a friend, bring some fake blood, and bring the BRAIIIIIIIIIIINS! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This zombie event is being organized by Boston Masquerade in association with other zombie groups in the Boston area. We hope to make this an epic march that people will be talking about for years to come. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;To keep everything shiny with our friends at the BPD, we ask that everyone stick to a few simple rules: &lt;br /&gt;*&amp;quot;No boozing &lt;br /&gt;*&amp;quot;No weapons, fake or otherwise &lt;br /&gt;*&amp;quot;Don’t be a [jerk] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If you have questions as to whether something is [jerk]ery, it probably is. If you feel that someone in the march is engaging in [jerk]ery, please talk to one of the organizers&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... on this site you can register your zombie, or get ideas about costuming. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note&lt;/b&gt;... Nerd Fun isn't &lt;i&gt;hosting&lt;/i&gt; the party. We are just &lt;i&gt;crashing&lt;/i&gt; the party. It's open to all, right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Zombie Anti-Defemation League&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Consciousness Raising for a Post Vital Existence&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://zadl.org/faq/"&gt;http://zadl.org/faq/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(From the FAQ. Go to the site to &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What is a Zombie?&lt;/i&gt; – Loosely speaking, a Zombie is anyone who woke up after dying. Basically Zombies are animated corpses of formerly living people, who now have the whole of their Death awaiting them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;How many Zombies are there&lt;/i&gt;? – More than you think. As of this writing, every second there are five people being born and two dying. In a 24 hour period that means 172,800 Deathstyle Choices every day!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Are Zombies dangerous&lt;/i&gt;? – No, no, no, no, no! Well, maybe. If vexed. Are the living dangerous?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Do Zombies eat brains&lt;/i&gt;? – Rarely, and then only on special occasions and some holidays. (Dios de Los Muertos and Ascension Thursday).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What is a “deathstyle crisis&lt;/i&gt;?” – It is the moment of waking up after death and wondering what next? For some, the answer is to move on to a spiritual plane, or “Heaven” and for others, the answer is a bit more practical. Many Zombies report that at the moment of their death they were involved in what they felt to be very important task that couldn’t be left to anyone else (at least that’s how it seemed at the time). The question is rarely religious in nature (Zombies appear to come from all faiths equally), but may arise due to one’s own sense of spiritual development.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What is a “deathstyle choice&lt;/i&gt;?” – How one chooses to face the rest of his or her death. “Will I become a mindless brain eating machine, or a productive member of society? How will I do this? Who will love me?” Zombies initially tend to wrestle with the opportunities available, and in more vitalist communities are often forced to eek a meager living haunting abandoned buildings, sewers and the like. It is to be hoped that as Zombie Awareness grows that fewer and fewer communities will force their Zombie populations underground, and will instead lend support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;What is Vitalism&lt;/i&gt;? – Vitalism is the prejudiced belief that life accounts for differences in character or ability based on living, and that a living state is superior to other states. It is discrimination or prejudice based on life. Misrepresenting the superiority of life to un-life has been so ingrained in societies around the world that most are totally unaware that this is a shameful condition, and blithely go about their daily routines unthinkingly insulting and oppressing the dead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Do I know any Zombies&lt;/i&gt;? – Do you? You may! Many Zombies have found refuge in Police forces and other thankless but essential jobs. Postmen, Garbage men, delivery services, gas station clerks, all night coffee shop servers, lawyers, and script-writers often find themselves in the company of Zombie coworkers, though they may not realize it. There are Zombie doctors, nurses, and other staff members on call at many of the major hospitals around the nation. Much of the nation’s overland freight is hauled by Zombies. State BMVs and the TSA are both very common Zombie employers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;When having a Zombie over for tea, is there anything I can serve to make him / her feel more at home?&lt;/i&gt; – Considering how rarely Zombies actually get invited anywhere, let alone someone’s house, we feel that you should congratulate yourself on overcoming vitalism! Topics of conversations should steer away from obviously vitalist interests and beauty products. Sports is always safe, as long as you avoid saying things like “The Celtics really killed the Knicks last night!” Blame any smell on the cat. It may do well to have a spare brain tucked discretely away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;If I date a Zombie, are there any extra precautions I should take&lt;/i&gt;? – Flowers are appreciated, but Lilies are right out, unless your lover has a good sense of humor. A very good sense of humor. Despite what some films may have led you to expect, pregnancy is not an issue, but a condom is suggested on principle. You may want to gently suggest a little “role play” to your lover, and propose the use of [CENSORED]&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>26</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256171188000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252445664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Zombie Walk 2009 (Copley Square) @ Boston Masquarade</name><id>11321554</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255804200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11321554/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/4/1/global_11248417.jpeg</photo_url></item>