<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Stanhope St. (in the alley behind Mistrale between Clarendon and Berkely and Columbus)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.344284</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brahmin</name><city>Boston</city><id>4211172</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077263</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Social Sundays is back for a Valentine's Edition. The brunch party will be party 3 of the Cupid Challenge taking place all weekend. More info here: &lt;a href="http://crawlinboston.com/2012/01/21/cupid-2/" target="_blank"&gt;http://crawlinboston....&lt;/a&gt; Please wear red, pink or black. Check out the pictures here from some of our past events &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/socializeinboston/SocialSunday3" target="_blank"&gt;https://picasaweb.goo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/socializeinboston/SocialSunday2" target="_blank"&gt;https://picasaweb.goo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/socializeinboston/SocialSunday1" target="_blank"&gt;https://picasaweb.goo...&lt;/a&gt; The mimosas and screwdrivers quickly turned to shots which quickly turned to dancing. Guests will be enticed by a delicious brunch menu as DJ Chris Roxx spins an infectious playlist. The lights will be dimmed, the shades will be closed, corks will be popping and we&amp;#146;ll be featuring $3 screwdrivers as well as a fresh brunch food menu. &lt;a href="http://crawlinboston.com/social-sunday/social-sunday-menu/" target="_blank"&gt;http://crawlinboston....&lt;/a&gt; Tired of the same old, same old brunch scene in Boston? We&amp;#146;re flipping the switch and keeping the weekend going on Sunday. This brunch is not for the conservative or the weary. No kids, no chores, no errands, no laundry&amp;#133;come ready to party, forget about real life for the afternoon. Grab your friends and check out Boston&amp;#146;s new hot scene as the weather gets cold. This is a truly unique experience where dancing on tables is encouraged. Come on down and see us. Reservations not required but encouraged. We've sold out our tables for the past 2 brunches. Please call 617-723-3131 to make yours&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329070121000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328400541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valentine's Brunch - Bar Crawl After Party</name><id>51060002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329064200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/51060002/</event_url></item>