<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come up and spend the weekend at the Wedeln Ski House in New Hampshire!  New Guest Intro Weekend has a special discount rate of only $10 a night - Yes you heard right, only $20 total for the 2 night stay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This weekend is an ideal time to check out the club for future mid-winter visits or even club membership. Friday night will be a casual BYOB around the bar at the Wedeln house. Saturday day will be a mixture of hiking, shopping and other options. If there is enough snow we may ski/snowboard instead. In the afternoon and evening there will be special events planned at other local ski clubs - more details on that if you sign up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most rooms have 2 bunk beds and are segregated by sex. If you are coming up with a friend of the same sex just let me know and we will try to put you in the same room. please bring your own sheet, blanket, pillows, towels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year we had about 20 guests come up for this weekend with about 15 regular members also staying at the house. The weekend was not just an introduction to the house but created friendships that lasted the rest of the season (well not just the season, we will still like you when the snow melts).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to invite friends but please have them sign up on the meetup as well. Max capacity is 78 and we will not sell out. Lets make this weekend a kick-off to the ski season!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update this event with additional details (dinner, breakfast options) as we get closer to the date. Email me if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;21+ only, sorry no kids.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>House will be open by Friday at 6pm - just introduce yourself.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259587592000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Adventurerists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak</urlname><id>1297030</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Ski, Snowboard, and Outdoor Adventurers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257523987000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Intro Weekend at Wedeln SkiHouse</name><id>11811869</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259370000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-adventurers-ski-snowboard-kayak/events/11811869/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/9/global_11667001.jpeg</photo_url></item>