<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Get involved with Living Forgotten Realms, the first RPGA campaign for Dungeons and Dragons 4th Edition! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Module: ADAP 1-1 - Barrow of the Ogre King&lt;br /&gt;DMs: Matt Maranda &amp;amp; Jerry Castaldo&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mustering starts at 6 PM, Game starts no later than 6:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For many years, goblins have laired in a nearby dungeon hidden in the boughs of the Southwood. This dungeon is known to some as the Barrow of the Ogre King. Recently, the goblins have become bold enough to leave their dungeon home to raid the nearby town of Loudwater. It is up to your newly-formed band of adventurers to deal with the threat the goblins pose and discover why they’ve attacked the town. An adventure set in Loudwater for characters levels 1-2. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 12 players. If you want to reserve a space, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.warhorn.net/BostonLFR/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.warhorn.ne...&lt;/a&gt; and click on Register to Attend. Walk-ins are welcome, in case a player doesn't show up, but we can't guarantee you a space unless you sign up and receive a confirmation. RSVPing on Meetup.com does not hold a space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must bring a character created using the guidelines provided by Wizards of the Coast. You can find these at &lt;a href="http://www.wizards.com/default.asp?x=dnd/lfrx/characters" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wizards.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223744592000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220677774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Living Forgotten Realms @ Pandemonium</name><id>8700307</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221602400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/8700307/</event_url></item>