<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Live from Theatre Royal Plymouth, we are pleased to present a Complicite co-production of the Olivier Award-winning play &lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;A DISAPPEARING NUMBER&lt;/span&gt;, directed by Simon McBurney.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A thrilling, thrilling, thrilling play” — David Finkel, Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Quietly mesmerizing…lucid, dynamic and continuously engaging” — Charles Isherwood, New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Technically dazzling and beautifully staged” — Frank Scheck, New York Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A DISAPPEARING NUMBER weaves together the story of two love affairs, separated by a century and a continent. The first happens now; the second is set in 1914. It tells of the heartbreaking collaboration between the greatest natural mathematician of the 20th century, Srinivasa Ramanujan, a penniless Brahmin from Madras in South India, and his British counterpart, the brilliant Cambridge don GH Hardy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a haunting original score by Nitin Sawhney, this piece of startling visual poetry from Simon McBurney and Complicite is a compelling meditation on love, mathematics and the pain of exile in an age when we think we can belong anywhere and have everything. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;National Theatre Live (NT Live) is a groundbreaking initiative to broadcast the best of British theatre to cinemas around the world. The first season of events, which began in June 2009 with the acclaimed production of Phèdre starring Helen Mirren, was seen by over 165,000 people on 320 screens in 22 countries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We couldn't have foreseen that the experimental National Theatre Live season would be such a hit with audiences around the world, who are hungry to see our work in their local cinema&amp;quot;, says Nicholas Hytner, Director of the National Theatre. &amp;quot;We're delighted that we can confidently build on its success with a second season of broadcasts.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other exciting productions include HAMLET, directed by Nicholas Hytner; a Donmar warehouse production of KING LEAR, starring Derek Jacobi; and FRANKENSTEIN, directed by Danny Boyle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can avoid getting shut out by purchasing your ticket:  &lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=6819~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;A Disappearing Number Tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will Meetup at the Panera Bread across the street from the Coolidge starting around 5:45.  Look for the group of people sitting around a table with a Red Meetup Sign.  Doors open and pre-show begins at 6:30pm; screening begins promptly at 7pm&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will Meetup at the Panera Bread across the street from the Coolidge starting around 5:45.  Look for the group of people sitting around a table with a Red Meetup Sign. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286729096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NT Live presents A DISAPPEARING NUMBER</name><id>15062564</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288047600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15062564/</event_url></item>