<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In one respect this dinner discussion is, in part, a sequel to the meeting on June 8th that was entitled “Transhuman or More Human?”  However, the subject here is not about how technology could potentially make the human animal “more human” but concerns the issues of a human being’s highest aspirations.  What is human greatness?  What do we humans want to become? How are we to overcome ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God, at least in one sense, is the religious or spiritual ideal of being. However, the gods of myth or, perhaps, of genuine historicity are also ideals that are not always the humane ideals we think of in terms of &lt;em&gt;moral&lt;/em&gt; greatness.  Greek and Roman gods, for example, often display the full range of human emotion both good and bad.  Those of us, such as myself, who are fascinated by alternative theories and speculations often think of books such as Von Daniken's &lt;em&gt;Chariots of the Gods&lt;/em&gt; or Sitchen’s &lt;em&gt;The12th Planet&lt;/em&gt; that argue that the gods referred to in the ancient biblical and Sumerian texts were actually astronauts from other planets.  Don’t be frightened off just yet! This discussion is not about ancient astronaut theories, but the notion of highly advanced beings who were viewed as gods by humans during their early development is precisely the sort of conception of “god” potential that we will discuss.  Humans may almost be on the verge of becoming “gods.”  If we can survive our self-destructive tendencies I have no doubt that in the future human beings will be the gods under whose tutelage beings in other parts of the universe begin their journey into civilization and higher consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may occur to you that the word ‘goddesses’ in the title is unnecessary.  That’s right, I just threw it in there to be a little provocative.  Perhaps there is not much point in making gender distinctions  in a discussion of god-like greatness.  But actually, I think, there is a legitimate line of questioning that entertains gender and/or sexuality amongst the gods. Perhaps the goddesses will rule! Perhaps the inner feminine is destined to rule?  Or perhaps not. Probably not...Maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who and what do we want to become?  That question sums up the topic for discussion.  Nietzsche’s &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ubermensch"&gt;Ubermensch&lt;/a&gt;, the Greek and Roman gods and other mythologies, the primary aspirations of ethics, Utopian ideals and finally, the possibilities of science all enter into the conversation.  But most certainly, the question of who we want to become also implies the question, “Who do we want &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to become?”  And perhaps that is the more fundamental question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people).   After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.  It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.  And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!  While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).  Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.  However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reach me at my office, call 617-964-4800&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;*****************************&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you RSVP for one of our events it is expected that you have every intention of attending. Please refrain from impulse reservations and impulse cancellations!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1345949225000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342891145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Of God, Gods and Goddesses</name><id>74311452</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345849200000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/74311452/</event_url></item>