<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 New Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.522877</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>National Park Service Salem Visitor Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>669333</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.892440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Okay guys, Halloween is again stalking our paths and our crazy members still have a hankering to get themselves as close to the mayhem as possible.  A cry was issued to repeat this event, and for those who haven't tried it, it's a great way to be immersed in Salem, that mecca of Halloween in NE, at the most intense time of year with only a moderate fear for your life or soul:-). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watson Adventures is again offering a Scavenger Hunt the night of October 25th. No, unlike most of the scavenger hunts of our youth, we will not be stealing articles of clothing or public property (the gravestones stay in the ground, people!!). Instead we will be dividing into teams of four to six to answer questions about the history (fact and fiction) of Salem. There are winners, and depending on turnout and the number of teams we contribute, we may have to have a little inner B &amp;amp; B competition complete with prizes. Although, speaking from experience this time, go for the gold, it's a pretty sweet T-shirt that Watson will bestow upon the grand champions.  This year we're taking it!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 and must be ordered on your own, in advance. They are pretty good at managing large numbers, but these are popular hunts, so I recommend purchasing early.   They are available online at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/performance.html?method=showPerformance&amp;amp;reset=user&amp;amp;perfId=544591&amp;amp;code=" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or if you're having trouble with that link, click on the time of the hunt (7 pm) off this site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/cal/483/1222900200000;jsessionid=923DD09425C0C96088D43FCCC5565196.app1" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note this is the &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Secrets of Salem hunt (adults only)&lt;/span&gt;, not the Witches of Salem Family Hunt held that afternoon at 4:30 pm (unless you're looking to hunt with the kiddies).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please mention or type in Meetup when ordering the tickets as they will let us team up against the masses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please do not RSVP yes without purchasing your ticket.  I have no magical witchcrafty powers to get you a ticket the night of the event.  They like us meetup folk, but not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; much:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at the visitors center from whence the hunt will commence at 6:30 p.m. to band our meetup crew into teams.   The visitor center is near Salem Commons, across 1A (Hawthorne Blvd) and next to the Museum Place Mall.  Will send my cell phone out to my attendees closer to the event so we can all find each other. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is an absolute disaster, so check out the MBTA schedule at www.mbta.com.  The commuter rail out of north station is a great option for getting there and back and will be my transportation means of choice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm up for catching dinner or checking out the sites earlier in the day, but be aware that tickets for any museums, or other walking tours sell out way in advance for that weekend, so don't plan on seeing anything unless you've planned ahead.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  Check out things to do at: &lt;a href="http://salem.org/visit/index.php?grp_ID=2&amp;amp;cat_id=4" target="_blank"&gt;http://salem.org/visi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  For events specific to that day, check out:  &lt;a href="http://salem.org/happening.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://salem.org/happ...&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  The basic &lt;a href="http://salem.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://salem.org...&lt;/a&gt; site provides great links for getting to and around the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Most of the &amp;quot;haunted happenings&amp;quot; conflict with hunt time so feel free to chose your poison according to your likings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please include in your RSVP whether you are just interested in the hunt, or if dinner or more strikes your fancy.  Even better, email me directly with your interests. Please note that &amp;quot;dinner&amp;quot; will like happen at 4-4:30 as the restaurants will be mobbed.  Will finalize details based on interest.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions? Contact Lisa (vetchick)&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225496760000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221590533000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watson Adventures Scavenger Hunt in Salem</name><id>8769485</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224973800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8769485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>