<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>[617] 621-1200 </phone><name>Friendly Toast</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>915453</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since they don't have any room for us at the Tavern this month, the October Social Meetup is now at the &lt;a href="http://thefriendlytoast.net/" target="_blank"&gt;Friendly Toast&lt;/a&gt; in Cambridge (Kendal/MIT T stop on the Red Line- one stop away). If you haven't tried the Friendly Toast before, you really should. It comes highly recommended and reviewed. It's got a unique atmosphere and some great food options (including all day breakfasts). We reserved their function room- so we'll get to talk sci-fi in private (and so we can hear each other). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm actually really excited about trying this new place and interested in what you guys think. I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;~Robyn~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come out and meet other Boston area Science Fiction and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the regular social meetup for the Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group, which always happens on the First Tuesday of every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll probably talk about the books, television, movies, comics and games that we like (and those we don't like, and even those we may be ashamed to admit that we like), but there is no set agenda!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're can't come on time, that's fine, there is usually still a critical mass of people until 9:00 PM (or later). If you want to come early, that is fine too, I try to get there around 6 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore? Feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (please, no sales here), but be sure that you take home anything that is left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286404019000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284042893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Social Meetup- New Location!</name><id>14710625</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286317800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/14710625/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>