<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Practice self and assisted rescues at Whitehall Reservoir,  Thursday, July 22, arrive by 5:45 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT we will be DOING/what you NEED to have for kayak and gear:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an informal practice session to help each other learn and practice self and assisted rescues.  We have several members of the group who are willing to help demonstrate and help each other practice!  As we have to be off the water by sunset, please arrive prepared to launch as quickly as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You either must have a kayak with bulkheads, or if your kayak does not have bulkheads then it must have some flotation in the back - beach ball, dry bag, or a real float back.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Things to bring: Boat paddle and PFD obviously. Dress for the water and bring a towel and a warm change of clothes. Other stuff it would be good to have include: paddle float (for self rescue), Pump, spray skirt.  I also highly recommend nose plugs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since we'll be pushing sunset, LIGHTS ARE ALSO REQUIRED for this one (a good flashlight will suffice), after practice we'll have about a 15-20 minute paddle back to the launch and there may be fishing boats around, so it is very important that they can see us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information - &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's directly on Rt. 135 in Hopkinton. I'll leave it to everyone to check a map for their best way there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4219141</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279918857000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279237792000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rescues practice at Whitehall Reservoir</name><id>14116205</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279835100000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/14116205/</event_url></item>