<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just finished an amazing round of this class. People were deeply moved and definitely felt that their consciousness was raised. Some couldn't get enough and have already started on more advanced classes. If this sounds like something you'd like to experience, I invite you to come, try the practice, meet some wonderful people, and start  having a taste of that ever-elusive sense of peace inside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are  beginning a new six-week class series called Meditation &amp;amp; Mysticism:  Experiencing God Within Yourself. This is a powerful introductory  course designed for those who are seeking an inner experience of God  through meditation. Classes include teachings on the practices of the  mystics and how they can be applied in the modern western world.  Mysticism refers to "the practice of knowing the reality of God through  direct experience." It is certainly nothing new, as it has always been  at the core of every religion and represents a more inner, experiential  way of coming to know God and the spiritual world. We offer this series  as an opportunity for you to discover whether the mystical path might be  right for you. Time will be spent teaching the principles of meditation  that will allow you to move deeper than the body, beyond thinking and  emotions, and into the reality of God's peace and presence within. In  each class we explore three areas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Understanding the universe  materially and spiritually, the Laws and Beings that govern it, and our  roles as living, conscious humans in that cosmos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Spiritual exercises designed to help you develop skills needed for inner work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3) Hands-on experiences, through which you can learn to see, hear, and feel the spiritual world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This  class teaches an introduction to mysticism in the Christian tradition,  though the truths are the same as those taught in all mystical  traditions. Everyone is welcome, no matter what your previous experience  or religious background may be.  &lt;br /&gt;The class is free, but RSVP is  required. Late admittance may be permissible (after the first week of  the class), but check with the organizer to be sure. Completion of this  series can lead into more advanced classes for those who are interested.   &lt;br /&gt;The class is offered on six consecutive Tuesday evenings at 7:30pm, beginning April 5, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Michael Knight</member_name><member_id>8983786</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302050688000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>If you are seeking a spiritual practice that is both practical and profoundly meaningful, regardless of your background (or even your religion!), this class is the place to start.</why><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301592274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation &amp; Mysticism: Experiencing God Within Yourself - a new class series</name><id>17131215</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302046200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/17131215/</event_url></item>