<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Still plenty of spots open for the June Meetup folks. Come out and support special guests from Pug Rescue New England! Tammy, President of this wonderful organization will be there to educate us about this wonderful organization that has helped thousands of pugs over the years. Tammy will be there with a few volunteers from her dedicated staff to hand out information and answer any question we may have about keeping our precious pugs safe from the heat this upcoming summer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She will also be doing some fun raffles and more, so PLEASE, if you can RSVP for this special guest so she will come back in the future! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly, Albert and I will be at Martha's Vineyard and miss you all, but PLEASE go and show your support for this hard working organization and we will see you at our house on July 24th for our Annual Pug Meetup Cookout!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly and I truly enjoy being the Organizers of the Grafton pug Meetup. We hope that we have met each of you individually, and if we have not, please come up and introduce yourself at the next one. We are constantly trying to come up with new treats for our precious pugs, and ideas to keep it informative and interesting. We welcome all suggestions. It seems to be very personal and we all have tons of fun.  We always welcome new members to come join in the fun and excitement at watching our little puggie friends romp and play in the spacious room at the Gibson Kennel in Grafton. Note: &lt;b&gt;this is a PUG Meetup&lt;/b&gt;...as not all breeds play well together.  There are other small breed Meetups, but this is for PUGS ONLY!     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******A receipt of current vaccinations must be brought with you in order to enter the play area (kennel rules)*********  (this has not been strictly enforced at the Meetups but, it's better safe then sorry since the owner of the kennel did request we have this on-hand)     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We will ask for a $5 fee per family for each Meetup&lt;/b&gt; to cover Meetup costs and any leftover money will be donated to the Curly Tail Pug Rescue as well as other animal related charity that we all agree on as a group. These donations go toward paying the monthly dues, snacks and to keep this website going so we can all see when the next Meetup is taking place.  We will also do special events from time to time to keep it fun and interesting!     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you all and I look forward to playing again with all you pug lovers out there and your pups! =)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will introduce ourselves...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>erin maguire</member_name><member_id>3828727</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth Mott</member_name><member_id>6811754</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura</member_name><member_id>10300396</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277641130000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Puggy Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pug-569</urlname><id>252667</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6900024414</group_lon><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271986855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grafton Pug Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>fdfdnynjbjc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277571600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pug-569/events/13264937/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/b/global_10981051.jpeg</photo_url></item>