<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I had a trip planned during the winter that I couldn't come through with because Zealand Falls Hut was full. Well, it's pretty empty for the night of April 10th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I posted this event in my NY group too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the plan:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are driving from NY up to Lafayette Campground in Franconia Notch about 8.5 miles North of Lincoln, NH on Friday night on Interstate 93. Those of you who live close by are welcome to join us at the trailhead on Saturday morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wake up at 630am. Cook breakfast in the campground and be ready to head out at 8am. We will then drive to the trail head, drop passengers off and shuttle cars to where we are going to finish on Sunday. For those of you joining us Saturday morning. Meet us either a little bit before 8am at the Lafayette Campground or meet us at 9am at the Parking Loot for Hale Brook Trail. If you need directions let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike from Hale Brook Trail up to Mt Hale and then head over to Zealand Falls Hut. We will drop our packs and then do a little day hike up to Zealand Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zealands Falls Hut is self-serve during this time. So bring your own camping stoves, food and sleeping bags.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wake up bright and early and be ready to head out by 7am. We will backpack to the cars we parked at the other end, on the way we will hit Mount Tom, Mount Field and Mount Willey. We should be out the latest by 2pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will do about 9 miles each day. This is not a trip for beginners! We don't babysit. We hike in groups of two or solo at our own speed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those RSVPing Yes, please make you reservations for a bed at Zealand Falls Hut on April 10th dailing 603-466-2727. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment (Not optional unless indicated otherwise) NO COTTON! COTTON KILLS!:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sleeping bag. At least a 0 degree sleeping bag. The White Mountains can be really really cold at night in April. We are going to be high up at Zealand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Snowshoes. We might or might not need them but we will carry them anyway. (I am not sure with the weather at this point whether we'll need them. If someone has been on those trail recently please let me know if snowshoes are still required or if it is just crampon time.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Crampons or microspikes. Your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Balaclava&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Ski goggles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Winter hat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Glove liners&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Mittens&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8. Synthetic base layer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9. Fleece&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. Hiking Pants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11. Wind and waterproof Jacket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12. Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;13. Tent (optional, we usually have enough tents to share and we will only use the tent on Friday night.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;14. Camping stove&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;15. Camping food for 2 days&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;16. Extra pair of dry clothes for the night. It helps to have a dry pair of clothes, seal them in a bag and don't wear them at all during the day. It helps fend off hypothermia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;17. Map of the White Mountains. (I prefer the maps from Map Adventures, easily available in NH and at Soho EMS.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thanks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Francisco&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email me any questions or comments to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;metope@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My number for the day of the hike is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;347-683-1242&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Francisco</member_name><member_id>822470</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271113369000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270248420000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Backpacking to Zealand Falls Hut and Peak Bagging 5 peaks in 2 Days</name><id>13072113</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270940400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13072113/</event_url></item>