<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here is an event I last lead in 2007. Tory's Cave is a great marble cave of modest extent with a few rooms and a crawlspace. We'll park and hike-in a little bit to a sinkhole entrance. This is a true cave but being a marble cave there are no flow/mineral features you would find in a limestone cave. We'll explore the cave and its features.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at the parking area off of Rte. 7 at 2:30 PM and spend no more than a couple hours at/in the cave so we should be done by 4:30 PM (sunset about then).  We can stop for dinner in New Milford or Danbury if there is the will.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who have a fear of tight or closed spaces should not attend this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is significant rain in the day or two before this event I may cancel the event. If there is rain on this day I will also cancel the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There is a hike our group is doing before this event at 9 AM to 2 PM starting from this location and covering about 5.8 miles. You may wish to consider doing that too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment:&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;* Headlamp (preferable) or flashlight is essential.&lt;br /&gt;* A helmet of some kind is strongly suggested for in the cave to protect from bumps. Acceptable helmets are: caving, bike, rock climbing, skateboard, or hard hat (cheap one is fine).&lt;br /&gt;* It is cool/cold/wet in the cave so dress warmly but not bulky into the cave (no cotton as will stay wet/cold!). Clothing into the cave may get snagged/damaged from rocks as well as wet/muddy so best not anything expensive or new.&lt;br /&gt;* Footwear should be something with a good grip for a little climbing and which is OK to get wet/muddy. Sneakers will be better than hiking boots.&lt;br /&gt;* You will get wet and muddy so a coat for outside the cave and a change of clothing/shoes is strongly advisable for after.&lt;br /&gt;* Plastic bag to put dirty/wet clothing in after.&lt;br /&gt;* Plastic bag to put dirty/wet equipment and boots in after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DECONTAMINATION NOTE: Because of the &lt;b&gt;White Nose Syndrome&lt;/b&gt; killing bats in the northeast, we are to treat our hiking clothes as contaminated, just in case. Clothing is to be bagged after the event and kept bagged. They are to be washed as soon as possible. Equipment (including shoes/boots) taken into the cave should also be bagged and washed as soon as possible after the event. (See my posting on this in 2008: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/messages/boards/thread/4243721"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Decontamination Procedures&lt;/b&gt; strongly recommended to protect bats:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Remove your caving gear when you get to the vehicle and put it in a closed plastic/garbage bag to prevent contamination of the interior or trunk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Wash caving clothes using hot water, detergent and a normal bleach cycle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Dry the clothes thoroughly and dry them at hot temperatures. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Scrape the dirt from boots and soak them in a 10% bleach solution (1 part chlorine bleach, 9 parts water) ? soak porous boots longer than nonporous boots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Do not forget to wash or soak cave packs and to thoroughly clean helmets/lights with a 10% bleach solution or a similarly effective disinfectant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Sunlight (UV rays) can also kill many things that live in dark places. (i.e. expose stuff to sunlight for extended periods of time)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to Tory's Cave parking - MEET HERE (a &amp;quot;bit north&amp;quot; of New Milford on Rte. 7/Kent Rd., around 480 Kent Rd., New Milford, CT)&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=480+Kent+Rd&amp;amp;city=New+Milford&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;country=US"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Textual directions to Tory's Cave parking&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 7 north out of New Milford center for about 3 miles at which point you'll pass the intersection of Rt. 37 west and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;* A short distance later a gas station will be on your left. Drive 1.3 miles (passing the first street sign for the semi-circular Squash Hollow Road) and turnleft into a large dirt parking area (in two parts: a semi-circle and then a huge open field).&lt;br /&gt;* Look for Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan!&lt;br /&gt;* The blue trail markers can be seen at the apex of the semi-circular parking lot.   The parking lot is at an old quarry construction site.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Note:  If you see the second street sign for SquashHollow Road, you've gone too far. Drive back  about 0.4 mile.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information about the cave see&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.berkshirehiking.com/hikes/torys_cave.html"&gt;http://www.berkshireh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289824921000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288540995000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Caving in Tory's Cave near New Milford CT</name><id>15285939</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289676600000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15285939/</event_url></item>