<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358156</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>708011</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063692</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>($5 for BBF card holders)</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>What better day than Independence Day for a trek across the entire &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Footloose_on_the_Freedom_Trail" target="_blank"&gt;Freedom Trail&lt;/a&gt; from the Massachusetts State House on Beacon Hill to the U.S.S. Constitution in the Charlestown Navy Yard?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our journey will begin with an easy downhill and an introduction to the stars of the show (many of whom  permanently reside at the Granary Burying Ground).  As we go past, we'll see the annual 4th of July parade which pays homage to the Revolutionary War heroes buried there. Then we are off to see the sites where they went to school, where they protested, and where they drank.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the heart of Colonial Boston, we'll just be in time to see that parade again and hear a bit of the Declaration read from the balcony of the Old State House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crossing the Greenway will bring us to the second portion of the trail, through a labyrinth of small neighborhood streets, where you'll hear the story of a man who hung a couple of lanterns and another who rode a horse.  Not to mention, visit yet another burying ground.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crossing the Charles marks the the final leg of the tour, to see where Boston began. We should hit the bridge just in time to see the USS Constitution depart on her annual turn-around cruise. This section includes the climb of a hill (Bunker? Breed's?), where your heart may break upon hearing the story of General Warren's death. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The finish line is adorned with flags (and some cannons), and you will be able to tell your friends you completed the entire course in about 3 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get patriotic, put on some sturdy shoes, and come out for the Footloose on the Freedom Trail walking tour. ($15 per person/$5 for card-carrying &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt; -- see &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org" target="_blank"&gt;web site&lt;/a&gt; for how to join).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for folks with BBF badges, bags, hats, etc.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gretchen G</member_name><member_id>7594534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247682962000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241636022000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Footloose on the Freedom Trail: Independence Day Celebration!</name><id>10353602</id><headcount>246</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246712400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/10353602/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/2/global_8514530.jpeg</photo_url></item>