<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the June meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, a reminder: we start the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we will jump into the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event: Everything you always wanted to know about NLP (but didn't know who to ask)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is the last NLP meetup for the summer (more on that later), I thought it would be useful to &amp;quot;open up&amp;quot; the session to what YOU wanted to know and do.  Pretty much anything is fair game, from questions around concepts (&amp;quot;What IS trans-derivational search, anyway?&amp;quot;), to techniques (&amp;quot;Can you demonstrate Bandler's Decision Destroyer process?&amp;quot;) to actual interventions (&amp;quot;Please help me overcome my fear of giant cockroaches&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;how can I get my sister's boss to give her a raise&amp;quot; [note that you would need to bring your sister, but not her boss]).  I'll do my best to meet everyone's needs, and we typically have quite a few other experienced NLP practitioners who I'm sure will be able to back me up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great session for both beginners (since you can get basic questions answered), as well as experienced NLPers (since you can get your advanced questions answered too!).  All levels are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I mentioned, this will be the last NLP meetup this summer.  I'm very excited to be attending Steve Andreas' &amp;quot;Tools for Transformation&amp;quot; Advanced NLP workshop in August in Colorado, and Leslie and Aaron and I will be heading out there as part of a two-month roadtrip.  We'll be back in September, and will start up the NLP meetups again then.   It will be held in a new location (TBD), since we're moving out of Newton Centre, and I'll let you all know as soon as I know.  If any of you have suggestions for where the future meetups should be, please let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three more things: &lt;br /&gt;1) if you want to email me your questions before the meetup, I will try to address those first when we meet&lt;br /&gt;2) if you've been wanting to do a free introductory NLP session with me, your time (before September) is running out!  Let me know asap, and make sure that you include several times and dates that you are available&lt;br /&gt;3) I don't say it enough, but I love doing these meetups, and I'm grateful to all of you who show up and make it possible.  Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;We meet on the first floor of Sturtevant Hall, 197 Herrick Road, which is near the library on the central quad of Andover Newton. &lt;br /&gt;Andover Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get a campus map and directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ants.edu/ants-difference/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ants.edu/a...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254434316000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243899347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP June Meetup - Everything you always wanted to know re NLP</name><id>10549211</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245364200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/10549211/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/8/global_3512920.jpeg</photo_url></item>