<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>381 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.394272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rosebud Bar &amp; Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>4400732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We are returning to Rosebud Bar &amp;amp; Lounge! We learned a lot last month, and while there were definitely some rough spots, we're going to try it again. A few things to keep in mind:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We know the food was very very slow to arrive. They didn't believe us when we told them how many of us there would be, so they only had one person working in the kitchen and one bartender. This time there will be two dedicated cooks, so it shouldn't be so bad. RSVP'ing helps us let them know how many people will be there, so please do RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* There is no table service, so you need to order at the bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* There were no movies, but that was a miscommunication issue (we thought they had a DVD player, they thought we were bringing one). This meetup _will have movies_ showing on some of the TVs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* The Rosebud "diner car" at the street is not affiliated with the Rosebud Bar &amp;amp; Lounge where we meet. You are not allowed to buy food from the "diner car" and bring it to the Rosebud Bar &amp;amp; Lounge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the normal meetup details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come out and meet other Boston area Science Fiction and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting! This is the regular social meetup for the Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In July, we are going back to the Rosebud Bar &amp;amp; Grill in Davis Square. They are normally closed on Mondays, but they are opening their back room area just for us, so we've moved our social meetup to the &lt;strong&gt;first Monday&lt;/strong&gt; of the month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more about Rosebud Bar &amp;amp; Grill here: &lt;a href="http://www.rosebudbarandgrill.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.rosebudbarandgrill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This space should be able to hold all of us, and it is reserved _exclusively_ for us. In addition, the space has three large TVs, so we should be able to show some SciFi/Fantasy movies in the background.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LOGISTICS: &lt;br /&gt;

 * There is no theme or agenda, just people talking about Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and geeky things that we like (and dislike). If you can't come on time, that's fine, we usually have a large group until 8:00 PM. If you want to come early, there are usually people there at 6:00. Rosebud says we can stick around until 1 AM if we want to (that's their closing time). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * If you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore, feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (no sales, please). Be sure to take home anything that isn't claimed before you leave! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * There is no charge for this meetup, but the restaurant that hosts us greatly appreciates your business (and doesn't charge us a room rental fee), so please come hungry (or at least buy a drink). Also, please don't forget to pay your bill before you leave!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 TRAVEL:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're taking the T, Davis Square is on the Red Line, and Rosebud is south of the T station, just off Elm St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=381+Summer+Street,+Somerville,+MA&amp;amp;aq=0&amp;amp;oq=381+Summer+Square,+Some&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.009735,0.021093&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=381+Summer+St,+Somerville,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02144&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;vpsrc=0" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=381+Summer+Street,+Somerville,+MA&amp;amp;aq=0&amp;amp;oq=381+Summer+Square,+Some&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.009735,0.0210...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are some metered parking lots near Rosebud, as well as street parking. There is a PDF with a list of public parking areas in Davis Square here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;rct=j&amp;amp;q=&amp;amp;esrc=s&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;cd=1&amp;amp;ved=0CCkQFjAA&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.somervillema.gov%2Fsites%2Fdefault%2Ffiles%2Fdocuments%2FDavis%2520Square%2520Parking%2520Map.pdf&amp;amp;ei=502gT_2sEYyHmQW8tdziAQ&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFsR0OhW927E_Hy2UvUVuVmxu3OvQ" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;rct=j&amp;amp;q=&amp;amp;esrc=s&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;cd=1&amp;amp;ved=0CCkQFjAA&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.somervillema.gov%2Fsites%2Fdefault%2Ffiles%2Fdocuments%2FDavis%2520Square%252...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Behind the diner car on the right side, in the restaurant building at the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342146828000</updated><rating><average>4.78999996185</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>77</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339357108000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Social Meetup 2012 (NEW DATE AND VENUE)</name><id>68577582</id><headcount>65</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341268200000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/68577582/</event_url></item>