<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Avenue of the Arts</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.830128</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.421.2787</phone><name>Veterans Memorial Auditorium</name><city>Providence</city><id>1409552</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416668</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join P-Collective member Joe to see the Rhode Island Philharmonic "Rush Hour" Series for Free!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never experienced the RI Philharmonic, this is your chance! Thanks to the generosity of the RI Philharmonic, we have a block of tickets reserved just for the Collective for &lt;strong&gt;THIS&lt;/strong&gt; Friday night! &lt;strong&gt;Seating is limited, so RSVP NOW if you want to go!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Rush Hour series happens 4 times during the regular season and is an abbreviated version of their of the full concert taking place this Saturday night. The series is hosted by TV news anchor Patrice Wood and will run from approximately&amp;nbsp; 6:30- 7:30pm, followed by an optional Q&amp;amp;A with the Music Director after the show. Tickets are normally $25 and up, but free for us as long as you give them your name and email address to opt in/out of their concert email list. Pretty good deal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the show, we will go next door to Temple Bar &amp;amp; Grille for some cheer and mingling with the musicians if they choose to join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please RSVP by this Friday at noon!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;We need to give them an accurate headcount as this is a ticketed event with assigned seating.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a unique opportunity for Collective members and many thanks to Joe who is on the roster as a Percussionist with the Philharmonic for offering this chance to check out the classical music scene in our beloved Providence!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Joe is hosting this one, please look at his picture!!! We will meet outside at 6pm under the awning before going into the concert</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe</member_name><member_id>34089782</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332803037000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332349158000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RI Philharmonic "Rush Hour" Concert THIS FRIDAY - Free!!!</name><id>57270352</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332540000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/57270352/</event_url></item>