<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 Drabbington Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02493</zip><lat>42.387293</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cat Rock Park</name><city>Weston</city><id>705511</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.280961</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This Weston park does not require dogs to be leashed and most (but not all) of the dogs I've seen there are off-leash. We had scheduled a meetup there last year, and in preparation for that Ron and I took Rufus there to see what it was like. We all liked it a lot! But unfortunately, on the day the meetup was to occur, there was heavy rain, so we cancelled it. &lt;br /&gt;

Several other members have been there with their Cavs, and reminded me about it at our March meetup. It's easy to find and you can see what some other people have said about it by Googling Cat Rock Park. I've scheduled it towards the end of the month so we have the best chance of good weather. But as before, heavy rain will cancel this meetup because the terrain won't be much fun if the ground is wet. &lt;br /&gt;

If it's nice and warm, the pond it great for swimming! &lt;br /&gt;

We'll meet in the enclosed area just in front of the entrance, unless it's being used by someone else for another activity, in which case we'll meet in the parking lot. One can enter the park either on the right or left side of the parking lot; but Ron &amp;amp; I thought it made a better walk to start on the left, i.e., to your left as you stand facing the park. That way you come to the pond towards the end of the walk, instead of right at the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karla Rab</member_name><member_id>10717717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367239816000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Cavalier King Chas Spnl Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CavalierLoversofMA</urlname><id>510192</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9700012207</group_lon><name>Cavalier King Charles Spaniel Lovers of MA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365038344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Cat Rock Park, its trails, hills, meadows, and a pond. </name><id>112570602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367074800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CavalierLoversofMA/events/112570602/</event_url></item>