<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5400 Computer Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01581</zip><lat>42.289696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree by Hilton Boston Westborough</name><city>Westborough</city><id>10753952</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572388</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/b/0/event_211245232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;We all need a night out, whether it’s to get away from the house for a little while or just hang out and relax with friends!&lt;/span&gt; Revamp your Girls Night Out with New England’s hottest dinner show, Tempted: The All Male Revue. The LIVE high energy dinner show designed exclusively for women debuts this month at the Westborough Double Tree Hotel on Friday March 22nd. Excite your senses as these handsome men seduce, entertain flirt with you and your friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The 1.5 hour show offers interactive entertainment that women of all ages will be clamoring to attend. The entertainment is all very classy and features creative choreography&lt;/span&gt; and extravagant costumes that are guaranteed to captivate female audiences! &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The Tempted: All Male Revue is not a bump and grind act, the show takes male revues to another level.&lt;/span&gt; While at the show ask about having your girlfriends in the "Hot Seat" on stage- an experience she will not forget! But remember, what happens at the show stays at the show; but we’re not ruling out some fun Facebook postings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for great dinner show in the ballroom at the Double Tree Hotel Boston-Westborough located at 5400 Computer Drive, Westborough, MA. Tickets are $45 for the dinner show-dinner starts at 7:00pm. $25 for show only-doors open for show only at 8:00 pm. Show starts at 8:30 pm. Advance tickets are recommended and can be purchased at &lt;a href="http://www.drinkwaterproductions.com/"&gt;www.drinkwaterproductions.com&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364004672000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>women-303</urlname><id>472102</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Girls Night Out Shopping Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362476939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tempted: The All Male Revue</name><id>107688902</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363993200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/women-303/events/107688902/</event_url></item>