<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Newton St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-522-6547</phone><name>Larz Anderson Auto Museum</name><city>Brookline</city><id>707120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138044</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;"Come celebrate the Art of Italian Style and Fashion at the Larz Anderson Auto Museum. Europeans in Boston is a sponsor of this event, and we highly encourage you to join us. Dress Italian; Arrive with your lovely friend, significant other, a partner or by yourself to a castle; Join us under a tent . Indulge yourself with Ruffino Italian wine or Solerno Blood Orange Liqueur specialty cocktails; Have some appetizers,
 &lt;br /&gt;provided by Root Catered Events, Sensational Foods and Jojo's Home Cooked Love. Italian dessert bites created by Cuisine Chez Vous Catering and Above and Beyond Catering. Get photographed by amazing photographers and videotaped by Italian TV RAI. Visit the Carriage House, which was designed after a French Chateaux in 1888, Check out the beautiful and historical exhibits inside. View a Fiat 500 like the one we will be raffling off at a live drawing in November.&lt;/span&gt; Take some time to get some works of wisdom from and admire the living Italian topiary, staged by Ten 31 Productions; Enjoy the fashion show and join us on the dance floor for some Euro club dance musicwith DJ Johnny Zucco. Italian Designers, Italian food with cocktailswill be featured all night long. $25 includes passed hors d'oeuvres and dessert. There will be a cash bar serving beer, wine and twospecialty cocktails. At the door the price will be $35.00."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Purchase tickets at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;nbsp;
&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=nawsxxcab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e4axqw6x854bc406"&gt;http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=nawsxxcab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e4axqw6x854bc406&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>THURMAN SMITH</member_name><member_id>1416920</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312556184000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312305954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>La Dolce Vita Fashion Show and Dance</name><id>27973781</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312498800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/27973781/</event_url></item>