<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>764 Dewey Mills Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05001</zip><lat>43.641312</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quechee State Park</name><city>White River Junction</city><id>324767</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.405006</lon></venue><fee><label>Camping Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ready to get out of the city? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're headed back to Quechee State Park in White River Junction, Vermont from August 13th to 15th.  Head up Friday morning or 9-5 working folks can carpool up as soon as you punch out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a special SoJust event that we are doing to gear up for our 4-year anniversary.  If you've found yourself not wanting SoJust events to end and more time to get to know the cool people you've met through SoJust, this is your chance!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several tentsites have been rented (we need exact numbers so be sure to RSVP!) where you can drive your car up and unload your tent.  We take care of all the food planning (and we'll eat REALLY well), there are fire pits, indoor toilets, quarter-fed hot showers, picnic tables, dogs allowed (&amp;quot;on-leash&amp;quot;), pretty woods and a half-mile hike to the Quechee Gorge (which is water you CAN swim in). Nearby is the Cabot store and a great local food only restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quechee State Park is about 3 miles off of highway 89, and also near 91, approximately 2 hours and 30 minutes from downtown Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thinking about joining us but never been to a SoJust event?&lt;/b&gt; We've had newcomers every camping trip and it's been wonderful to get to know them. If you like the idea of camping and want to get to know fun progressives you should totally join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Check out the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/messages/boards/thread/9284095#36246030"&gt;new Camping for Justice Thread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to learn more and plan carpools, sleeping arrangements, communal meals, packing list suggestions - everything you need to plan a great weekend of camping!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP deadline is set for August 6th&lt;/b&gt; - this is to ensure we have enough time to arrange carpools and plan the campsites.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Your payment of $40 needs to be sent at the time of your &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP to reserve your space.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; Payment includes camping for two nights and meals throughout the weekend. Check out the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/messages/boards/thread/9284095#36246030"&gt;new Camping for Justice Thread&lt;/a&gt; to see the great meals we have planned!&lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;It's just $40 per person for all this fun!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1300 members and almost 4 years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282064731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276738902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping Weekend for Justice</name><id>13825706</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281733200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/13825706/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/b/global_4697339.jpeg</photo_url></item>