<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Address TBA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01747</zip><lat>42.126438</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>774 232 0000</phone><name>Catherine's Home</name><city>Hopedale</city><id>1028317</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.536812</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Over the years, our group has had hundreds of fun events and a lot of great friendships have been formed. Join us for a special celebration for the 5th anniversary of our meet-up group! We will be enjoying a BBQ, drinks, outdoor games and some board games. &lt;strong&gt;Guests are asked for a $10 payment at the party to cover the cost of food and supplies. Please bring your own alcohol or other beverage of choice to enjoy at the party!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can play outdoor games including whiffleball and frisbee, along with some fun board games indoors. Feel free to bring a lawn chair too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food will include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hamburgers, hotdogs, shrimp, pasta salad, potato salad, cole slaw, fresh corn, salad, cheese/crackers, chips/dips, fruit, desserts, ice cream sundae bar and some other good things too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a couple of people would like to come a little earlier and help set up, that would be great- please send me a message. I'll also need a couple of volunteers to help with the grill!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to carpool, please specify it in your RSVP and members can arrange carpooling with each other. I live on a quiet residential street, so there is plenty of easy, free street parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please only sign up if you can definitely attend. If your plans change, please update your RSVP. I need to have an accurate headcount, so I know how much food to purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you for a great summer party! If you are new to the group or haven't been to an event in a while- then be sure to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address will be emailed to guests before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342704637000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340310393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet Up Anniversary Party, BBQ and Games</name><id>70169862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342296000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/70169862/</event_url></item>