<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You can walk with the pack as long as you like, please do not feel obligated to stick with the walk the entire time. &lt;br /&gt;All you do is show up with your leashed dog and we all walk together, socialize and let the dogs mingle as we lead the way. It's actually remarkable the way they fall into the pack mentality. After the initial excited 5-7 minutes of greeting each other and finding their comfortable slot in the pack, they settle in and march like soldiers. Please bring water for the walk. I will provide bowls and water for the beginning and end of the walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: If it is raining, too hot, too cold, etc. a cancellation notice will be sent via email and posted on the meetup website 1.5 hours prior to the meetup time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a $15 a month meetup fee. This is a group fee and if not paid, our meetups would not exist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer is in charge of paying this fee every month. It would be greatly appreciated if at each meetup, each member can submit a donation that goes towards the monthly $15 fee. Give $1, give $10. If at the end of the meetup, the organizer has not collected enough to meet the $15, she will pay the difference. If she receives more than $15, the extra would go towards the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Please do not feel you need to bring cash to the walk. I have setup a paypal account so those who would like to contribute can do so safely and securely whenever they can**&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As always, I will wait by the green forrest board with either 1 or 2 of my french bulldogs - you wont be able to miss us!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208398109000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We had record numbers this past week. So many new people, it was great!! Everyone seemed to enjoy themselves and all the pups got along so well. They stuck together and ran and played - it was a great time.</why><group><who>Dog Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>packwalk</urlname><id>1030709</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dog Lovers Pack Walk</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205073615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South Shore Dog Lovers Pack Walk Meeting</name><id>7496473</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208095200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/packwalk/events/7496473/</event_url></item>