<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381539</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics (CfA)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1343951</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.128653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;RSVPs open one week before.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I (Marianne) plan to be there early, before 6:45 p.m. I will carry a meetup sign. Say hello and introduce yourself.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Doors open at 7:00 p.m., but &lt;strong&gt;get there early . . . even before 6:45 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt; Seating is first-come, first-served for the main lecture room. The overflow crowd sits in a separate screening room. Admission is free.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heather and I arrive at different times. Look for both of us and our meetup signs in the lines, at the back left of the auditorium, and/or on the observatory roof. Say hello and introduce yourselves.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If weather permits, rooftop stargazing through telescopes will follow the presentation. Dress for stargazing. No experience is necessary. The &lt;strong&gt;Center for Astrophysics&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Amateur Telescope Makers of Boston&lt;/strong&gt; set up all the telescopes. All you have to do is peek through the lens!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Free parking is available to everyone after 5 p.m. Ignore the "staff only" signs. Drive up to the back, up the hill. The presentation is up the stairs that are opposite the observatory-in-a-box.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;From the Harvard stop on the MBTA Red Line, take any bus or trackless trolley going west on Concord Avenue in Cambridge (Arlmont Village and Belmont Center buses; Huron Avenue trolley) and get off at the Observatory Hill stop.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The lecture goes on rain or shine or clouds or snow (within reason, of course!). The observation part of the event is often determined the moment the lecture ends.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;For more information about and directions to this event, visit the CfA website:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events"&gt;http://www.cfa.harvard.edu/events&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;or call them at 617.495.7461.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;A line forms early for this event. Please do not cut in line because we will meet inside the auditorium: go to the back left of the seats. The overflow crowd goes into a separate screening room, so everyone gets in to see the presentation. Even if we don't sit together, we will meet in the courtyard after the lecture and before we go up on the roof. (If you are in the separate screening room, turn right after you exit and walk toward the courtyard, then look for signs pointing the way to the telescopes.) You can also look for the meetup sign while we are waiting in line to look through the telescopes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Sitting at the left rear of the lecture hall is a way to let people find me and an empty seat that much more easily. The lectures are lots of fun, though, and I can certainly understand if you would like to sit up front and closer to the (very entertaining!) talks. Please sit where you are most comfortable. If you are bringing children to the event, you may want to sit toward the front so they can see and ask questions. We will be able to chat after the lecture, while we wait in line for a chance to stargaze through the several rooftop telescopes. Each telescope is usually trained on a different sight in the nighttime sky, so waiting in several lines gives us plenty of time to introduce ourselves. And plenty of nighttime objects to observe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;The CfA prefers that attendees not take pictures, but if you decide to, please do not use a flash.&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;******************************&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the CfA:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observatory Night: "Black Hole Chaos," Belinda Wilkes and Francesca Civano, CfA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Giant black holes at the centers of galaxies are the most powerful engines in the universe. In active galaxies, they blast out jets of material at near light speed. And when galaxies collide, their black holes merge with a dramatic burst of gravitational waves that can kick the black hole out of the galaxy entirely. Travel to the lairs of these hungry monsters and uncover their secrets.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;******************************&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign. I usually find a seat at the left rear of the lecture hall; look for me there. After the lecture (and weather permitting), we will meet in the courtyard or in the telescope lines up on the observatory roof.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marianne</member_name><member_id>9387943</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368765816000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357083091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CfA/Harvard-Smithsonian Observatory: Lecture and Observatory Night</name><id>97363292</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368744300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/97363292/</event_url></item>