<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Memorial Drive </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360054</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building 10, Room 250, at MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>950723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084824</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What's the silliest scientific research you ever heard of?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ever year, the Annals of Improbable Research scour scholarly journals for the wackiest, silliest, craziest research studies published that year.  And those intrepid scientists--&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;who studied things such as:  electronically modifying the sound of a potato chip to make the person chewing the chip believe it to be crisper and fresher than it really is; discovering that the fleas that live on a dog can jump higher than the fleas that live on a cat; discovering that slime molds can solve puzzles (yes, these are all real research studies)--&lt;/span&gt;receive an Ignobel prize, given out by real Nobel Prize winning scientists.  The award ceremony is Thursday night, but costs $40.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I'm going to the lectures instead--5-minute mini-lectures on each topic, with challenging questions from the audience encouraged (get your Nerd Brain ready!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's meet at 12:30, so we can chat beforehand.&lt;/b&gt;  I will hold seats until 12:45--after that, you're on your own.  One person will be at the doors with Meetup sign, another will be inside holding seats with Meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Remember--if you RSVP Yes and don't show up, it's rude to both the organizer and other attendees who were expecting you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Links and directions are below; site is MIT's main campus--from Memorial Drive, in the big MIT yard/mall/grassy area, it's the building smack in the center of the U.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://improbable.com/ig/2009/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://improbable.com/ig/2009/" target="_blank"&gt;http://improbable.com...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; (scroll down--they have a lot of blank space at top of page)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;map &amp;amp; directions: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?mapterms=10-250" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?mapterms=10-250" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ig Informal Lectures&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Oct 3, 2009, 1:00 pm.&lt;br /&gt;MIT Building 10, Room 250 &lt;br /&gt;77 Massachusetts Avenue, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;(Click here for a map and directions)&lt;br /&gt;FREE ADMISSION -- but seating is limited&lt;br /&gt;A half-afternoon of improbably funny, informative, brief (5 minutes each, plus a few questions &amp;amp; answers with the audience), high-spirited public lectures, in which the new Ig Nobel Prize winners (and a few past winners, too) attempt to explain what they did, and why they did it. &lt;br /&gt;This free event is organized in cooperation with the MIT Press Bookstore.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>6019932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1255535468000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253537561000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ignobel Award lectures</name><id>11425549</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254587400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11425549/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/4/global_8362388.jpeg</photo_url></item>