<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Description by Kevin:&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;So I’m walking down Mass Ave in Cambridge and this gorgeous woman crosses my path. I smile. She glances over and keeps walking without giving me a 2nd thought. I think to myself, “what would it take to attract a woman as lovely as she”?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, good looks would help. But I missed the boat on that one at birth. A charming personality and a command of witty banter might do the trick. Is there a pill I could take for that? Maybe having lots of money would work. Would that beautiful woman be impressed if she knew that I was a “thousandaire”?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I’ve got it! I’ll impress her with newly honed climbing skills! Join me at MetroRock as I work on becoming a real 5.10 climber. AND capture the heart of my true, though anonymous, love. Really, who can resist a good climber? Or, in my case, a solidly average one. If there’s interest, we’ll all head out for drinks and food after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: you will need to pass a belay test if you are an experienced climber but new to the gym. You can take a belay test when you get there. If you have never climbed before, you should take a class at Metrorock. Please call the gym in advance to make arrangements to take the class. You can use the message board on this meetup to find other people that want to take the class. Metrorock will charge you $16 for a daypass if you are not already a member or a punch card holder.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metrorock is hard to find for first time visitors. So if you find yourself going in circles here are some hints - From the traffic circle near Wellington Station take Santili Highway towards Best Buy and Mellon:&lt;br /&gt;If Best Buy is on your right and the Mellon building is on your left as you are going away from the circle, you are on the correct road. Then, take a left when you see a sign that says MetroRock. This sign is very very easy to miss as it is quite dark at night. Also, the road is full of potholes so drive slowly. Then take the next left to MetroRock.&lt;br /&gt;Or, see &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock...." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt;. for directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gym also has a shuttle to the gym from the T - Wellington Station if you don't have a car. Last shuttle back to the T is at 9:30 or so. But, if you want to stay until 10 and/or join us for post-climb food and beverages, rides will be arranged.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>tables at 7</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan</member_name><member_id>2230421</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251760359000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251300964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>friday rocks @mrock</name><id>11205932</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251500400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/11205932/</event_url></item>