<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Boston Post Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01776</zip><lat>42.362637</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-443-2351</phone><name>Best Friends Pet Care</name><city>Sudbury</city><id>669377</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new Meetup:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: October 25, 2009 1:00 - 3 PM, Halloween Party &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt;Best Friends&lt;br /&gt;150 Boston Post Rd &lt;br /&gt;Sudbury, MA 01776&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to all that attended today and for bringing lots of food and beverages!  I enjoyed this meet tremendously, and couldn't believe how ADORABLE  the dogs attending were!  They got along together even better than I had hoped, and were extremely well behaved!!!!  I never even heard one tiny growl!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The staff at Best Friends, Paula and Angelica, took excellent care of us.  We had access to a large room, a small room and the outside play yard, all very nice, although the drizzling rain kept us from using the play yard properly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angelica took pictures of today's Meet and she and Paula hope to have them up on the Best Friends' website this week, as well as downloaded into our Meetup.com sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next Sudbury Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meet will be again combined with the Mass.  Small Dog  Breed Group  at Best Friends and will take place on Sunday, October 25th, 1-3 pm.  Halloween Party, costumes appropriate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the meanwhile, we will also have a Holliston meet convenient for those that live closer to that area, including Cape Cod and South Shore members.  All members are of course invited.  I will check in with Anne Byers at the Holliston Meadows tomorrow to pick a good date.  Possibly Oct. 11th, possibly Oct. 18th. 3-5 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All of you reading this, please write back and tell me which date (Oct. 11th or 18th) at Holliston would work for you:    laptopmaltese@aol.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small dog best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask anyone attending where Kim is</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256663978000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254107956000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meet, Oct. 25, 1-3pm, Halloween Party, Best Friends</name><id>11483704</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256490000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/11483704/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/c/global_83228.jpeg</photo_url></item>