<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Union Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.379608</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 623 9211</phone><name>Precinct Bar</name><city>Somerville</city><id>743340</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095481</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>hey there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the Sea Monsters have been tearing it up every sunday night at Precinct in Somerville's Union Square.  they're an incredible collection of excellent boston area musicians and their shows are eclectic and electric, guaranteed to get you up on your feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;here's what the salem soul &amp;amp; jazz festival said about them:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;Sea Monsters is a collaborative Boston-area band featuring some of the regions top musicians.  Fronted by Christian McNeill and Jesse Dee, seasoned performers whose songwriting, guitar playing and stage presence never cease to amaze, Christian, Jesse and the rest of the Sea Monsters have become one of the hottest acts around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both have played across the US and Europe, and with distinctly different styles, yet a natural synergy between them, you'll never get bored as they trade off on lead vocals. The supporting band, equally seasoned, includes Michael Miksis on bass, Jeremy Gustin on drums, and Lyle Brewer on electric guitar.  Sea Monsters also boasts one of the strongest horn sections around in John Aruda on sax, Scott Aruda on trumpet and Jeff Galindo on trombone, adding a soulful edge to every show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sea Monsters love to share the stage with special guests such as Tim Gearan, Dwight Richter, and Reva Williams at most every performance as well, making each show completely fresh and electric in energy.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;you simply have to see them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;unfortunately they go on a bit late (10 pm) for a sunday night, so it can be difficult to go out and really enjoy them if you have to get up in the morning and think.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;however, next sunday night, 6 september, is the night before Labor Day and, as everyone knows, that's a Thought Free Day™.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so don't think about it, just come on out and see the sea monsters.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>i'll email a cell # to everyone who RSVPs 'Yes' or 'Maybe' by 6 september, 6 p.m.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252868369000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251737253000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sea Monsters @ Precinct</name><id>11247325</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252287000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/11247325/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/6/global_10484550.jpeg</photo_url></item>