<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25-27 Edinboro St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351676</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-9998776</phone><name>US.China.Chan Association</name><city>Boston</city><id>864918</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059855</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.wearechange.org/2008/07/wearechange-meets-nancy-pelosi-again.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wearechang...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8/4/2008 John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum Columbia Point, Columbia Point, Boston, MA 02125, 617-514-1645, 5:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jfklibrary.org/JFK+Library+and+Museum/News+and+Press/Upcoming+Events/Book+Signing+Speaker+of+the+House+Nancy+Pelosi+to+Sign+Copies+of+Know+Your+Power+at+the+Kennedy+Libr.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jfklibrary...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book Signing - Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi to Sign Copies of &amp;quot;Know Your Power&amp;quot; at the Kennedy Library &lt;br /&gt;On Monday, August 4, 2008 at 7:00 p.m., the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum will host Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi, who will sign copies of her latest book, Know Your Power: A Message to America’s Daughters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Know Your Power, Pelosi draws on her personal and professional experiences in appreciation of the powerful women who came before her, as well as those countless women whose lives have touched her own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nancy Pelosi became Speaker of the House in 2007 after serving 20 years in Congress, representing California’s Eighth District in the House of Representatives.  She and her husband, Paul, have been married for 45 years.  She is the mother of five children and the grandmother of seven. She divides her time between Washington, D.C., and San Francisco California.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The book signing will take place in the Pavilion at the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum starting at 7:00 p.m. on August 4th.  Copies of Know Your Power will be for sale at the Museum Store during the signing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets to the preceding Kennedy Library Forum – A Conversation with Nancy Pelosi, are no longer available &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kennedy Library Forums: A Conversation with Nancy Pelosi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, August 4, 2008, at 5:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.jfklibrary.org/JFK+Library+and+Museum/News+and+Press/Upcoming+Events/Kennedy+Library+Forums+A+Conversation+with+Nancy+Pelosi.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jfklibrary...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi will speak at the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum on August 4, at 5:30 p.m., to discuss current political events and her recently published autobiography, Know Your Power. Ambassador Swanee Hunt, Director of the Women and Public Policy Program at Harvard’s Kennedy School of Government, will moderate the discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This forum will be held on Monday, August 4, from 5:30 to 7:00 p.m. in the Stephen Smith Center at the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum, Columbia Point, Boston.  Tickets to this event are no longer available to the general public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** - If you are a member of the media wishing to attend this forum please contact Brent Carney at brent.carney@jfklfoundation.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the Forum at 7:00 p.m., Speaker Pelosi will sign copies of her new book, Know Your Power: A Message to America’s Daughters.  The book signing is open to the public and copies of Know Your Power will be available for sale in the Museum Store.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218058450000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217437010000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>$1000 reward for asking Nancy Pelosi a question! </name><id>8441760</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217885400000</time><rsvp_limit>447</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8441760/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>