<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-723-2500</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>731371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070306</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Food, Glorious Food&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Palate vs. Our Planet?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With Corby Kummer, senior editor, The Atlantic Monthly; host, The Atlantic Food Channel; author, The Pleasures of Slow Food; Joanne Chang, pastry chef and owner, Flour Bakery and Cafe; chef and owner, Myers+Chang; Helene York, director, Bon Appétit Management Company Foundation. This presentation is part of the ongoing series DIY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, May 07, 2010 | 7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;Cahners Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrity foodies Corby Kummer and Joanne Chang, along with national food sustainability expert Helene York, explore the relationship between our love affair with food and our desire to protect the planet. Join us for a conversation about how we can radically redesign what we eat to help the Earth without sacrificing the joy, flavor, and glorious experience of eating food. Book signing to follow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seating is limited. Passes are available in the Museum lobby beginning at 5:45 p.m. on the day of the program. First come, first served. Museum members may reserve a limited number of seating passes in advance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: Free &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This program is part of the DIY series, in which you can &amp;quot;Do It Yourself&amp;quot; with new programs devoted to personal empowerment, good health, and fresh food at your fingertips. Admission to this program is free thanks to the generosity of the Lowell Institute.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273446401000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263845250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>More Food</name><id>12354480</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273273200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12354480/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/1/global_12420273.jpeg</photo_url></item>