<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.842763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Surfside 5 Beach Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>962091</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.816092</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Sunday, 5/24, 1:00pm:  I checked the accuweather forcast and they predicted a few passing thunderstorms early in the day, but expect it to be clear and sunny by 3:00pm... so I will be there.  Hope to see you there too.....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, May 24th is the grand opening of Surfside 5 Beach Bar and Grill, which overlooks Salisbury beach. It has a huge 8,000 ft oceanfront deck!!  The reggae band, &amp;quot;Hot Like Fire&amp;quot;, will be kicking off their summer season, and playing from 4:00pm-8:00pm on the oceanfront deck (weather permitting). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hopefully, they will take reservations on the deck, but if not we'll put our name in for a table and try to have some dinner while we listen to the music.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also, there will likely be a cover charge to see the band.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hot Like Fire has emerged as the most sought after authentic reggae party band on the East Coast music scene for the past nineteen years. They perform current, popular reggae and soca music as well as classic favorites by Bob Marley and of course that &amp;quot;Hot Hot Hot&amp;quot; song! New England Performer magazine says Hot Like Fire is &amp;quot;energetic, upbeat and highly addictive&amp;quot;. People are always dancin' when Hot Like Fire is jammin'&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;(The Band's website) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hotlikefire.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hotlikefir...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**NOTE: Due to this type of venue, it is very difficult for the group to stay together... If this is a problem for anyone, it may not be the right event for you to attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Please indicate on your RSVP if you want to car pool and where your coming from. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* RAIN cancels.  So, please be sure to check for any updates before heading out.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ATTENTION:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is also listed as a co-event with the &lt;b&gt;Beantown and Beyond Singles group&lt;/b&gt;, and&lt;b&gt; the Social Fun group&lt;/b&gt;.  It is also listed as a separate event on&lt;b&gt; the Merrimack Valley Single Friends Alliance group&lt;/b&gt;.   *&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt; &lt;b&gt;Please only RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; on one of the groups&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; *   Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will meet you in the bar area</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen A</member_name><member_id>3582765</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243647923000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242684989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reggae Sunday @ Surfside 5 Beach Bar and Grill in Salisbury </name><id>10440689</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243195200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/10440689/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_8698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>