<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join us for a hike to the Madison Springs Hut. Some of our members will be summiting Mt Madison in a different group. This will be Peter's 48 4000 peak so we don't want to hold the hikers back from tagging that peak, but want to be there to cheer them on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our moderate paced group is hiking the beautiful trail to the hut, With a elevation of +3629 ft, this is enough of a hike for me, but one that I found to be quite nice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was one of my first hikes on ice a few years ago. &lt;b&gt;Don't forget your spikes, crampons, and snowshoes and headlamps. If &lt;u&gt;experienced&lt;/u&gt; hikers would like to ascend Mt Madison in good weather, we recommend a minimum group of 3 well equipped  experienced hikers, and add 1 extra hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hut is closed for the winter but a good place to take in the alpine scenery, summit of Mt. Washington and Adams and surrounding presidential range. We will then descend the Valley Way trail and hopefully join in a trailhead celebration to make the day complete.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  7.46 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  7 hr 18 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +3629 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -3629 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  0 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a memorable Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost trying to find the meetup. We must start on time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the &lt;br /&gt;hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. Review the trail maps and itinerary available in the White Mountain Guidebook. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members. Jefferson, NH is farther than many of our hikes. Please allow time to get there on time.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Diane's Cell phone 603-477-5116</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231269867000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229383866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Madison Springs Hut via Valley Way ( Appalachia)Trail</name><id>9343840</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231073100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9343840/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/5/global_4754725.jpeg</photo_url></item>