<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Time to look forward to a Monday again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What better way to finish the first day of the workweek than by hanging out with a group of fellow climbers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be bringing a rope for those interested in doing a lead climb or two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will typically wait until about 7:15pm for everybody to arrive and team up. If you happen to come after we already hit the walls, just try to find me. There's a dry-erase board between the two locker rooms, I will post a description of what I'm wearing on it so you can find us more easily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: you will need to pass a belay test if you are an experienced climber but new to the gym. You can take a belay test when you get there. If you have never climbed before, you should take a class at Metrorock. Please call the gym in advance to make arrangements to take the class. You can use the message board on this meetup to find other people that want to take the class. Metrorock will charge you $16 for a daypass if you are not already a member or a punch card holder. Ladies get a discount on Monday nights! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Monday night belay classes are filling up quickly, so sign up early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock.com/e-directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt; for directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gym also has a shuttle to the gym from the T - Wellington Station if you don't have a car.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jens</member_name><member_id>7100014</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256771497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255051854000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mondays @ Metrorock</name><id>11585412</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256598000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/11585412/</event_url></item>