<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>792 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Royal East</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669107</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097340</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Greater Boston Humanists have a most pleasant tradition,
celebrated every June, to gather for brunch and listen to a
lecture. If you'd like to attend -- even if you've not been to a
GBH event before -- you can RSVP by writing to Tom Ferrick,
thomasferrick@gmail.com, or giving him a call at 617-547-1497.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;You'll be asked to pay your $22 for the meal at the
restaurant, with check or cash. The meal begins at 1 PM.&amp;nbsp;
Remember, you may park free in the MIT Lot on Windsor St.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Directions: in Cambridge&amp;rsquo;s Central Square area, turn
from Massachusetts Avenue onto Main Street.&amp;nbsp; After passing by
the Royal East on your right, a pink building, take the next right,
Windsor Street, and turn into the first parking lot on your LEFT,
repeat, LEFT.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;After food and some announcements, there will be a timely and
thoughtful talk from Dr. Leonard Bernstein, entitled EARLY
CHILDHOOD EDUCATION IS THE IMPERATIVE.&amp;nbsp; He is a Board Member
of Greater Boston Humanists, and a resident of Brookline. Most
people would agree that statistics and news headlines suggest there
is a crisis in education and the finger of fault moves wildly and
accusingly.&amp;nbsp; Dr. Bernstein formulates his case in this manner:
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&amp;ldquo;When people speak about an educational system for
primary and secondary school they are generally referring to the K1
- 12 format. They also may think this process is the most important
part of making an educated person, a good citizen and a person able
to reason and function well in society. But is it? The answer is
no. It appears that the most critical period for the childhood
learning experience is from birth through age 5. Dr. Bernstein will
talk about the factors involved in the importance of these years
and will make the case for the importance of early childhood
education and intervention. He will present some evidence as to
what can and has to be done and how all this relates to societal
demands for its workforce. He will endeavor to make the case that
it is imperative to do so.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;In order for humanistic concepts to take hold in a person's
mind, a mind capable of being able to think critically and
reasonably, a mind with the tools to do so is required. As Dr.
Bernstein will try to show, for too many children, the chance to
start the thinking process is thwarted by societal and parental
strictures. Is early childhood education the way to go to achieve
educational, let alone humanistic, goals? Dr. Bernstein will
present material that he hopes will allow you to make your own
conclusions.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leonard &amp; Jane Bernstein</member_name><member_id>10934949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307977833000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307640849000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Humanists Summer Luncheon</name><id>21605771</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307896200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/21605771/</event_url></item>