<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Just because it's still winter in the mountains it doesn't mean that you can't start looking ahead to the spring. Think about it - no snowshoes or crampons, lighter boots, and less "extra" clothing and gear to stuff in your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you are planning to become more active once the snow melts, or if you simply want to brush up on the knowledge, skills, and abilities that you already have,&amp;nbsp;the Spring Hiking and Backpacking Program being offered by the Boston Chapter of the AMC is a great place to start.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Program Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This course uses lectures, demonstrations, group activities, and case studies to teach the basics of three-season hiking and backpacking - wilderness safety, clothing, footwear, gear, equipment, nutrition, weather,&amp;nbsp;above treeline travel, overnight trips, etc. It's&amp;nbsp;taught by AMC trip leaders, some of whom also organize hikes with us here at the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The program runs on five Tuesday nights from 6:30 PM - 9:00 PM. The first three nights (04/17, 04/24, and 05/01) will focus on day hiking while the final night (05/15) will focus on overnight trips. The fourth night (05/08) will be a mix of different topics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Program Registration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The Program costs&amp;nbsp;$50 for AMC members and $55 for non-members. You can pay via Paypal when you register online by clicking &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hbbostonamc.org/index.php/Table/Spring/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; or you can send&amp;nbsp;a check payable to "HB COMMITTEE" to Chris McCarron c/o Phoenix Realty, 1318 Beacon St Unit #18, Brookline MA 02446. The program fee includes&amp;nbsp;a comprehensive course manual and the current AMC White Mountain Guide book included.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There will be weekend trips offered exclusively or preferentially to participants in this class so you can put your learning in practice. Plus, this is a great opportunity to meet lots of other people who love the outdoors, and to make new friends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The program takes place at AMC Cabot Auditorium located at 4 Joy Street in Boston, MA. It's near the Park Street T Station, the Massachusetts State House and the Boston Common. Discount parking passes are available for the Boston Common Garage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Questions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you have general questions about this program, you can either contact me, the program organizer Robert Knudsen (springhiking@hbbostonamc.org), or the registrar Chris McCarron (chrishbamc@gmail.com).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334796246000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327183615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC's 2012 Introduction to Spring Hiking and Backpacking - Class 1 of 5</name><id>dqlcmcyqgbwb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334701800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/49062802/</event_url></item>