<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://jonathantr.zenfolio.com/img/s1/v0/p666683898-4.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Island backpacking on Isle au Haut in Penobscot Bay, part of Acadia National Park.  We'll take a ferry from Stonington Maine to the Isle au Haut town landing and backpack ~5 miles to the Duck Harbor Campground, where we have two lean tos reserved.  No running water, no electricity, pit toilets.   We'll do some easy to moderate day hiking on the island's numerous trails.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is cross posted with the Maine Outdoor Adventure Club.  I have &lt;u&gt;three&lt;/u&gt; remaining slots available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is for experienced, self-sufficient backpackers with all their own food and gear.  You must have a full backpack, 20 degree mummy style sleeping bag or warmer, sleeping pad, cookstove and fuel, water filter, etc.  Warm clothing is recommended for potentially cool and breezy seaside camping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a two night trip, from Saturday 10/2 to Monday 10/4.  The Isle au Haut Ferry does not run on Sundays, so it will not be possible to join us for just one night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ferry schedule is available at &lt;a href="http://www.isleauhaut.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.isleauhaut.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Most of us will be taking the 10:00 AM boat from Stonington on Saturday 10/2 and the 10:50 AM boat from Isle au Haut town landing on Monday 10/4.  Please feel free to take whatever scheduled run works best for you.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costs: you will pay one equal share of the $50 national  park permit fee, plus your own ferry fare ($36 round trip), and possibly for parking in Stonington.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I DO have open slots available, but I would like to talk to interested participants prior to registration.  So please, if you want to attend, go on the waiting list and contact me.  I will get back to you as soon as possible!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Rundell</member_name><member_id>11084760</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286018630000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284558127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Island backpacking on Isle au Haut - Acadia National Park-3 spots left</name><id>14778222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286013600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14778222/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>