<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(behind Mohr &amp; McPherson)</address_2><address_1>460 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342475</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 292-2822</phone><name>Galeria Cubana</name><city>Boston</city><id>1211056</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065602</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Take a private, intimate art gallery and add a flowing open wine bar and delicious cheeses and chocolate desserts. To complete the scene, mix in about 35-50 professionals ages 25-45. What you have is a private affair for Moxie members, complete with 40+ bottles of wine, a table full of food and an art gallery rented for our exclusive use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADMISSION - PLEASE READ:&lt;br /&gt;If we have to rent a second gallery, we will need at least a week's notice. So PLEASE try to prepay by May 17th so we can book a second gallery.&lt;br /&gt;$25 if you prepay by May 19th&lt;br /&gt;$30 if you prepay May 20th or after&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REGISTER HERE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonmoxieinthecity.eventbrite.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://bostonmoxieint...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress is trendy/upscale. No, guys, suits are not required. But when you see how fashionable the ladies look, you`ll be glad if you dressed to impress. Ladies, you can wear anything from your little black dress to what you wore to work that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;YOUR HOST:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Frequently described as&lt;a href="http://www.theprofessionalwingman.com" target="_blank"&gt; “Boston’s Hitch,”&lt;/a&gt; Thomas has helped men find relationships and more fulfilling lives, through personal development over the course of months of coaching. With his unique approach to helping others find love combined with his infectious personality, he’s been able to help men and women of all kinds find the happiness they’ve been looking for.&amp;quot;  Twitter: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/URwingman" target="_blank"&gt;twitter.com/URwingman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Light music will play and new friends will be made. Show up with your room mate, your life mate, your co-workers..or show up alone. There will be a staff of 2 or more volunteers on hand to help introduce you to other members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THIS IS A PERFECT EVENT IF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You`re new in town and want to meet new people&lt;br /&gt;You`re looking to make new friends&lt;br /&gt;You`re looking to networking and make contacts&lt;br /&gt;You`re single and want to meet someone special&lt;br /&gt;You just want to get out of your house and off the internet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE ABOUT THE AGE RANGE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Average age range of these events is 25-45&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ADMISSION INCLUDES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open Wine Bar from 7-9:30pm (40+ Bottles of wine purchased)&lt;br /&gt;Desserts, Cheeses &amp;amp; Chocolates served at 7pm until gone&lt;br /&gt;Private art gallery rental (no blaring music!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DRESS CODE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a dress to impress event. No jeans, sneakers or active wear. You`re worth it! Break out the iron, strap on those sexy heels! This is the time to put your best, sexiest foot forward! Show everybody how amazing you are!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THINGS TO KNOW:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Light appetizers served from 7-7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;*Check in staff will be located at tables as you enter&lt;br /&gt;*Bring business cards!&lt;br /&gt;*This event is open to all!&lt;br /&gt;*Average age range of attendees varies. The majority of guests are between the ages of 24-44.&lt;br /&gt;*Dress code is trendy business casual.&lt;br /&gt;*Expect to meet people from all fields - Medical, Legal, Creative, Fashion, Entrepreneurs, Event Planning, Finance&lt;br /&gt;*Ethnically diverse crowd of  professionals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.lagaleriacubana.com/uploads/paintings/thmb_139.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ABOUT TONIGHT`S EXHIBIT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Galería Cubana offers an exceptional collection of contemporary Cuban art gathered from artists living on the island of Cuba. Cuba's distinct cultural history has produced extraordinary art varying broadly in styles, methods and materials. After decades of anonymity, Cuban art has finally been gaining greater exposure and international recognition for its accomplishments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT GALERIA CUBAN&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Galería Cubana is pleased to showcase the creative, technical, and experimental achievements of Cuban artwork by featuring a range of artists at various points in their career. We carry work of the highly-trained, self-taught and even street artists. Our collection includes oils and acrylics on canvas and paper, prints, drawings, watercolors and mixed media works. This range of work has been selected to encapsulate the cultural depth, aesthetic diversity, and political edge unique to Cuban art.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3910727</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276784112000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>moxiebizsocial</urlname><id>504315</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Social/Singles Networking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271775301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Art, Wine &amp; Introductions Event </name><id>13236181</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274482800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/moxiebizsocial/events/13236181/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/c/global_14523004.jpeg</photo_url></item>