<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We have a special treat for the New Year!  David Elliot will be coming to speak to us about some of his creative use of indicators.  David leads the First Wave club - largest club on TCNet (that's the chat on TC2007).  I've been a member for three years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David will be talking to us about MAP, MOBO, EPPV and more!  MAP is David's term for Moving Average patterns - patterns that repeat daily and throughout history.   MOBO is Momentum indicator using the most common mathmatical formula.  EPPV is the Elliot Predictive Price Volume indicator.  Signaling tomorrow's move today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have reserved a large room for this talk, but please RSVP, because there will also be members of the First Wave Club in attendance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is his bio:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Steelsmith Elliott has been a well-respected financial market professional and researcher for more than 30 years. Twice named #1 Market Timer by USIC, and voted to the Readers Choice List of Outstanding Seminars by Stocks &amp;amp; Commodities Magazine in 2006, he is renowned for his uncanny ability to forecast price movements in both stocks and indexes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David has developed many unique successful new proprietary strategies using long-standing technical indicators combined in such a way as to produce directional market signals independent of trend and applicable to all markets, among them MAP – Moving Average Price Patterns, MOBO-Momentum Breakout Entry and Exit Triggers, FlatWaves – Market Direction Prediction, SnapBacks – New Highs and New Lows Indicator, and STAMP – Stochastics Amplified; all have all had a significant influence on the way market technicals are viewed by industry professionals. He has also developed a software template incorporating these and other studies, which gives entry and exit points on all fractal time periods for the E-mini markets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David has been a registered Commodity Broker and a certified Commodity Trading Advisor (CTA). He has been an arbitrator for the National Futures Association; has worked for Dean Witter, Paine Webber, Blythe Eastman Dillon, and Conti Commodities; and has managed and owned his own successful brokerage houses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David has been a seminar speaker for twenty-five years, has been licensed to teach investments on a university level, and has been invited to speak on the financial markets and technical analysis investment strategies to many diverse groups, most notably the Chicago Board of Trade and NAAIM, the National Association of Active Investment Managers, which includes roughly 200 member firms nationwide, managing an estimated $14 billion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his 1998 book, Everyone's Guide to Making A MILLION DOLLARS, he accurately predicted the Year 2000 Crash; he is currently authoring another, Predictive Patterns for Profit. He is the author of the VHS series, Beyond Theory - Applying Technical Analysis to the Bottom Line, the very popular CD course, Advanced Equity Trading, and The Ultimate Emini Seminar, each of which have greatly impacted the financial well-being of his followers and students. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David derives his greatest satisfaction as a teacher, and his technical analysis classes are well attended across the US, in Canada, and in Europe. He also hosts “Seminars at Sea,” offering advanced market-trading classes while cruising in the Caribbean and other seas. And he is known to many for his generosity in sharing his knowledge and insights through his free daily emails via the Yahoo Investment Club MentorCenter, and his free daily live voice chats via his FirstWave Club, the largest chat club on Worden Brothers’ TCnet.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231893690000</updated><rating><average>4.84000015259</average><count>31</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>134</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230051173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Presentation by David Elliot</name><id>9380404</id><headcount>134</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231545600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9380404/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/7/6/global_6730214.jpeg</photo_url></item>