<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Behind Woodstar Cafe</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01063</zip><lat>42.317646</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation Community Room</name><city>Northampton</city><id>508449</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.638031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>5:30 to 8:00 p.m. (program 6 to 7:30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested donation at the door: $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Search Engine Optimization (SEO) brings powerful business tactics &lt;br /&gt;but also plenty of confusion and hype. During our Google Analytics &lt;br /&gt;event last spring, many of our members requested a follow up event on SEO. &lt;br /&gt;Join us for this interactive panel discussion, where three local experts in SEO, &lt;br /&gt;web business, and marketing strategy will take the hype out of SEO and share &lt;br /&gt;practical tips on making the most of SEO. The focus will be on your questions&lt;br /&gt; - from the basic to the advanced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Topics to be covered by our panelists include:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Incorporating SEO into the design and architecture of your web site&lt;br /&gt;- Advanced SEO techniques and SEO lessons from high volume web sites&lt;br /&gt;- Integrating social networking (Twitter, Facebook, etc) into an SEO plan and marketing strategy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our panelists are: &lt;br /&gt;Silvana Gravini of &lt;a href="http://www.silvana.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.silvana.ne...&lt;/a&gt; (and a long time Hidden-Tech board member), &lt;br /&gt;Jason Gates of &lt;a href="http://www.getfused.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.getfused.c...&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;br /&gt;Val Nelson of &lt;a href="http://www.valnelson.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.valnelson....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The panel will be moderated by Jon Reed, Hidden-Tech board member and the owner of JonERP.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will not be a &amp;quot;lecture panel&amp;quot; - your questions will be the focal point of our &lt;br /&gt;discussion, so bring your SEO topics and concerns. Whether you want to know more about &lt;br /&gt;Google Page Rank, the SEO impact of blogging, or determining the best key words and search niches &lt;br /&gt;for your industry, our panelists will have answers for you. They will also share how they &lt;br /&gt;have increased their own visibility and marketing reach through SEO-informed efforts. Please bring &lt;br /&gt;your SEO success stories as well. Note: this panel will be focused mostly on &amp;quot;organic&amp;quot; search &lt;br /&gt;strategies rather than PPC (pay per click).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About our panelists:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jason Gates&lt;/b&gt; is a Search Engine Optimization expert. As a partner at Getfused, Jason helps &lt;br /&gt;clients with implementing best practices for search into their sites and their business &lt;br /&gt;processes. Jason's work generates real and measureable results for Getfused's clients. &lt;br /&gt;Getfused is a full-service digital marketing agency, founded in 1996. Getfused helps their &lt;br /&gt;clients leverage technology to provide immediate and long-term results. &lt;br /&gt;Check out his work at &lt;a href="http://www.getfused.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.getfused.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Val Nelson&lt;/b&gt; is a business coach and career coach who helps people access more clarity, &lt;br /&gt;more ease, and more impact in their work. While helping hundreds of clients with web &lt;br /&gt;marketing, she noticed many of them were blocked by internal barriers to &lt;br /&gt;self-promotion. (Introvert anyone?) Since adding coaching, her clients are happier and &lt;br /&gt;more successful. Coaching is now her focus,  and she still brings marketing expertise &lt;br /&gt;to the table.  She knows what works and what's a waste of time. &lt;br /&gt;She provides lots of tips on her blog/website: &lt;a href="http://www.valnelson.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.valnelson....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once upon a time, a Web presence -- any Web presence -- was enough. That's just not the case &lt;br /&gt;anymore! Achieving solid ROI from your online endeavors takes the marriage of smart strategies &lt;br /&gt;and intuitive, elegant design. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Silvana Gravini&lt;/b&gt;, principal of Silvana.Net, is a specialist in Web &lt;br /&gt;site Design/Development, Organic Search Engine Optimization (SEO), and Social Media strategy and &lt;br /&gt;implementation.  A Web designer/developer since 1996, Silvana is an established leader in the &lt;br /&gt;field. Her prior experience includes years of success in marketing and sales. This combination &lt;br /&gt;of design and marketing expertise makes her uniquely able to provide clients with intelligent &lt;br /&gt;and effective Internet solutions.&lt;br /&gt;Contact Silvana at: &lt;a href="http://www.silvana.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.silvana.ne...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hidden-tech.net/events.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hidden-tech events page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon Reed</member_name><member_id>9974627</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287010317000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284082903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SEO (search Engine Optimization) Panel</name><id>14718757</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287005400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/14718757/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/9/global_17692633.jpeg</photo_url></item>