<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>from</description><amount>319.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : xx-large"&gt;Experience QUEBEC City - with all of your senses!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/f/4/event_125846612.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quebec is a UNESCO&lt;/strong&gt; World Heritage site bursting with rich history, amazing food, unique shops, and a wealth of art and entertainment. For a small city, there's so much to see and do, you won't know where to begin!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRING YOUR BICYCLE&lt;/strong&gt; to best experience the town or &lt;strong&gt;WALK&lt;/strong&gt; and ride the excellent public transportation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quebec is known&lt;/strong&gt; for its restaurants, street performers, walled city, stone forts, large parks, food market, the St. Lawrence River, interesting neighborhoods, and its friendly English- and French-speaking residents. And don't worry about the language. Most people in the city speak English (and we'll have my high-school French as backup!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We'll stay for three nights&lt;/strong&gt; (or longer if you wish) with plenty to do either with the group or on your own. Take a tour, watch the street performers, take photographs, have your portrait painted, shop, eat, stroll through old town...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/d/c/event_125875772.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;History: Quebec is over &lt;strong&gt;400 years old&lt;/strong&gt; and there is an intact and still-inhabited walled city to explore. There are ornate churches, impressive forts, and French language and culture (and food!) that feels more European than North American. Jacques Cartier and Samuel de Champlain are remembered here, and an important battle from the French and Indian War that took place on the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plains_of_Abraham"&gt;Plains of Abraham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Street Performers&lt;/strong&gt;: Quebec nurtures and encourages its performing artists. On the streets there is music, comedy, tragedy, acrobatics (and yes, even mime!) performing all over at all times in the summer. You never know what you might see and often this is reason enough to spend a few days in Quebec.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/5/6/e/event_125850062.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a French city! Need I say more? But there are also plenty of tourist traps serving mediocre, over-priced meals. So either do your homework or rely on the services of someone who has... C'est Moi! Food is important to me so rest assured I'll have a list of many of the best but not expensive places to eat. I've sampled a few of them on previous trips. And there are croissants and crepes and bistros galore!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walk &amp;amp; ride the quick shuttle or bring your bike&lt;/strong&gt; and we can ride through the Bois de Coulonge and Plains of Abraham Parks from our lodgings directly to Old Town and other neighborhoods to see the sights. We can stay together or split up &amp;amp; meet for meals. This is an easy place to do your own thing at your own pace - or stay with the group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AND at NIGHT there's even more to experience...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CIRQUE du SOLEIL was born in Quebec and PERFORMS FOR FREE several nights per week outdoors in the summer! (&lt;/strong&gt;You can also buy tickets if you want to catch their newest full stage show, &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cirquedusoleil.com/en/shows/amaluna/default.aspx"&gt;AmaLuna&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; which will be playing while we're there.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/3/4/event_125857172.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The free performances&lt;/strong&gt; take place under a bridge in a corner of town that you might not find if it weren't for the slowly growing mass of people walking toward someplace over &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; way under a darkening sky... The procession grows until you reach what looks like ropes and lights and what's that? - a stage - hanging from underneath the concrete span of a highway bridge. As you stand with others, anticipating what comes next, you hear music. Drums. They're getting louder and what's that!? Fire! Lights! Costumes! And the show begins!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And if that weren't enough, here's more!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/c/6/event_125859622.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imagine lounging on a blanket with a glass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;of wine&lt;/strong&gt; in a park by a river on a warm summer night, surrounded by French and English and other excited voices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now imagine that&lt;/strong&gt;, on the opposite bank of that river is an enormous length of connected grain silos measuring 100 feet high and 2000 feet wide - that's over 1/3 mile long. And imagine a spectacular light and image show being projected onto those grain silos. &lt;strong&gt;And imagine&lt;/strong&gt; incredible synchronized music emanating from speakers somewhere in the park above your head. And imagine a hushed audience of people from all over the world oohing and aahing together as they experience something unique in the world - something unlike anything they've seen before ...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/1/2/event_125859442.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://lacaserne.net/index2.php/other_projects/"&gt;Image Mill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a creation of playwright, composer, and eclectic artistic genius, Robert LePage. The work was designed for Quebec's 400th anniversary a few years ago and continues to amaze people each summer when it is performed outdoors on the St. Lawrence River. And it's free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AND YET MORE...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's an old Quebecois tradition called &lt;strong&gt;"Boites a Chansons"&lt;/strong&gt; which is amazing good fun. Later at night there are certain clubs where live bands plays everything from traditional celtic and Quebecois folk songs to REM and Elton John and anything else they know. And great friendly crowds of people good-naturedly drinking together stand or sit and sing as one to the music. This can last for hours on end with hardly a break. Some of the songs are in French, some in English, and all are sung with gusto by the whole bar. It's a unique experience not to be missed - if you enjoy laughing and drinking with friendly strangers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So if you come to Quebec -&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prepare to be dazzled and prepare to have fun!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/b/2/4/event_125863812.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Lodging: Lots of people arrive in Quebec in the summer and hotel rooms are expensive. However, we have another option! Historic &lt;strong&gt;Laval University&lt;/strong&gt; has modern, clean rooms available at a very low rate - half what you might pay at expensive tourist hotels. The university is located in a nice area just a short bicycle or shuttle-bus ride from Old Town. There are private or shared rooms available with private or shared bath.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rates&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; nights included)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;249&lt;/span&gt; per person - shared* 2-twin room - w/ shared bath&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other Rates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$279 per person - shared* 2-twin room - w/ &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;private&lt;/span&gt; bath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$309 Private 1-twin room - w/ shared bath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$419 Private 1-twin room - w/ private bath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Couples Rates&lt;/strong&gt; - lower per-person rates for couples signing up together - just ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;All room configurations might not be available&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;(especially double, queen &amp;amp; pvt bath)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;so sign up early!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Shared rooms require an available roommate. Otherwise a private-room rate may apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/9/8/event_125864952.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Make Checks Payable to:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Larry Pilla - 21 Baker St. Dover, NH 03820&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your spot is reserved when payment is received.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting there:&lt;/strong&gt; Those who want to will &lt;strong&gt;carpool&lt;/strong&gt; to share the expenses and the experience. Two routes are available: North on I-93 through Vermont &amp;amp; Sherbrooke, QC or the slightly shorter route up into Maine via Waterville and Jackman. The trip takes about 6.5 hrs and there will be a set amount for gas/tolls asked of each person sharing a ride depending on #of riders, current gas prices, etc. &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;(Total fuel bill to split among car's passengers should be about $120-$140)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/8/8/event_126692392.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/6/0/event_125879232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cancellations will be dealt with on an individual basis and may be dependent upon finding a suitable replacement. Reservations and non-refundable payments need to be made by your organizer weeks or months in advance in order to offer fun trips like this!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Photos&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;1.Quebec sunrise; 2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Le Lapin Saute bistro; 3.Vieux-Quebec&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;(old city) scene; 4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Street performers; 5.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Une porte rouge - Rue St. Jean; 6.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Raspberry French Toast &amp;amp; Poached eggs with salmon!; 7.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Street performers; 8.Lapin Pie; 9.Queen Room; 10.Chateau Frontenac&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are a couple of bike rental companies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cyclo Services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;289, rue Saint-Paul &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Québec&lt;/span&gt;,  &lt;span&gt;QC&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;G1K 3W6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Phone:418-692-4052&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Toll free line:1-877-692-4050&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Écolocyclo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Marché du Vieux-Port &lt;br /&gt;

 160, Quai Saint-André &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Québec&lt;/span&gt;,  &lt;span&gt;QC&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;G1K 3Y2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Phone:418-828-0370&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.ecolocyclo.net/" target="_blank"&gt;www.ecolocyclo.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344543886000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338738616000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Experience Quebec City!</name><id>67531692</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>270000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344009600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/67531692/</event_url></item>