<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennet Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel</name><city>Cambridge, Harvard square</city><id>3395632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Juanito Pascual New Flamenco Trio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Virtuoso flamenco guitarist/composer/improviser Juanito Pascual has been called "one of the hottest flamenco guitarists in recent years" by National Public Radio, a major accolade which in this case is just the jumping off point for the Minneapolis native's musical style. His sound is a truly organic blend of a mastery of traditional and contemporary flamenco with his love of jazz, classical, rock, and more. A graduate of New England Conservatory's Contemporary Improvisation program (formerly Third Stream), he has spent the last 20 years forging a unique path fusing an array of influences into his flamenco-based vocabulary. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Pascual returns to the Regattabar presenting his latest project the Juanito Pascual New Flamenco Trio featuring two highly versatile and dynamic musicians, Grammy-nominated percussionist Tupac Mantilla (Julian Lage Group, Bob Moses, Kenny Werner) and bassist Brad Barrett (Jason Moran, Ran Blake). Fusing their distinct musical backgrounds with a palpable personal chemistry, the Trio has created a distinctive and exhilarating sound. Currently, they are producing their first CD, scheduled for release in fall of 2013.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;I have to admit that I am not a big Flamenco music fan.  By chance I happen to have seen Juanito Pascual and was just blown away.  A group of us went to see the trio last year and again the concert was just awesome.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;This event is scheduled with a few different meetup groups so we should have a good time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;Ticket price is $25 and can be purchased at the Regatta Bar Web Site&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.peltrix.com/getshowtix/rbar2012/purchase.cgi?id=2871"&gt;https://www.peltrix.com/getshowtix/rbar2012/purchase.cgi?id=2871&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;I will only assume you are coming when your reservation says ticket purchased.  If you would like to sit with the group then you will need to let me know by indicating this in your meetup rsvp by Wed the 8th.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>10329460</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368403939000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364847546000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Juanito Pascual New Flamenco Trio</name><id>112134672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368313200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/112134672/</event_url></item>