<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Last Dickens by Matthew Pearl&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a brief synopsis of the book:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his most enthralling novel yet, the critically acclaimed author Matthew Pearl reopens one of literary history's greatest mysteries.The Last Dickens is a tale filled with the dazzling twists and turns, the unerring period details, and the meticulous research that thrilled readers of the bestsellers The Dante Club and The Poe Shadow. Boston, 1870. When news of Charles Dickens's untimely death reaches the office of his struggling American publisher, Fields &amp;amp; Osgood, partner James Osgood sends his trusted clerk Daniel Sand to await the arrival of Dickens's unfinished novel. But when Daniel's body is discovered by the docks and the manuscript is nowhere to be found, Osgood must embark on a transatlantic quest to unearth the novel that he hopes will save his venerable business and reveal Daniel's killer. Danger and intrigue abound on the journey to England, for which Osgood has chosen Rebecca Sand, Daniel's older sister, to assist him. As they attempt to uncover Dickens's final mystery, Osgood and Rebecca find themselves racing the clock through a dangerous web of literary lions and drug dealers, sadistic thugs and blue bloods, and competing members of Dickens's inner circle. They soon realize that understanding Dickens's lost ending is a matter of life and death, and the hidden key to stopping a murderous mastermind.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the table closest to the cafe door. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256946011000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240958504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Book Club - The Last Dickens</name><id>10289054</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256770800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/10289054/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/b/global_7133307.jpeg</photo_url></item>