<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join fellow Members and Guests of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun Friday Night Dinner @ Nino's Steak and Chop House in Hingham, one of the top voted Restaurants from the 2007 Restaurant Suggestion and Recommendation Discussion Thread!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what some fellow diners had to say about Nino's on yelp.com.&lt;br /&gt;Jim S. from Weymouth states: &amp;quot;I always thought this place was going to be fancy because of how nice the exterior looks.  It's a nice place but very family oriented.  The interior is very comfortable and all the stone work makes for a dramatic and old world feeling.  The food is very average but you can count on it and that can be a  good thing some nights.  It seems like a good place to be a regular.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Amy R. from Hingham states: &amp;quot;I really enjoyed this place on a cold and rainy night.  The interior, with the stone work and pitched roof reminds me of a church a bit....where I prayed to the Holy Balsamico Sirloin Steak (perfectly cooked too). Holy YUM for 18.50.  I got a massive and perfectly cooked baked potato, a lovely assortment of beans, and washed it down with a large glass of Valpolicella.  We also had the polenta with peppers and onions and sauce and it was AMAZING. I'd have gotten it as a starter though as there was just too much food to eat.  I took home more than half my meal. My husband will be loving those leftovers today...or tomorrow!  I am a big big fan of this place!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;To read more reviews go to yelp.com and type in &amp;quot;Nino's&amp;quot; in the Restaurant Search and &amp;quot;Hingham, MA&amp;quot; in the City Information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yelp states the approximate cost for one meal including drink, tax and tip is approximately $11-$30.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy.  This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash.  You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner @ Nino's Steak and Chop House&lt;br /&gt;Friday, August 29th, 2008 @ 6:45pm&lt;br /&gt;415 Whiting Street&lt;br /&gt;Route 53&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-340-7300&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela &lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Min of 6 people 48 hours in advance.  Max of 20 people.  &lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per Member&lt;br /&gt;Fees: Annual Members and one Guest- FREE, Group Members - $2, Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 10AM on Friday, August 29th.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page.  (It's OK if you are a couple minutes late given that it's Labor Day weekend and we may have to wait a few minutes to be seated.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please Note: Annual Members are allowed to bring ONE GUEST FREE to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: &lt;i&gt;Outside the front door if it's nice out.  We will then go in together as a Group.&lt;/i&gt;  Otherwise, inside the Lobby.  If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under &amp;quot;Angela.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Rt 3:&lt;/b&gt; Exit 15 - Derby Street, Hingham.  Follow Derby Street straight past the Derby Shoppes and take a Left at the 2nd light onto Cushing Street.  Follow Cushing Street to the next light.  Take a left onto Route 53N and pick-up form Route 53N below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heading South on Route 53:&lt;/b&gt; 1/4 mi south of the Weymouth line on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heading North on Route 53:&lt;/b&gt; 1/4 mi north of Linden Ponds on the right.  (About 1.5 miles north of the light at the intersection of Cushing Street.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: In lot behind restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the Front Door.  Late arrivals should ask the host for "Angela."</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222349913000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218291608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Dinner @ Nino's</name><id>8509066</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220049900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8509066/</event_url></item>