<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10:00  shuttle at 10:30.  &lt;br /&gt;Trip organizer: Mark Roberts 401-533-1883 Cell email:  hrmmark@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Changes and cancellations to trips will be posted by email by 8AM morning of trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CT River Opera House to Ferry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-95 North: Go to exit 70, left at end of ramp, then pass under I-95 to traffic light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I-95 south: Go to exit 70, go straight (slight zigzag to left) and travel .7 miles to second traffic light. Turn right at traffic light onto Route 156. From the traffic light, travel north for 8.5 miles to the stop sign at the end of at the end of Route 156. Turn left at stop sign onto Route 82 and travel 3.3 miles, go right at first stop sign and continue north on 82. Follow signs to East Haddam. Once in East Haddam, the road turns into a one way. As, two-way traffic begins again, the Opera House is directly in front of  you. Take the left just before the Opera House, go past the parking lot and turn right down the small dirt road just before the airport entrance (Dock Rd).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our leaders provide directions as a courtesy to paddlers however, you are responsible to refer to a map and familiarize yourself with the trip location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281931014000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279107054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT River - Goodspeed Opera House to Ferry</name><id>14098503</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281837600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/14098503/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/9/global_16422793.jpeg</photo_url></item>