<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Fox Run Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.099780</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fox Run Mall</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671465</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.806915</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There are a couple things I'd like to discuss, but a lot of this will have to be done through e-mail:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scheduling base line readings at Central Wave, and the investigation itself.&lt;br /&gt;Business cards and the website.&lt;br /&gt;Additional investigation sites - places we can access easily (I'd like to do a couple basic investigations and develop a level of proficiency and organization before we start tackling some of the more peculiar places).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's going to be a lot more &amp;quot;business&amp;quot; discussed at this meeting than some of the others, so if you plan on participating actively, this might be a good one to attend!  I chose the mall because it's easy to find, there's something to do if you get there early, and because it's not so easy to find a place that holds 20+ people without fixed reservations.  This is still only an interrim meeting place, so I'm still looking for alternatives!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I've added my photo to the MeetUp site, and I'll try to get a table as close to the food court entrance as is practical.  I'll be wearing a bright red zip up fleece with red shoulders.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234961722000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200618240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group February Meetup</name><id>7139755</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203638400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/7139755/</event_url></item>