<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Summer is here and it's time to play some tennis matches!  Join players of all levels as we get together for some rallies and Tennis Games.  The game plan is to warm-up with some rallies and then break out into some games or singles, doubles and round robin play!  We are here to have fun, get to know each other and play Tennis!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is part of our 3rd Saturday Morning of the Month Tennis Series and we hope you will join us and mark your calendars through October as well.  Players of all levels are welcome as long as you know the rules of the game and are able to rally.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School offers plenty of opportunity to play tennis on its 6 tennis courts and two practice backboards.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3rd Saturday of the Month Tennis&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 18th @ 10am&lt;br /&gt;Braintree High School&lt;br /&gt;128 Town Street&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Meeting Place: At the Tennis Courts between the practice boards and door to the courts on the side of fields (not the street/parking side).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Alternate Meeting Place: Look for us on one of the courts.  Courts are first-come-first-serve and we try to get courts next to each other.  We try to play on the courts by the backboards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Organizer(s): Kirsten C. &amp;amp; Nan / (Chandra is the AO overseeing this event.) / Please contact Kirsten or Nan w/ any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Fees: Annual Members &amp;amp; Org Team - Free, Members and Guests - $2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Min/Max: Currently, there is no maximum.  We need at least 5 Yes RSVPs by Noon on Friday, July 17th for this event to take place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Guests: 2 per member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*RSVP Deadline: 4pm on Friday, July 17th.  (Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer until after the event.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Case of Inclement Weather:&lt;br /&gt;If it is raining the event will be cancelled.  Heavy rains will cancel.  All Yes RSVPs will be emailed around the RSVP Deadline with more info.  The Event Organizer(s) may also post a note in the &amp;quot;Talk About It&amp;quot; section so be sure to check the event site if you are unsure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Directions: Posted on the &amp;quot;Directions to Frequently Used Venues&amp;quot; Discussion Thread on the Message Board (Pinned, so they're on the first page.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet by the entrance to the courts near the practice boards or on the courts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>chandra</member_name><member_id>4844140</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248307034000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245169909000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Morning Tennis</name><id>10663879</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247925600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10663879/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/0/global_3889440.jpeg</photo_url></item>