<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>114 Clay Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.396736</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ben &amp; Regan's House</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1345435</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The day after Thanksgiving is the best day for a pot luck. Everyone who celebrates it cooks too much of something. So bring your leftovers if you have them or something else if you don't (we can always use drinks, snacks and more games). Just make sure to bring yourself; someone has to eat all of this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner time will be somewhere around 5-7, but snacks and deserts will be eaten all day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unlike my other events, this will be a one day event only so it will end between 12 and 2 AM depending on when the games end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring (select all that apply ;)&lt;br /&gt;Games - We have plenty, but we don't have them all&lt;br /&gt;Food (non-snacks) - We can refrigerate or heat whatever you want to bring. I will cook a main dish of some sort, but it won't be enough for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;Food (snacks) - If you bring it, it will probably get eaten.&lt;br /&gt;Drinks (non-alcoholic) - Sometimes everyone brings some; sometimes no one does. &amp;quot;You pay your dime you take your chances.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Drinks (alcoholic) - I'm not driving and we'll have plenty of room for those who want to crash, but we're not big drinkers ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;Chairs - We have a decent number of chairs, but if it's not too much trouble you may want to bring one. You can even bring them and leave them if you have any you want to get rid of.&lt;br /&gt;Other - Bring anything you like as long as it doesn't get anyone in trouble with the law&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travel/Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Parking - I live close to the beginning of the street, so at soon as you make the turn start looking for parking. Most of the parking in the area is resident only, but I will have parking permits by the front door for everyone to park on the street. We have a driveway that can fit 3 tandem so if everyone noses up, so please pull all the way in.&lt;br /&gt;Train - we live 6-8 minute walk from the back exit of Alewife. Just walk away from the main road (the only one you can see from that exit) When you come to a fork in the trail take the middle one. Clay street is a strait shot from there. Turn left at Clay and we are on the left in a brown building.&lt;br /&gt;Bus - nearby is the 350, 77, 79, 83, 87, 88, 89&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call me if you have any questions at all. Ben 617-997-3545&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. I have a gas stove/oven, a crockpot, a smallish microwave, and a fondue pot if you want to bring anything that needs heating up. Just give me a call to make arrangements.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Warmus</member_name><member_id>5401423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290906354000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287692844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Infamous Leftover Pot Luck at Ben's</name><id>15186358</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290794400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/15186358/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/3/global_1509331.jpeg</photo_url></item>