<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Verney Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03047</zip><lat>42.974014</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crotched Mountain Rehabilitation Center</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>6460082</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.872635</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that if you actually followed the directions to get to Verney Drive (proceed 2.0 miles on Crotched Mountain Road) Google Maps gave you from our hiking website you would have passed the trail head parking lot on your left and gone an extra 0.5 miles.  Also there is both a Varney Drive and a Verney Drive at the Crotched Mtn. Rehab. Center.  You will pass Varney Drive on your right at 1.4 miles on Crotched Mtn. Road and the parking lot is just 0.1 of a mile further on your left on Crotched Mtn. Rd.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To my mind the almost 360 degrees of numerous Mountain views and the varying scenery makes this hike worth the effort it takes to do it. &lt;strong&gt;As far as I can figure over the whole hike there is a total of a 1,450 elevation gain.&lt;/strong&gt; Of course since we are ending up where we started that means you go downhill the same amount over the course of the hike. There are places where there are shorter sections of both steep ascents and descents. Hiking poles could be a big help if you have any.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a loop hike for the most part although if at least a minimum of two people or more only wanted to do a 3.6 mile hike (round trip) the first 1.8 miles of the hike could be done as a line hike (1.8 miles one way) with an elevation gain of only 800 feet.&lt;/strong&gt; This would put them at the top of the first knob/ledges of the mountain (and avoid the 1.5 mile walk along the ridge line of the mountain past several knob/ledges and return (2.6 mi.) to the parking lot also avoiding an additional 650 feet of elevation gain). But you would miss out on a lot of additional scenery and would need to remember which way to go at several intersections on the return trip (not that hard to do).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People doing the whole hike should definitely bring something to drink for both themselves and their dog(s) as well as some snacks or food (lunch?) for themselves.  It took me about 4.5 hours to do the whole hike (while also taking about 312 pictures)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the sun setting at 7:46 PM that day we will have over 10 hours of daylight to finish the hike so there will be no need to rush, there will be plenty of time to enjoy the views, just take a break, or stop for lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start on the Shannon Trail going almost to the summit (1.8 miles, elevation gain 800 ft.).  Then traverse the ridge line/knobs on the Upper Link Trail  and Summit Trail (1.5 miles, elevation gain 250 feet, but most of it is downhill).  Descend 0.2 miles on the East Summit Trail and then use the Old Mountain Road and Lower Link Trail to where it runs into the Shannon Trail 1.6 miles, elevation gain 400 ft.).  Then descend (0.8) miles on the Shannon Trail to get back to the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail map: &lt;a href="http://www.francestown-nh.gov/Pages/FrancestownNH_ConCom/crotchedmap.pdf"&gt;http://www.francestown-nh.gov/Pages/FrancestownNH_ConCom/crotchedmap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With more people willing to car pool or wanting a car to follow to get to Crotched Mtn. Rehab. Center who will be going through or near (all of us so far) Manchester to get there I am going to set up a meeting place at Harvest Market, 209 New Hampshire 101, Bedford, NH for 8:50 AM. The entrance to the parking lot is on Wallace Road. The weather is supposed to be sunny and in the low 50's for the hike. Northwest winds 15 - 20 miles per hour.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Once you turn off of Rt. 31 onto Crotched Mtn. Rd. proceed for 1.5 miles and then turn left into the trailhead parking lot.  At 1.4 miles you will drive straight past Varney Drive on your right, staying on Crotched Mtn. Rd. another 0.1 miles, turn L.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335791869000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333170120000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crotched Mtn. - 5.9 miles - Scenic Mtn. Views (almost 360 degrees) Moderate +</name><id>58627632</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335708000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/58627632/</event_url></item>