<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>47 Charles Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357422</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Toscano Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>5631252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070076</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Restaurant week is nigh....so join me for Italian fare at &lt;a href="http://www.toscanoboston.com/"&gt;Toscano&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in Boston's Beacon Hill. Their stellar reputation has been earned from their wonderful Tuscan gastronomic interpretation. Take a look at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.restaurantweekboston.com/restaurant/toscano/"&gt;Toscano restaurant dinner week menu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;so you're prepared to place your order and we are able to enjoy our meal soon after we're seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Restaurant Week prix fixe dinner menu cost is $33.12 for three-course dinner which does NOT include beverages, tax or gratuity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may choose only one dish from each of the Restaurant Week Menu courses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to create your route by public transit. Ten minute walk from Park station (green line) or Charles/MGH station (red line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRIVING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to plan your route&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're able to find parking on the street, I suggest you read the street signs to ensure it is a legal space, otherwise check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://boston.bestparking.com/#1" target="_blank"&gt;Best Parking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://parkingcarma.com/ParkingSearchResults.aspx?Address=545%20boylston%20street%2002116" target="_blank"&gt;Parking Carma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for nearby parking garages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced. I want to assure you I do understand if you've RSVPd YES and on the day of our meal you have a sudden change of plans because you're lost, you don't feel well or you have transportation issues. My only request is for you to let me know as soon as possible so we don't worry about you and our reservation is adjusted. As long as you contact me you will not be considered a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules for Events with Reservations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it is less than an hour from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;(617) 445-7549&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All RSVPs are on a first reply, first seated basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the meal is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP and if you answered the RSVP question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the meal and you have not attended nor contacted me, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update meal confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW each will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within an hour of the reservation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you do not contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events with reservations you are removed from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be arrive at 5:45 PM to welcome you from the Toscano entrance.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call/text my cell (617) 445 7549 or email snowrover@yahoo.com to find us - Tonya</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1333052931000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330205486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Restaurant Week Dinner at Toscano on Wednesday March 28th at 6 PM</name><id>53801602</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332972000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/53801602/</event_url></item>