<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Weisner Bldg (E15) Lower Level</address_2><address_1>20 Ames Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.360748</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5229</phone><name>MIT Bartos Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1396923</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/9/0/event_157739792.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2012 MIT Auto-ID Labs Big Data Startup Competition and Conference &lt;br /&gt;

 Big, Cloudy and Mobile Applications in omni-channel retail supply chain, smart transportation logistics and mobile retail commerce October 9-10, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Challenge &lt;br /&gt;

 What’s the challenge? Create a mobile retail application prototype or develop a mobile retail application or service to improve the retail demand chain using Big Data. &lt;br /&gt;

 1) Developers should address how their application or service will improve marketing, sales, or customer service. &lt;br /&gt;

 2) Developers are encouraged to point out where industry specifications would assist in ensuring interoperability across stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit Today! &lt;br /&gt;

 Submit your completed (1) page Entry Form* to MIT Auto-ID Labs [s_miles@mit.edu] by September 15, to be short-listed for this completition with information including: &lt;br /&gt;

 • Name (with full contact) &lt;br /&gt;

 • Team/Company &lt;br /&gt;

 • Concept or Prototype &lt;br /&gt;

 • How Will It Work &lt;br /&gt;

 o What Is Required for the Consumer, for the Retailer? &lt;br /&gt;

 • Expected Results &lt;br /&gt;

 o Why Will Retailers Want and Need It? &lt;br /&gt;

 o How Will It Help Improve the Retail Experience and Drive Sales? &lt;br /&gt;

 * Auto-ID Labs Big Data Start-up Competition Entry Form can be found at: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://autoid.mit.edu/cs/" class="linkified"&gt;http://autoid.mit.edu/cs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Big, Cloudy, and Mobile: The Mobile Retail App Developer Competition&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overview &lt;br /&gt;

 Everywhere you look, consumers are turning to their smartphones and social media to get more value and better inform their shopping experience. The resulting data is creating new opportunities for retailers to better understand the wants and needs of their consumers, to improve the customer experience and ultimately drive more sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retail chains are complex ecosystems producing large and diverse data-sets. Object identification technologies like RFID, NFC and barcodes also create new streams of data. And numerous platforms and websites are sprouting up that offer location-based deals and sales promotions for consumers using the myriad data sources. There is tremendous potential for Big Data applications that mine and aggregate information from these data silos and merge this with Hadoop data sources to improve retailer supply chain efficiencies and enhance the shopping experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How can retailers improve the real-time interaction between consumers and goods on the retail floor using mobile? What can be learned to drive sales and profit for retailers – large and small? How can retailers improve the overall brand experience for consumers? Those are just a few of the questions that should be answered in the Mobile Retail App Challenge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Challenge &lt;br /&gt;

 What’s the challenge? Create a mobile retail application prototype or develop a mobile retail application or service to improve the retail demand chain using Big Data. &lt;br /&gt;

 1) Developers should address how their application or service will improve some business process such as marketing, sales, or customer service. &lt;br /&gt;

 2) Developers are encouraged to point out where industry specifications would assist in structuring data and ensuring interoperability across stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can you use? &lt;br /&gt;

 Retail ID technology, including any combination of RFID and NFC technology, Android or iOS, barcodes (QR or other), social media, augmented reality (ie. MagicMirror), and other mobile technologies (ie. contactless payments).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All applications should adhere to the GS-1/EPCglobal Electronic Product Code (EPC) standards for identifying products to ensure interoperability between retailers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who is qualified to enter? Why should you enter? &lt;br /&gt;

 • Only companies less than 5 years old and either privately funded or “C” series funding or below are eligible for the Auto-ID Labs Big Data Start-up Competition. &lt;br /&gt;

 • Companies must register to attend the Auto-ID Labs Big Data Conference Oct 9-10 where presentations to judges by the finalists will be made. &lt;br /&gt;

 • The winner will receive a consulting session with a major retailer, and a private lunch with a Big Data investor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit Today &lt;br /&gt;

 Submit your completed (1) page application to MIT Auto-ID Labs by September 15, including: &lt;br /&gt;

 1. Name (with full contact) &lt;br /&gt;

 2. Team/Company &lt;br /&gt;

 3. Concept or Prototype &lt;br /&gt;

 4. How Will It Work - What Is Required for the Consumer, for the Retailer? &lt;br /&gt;

 5. Expected Results &lt;br /&gt;

 a. Why Will Retailers Want and Need It? &lt;br /&gt;

 b. How Will It Help Improve the Retail Experience and Drive Sales?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top 10 submissions will be selected and notified by September 22. The semi-finalists will present their prototypes and applications pecha-kucha style (20 slides x 20 seconds) on October 9 at the Auto-ID Labs Big Data Conference at MIT, to a panel of judges including: &lt;br /&gt;

 • Abhi Dhar, CTO, Walgreens.com, Walgreens &lt;br /&gt;

 • Mike Baker, CEO, DataXu &lt;br /&gt;

 • Chris Lynch, Atlas Ventures, former CEO Vertica &lt;br /&gt;

 • Sanjay Sarma, Co-founder Auto-ID Labs &lt;br /&gt;

 • And other judges to be announced&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presentations by finalists occur over lunch on October 9 and the winner will be announced October 10 at noon. You must register to participate: &lt;br /&gt;

 2012 MIT Auto-ID Labs Big Data Conference &lt;br /&gt;

 Big, Cloudy and Mobile Applications in omni-channel retail supply chain, smart transportation logistics and mobile retail commerce &lt;br /&gt;

 October 9-10, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://ilp.mit.edu/conference.jsp?confid=70&amp;amp;tabname=overview" class="linkified"&gt;http://ilp.mit.edu/conference.jsp?confid=70&amp;amp;tabname=overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For questions please contact Stephen Miles, Research Scientist and Conference Organizer at: s_miles@mit.edu&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Miles</member_name><member_id>10116261</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350308395000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347280262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Auto-ID Labs Big Data Startup Competition and Conference Oct 9-10 at MIT</name><id>81696252</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349784000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/81696252/</event_url></item>