<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Anderson Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.669738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Urban Farm Fermentory</name><city>Portland</city><id>1327313</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256485</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us this Thursday night for a social and educational event... &lt;strong&gt;The New England Climate Riders* are in town and we'd like to welcome them with a potluck supper at Portland's own Urban Farm Fermentory&lt;/strong&gt; on Anderson Street in Portland (just off of Marginal Way). &amp;nbsp;Enjoy a warm summer evening meeting the riders, connecting with one another and admiring the progress of the UFF's "urban farm" in the middle of the city. &amp;nbsp;We'll also be drumming up support for our own imminent series on "Growing Food in the City" that will start in September. &amp;nbsp;Weigh in on other upcoming skillshares and events for our permaculture group, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 Potluck/Social Time (bring a dish/drink to share and your own potluck kit)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 Announcements &amp;amp; Introduce Climate Riders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:30 Climate Riders report on their progress/share some of their findings and footage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Socialize &amp;amp; closing...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.climatesummer.net/the-teams/maine/"&gt;Meet the Maine Team!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*About Climate Summer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"New England Climate Summer is a summer internship program for college students, graduate students, and recent graduates. Climate Summer riders travel exclusively by bicycle in small teams across New England, spending approximately one week in a community before biking on to the next. While in each town, riders connect with community leaders that are actively addressing society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to fossil fuels by crafting local solutions that strengthen communities. Riders bring with them a movement-building perspective and ethos, empowering those they meet and helping to highlight the important work of local organizations with the local press as well as in the 2011 State of the Movement Report, which will catalogue the efforts of groups in all the communities the various teams visit."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Homa </member_name><member_id>2587064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309554342000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309203904000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck &amp; Forum w/The New England Climate Summer Riders</name><id>23708061</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309473000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/23708061/</event_url></item>