<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Gainsborough St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.341120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jordan Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>668980</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/2/1/e/event_22653310.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;It's time for the next FREE classical music concert for the spring season at the New England Conservatory of Music!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight, The NEC Chamber Orchestra takes the stage again for a program featuring the works of Veress, Mozart and Schoenberg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NEC Chamber Orchestra, NEC's conductorless orchestra, was created in 2000 by double bassist &lt;a href="http://necmusic.edu/faculty/donald-palma?lid=2&amp;amp;sid=3"&gt;Donald Palma&lt;/a&gt;, a founding member of Orpheus Chamber Orchestra.  It gives young players a chance to work together in a completely new way, each player taking full responsibility for the sound of the group. Palma's regular coaching is supplemented by other members of the NEC faculty.Music of the classical era by Handel, Haydn, and Mozart is at the core of virtually every program, along with an occasional baroque work, as well as modern pieces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight's concert features &lt;em&gt;Four Transylvanian Dances&lt;/em&gt; by Sándor Veress, who was mentored by Bartok, and who is said to have "out-Bartoked Bartok." The younger Hungarian composer completed these dances in the late 1940s shortly after he had decided not to return to his homeland and risk political and artistic repression and it is hard not to hear both defiance and a leave-taking in this music. The composer describes the dances as "free re-creations of certain styles of dance music indigenous to Hungarian villages, particularly to the Székler of Transylvania."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other works include the Mozart &lt;em&gt;Divertimento No.11 in D-major, K.251&lt;/em&gt; and Schoenberg's &lt;em&gt;Transfigured Night&lt;/em&gt;.  The latter is heard in the string orchestra version that the composer arranged in 1917 and subsequently revised in 1943. This performance, paired with the January 31 &lt;a href="http://necmusic.edu/transfigured-night"&gt;NEC Contemporary Ensemble&lt;/a&gt; performance of the original 1899 sextet version, offers listeners an unusual opportunity to see how the composer's vision of the piece—probably his most popular—changed over the course of his life. (Listen to excerpts below; the names in the list link to youtube performances of the works.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let's meet up at no later than 7:30pm,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; so the group can grab a bunch of seats together when the doors open, and then socialize before the concert.  We will probably end up sitting in the back of the center section in the main hall, as they usually don't open the balcony for these concerts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to Jordan Hall:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The hall is located at &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=jordan+Hall,+Boston+MA&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=59.467068,135.263672&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.342781,-71.085577&amp;amp;spn=0.006883,0.020599&amp;amp;z=17" target="_blank"&gt;the corner of Huntington and Gainsborough streets&lt;/a&gt;, about a block south of the Symphony T stop on the Green Line. It's also close to the Mass Ave station on the Orange line.  Look for the building with the YMCA sign on top of it as you walk down Huntington Ave--it's near that building. The main entrance is reached from Gainsborough Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This evening's program will include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KQVPKN7ybq4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sándor Veress&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KQVPKN7ybq4"&gt;Four Transylvanian Dances&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O5v6XYF1Xpw"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mozart&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O5v6XYF1Xpw"&gt;Divertimento No.11 in D-major, K.251&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vQDxn_LMCfQ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schoenberg&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vQDxn_LMCfQ"&gt;Transfigured Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will stand in the lobby until 7:45, after which I will join the group upstairs in the left-middle balcony section.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Will</member_name><member_id>7339843</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362164361000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360290668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEC Spring Concert Series: NEC Chamber Orchestra + Veress, Mozart &amp; Schoenberg</name><id>103605232</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362011400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/103605232/</event_url></item>