<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St., Suite 6B</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-639-1236</phone><name>A Higher Balance Healing Center</name><city>Salem</city><id>1342529</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895192</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>475.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Soul Therapy Practitioner Certification Program&lt;br /&gt;With Elizabeth Foley&lt;br /&gt;Four weekends, Jan. – April 2011&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each of us has a unique Divine soul and soul mission. The Soul Therapy Practitioner (STP) Program is dedicated to an in-depth discovery, healing and clearing of the different aspects of your mental, emotional, physical and spiritual bodies. The goal of the STP program is to help you discover and align your inner spiritual life with your outer life and to empower yourself and others. In this powerful certification course, not only will you embark on your own inner sacred quest, but you also will learn how to assist others on their spiritual journey and discovery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Soul Therapy Practitioner program is a program that includes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  1.. What is the Soul and Understanding the Energy of Your Soul &lt;br /&gt;  2.. Listening and Connecting to Your Soul &lt;br /&gt;  3.. Understanding and Opening the Seven Seals (the chakras) &lt;br /&gt;  4.. The Seven Rays and How They Guide Your Soul &lt;br /&gt;  5.. Development of the Soul (discovering your soul age, level and role) &lt;br /&gt;  6.. Basics of Spiritual Psychology  &lt;br /&gt;  7.. Awakening the Physical, Mental, Emotional &amp;amp; Spiritual Body &lt;br /&gt;  8.. Tools for Emotional and Spiritual Healing&lt;br /&gt;  9.. Tests of Initiation of the Soul &lt;br /&gt; 10.. Steps to Attain Mastery and Manifest Your Mission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Program fee:  $475.  Program runs Jan 22-23; Feb 19-20; Mar 19-20 and Apr 16-17, 2011; 10AM - 4PM  (no sessions can be missed in order to graduate)&lt;br /&gt;Registration required:  findrskeep@aol.com or 781-639-1831&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth J. Foley, EdM, MPH is an international Angelologist, teacher,healer and author and conducts private angel sessions and spiritual workshops on angels, psychic development and Soul Therapy throughout the country. For more information, go to &lt;a href="http://www.divinehealing.us" target="_blank"&gt;www.divinehealing.us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy Copp</member_name><member_id>8642061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295713750000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Evolving Beings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Evolving-Beings</urlname><id>1429576</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>Evolving Beings</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294371488000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Soul Therapy Practitioner Certification Program with Elizabeth Foley</name><id>15953944</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Evolving-Beings/events/15953944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/4/global_8055188.jpeg</photo_url></item>