<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Mountain Rd</address_2><address_1>Route 171</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03254</zip><lat>43.752885</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ossipee Mtns - Shannon Brook Trail</name><city>Moultonborough</city><id>1236796</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.372738</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE SLIGHT TIME CHANGE -&amp;nbsp;Carpool: 10AM&amp;nbsp;// Trail: 11:30AM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;The Ossipee Mountain range is a 9-mile wide circular wilderness that rises 2000'-3000' directly above Lake Winnipesaukee. Views of the lake, the White Mountains, and the surrounding countryside are absolutely outstanding. Our route along Shannon Brook will bring us past streams and waterfalls and up to a granite ledge lookout point. We'll be hiking near the grounds of &lt;a href="http://www.castleintheclouds.org/"&gt;Castle in the Clouds&lt;/a&gt;, an Arts &amp;amp; Crafts-style estate owned by the &lt;a href="http://www.lrct.org/"&gt;Lakes Region Conservation Trust&lt;/a&gt;. Trails vary from wide and flat to rocky and steep but this hike will mostly easy. The difficulty level is about the same at Mount Major. We should be on the trail for about 3.5 to 4 hours. Bring something to eat for the hike but we'll also stop at the &lt;a href="http://www.poorpeoplespub.com/"&gt;Poor People's Pub&lt;/a&gt; on the way home. It's a very friendly place we found after a snowshoe last winter, located on RT 109 in Sanbornville half a mile east of Rt 16.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CARPOOL&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;10:00 AM &lt;/span&gt;@ Dover CJ Trailways Park &amp;amp; Ride Spaulding Tpk north to Exit 9 - Left @ light - then Left @ 2nd light.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt;: Follow Rt 16 north to Rt 171 (~36mi from Dover exit 9). Turn LEFT &amp;amp; follow Rt 171 for &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;exactly 12.5 miles&lt;/span&gt; from Rt 16. The Shannon Brook Trail parking area is on the left, just before the intersection w/ Severance Rd in Moultonborough, NH. Drive time from Dover is ~65 minutes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.franklinsites.com/hikephotos/files/nhtrailbanditossipees.php"&gt;Click here for a trail map.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;PLEASE ASK ME BEFORE BRINGING&amp;nbsp;A DOG. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #272727"&gt;The isolated and undeveloped mass of the Ossipee range is the largest and least disturbed wildlife habitat in the region. The range is 9 miles in diameter, its tallest summit rising to an elevation of 2,975 feet. The Ossipees consist of a circular land mass of more than 40,000 acres, accessed by only three interior roads, none of which bisect the area. There are 25 named mountains and dozens of unnamed summits within the range; 16 named brooks originate in the Ossipees, while scores of smaller watercourses create ravines within its borders. As a part of its conservation work within the Ossipees, the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.lrct.org/"&gt;Lakes Region Conservation Trust&lt;/a&gt; has commissioned a series of scientific bioinventories which serve to underscore the uniqueness of this natural treasure. The biodiversity of this land has been largely unaffected by human hands, to the great benefit and consistent proliferation of the species inside its borders. Old growth softwoods dating back to the 1590&amp;rsquo;s have been discovered, hardwood groves exceeding 300 years of age have been catalogued, 38 natural communities described, and more than a score of species deemed endangered or threatened on a statewide to global scale. Working in cooperation with the Nature Conservancy, the AMC, The New England Wildflower Society, The Society for the Protection of New Hampshire Forests, and other groups, the Trust seeks to protect the remainder of the Ossipees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&lt;/strong&gt; hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs,&amp;nbsp;and all members&amp;nbsp;and participants&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group&amp;nbsp;from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage&amp;nbsp;including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience&amp;nbsp;and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;As organizer, I make no claims regarding any skills or expertise for this outing.&amp;nbsp; -Larry Pilla&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306762392000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306261113000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ossipee Range - Shannon Brook Trail</name><id>19558791</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306626300000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/19558791/</event_url></item>