<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Robin Hood Spring Festival transports attendees into a merry medieval village named in honor of the fabled wealth redistributor. Regular shows during the festivities enthrall guests with Robin Hood’s legend, as Sheriff Nottingham, Maid Marian, and Prince John wander the grounds, desperately searching for the portal back to the 15th century. In addition to playing games and gazing in awe of performances by fire breathers and archers, patrons can learn to sing Middle Ages tunes, don a costume and march along with the Royal Procession parade, or cheer on their favorite armored knight during jousting tournaments. After the final joust, a final sing closes out each day with songs and skits by bards and performers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Connecticut Renaissance Faire 
&lt;p&gt;A crack rings out from the jousting arena as armored knights clash in the pursuit of honor, while sword-swallowers thrill crowds with their death-defying art, jesters spin windy jokes, and townspeople in 15th-century garb roam the grounds tearing into turkey legs with their teeth. The Connecticut Renaissance Faire hosts these medieval-theme blowouts every year, including the Robin Hood Spring Festival and King Arthur’s Fall Harvest Faire. Under the themed umbrella of each gathering, actors caper about a constructed medieval village, engaging in Old English–flavored conversation and clapping games with fair-goers. In a tented marketplace, vendors sell beaded crafts, art, and tyrannical-king repellent alongside stands serving mead, beer, and other satisfying sundries. Although the shows and events vary at each fair, past spectacles have included archery displays, pub sing-alongs, and costume parades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See webpage for more details:  &lt;a href="http://www.robinhoodsfaire.com/connecticut/ct_special_events.php"&gt;http://www.robinhoodsfaire.com/connecticut/ct_special_events.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP and we'll set up a rendevous point.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda</member_name><member_id>3403216</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph Ring</member_name><member_id>3405781</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336954044000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-28</urlname><id>364032</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Heights Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336008282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT Renn Faire</name><id>63185792</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336928400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-28/events/63185792/</event_url></item>