<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Young Producing Change&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; by various directors (2009, 62 min.). Founding presenter: Adobe Youth Voices. &lt;b&gt;A program of short films created by filmmakers under the age of 19. Armed with digital cameras and their own creativity, young people across the globe are bravely exposing human rights issues faced by themselves and their communities. Discussion with the directors follows screening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teen filmmakers from Seattle, New York and Boston will be in attendance for a Q&amp;amp;A. There will be a free reception following the screening at the School of the Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: coral"&gt;Leila&lt;/span&gt; by 16 youth filmmakers from Camera-etc. (Burkina Faso, 2007, 4 min). This enchantingly rendered animated short tells the story of Liela, an only daughter of poor farmers who decide to exchange her for one bag of millet to feed the rest of their family. The story focuses on the lives of children that are sold into servitude. In French with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;Sako&lt;/span&gt; by Aram Abrahamyan and David Martirosyan of Manana Youth Center (Armenia, 2005, 5 min.). Meet Sako, a 13 year old boy who works in a gravestone factory in order to support his family. Sako speaks about his daily life, and his dreams of going to school. In Armenian with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Mozambique&lt;/span&gt; by Alcides Soares in association with BYkids (US/Mozambique, 2008, 12 min). Alcides, who recently lost both parents to HIV/AIDS, documents the community impact of the epidemic. His story focuses on the realities for children left to fend for themselves; their resilience to recreate family and to persevere. In English and Portuguese with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Thoughts&lt;/span&gt; In A Hijab by Cliona Byrne, Eimanne El Zein, and Sahar Shakeri of Reel Grrls (US, 2008, 7 min). A young woman who recently emigrated from Iran, and her choice to continue wearing the hijab (Islamic head covering) that once symbolized oppression for her family. In English and Persian with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Noè’s Story&lt;/span&gt; by Noè in association with Beyond Borders: Mas Alla de las Fronteras (US, 2008, 5 min.). Noè, 15, a recent immigrant to the US, explores his identity in his new country. Driven to succeed despite obstacles he faces, he challenges other new immigrants not to give up hope. In Spanish with English subtitles.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;What Courage Means to Me&lt;/span&gt; by Lekphel, Lungsang, Pema, Tashi, and students at Tibetan Children’s Village in collaboration with Bridges to Understanding (US/Tibet, 2008, 4 min.). Inspired by the courageous story of a Tibetan nun and former political prisoner who escaped Tibet, Lungsang resolves to keep Tibetan culture alive for the next generation. In English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Aquafinito&lt;/span&gt; by Annalise Littman in association with the Fast Forward Program at the Insitute of Contemporary Art (US, 2009, 10 min.). Access to clean water is a basic human necessity, yet corporations seeking profit are purchasing community water supplies around the world. Aquafinito raises awareness of the human rights and environmental impact of bottled water. In English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;It’s Not About Sex&lt;/span&gt; by Ibrahim Al Hashidi, Aaron A. Alberto, David Brice, Jessica Cele, Everin Khatun, Will Lucas, Shon McGoy, Justin Miro, Paola Pazymino, Daniel Potts, Luis Rodriguez, Sara Siddique Akeem Smith in association with Educational Video Center (US, 2009. 8 min.). Shocked by the claim that more than half of all rapes happen to people under 18, young filmmakers search for the roots of sexual violence and call for change. In English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orange"&gt;Just a Normal Day&lt;/span&gt; by Fiona Whelan, Samantha Williams, and Arran Walker in association with BFI Reel Lives (UK, 2008, 5 min.). The grim reality of life for young people in London who are targets of arbitrary &amp;quot;stop and search&amp;quot; and maltreatment by police. In English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;In My Shoes&lt;/span&gt; by 12 youth filmmakers from Urban Arts Partnership (US, 2008, 8 min.). Each night 1,600 teenagers in New York City find themselves homeless. Clevins and Jackie, two formerly homeless teens from New York City share their stories of overcoming adversity and their work to create a community of support around teen homelessness. In English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Member, seniors, and students $8; general admission $10&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special Offer: BUY ONE STUDENT TICKET for 7pm screening at the box office, GET ONE FREE upon presentation of valid student ID. Offer not valid for online or telephone ticket purchases.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for John's Meetup Sign somewhat near the front, and throughout the reception at the Museum School of the Arts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263756672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Youth Producing Change</name><id>12344377</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264204800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12344377/</event_url></item>