<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;White Sun of the Desert&lt;/b&gt; USSR 1970  85 minutes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most popular Russian films of all times, this action/comedy/music/adventure, has achieved cult status. Set during the the Russian Civil War, a soldier named Sukhov (Anatoly Kuznetsov) is making his way through the desert to return home to his wife, when he's forced to guard the harem of rebel leader Abdulla (Kakhi Kavsadze). Director Vladimir Motyl, influenced by classic American movies &lt;b&gt;Stagecoach&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;High Noon&lt;/b&gt; described his film as a &amp;quot;cocktail&amp;quot; of both a Russian folktale and a western. Come and be intoxicated!  Coolidge Corner description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rumored to be required viewing by all cosmonauts before shooting into space, it's easy to see how this military adventure has become a cult favorite, with its oddball wit and an elegant simplicity to what was likely underfunded stunt work. Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soviet action-adventure films set during the Russian Civil War of 1918-1921 were often jokingly referred to as &amp;quot;easterns&amp;quot; since they used the conventions of the Western genre while transposing them to Eastern European settings. &lt;b&gt;White Sun of the Desert&lt;/b&gt; took the genre even further east, to Central Asia, where fighting between the Red Army and the local nationalist forces continued well into the 1920s. This movie became a huge hit in its home country, largely because of its unabashed lyricism, deadpan humor, and the absence of the heavy ideological clichés that permeated the genre at the time. Viewers could also sympathize with the folksy, resourceful protagonist who resembled more a character from Russian fairy tales than an actual Red Army soldier. And despite spouting revolutionary slogans in a poker-faced manner, Sukhov remained essentially an ordinary Russian with whom anybody could identify. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row at the film's conclusion.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214932171000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213826535000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>USSR's White Sun of the Desert</name><id>8168488</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214758800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8168488/</event_url></item>