<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Lansdowne Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.247.1222</phone><name>The Lansdowne Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>1088408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094957</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Folks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week's Live Karaoke event was a smashing success. We had about 18 people from our group and &amp;quot;Fun with Alcohol!&amp;quot;. It turns out we have some talented folks in the groups. Matt truly rocked the place on the harmonica. The live band twist on Karaoke is really great - it's so much more fun singing on stage with a band backing you (and helping when you screw up!). The free appetizers were great too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who couldn't make it last week here's the deal:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lansdowne Pub has a fun new twist on Karaoke - a live backing band! No more crappy sound system and cheezy fake music behind you. Get up on stage and belt with the band. The backing band is the &amp;quot;Jukebox Heroes&amp;quot;. They have a song list of ~150 songs - something for everyone! I will be posting their song list so look for it under the &amp;quot;Files&amp;quot; menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We''l start at 9:00PM so we have have time for a few drinks before the Karaoke starts. Nobody should attempt karaoke without having a few drinks first :-) We've reserved a table for 20+ people near the stage and The Lansdowne is providing free appetizers for the first hour!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on out and channel your inner rock star!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Friendly organizer,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patrick&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;This is a joint meetup with Fun with Alcohol, so we're gonna have a big, fun group - again!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the "L" shaped table to the left of the stage.  I'm the guy with the ponytail who looks suspiciously like my picture :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick</member_name><member_id>8876864</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261624055000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260546303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Band Karaoke at The Lansdowne Pub!</name><id>12065436</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261101600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/12065436/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/6/8/global_11887640.jpeg</photo_url></item>