<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you've ever been backpacking, you've probably heard people boast that their pack weighs 50 or 60 lbs. Those days are over. With a little knowledge and careful gear selection, it is possible for anyone to reduce their pack weight to a comfortable 20 or 25 lbs, even for a week long trip. By carrying less weight in your pack, you can hike further, see more, experience less fatigue, and prevent injuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this talk, Philip Werner will discuss a number of different strategies for reducing your gear weight and demonstrate some of the cutting edge gear used by lightweight and ultralight hikers, including products from leading manufacturers, both small and large, that are leaders in the lightweight backpacking revolution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Philip Werner is a well-known lightweight backpacker and author of the highly acclaimed backpacking and hiking blog&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://sectionhiker.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SectionHiker.com&lt;/a&gt;. When he&amp;rsquo;s not section hiking the Appalachian Trail, he spends most of his time roaming the White Mountains and writing about backpacking, hiking, camping, and mountaineering. Philip is also a Trail Ambassador for Gossamer Gear and an evangelist for lightweight and ultralight backpacking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doors open @ 6:15 PM - potluck @ 6:30 PM then show @ 7:15 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you plan to attend, please send your RSVP to Julie at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a&gt;AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30, feel free to use the following guidelines: Last names beginning with A-J bring a main dish, K-S bring an appetizer or side dish, T-Z bring a dessert or drink. Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome:) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The AMC Auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (stovetop, oven, microwave, sink, fridge, etc).&amp;nbsp;Please bring your own pot for rewarming dishes on the stovetop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the event of a schedule change or cancellation, an email will be sent out to those who RSVP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subway Directions:&amp;nbsp;Take the Red Line T to Park Street Station. Walk through the Boston Common uphill towards the State House &amp;amp; Beacon Street. Continue up Joy St, which runs along the left side of the State House. The Auditorium is #4 Joy Street (just before the AMC Headquarters Building, on the left side).&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4471089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306539675000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304333816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Lightweight &amp; Ultralight Backpacking (Potluck &amp; Demonstration)</name><id>17508182</id><headcount>52</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306276200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17508182/</event_url></item>