<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>263 Pearl St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358239</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gallery 263</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1008719</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109611</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Greetings AWers -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At our last meeting, we discussed starting a new cluster group that will meet monthly. The new salon cluster will provide a resource for sharing of creative work, supportive networking and establishing &amp;quot;believing mirror&amp;quot; mentoring, as well as guest lecturers and artists.  The salon is designed for those who have read the Artist's Way book and/or others of Julia Cameron's trilogy on the theme of creative reawakening.  The salon is not a working group on the book, but rather an extension of the peer networking established after working through a cluster which has focused on the chapters.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first salon will be on Thursday June 10th at 7pm. I am hoping we can meet at the Gallery (263) as we have done for the past several months. I will be posting the confirmation shortly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in presenting your work and are open to a Q&amp;amp;A with the salon membership, please submit your idea and topic a minimum of two weeks prior to the salon date.  (This will allow for a line up of possible presenters and give me an opportunity to pair presentations appropriately.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All media are welcome -- we are writers, poets, musicians, glass makers, sculptors, photographers, painters, performance artists, chefs (!), book and paper makers, film and videographers -- and all other forms accepted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep the faith, the inspiration, the courage and the discipline --&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will greet you at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brooke</member_name><member_id>8390120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276283282000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Artists and Creators!</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Artists-Way-Boston-area</urlname><id>1471304</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Artists Way Boston Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272764365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Artist's Way Salon Evenings</name><id>13353375</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276210800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Artists-Way-Boston-area/events/13353375/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/9/global_13316729.jpeg</photo_url></item>