<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1008 Cambridge Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.372640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 354-3296</phone><name>Muqueca Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1111960</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093872</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Due to popular demand, I have scheduled a Meetup at Muquecas. &lt;br /&gt;The reservation is set for 7pm.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will look for an after dinner Meetup option.  &lt;br /&gt;There will most likely be some Brazilian music event in the area, once I learn what is happening later in that evening, I will notify the group, so stay tuned. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before you confirm you reservation, I ask that you only reserve &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; if you are absolutely certain that you are able to attend the Meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;If you are uncertain, please choose &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;Also, if you reserve &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and have a change of plans, please change your reservation to a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; as soon as possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order for this to be a successful Meetup, I need an accurate count in order to ensure enough seats for all who have signed-up. The restaurant will be setting seats aside for our Meetup group and away from customers, so I want to be courteous and establish a good reputation for future Meetups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.muquecarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.muquecarestaurant.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.muquecares...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Muqueca Restaurant is located in the charming neighborhood of Inman Square, less than a twenty minute walk from the major universities. Stop by anytime and find out a small family-style ambiance offering an authentic menu from the region of Espirito Santo, where seafood such as fish and shrimp flavored with cilantro, annatto seeds, and olive oil are cooked with freshest and purest ingredients in a huge clay pot.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joana</member_name><member_id>4876115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276261133000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273085518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Muquecas - Northeastern Brazilian food - New start time **7PM***</name><id>13395188</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275692400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/13395188/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/7/global_14852439.jpeg</photo_url></item>