<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:10, so let's meet at 6:30 on Friday night to buy our tickets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as current as you can. And please call me if you're going to be late or have a last-minute RSVP (508/308-4897).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you Friday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810049115/info" target="_blank"&gt;Duplicity&lt;/a&gt; with Julia Roberts and Clive Owen opened last week, so let's go see it this Friday night. I'll update the time when the theater releases its showtimes (should be tomorrow or Thursday).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;CIA officer Claire Stenwick and MI6 agent Ray Koval have left the world of government intelligence to cash in on the highly profitable cold war raging between two rival multinational corporations. Their mission? Secure the formula for a product that will bring a fortune to the company that patents it first. For their employers--industry titan Howard Tully and buccaneer CEO Dick Garsik--nothing is out of bounds. But as the stakes rise, the mystery deepens and the tactics get dirtier, the trickiest secret for Claire and Ray is their growing attraction. And as they each try to stay one double-cross ahead, two career loners find their schemes endangered by the only thing they can't cheat their way out of: love.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers eacg for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are always welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Duplicity!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238370466000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237913656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Duplicity</name><id>10024652</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238193000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10024652/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>