<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395439</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Eastern Bank (formerly Wainwright Bank) </name><city>Somerville</city><id>1616823</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTON DYKE MARCH: THE NEXT GENERATION &lt;br /&gt;

 Join the NEW Boston Dyke March Committee!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEXT TWO MEETINGS: Tues April 16 &amp;amp; April 23, 7:00-9:00pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Eastern Bank Meeting Room, Davis Sq. Somerville&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help plan one of the country's largest and most progressive Dyke Marches and have a great time doing it! Since 2000 the Boston Dyke March has increased from 350 participants to close to 3000 participants. The Boston Dyke March is recruiting a brand new committee to continue the successful legacy of the 3rd largest dyke march in the nation. Now it is time for YOU to carry the torch into the next generation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Dyke March is a non-commercial, community-centered, grassroots, inclusive pride event. Come be a part of the transformative action: plan fun events, network with cool people, meet hotties and make new friends, build your resume, and help make the March what you want it to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dyke March is for everyone: Dykes, Lesbians, Queers, Bi-Folks, Transwomen, Transmen, Genderqueers, and Allies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artists, writers, organizers, political activists, fun social people, quiet detail-oriented people, techies, photographers, handi-queers, inexperienced people who want to learn exciting new stuff, experienced people who like the freedom of grassroots organizing, fundraisers, shy people who like working in groups, rowdy people that make everyone laugh, single people just looking for to meet someone new, partnered people who love socializing, business types, academics, jack-of-all-trades… the Dyke March needs YOU!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info… &lt;br /&gt;

 Website: www.bostondykemarch.com &lt;br /&gt;

 Facebook: facebook.com/dykemarch [Boston Dyke March] &lt;br /&gt;

 Meetup: &lt;a href="http://lgbtfriends.meetup.com/186/" class="linkified"&gt;http://lgbtfriends.meetup.com/186/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Email: dykemarch@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boston Dyke March</member_name><member_id>3425442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366160562000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of the Boston Dyke March</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostondykemarch</urlname><id>997856</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Dyke March</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365987544000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join the NEW Boston Dyke March Committee!</name><id>114364382</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366153200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostondykemarch/events/114364382/</event_url></item>