<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>561 Cambridge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.371788</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-3278</phone><name>East Side Bar &amp; Grille</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1221704</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085669</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This will probably be the last ice skating event I'll schedule for the season. Most ice skating rinks are managed by the state and have closed for the season. Simoni ice skating rink in Cambridge is privately managed and is open for a couple more weeks. On Fridays they have an adult skate from 10:00 p.m. to midnight. It's $5.00 to skate, and if you don't have your own skates there is a $4.00 rental fee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to meet at 8:30 p.m. at East Side Bar &amp;amp; Grille for drinks and pizza and socializing beforehand. East Side Bar &amp;amp; Grille has a great selection to drink, plays only Frank Sinatra music and is one block from the rink. It's on Cambridge Street at the corner of 7th Street. Closest T stop is Lechmere on the green line at First Street, so about a 6 block walk. There are also buses that travel down this street. If you are driving, I would suggest parking at the skating rink lot and walking down Seventh Street to the East Side. The rink is located next to Twin City Plaza on McGrath/O'Brien Highway. I think the rink has a separate parking area from the strip mall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, if your plans change, please update your RSVP. If you have any questions, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Outside in front of the bar</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270427721000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269009402000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beer, Pizza &amp; Ice Skating - in that order</name><id>12932258</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270254600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/12932258/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/e/7/global_13750071.jpeg</photo_url></item>