<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;While the weather looks bad for the weekend, forecasts for Monday are very appealing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Moat Traverse is made up of three peaks, North Moat (3201&amp;rsquo;) Middle Moat (2802&amp;rsquo;) and South Moat (2772&amp;rsquo;) and runs along the west side of&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;North Conway&lt;/span&gt;, Paralleling the&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Saco River&lt;/span&gt;. The ridge-walk from Moat to Moat is one of the finest in&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;New England&lt;/span&gt;. Much of it is bare due to a forest fire many years ago, and the views are marvelous. Both North and South Moat are on the list 52 With a View.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan: &amp;nbsp;We will need at least two cars to do the traverse so that we can leave one car (or more) at Diana's Bath and drive down to the southern terminus of the traverse at Dugway (&lt;span&gt;Passaconaway&lt;/span&gt;) Rd. &amp;nbsp;We will then hike south to north,&amp;nbsp;ending at Diana&amp;rsquo;s Bath. &amp;nbsp; If you may want to take a quick dip there, you might want to bring appropriate clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 9.6 miles&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Elevation gain: 3300&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Hiking time 7.5 hrs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rock and Root Rating: 3&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Hilliness: 4&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Moat Ridge is the Mt. Washington Valley&amp;rsquo;s version of the Franconia Ridge. The views from the ridge span in all directions. There are great views of the Presidentials from North Moat and great views of the Mt.Washington Valley and&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Chocorua&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;from Middle and South Moat. Most people start this run from the Diana&amp;rsquo;s Bath Trailhead off of West Side Rd., climb North Moat, and head south. The climb up North Moat is steep at times, but worth the effort. After summiting North Moat the trail drops down a few small ledges and enters the scrub. More great views can be seen from the Red Ridge Intersection. Most of the trail is in the open from middle Moat to South Moat. The trail drops down to the new trailhead located on Dugway (&lt;span&gt;Passaconaway&lt;/span&gt;) Rd.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Directions:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

To Diana&amp;rsquo;s Bath: Take River Rd. to West Side Rd. in North Conway. Follow West Side Rd. north past the entrance to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Cathedral Ledge Rd&lt;/span&gt;. The Diana&amp;rsquo;s Bath trailhead is about 0.5 miles ahead on the left.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

To Dugway Rd.: Take West Side Rd. from Conway Village about 1.5 miles until you reach Passaconaway Rd. on the left. Follow this about 5 miles until you see the parking lot on the right. If you reach the Dugway Picnic Area you have gone too far.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Anyone considering this trip should look at the map check AMC guide.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Responsibility Code described at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.hikesafe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. You need to understand that the host&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;of this activity is a volunteer, his function is social and he does not hold himself out as having any special knowledge, training or responsibility with respect to hiking safety, emergency assistance, or outdoor leadership. &amp;nbsp; By coming RSVPing for this trip, you release, hold&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;harmless, and indemnify the host(s) and all members of this&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;group from any and all claims for property damage, injury,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some equipment recommendations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Headlamp (or flashlight) with spare batteries, or a second headlamp/flashlight (there is always a risk of injury or other delays which may require hiking out in the dark).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Clothing: Layering will be important wool, synthetic or blended shirt/pants - no jeans or cotton. Cotton does not insulate well when wet. Windy ridge conditions can compound this. Insulating layers will be essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Outerwear: Waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and something (even a fleece vest) to wear for extra insulation if needed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Food and Water: High-energy snacks and at least two quarts of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Other Gear: Sunscreen (possibly insect repellent).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Trail hardy Footwear. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; &amp;nbsp;The ten essentials.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;For more information&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;please look for the list of 10 essentials, other gear and the Hiker Responsibility Code at&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=the-10-essentials"&gt;http://hikesafe.com/index.php?page=the-10-essentials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; &amp;nbsp;Any equipment or medication required to meet your medical needs in case of any foreseeable emergencies (e.g. an epi-pen if that is something you may need).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Anything else your experience, judgment or research tells you that you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Car Pooling&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; Lets save some gas money and shrink our carbon footprint! If you have a ride to offer or need a ride please post your needs or availability on your RSVP. Please note your interest in giving or getting a ride and contact hikers directly if their posts or profiles indicate it might be convenient to share rides with them. It looks like my car is close to full (I will be taking a dog and two other hikers), but could probably squeeze in another and I'll likely have more room for the return trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs&lt;/strong&gt;: Well behaved dogs are welcome, I'm bringing mine. Please mention your dog in your RSVP if you are bringing one. &amp;nbsp;I plan on limiting dogs to three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please allow plenty of time and let me know ASAP if you are running late as cell phone coverage is not reliable. Having been burned by no shows a few times, I will not keep people waiting unless I am sure you are coming.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MY DISCLAIMER: MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT. HOPEFULLY WE'LL ALL HAVE SOME FUN AND ENJOY A GREAT HIKE IN GOOD COMPANY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be there with a well groomed black dog.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309359010000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308939530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Moat Mountain Traverse</name><id>23397791</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309181400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/23397791/</event_url></item>