<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, we present a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When cryogenically preserved Miles Monroe (Woody Allen) is awakened 200 years after a hospital mishap, he discovers the future's not so bright: All women are frigid, all men are impotent, and the world is ruled by an evil dictator...a disembodied nose! Pursued by the secret police and recruited by anti-government rebels with a plan to kidnap the dictator's snout before it can be cloned, Miles falls for the beautiful--but untalented--poet Luna (Diane Keaton). But when Miles is captured and reprogrammed by the government-- to believe he's Miss America!-- it's up to Luna to save Miles, lead the rebels, and cut off the nose...just to spite its face...Sound funny? Wonder why? Join us before the film for a discussion on the science of humor!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As is the custom of our group, I'll be holding a meetup sign at the front of the theater. I'm 5'3, brunette, with hair to my neck and glasses.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Science on Screen events have been enjoyable for the entire group. The speaker beforehand brings up great topics that help the group have thougtful conversations after the film. You also get a chance to hear the ideas of Boston's finest scientists.</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198375157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: Sleeper</name><id>6956773</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200960000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6956773/</event_url></item>