<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A roughly 1.5 hr. easy looping hike (just slight rolling) at Northwest Park in Windsor. We'll pass through field, forest, and nice evergreen forest with views of the reservoir about half way through.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the parking lot and we'll hike from there and take various trails or portions of trails as conditions allow. We'll definatly hit the Rainbow Reservoir trail for the views and back to the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children and leashed dogs are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;General directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;* From Interstate 91 heading north, take Exit 38. From Interstate 91 heading south, take Exit 38A.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right at the exit on to Poquonock Avenue (Route 75).&lt;br /&gt;* Go about 1.5 miles and turn left on to Prospect Hill Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn right at the traffic circle on to Lang Road&lt;br /&gt;* Continue up the road to the Nature Center parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/%5B76-103%5D+Lang+Rd+Windsor+CT+06095/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northwestpark.org/pdf/New_NWP_Map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northwestp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Northwest Park and programs:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northwestpark.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.northwestp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>19</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252249895000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251478015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Northwest Park in Windsor CT</name><id>11225170</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252015200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11225170/</event_url></item>