<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Harvard Book Store Site&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2444" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: Free &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome computer scientist &lt;b&gt;JARON LANIER&lt;/b&gt; for a conversation about his new book, &lt;b&gt;You Are Not a Gadget&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Jaron Lanier&lt;/b&gt;, a Silicon Valley visionary since the 1980s, was among the first to predict the revolutionary changes the World Wide Web would bring to commerce and culture. Now, in his first book, written more than two decades after the web was created, Lanier offers this provocative and cautionary look at the way it is transforming our lives for better and for worse. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The current design and function of the web have become so familiar that it is easy to forget that they grew out of programming decisions made decades ago. The web's first designers made crucial choices (such as making one's presence anonymous) that have had enormous - and often unintended - consequences. What's more, these designs quickly became 'locked in,' a permanent part of the web?s very structure.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lanier discusses the technical and cultural problems that can grow out of poorly considered digital design and warns that our financial markets and sites like Wikipedia, Facebook, and Twitter are elevating the 'wisdom' of mobs and computer algorithms over the intelligence and judgment of individuals&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I remember back in 1989, before I became a computer science major, being enthralled about his predictions about virtual reality coming to pass. It was the latest fad. Ah, memories! Blocky animation and bulky goggles were going to take over the world.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Bookstore has hideously limited seating.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care to grab something to eat beforehand? T.J. Maher will be at the food court at The Garage at 36 JFK Street &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-garage-cambridge" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; on the lower level waiting at Flat Patties across from Subway starting at 5:40 pm. We can head there as a group starting at 6:30 pm. Let's grab seats at 6:40 pm. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign on his black messenger bag.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the book, according to Amazon.Com:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/You-Are-Not-Gadget-Manifesto/dp/0307269647/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1262634057&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Computer scientist and Internet guru Lanier's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Lanier's fascinating and provocative full-length exploration of the Internet's problems and potential is destined to become a must-read for both critics and advocates of online-based technology and culture. Lanier is best known for creating and pioneering the use of the revolutionary computer technology that he named virtual reality. Yet in his first book, Lanier takes a step back and critiques the current digital technology, more deeply exploring the ideas from his famous 2000 Wired magazine article, One-Half of a Manifesto, which argued against more wildly optimistic views of what computers and the Internet could accomplish. His main target here is Web 2.0, the current dominant digital design concept commonly referred to as open culture. Lanier forcefully argues that Web 2.0 sites such as Wikipedia undervalue humans in favor of anonymity and crowd identity. He brilliantly shows how large Web 2.0–based information aggregators such as Amazon.com—as well as proponents of free music file sharing—have created a hive mind mentality emphasizing quantity over quality. But he concludes with a passionate and hopeful argument for a new digital humanism in which radical technologies do not deny the specialness of personhood&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Get a signed event book&amp;quot;!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2444" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harvard.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;If you would like a signed event book and will be unable to attend the event, please let us know in the comments field of your order form when you place your order online. All orders for signed books must be placed through our website at least 48 hours in advance of the event. We can not guarantee signed copies - authors are sometimes unable to sign books - but we will try our hardest to get you one&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can order books from Harvard Bookstore at &lt;a href="http://site.booksite.com/1624/showdetail/?isbn=0307269647" target="_blank"&gt;http://site.booksite....&lt;/a&gt; ($24.95). And it's only $14.97 from Amazon.com.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about the book&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jaron Lanier's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Lanier's website &lt;a href="http://www.jaronlanier.com/gadgetwebresources.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jaronlanie...&lt;/a&gt; lists Q &amp;amp; A regarding the book's political and economic arguments, so-called &amp;quot;deleted scenes&amp;quot;, and other Frequently Asked Questions.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Jaron Lanier, according to Wikipedia: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jaron_Lanier" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Jaron Zepel Lanier (born May 3, 1960 in New York City, USA) is an American computer scientist, composer, visual artist, and author.[ He was a pioneer in, and popularized the term 'Virtual Reality' (VR) in the early 1980s. At that time, he founded VPL Research, the first company to sell VR products. His current appointments include Interdisciplinary Scholar-in-Residence, CET, UC Berkeley. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Lanier’s interests include biomimetic information architectures, user interfaces, heterogeneous scientific simulations, advanced information systems for medicine, and computational approaches to the fundamentals of physics. He collaborates with a wide range of scientists in fields related to these interests. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In the late 1980s he led the team that developed the first implementations of multi-person virtual worlds using head mounted displays, for both local and wide area networks, as well as the first &amp;quot;avatars&amp;quot;, or representations of users within such systems. While at VPL, he and his colleagues developed the first implementations of virtual reality applications in surgical simulation, vehicle interior prototyping, virtual sets for television production, and assorted other areas. He led the team that developed the first widely used software platform architecture for immersive virtual reality applications. Sun Microsystems acquired VPL's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;VPL's seminal portfolio of patents related to Virtual Reality and networked 3D graphics in 1999. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;From 1997 to 2001, Lanier was the Chief Scientist of Advanced Network and Services, which contained the Engineering Office of Internet2, and served as the Lead Scientist of the National Tele-immersion Initiative, a coalition of research universities studying advanced applications for Internet2. The Initiative demonstrated the first prototypes of tele-immersion in 2000 after a three-year development period. From 2001 to 2004, he was Visiting Scientist at Silicon Graphics Inc., where he developed solutions to core problems in telepresence and tele-immersion&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... He also seems to have pock-marked his own Wikipedia entry with his own criticism about the very concept of Wikipedia and any anonymous group that claims to be authoritative, fearing, from what I can tell, how easy it would be for any group like that to spread disinformation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I was reading this and thought, you mean, like ... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Did you know that the population of elephants tripled in the last six months&amp;quot;?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- S. Colbert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;[ Go to Comedy Central's site where someone has collected examples of &lt;b&gt;Stephen Colbert&lt;/b&gt; and his &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Wikiality&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;a href="http://ccinsider.comedycentral.com/2009/11/02/colberts-best-wikipedia-moments/" target="_blank"&gt;http://ccinsider.come...&lt;/a&gt; for a possible example of what Jaron Lanier is talking about. ]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263600676000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262636151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jaron Lanier discusses his book "You Are Not a Gadget" @ Harvard Bookstore</name><id>12219187</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263427200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12219187/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/c/9/global_12502809.jpeg</photo_url></item>