<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>415 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.347134</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name> Boston Convention &amp; Exhibition Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>10922072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.044090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;!!!!!!! &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please note date change&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; !!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The prediction for the weather on Sunday is looking grim.  So, as threatened, I'm changing to Friday.  I hope you can all still attend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've enjoyed going to this show for the past couple of years. It fills a need to at least be around boats, at this time of year :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $15, but you get a free subscription to one of Yachting, Cruising World, Islands, Ski, TW Snowboarding, or Flying. And, not only are there boats and boating organizations galore, but there are workshops and seminars throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a link to the show website: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.newenglandboatshow.com"&gt;http://www.newenglandboatshow.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be waiting for people just outside the inside entrance to the show -- where the ticket takers are. (When you enter the building, ask where the show is -- it's quite a ways off -- and proceed there.) Also, the signup for subscriptions is just outside where the ticket takers are, so if you get there a few minutes early you can sign up then; otherwise, you can do it on your way out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a big place so I don't expect us to spend the whole time together as a group, but we can at least start out that way and hopefully run into each other during the rest of the event. (I'll see if I can get some Meetup nametags.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361584929000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361292148000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England Boat Show</name><id>105339762</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361574000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/105339762/</event_url></item>