<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Once again The Brattle has set up a unique program of films- this time based on favorite flicks by local legend Andrew Bujalski, director of Funny Ha-Ha and Mutual Appreciation. This showcase features two well-known films, &lt;b&gt;Vertigo&lt;/b&gt; by someone named Hitchcock  and &lt;b&gt;12 Monkeys&lt;/b&gt; by Monty Python alumni Terry Gilliam and two by  French director, Chris Marker- the feature length &lt;b&gt;Sans Soleil&lt;/b&gt; and his 1962 short &lt;b&gt;La Jetée&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start the day with &lt;b&gt;12 Monkees&lt;/b&gt;  at 2 PM, &lt;b&gt;Vertigo&lt;/b&gt; screens at 4:30 and the two by Chris Marker start at 7 PM - which would get us to a restaurant at 9:30 for a well-deserved meal. There should also be enogh time to grab a quick  bite to eat after Vertigo. When you RSVP, let me know which of the films you will be attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;b]La Jetée&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt; One of the finest science fiction films ever made, Chris Marker's La jetée is a brilliant philosophical treatise packed into 28 minutes of film. Though it is Marker's only fictional work, it stands as one of the most eloquent visions of his artistic obsessions: travel, images, and memory. Concerning a nameless protagonist who voyages from the radioactive rubble of the post-WWIII present to the verdant past, the film is a travelogue of sorts--a journey through time instead of space--in which the man's childhood memories literally define his existence. Faced with a choice of living in a perfectly ordered distant future or in the moments immediately before nuclear destruction, he chooses to return to the woman from his youthful dreams and live in a vertiginous state of nostalgia. The film's &amp;quot;photo-roman&amp;quot; (still photo) style seems to mirror the impressionistic quality of memory, which the viewer pieces together into a coherent visual experience. Yet, at one point in the film, the protagonist's lover stares into the camera -- until suddenly she blinks. Subtle yet shockingly effective, La jetée brilliantly explodes the rules of what makes a film, forcing the audience to reassess its preconceptions about cinema, as well as about time, memory, and how we experience reality.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vertigo&lt;/b&gt; To briefly acquaint new viewers with the plot: James Stewart plays a detective who has left the police force because his fear of heights has caused, he believes, a tragedy. When an old college friend summons him to investigate the eccentric actions of his psychologically perplexing wife (Kim Novak), Stewart?s life takes a new, obsessive course from which he never recovers. &lt;br /&gt; I was awestruck. Having only seen &amp;quot;Vertigo&amp;quot; on 16mm prints and videotape, I had not appreciated the piercing blueness of Stewart?s eyes, Novak?s eyebrow-raising voluptuousness, Bernard Herrmann?s soaring score and the expansive splendor of Vistavision, as Stewart and Novak saunter against a San Francisco backdrop of hilly streets, parks and the Golden Gate Bridge. To watch this movie as it should be seen is too primal an experience to miss. Do yourself an aesthetic favor: Take the plunge. You?ll love the fall all the way down.  Washington Post&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;12 Monkeys&lt;/b&gt; is a grandiose cinematic invention, cleverly turning the present-day urban American world on its ear. It offers an alarming vision of a near future where animals have reclaimed Earth and humans are imprisoned in subterranean catacombs, struggling for survival and answers about what nearly wiped them out in 1997. The movie is based on a 1962 French New Wave film, the 27-minute ``La Jetee'' by Chris Marker  San Francisco Chronicle  Has to be the only movie with Bruce Willis that I would host. Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sans Soleil&lt;/b&gt; At the core of &amp;quot;Sans Soleil,&amp;quot; it seems, is the way society chooses to remember things -- and what happens when assumptions are replaced by new facts and a new reality. If this sounds (to use a 1960s expression) &amp;quot;far out,&amp;quot; that's because &amp;quot;Sans Soleil&amp;quot; does what few other nonfiction films have done before or since: Link disparate cultures (in this case, Japan, Iceland, Guinea- Bissau and the United States) through street scenes that range from the mundane (&amp;quot;banality,&amp;quot; in Marker's onscreen words) to the extraordinary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Well if you read this far, you should agree this will   be an interesting day to say the least - hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after each film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203223203000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eclectic Triple Play at the Brattle</name><id>7346168</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205604000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7346168/</event_url></item>