<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue Boston, MA 02115</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>4859212</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dance @MFA First Fridays &lt;strong&gt;Friday, March 1, 2013,&lt;/strong&gt; 6:00 pm - 9:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=465%20Huntington%20Avenue%2C%20Boston%2C%20MA" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Museum of Fine Arts&lt;/a&gt; 465 Huntington Avenue, Boston, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Ob1: 603-491-1962  ob@tds.net  Carpooling from Nashua, Woburn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Admission $25.  Discount tickets can be found at your local library for free. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Ob1 wrote: We did this event last month, and had over 125 rsvps for it. Out of the 12 Groups this was posted. Plus, we had such a good time. I am Hosting it again. Also, the event hit its max attendance of 400 &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/d/d/event_13129629.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;people, and it was sold out by 7:15 pm. That was one of the reasons, we only had 93 join us from Meetup. So, get there early, or take your chances. We also found those who got their passes at the door, got a better deal. Than those who bought their tickets before. The library passes really helped with the price also.  So, lets dance and have some drinks, and enjoy some art at the same time. MFA First Fridays is on the first Friday of each month from 6:00–9:30 pm. Join Steve Ob1. and friends for fine art, music, cash bars. Steve Ob1. will be there to dance. The Dj is very open to our request. The dance is large. They are featuring signature cocktails, and delicious tapas available for purchase. Friday, March 1, features DJ. Steve Ob1. will have Meetup signs on the tables close to the Dj. As always, You show up and introduce yourself, and Steve Ob1. will introduce to  everyone at our tables and beyond. If you go to our tables and can't find us? Look on the Dance floor. 90% of the people dancing were Meetup. This event ends at 9:30 pm.. So, maybe we will go out, and continue to dance some where ells? I am looking for ideas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open to visitors 21+. Valid ID with proof of age required for entry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org/programs/special-event/mfa-first-fridays" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mfa.org/programs/special-event/mfa-first-fridays&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look 4 the Meetup signs by the Dj.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362248064000</updated><rating><average>4.11999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>90</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359825497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance @ the Museum of Fine Arts</name><id>102669462</id><headcount>65</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362178800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/102669462/</event_url></item>