<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Further to our recent HoopHouse &amp;amp; Season Extension SkillShare, we are putting on a series of&lt;b&gt; 3 free work parties to give members some hands-on experience&lt;/b&gt; in building a standard season-extension hoophouse for backyard/garden use.  The model we're building is scalable and we will have hand-outs giving the directions for this size and suggested variations that you might want to consider if you build one yourself later (and teach your friends and neighbors:)  Member and experienced season extender &lt;b&gt;Tree&lt;/b&gt; will be leading the work party with support from LisaF and/or Dave Homa.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be 3 HoopHouse Raisings (Portland, Biddeford and North Yarmouth) so please check the calendar and sign up for the one closest to you.  All the hosts attendeed the recent skillshare and would be covering some of the materials costs and will end up with a functioning hoophouse by the end of each work party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exact address details to be posted soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no cost for this work party.  Simply arrive at 8:30 for a briefing on the hoophouse design and construction, an overview of the work plan for the morning.  We will try to start the work by 9am.  Bring appropriate work clothes/shoes/gloves.  Some power tools will be in use so please bring eye protection if you are comfortable using a saw, drill, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Work will proceed until about 12 or 12:30 then we will share a potluck lunch.  Please bring a dish to share and your potluck kit (dish/bowl/cup/utensils/napkin).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeannie Gallant</member_name><member_id>11924665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284595873000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279825838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HoopHouse Raising #2: North Yarmouth</name><id>14182650</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283689800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/14182650/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/5/3/global_15151107.jpeg</photo_url></item>