<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>From Harry Bloom:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On March 1st at 4pm at the SASSDS Campus at One Commerce Way in Norwood, &lt;br /&gt;the snow delayed program about /Janusz Korczak/ will take place.&lt;br /&gt;(Please see attached mailer for details.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP for what promises to be an outstanding Middle School (and &lt;br /&gt;up) parent/child learning opportunity sponsored by the Israel Arbeiter&lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Understanding. Our own gifted educator, Moreh Shem (Bob &lt;br /&gt;Minder), will be introducing a film by award&lt;br /&gt;winning Polish director Andrej Wajda about /Janusz Korczak,/ a famous &lt;br /&gt;physician and author and educator who ran an orphanage in the Warsaw&lt;br /&gt;Ghetto during the 1930's and who insisted on accompanying his charges &lt;br /&gt;when they were deported to a concentration camp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moreh Shem is an enthusiastic expert about /Janusz Korczak/, one of the &lt;br /&gt;most enlightened child advocates of the 20th century. Based on alumni&lt;br /&gt;testimonials, Moreh Shem's teaching is typically one of the most &lt;br /&gt;remembered highlights of our students' experiences at SASSDS. This is a&lt;br /&gt;golden opportunity for parents to learn from Moreh Shem with their &lt;br /&gt;children. Don't miss it. However, space is limited and you must RSVP to&lt;br /&gt;attend. Please email Diane Joiner at djoiner@sassds.org *no later than &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, February 25th* to reserve your places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A limited number of bound copies of an original essay by Moreh Shem will &lt;br /&gt;be available for session participants. Please indicate when you reserve&lt;br /&gt;your places whether you would like us to put a copy aside for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236525888000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233845705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film and Lecture about Janusz Korczak</name><id>9679325</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235941200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/9679325/</event_url></item>