<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Dorrance St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.824384</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 401.351.4500</phone><name>McCormick &amp; Schmick's</name><city>Providence</city><id>699184</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.413496</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend, we had our second photowalk in Plymouth, MA and it was a great success.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Lovely weather, combined with lots of interesting photo opportunities along the waterfront, made for a wonderful day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Saturday, July 16th at 3PM, we'll meet at 11 Dorrance Street in Providence, outside McCormick &amp;amp; Schmick&amp;rsquo;s restaurant.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This puts us in the downtown area, and within easy walking distance of College Hill.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We will have many opportunities to photograph wonderful architecture and hopefully we&amp;rsquo;ll have some models to make it even more interesting!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; WaterFire is supposed to ignite just after 8:15PM.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; It has been suggested that bringing tripods to mount your cameras on, would be a useful to have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;As was the case on previous photowalks, models will have to come dressed with hair and make-up the way they want to be photographed. Unlike Mike &amp;amp; Pat's Great Model Shoots, we won't have those resources available to us.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; There is paid parking in the area. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;There is no charge for this photowalk. However, we will more than likely find someplace to sit and have a meal together like we did last time, so there is the cost of dinner.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; I also strongly recommend wearing comfy walking shoes worthy of pounding the pavement in search of the perfect photograph.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is important to RSVP for this event.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We may have an opportunity to get some unique shots, but it will depend on the number in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;If you have any questions, feel free to post them here, or send me a message. Also, please feel free to pass along this information to anyone you think might enjoy a fun day of photography &amp;amp; friendship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>11 Dorrance Street; Providence, RI</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311208506000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306872463000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photowalk of Providence, including WaterFire</name><id>20403131</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310842800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/20403131/</event_url></item>