<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>428 washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02188</zip><lat>42.209300</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 331 0700</phone><name>Indian Delight</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>1112187</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.958000</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>INDIAN DELIGHT!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quick, what's a tandoor?! No, it's NOT an elephant!! It's a pitcher-shaped clay oven used in traditional Indian cooking to slow-bake foods over charcoal so that they retain their moisture and flavor. Much better than an elephant, Sahib!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Of course we are not so much interested in the tandoor per se as we are in the tandoori chicken (tender, marinated in yogurt and spices and served on sauteed onions and peppers), the seekh kabab (minced lamb, seasoned with chopped onion, herbs and spices) and the naan (unleavened flat bread served hot from the tandoor).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Those of you who find yourselves salivating or merely curious may join us for lunch at Indian Delight, 428 Washington Street (Rt. 53), Weymouth at 12:30pm on Saturday, March 10. We will be exploring the many delights of Indian cuisine (which are not all searingly hot, and heat levels can be adjusted to taste, as well), with the option of taking advantage of the diverse offerings of the Super Brunch Buffet ($9.95), which includes everything from soup to desserts. Anyone who would like to learn a little more about the food in advance can read Christine Ordway's excellent review of Indian Delight here: &lt;a href="http://ledger.southofboston.com/articles/2006/11/08/life/life01.txt" target="_blank"&gt;http://ledger.southof...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This will be the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group's first venture into ethnic dining (on the South Shore, ethnic is defined as &amp;quot;not American or Italian&amp;quot;). Please join us as we add a little spice to our gustatory lives!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note updated directions!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Rt 3 North (coming from Cape Cod) take Exit 16 and go right onto Rt 18 North. From Rt 3 South (Coming from Braintree or Boston) take Exit 16A (Rt 18 North). Go straight through the first traffic light you come to (you should see a Dairy Queen on the far right corner).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue past the mall where Building 19 is located.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next traffic light is where Rt 18 ends at its intersection with Rt 53. You will see a CVS straight ahead of you. Turn left onto Rt 53 North.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you complete the turn onto Rt 53, Indian Delight is close enough to see. Pass Martinis (Italian restaurant) on your right, slow down as you come to Public Storage because Indian Delight is the very next building. Parking is mostly behind the restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $2/person&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: None, for now.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, March 9th @ Noon&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;Host: Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indian Delight&lt;br /&gt;428 Washington St (Rt 53)&lt;br /&gt;Weymouth, MA 02188&lt;br /&gt;781 331-0700&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 10th @ 12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312746416000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172426979000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indian Luncheon</name><id>5512642</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173547800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5512642/</event_url></item>