<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennett St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372297</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.661.5000</phone><name>Regattabar </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>796303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, January 29th, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2190" target="_blank"&gt;Regattabar at The Charles Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;1 Bennett St.&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge Massachusetts 02138&lt;br /&gt;Tel; 617-395-7757 &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=1+Bennett+St.%2CCambridge%2CMassachusetts%2C02138%2CUS" target="_blank"&gt;[map]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price: &lt;a href="https://www.peltrix.com/getshowtix/regattabar/purchase.cgi?id=2190" target="_blank"&gt;$15&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com" target="_blank"&gt; Atlas Soul&lt;/a&gt; is an award-winning band based in Boston performing original music that celebrates and bridge Afro-Mediterranean melodies &amp;amp; grooves with Jazz and Funk thus naturally creating new powerful genres of music one could describe as Maghrebien-Funk, Rock’n Raï and/or Shaabi-Jazz.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;Atlas Soul's blend of jazz, funk and Middle-Eastern/Arabic grooves is a fascinating sonic stew that will catch any listener's ear. This is their second appearance on our CD's compilation. We like'em, and you will too&amp;quot;.  Global Rhythm Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Their powerful energetic &amp;amp; tight live performance is guaranty to move any audience and soon have every one sing along (often in a foreign language) up &amp;amp; dancing &amp;amp; sharing the positive energy produced from the stage!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;They have played venues such as The Montreal Jazz Festival, The Kennedy Center, The Festival International de Louisiane, The Houston International Festival, Musikfest, The FNX/Boston Phoenix Jazz Series at the Hatch Shell, The Festival International Nuits d’Afrique (Montreal) The Boston Globe Jazz Festival, The Steppin’Out Festival, MASS MoCA , Les Francofolies de Montreal, and many more…They have been booked on the same bill and shared the stage with international artists such as Lady Smith Black Mombazo, Thomas Mapfumo, Gigi, Alpha Blondy, Hassan Hakmoun, Baba Maal and Cheb Nasro to name just a few.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“What hits hardest about Atlas Soul’s sound is the natural funk of North African music and also powerful vocals, which span fluid, passionate Gnawa melodies and husky Raï hooks. There is great wisdom in a world-music outfit that embraces divergent genres  (but not so many that the sound loses its identity)&amp;quot; writes world music journalist Banning Eyre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Atlas Soul sings in French, Arabic, Hebrew and English. The lyrics speak of love, natural wonders, oppression, poverty, and of the melancholy of immigrants longing for their homelands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their motto is world-music-for-world-peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; They have won or placed 3 times the Independent Music Awards, the Billboard World Song, The Unisong International, Global Rhythm Magazine, Just Plain Folks Music Awards, Boston Music Awards and many more..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com" target="_blank"&gt; More info here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheila </member_name><member_id>6189105</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pasquale</member_name><member_id>9961972</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296615671000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293997690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atlas Soul - Maghrebian-Funk, Shaabi-Jazz, Rock'n Raï</name><id>15886042</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296347400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/15886042/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/global_13896170.jpeg</photo_url></item>