<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As usual meeting begins at 6pm and film at 7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARTIAL LAW&lt;br /&gt;9/11: RISE OF THE POLICE STATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evil has spread across the land. Martial Law: 9/11 Rise of the Police State exposes the high-tech control grid that is being set up across America&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Out of the ashes of the September 11th tragedy, a dark empire of war and tyranny has risen. The Constitution has been shredded and America is now a Police State. This film exposes not just who was behind the 9-11 attacks, but the roots and history of its orchestrators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LEARN THE TERRIFYING SECRET THAT HOLDS THE FUTURE OF THE WORLD IN ITS GRASP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the frontlines of the Police State to the darkest sanctum of the secret society that controls it, Martial Law reveals the master plan of a group hell-bent on capturing America today -- and tomorrow the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE NEW WORLD ORDER HAS SET IN MOTION THE FOURTH REICH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Martial Law is a blazing spotlight piercing the electronic Berlin Wall that is the corporate-controlled media. Plumb the depths of the Elite’s minds: their ideology, their driving philosophy – and uncover the power-mad “cult of Death” that is sworn to turn the Earth into a prison planet. Discover the documented truth yourself -- before it’s too late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MARTIAL LAW 9/11: THE RISE OF THE POLICE STATE&lt;br /&gt;THE POWERFUL WEAPON YOU NEED IN THE INFOWAR TO BLAST THROUGH THE GLOBALISTS' LIES!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To order and for more on this film, see: &lt;a href="http://www.infowars.com/martial_law_911.htm" target="_blank"&gt;www.infowars.com/martial_law_911.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more resources, see: &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/cgi-local/newspro/viewnews.cgi?newsid1014738186,11057," target="_blank"&gt;Bush and 9/11 Investigative Reports, looking into the unanswered questions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The community meeting space is in the back of building at the Woodstar Cafe</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226773566000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221603030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Martial Law 9/11: Rise Of The Police State </name><id>8770937</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/8770937/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/8/global_5539096.jpeg</photo_url></item>