<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Welcome to what I hope to be the first of many weeknight meetups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This first meetup will be geared towards people who would like to learn a quick fun game. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be holding the meetup inside Portsmouth's Science Fiction fantasy superstore, Jumpgate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will only be allowing the amount of people for one small game as space is limited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a larger game night in the works along with our ever popular all day Saturday Games Day coming up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details for the Night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Game we will be playing: &lt;b&gt;Ticket to Ride&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/9209" target="_blank"&gt;Boardgamegeek link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From BGG &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With elegantly simple gameplay, Ticket to Ride can be learned in 3 minutes, while providing players with intense strategic and tactical decisions every turn. Players collect cards of various types of train cars they then use to claim railway routes in North America. The longer the routes, the more points they earn. Additional points come to those who fulfill Destination Tickets – goal cards that connect distant cities; and to the player who builds the longest continuous route.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be gathering around 6PM and will wait for all the player to arrive. The game will be explained quickly and we will jump right in. We should have enough time to play a round of Ticket to Ride and a quick game of something esle before we need to be out of there at 7:30. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being as we are holding this gaming session in a store there are a few rules we need to follow. Nothing to outrageous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rule for the Venue:&lt;br /&gt;1.) No food or Drink is allowed in the store.&lt;br /&gt;2.) Be respectful to the customers in the store.&lt;br /&gt;3.) Be willing to explain the game to anyone who asks or direct them to me. &lt;br /&gt;4.) Keep the noise level controllable.&lt;br /&gt;5.) Be out of the store by 8pm. (We can stay and chat outside if we need ;-))&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to fill this game up and list another one soon!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be the man with the Red Shirt in the back. Trouble? Ask at the front desk.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wayne</member_name><member_id>1411667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1243650983000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>sagesofrpg</urlname><id>747276</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth, NH / Seacoast Boardgames Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238079383000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn Ticket to Ride!</name><id>10040951</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238709600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sagesofrpg/events/10040951/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/1/4/global_7844580.jpeg</photo_url></item>