<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352087</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>China Trade Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>713451</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thanks to one of our members, Lana, we will be having our 1st weekday afternoon  meet up from 2-4 PM at basement of The Chinatrade Center at 2 Boylston Street, Boston (Chinatown) on Wednesday, 4/8. She will have a sign on the table.  Feel free to bring questions, books and other materials you are working on or would like to share with others.    The meeting is at the China Trade Center at 2 boylston Street , in Boston Chinatown area.  I believe you can buy food and drinks there too or bring your own food/drinks if you want something to eat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking The MBTA:     &lt;br /&gt;Take the Orange line Forest hill direction to the Chinatown station. This is an accessible station. After exiting the station, you will be at the intersection of Boylston and Washington St. The China Trade Center is located on the southwest corner of this intersection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For maps and more information visit the MBTA website @ www.mbta.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 to Boston and the Chinatown exit. Turn right onto Kneeland Street. Follow Kneeland St. five blocks to Washington St. Turn right onto Washington St. VSAM is in the China Trade Center at 2 Boylston street. You can park in a surface lot one block further on Washington street or trun right on Essex Street and and park in the surface lot behind the Registry of Motor Vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 to Boston and the Chinatown exit, at the end of the exit ramp take a left onto Kneeland Street. Follow Kneeland Street five blocks to Washington Street. VSAM is in the China Trade Center at 2 Boylston street. You can park in a surface lot one block further on Washington street or trun right on Essex Street and and park in the surface lot behind the Registry of Motor Vehicles.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; From the West:&lt;br /&gt;Take I-90 East to Boston. Pay toll and proceed on the Mass. Turnpike Extention to the first exit (Prudential/Copley). On the exit ramp stay to the right. Exit onto Stuart Street and continue straight to Washington Street (This will be six blocks; at Charles Street Stuart Street changes its name to Kneeland Street, Washington Street will be the next block after Tremont Street in the vicinity of New England Medical Center). Turn left on to Washington Street and park in the surface lot at the Corner of Washington and Beech Streets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the China Trade Center is at 2 Boylston Street across from the Mass. Registry of Motor Vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: There are several parking lots located near The Chinatrade Center, you will find parking on&lt;br /&gt;1. Lagrange St 2. In a garage on Boylston St directly across from the China Trade Center 3. On the corner of Hayward Pl and Washington St 4.A large underground garage in the Boston Common (entrance on Charles St between the public garden and the common)&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;for othere driving directions visit www.mapquest.com&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I will not be there so look for Lana.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If there is enough interest, she will have more afternoon meet ups in the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Care!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adele&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lana will have a sign at one of the tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adele</member_name><member_id>481803</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239495288000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238699400000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1ST Weekday afternoon meetup, 4/8</name><id>10099830</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239213600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/10099830/</event_url></item>