<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Eastern Promenade</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670040</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fort Allen Park</name><city>Portland</city><id>2250571</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.246933</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The City of Portland would like us to host Valet Bicycle Parking for the Fourth of July Fireworks, to encourage people to bike to the event! As bicycle commuters, of course you will want to do that, but please RSVP Yes to this event to help volunteer. This is an excellent opportunity to encourage and educate about bicycle transportation. Gorham Bike &amp;amp; Ski will also be selling lights so that bicyclists have the opportunity to ride home safely and legally in the dark. We will set up from 4 to 5 PM, and park bikes from 6 PM until 10:30 PM, after the fireworks. Let's say shifts are 4-5 for setup, 6-8 and 8-10 for parking, and 10 - 10:30 for teardown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bicycle educator and environmentalist Chael MacArther, of the 
&lt;a href="http://chaelmacarthur.wordpress.com/"&gt;Keep the Cycle Going&lt;/a&gt; blog, is passing through Portland on a summer tour offering workshops focusing on the cycles of one planet living and two-wheeled motion. He will be offering a workshop at our parking area at the top of Fort Allen Park, at 1 PM, combining general bicycling skills, touring, and smart city riding. Please stop by and meet Chael, an educator with 
&lt;a href="http://www.seatosky.bc.ca/"&gt;Sea To Sky Outdoor School For Sustainability&lt;/a&gt; in British Columbia, Canada.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Secondly, a group of young people from 
&lt;a href="http://www.climatesummer.net/"&gt;New England Climate Summer&lt;/a&gt; are traveling by bicycle across New England, coming through Portland that evening, and will be helping us park. So, more interesting bicycle people to meet!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Tell all your friends to see the fireworks by bike, and meet interesting people at the Valet Bike Parking at Fort Allen Park, 6:00 - 10:30 PM Monday ("Longin' the Saddle/Cruisin' The Strip" workshop with Chael at 1 PM).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309813697000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Bike Commuters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Bike-Commuting</urlname><id>225788</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Bicycle Commuting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308623444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valet Bicycle Parking at Portland Fireworks</name><id>22929441</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309809600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Bike-Commuting/events/22929441/</event_url></item>