<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Time Approximate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visionary director Wes Anderson's first animated film utilizes classic handmade stop-motion techniques to tell the story of the best-selling children's book by Roald Dahl (author of Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and James and the Giant Peach). Mr. and Mrs. Fox (voices of George Clooney and Meryl Streep) live an idyllic home life with their son Ash (Jason Schwartzman) and visiting young nephew Kristopherson (Eric Anderson). But after 12 years, the bucolic existence proves too much for Mr Fox’s wild animal instincts. Soon he slips back into his old ways as a sneaky chicken thief and in doing so, endangers not only his beloved family, but the whole animal community. Trapped underground and with not enough food to go around, the animals band together to fight against the evil Farmers—Boggis (Brian Cox), Bunce (Hugo Guinness) and Bean (Michael Gambon)—who are determined to capture the audacious, fantastic Mr. Fox at any cost. Also featuring the voices of Bill Murray, Wally Wolodarsky, Willem Dafoe, Owen Wilson and Jarvis Cocker. Official Web Site&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;From The New Yorker  by Richard Brody &lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For his stop-motion adaptation of Roald Dahl’s book—about a fox who steals from three grotesque farmers, who go to absurd lengths to capture him as he leads his family and friends on increasingly desperate adventures in order to survive—the director Wes Anderson, co-writing the script with Noah Baumbach, greatly amplified the story and its emotional spectrum. Mr. and Mrs. Fox (voiced by George Clooney and Meryl Streep)—he’s a journalist, she’s an artist—bring to life a view of marriage that’s as bittersweet and insightful as that of any recent live-action movie, and their idiosyncratic son (Jason Schwartzman) is set up in a touching rivalry with his cousin (Eric Anderson, the director’s brother). Visually, the movie is a wonder, with its profusion of detail and exquisitely focussed “performances” by the figurines, whom Anderson frames in images as precisely composed as those featuring actors in his live-action work. The voice performances are sparkling and apt; the adventure plot is realized with a scenographic splendor that’s as understated as it is dazzling, and is also invested with a surprising moral weight. Though the emotional realms—and the philosophical twists—that Anderson evokes are unusually sophisticated for a children’s film, its exuberance is a universal tonic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more: &lt;a href="http://www.newyorker.com/arts/reviews/film/fantastic_mr_fox_anderson#ixzz0WpZBLHmq" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newyorker....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, Dave and John will lead an animated discussion at &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Friendly Toast&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dave and John go to absurd lengths to capture members as they lead their family and friends on increasingly desperate adventures in order to survive, all while holding pathetic homemade MEETUP signs  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258196952000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fantastic Mr. Fox</name><id>11872021</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260049500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11872021/</event_url></item>