<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>295 Nashua Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367059</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nashua Street Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>998031</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067727</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Back by popular demand - it's the made-for-nerds walking tour of the Charles River Basin with Boston By Foot!  If you missed this tour in July when it was the tour of the month, please join us for the tour scheduled just for Nerd Fun!  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/10777441/"&gt;(Click here to see the photos from the July tour)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a 2-hour trek of discovery exploring the new open spaces along the lower Charles River. A hub of transportation and recreation, the lower basin has experienced several cycles of dramatic change resulting from the construction of bridges and dams, the expansion of Boston, and the Big Dig project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This most awesome unique walking tour explores the evolution of the Charles River Basin and the engineering of a city. If you like the &amp;quot;Boston Underfoot&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Boats, Bridges &amp;amp; Locks&amp;quot; tours and are looking for more, this tour won't disappoint. Looking at the artifacts we'll see how the Charles River was changed from a tidal estuary to the &amp;quot;river&amp;quot; we know today through a concerted effort to reshape Boston through land-making and the construction of a dam (and 10,000 wooden pilings).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll see the impact that the many railway lines of the 19th century and the construction of the Northern &amp;amp; Southeast Expressways in the 20th century had on the lower basin. We'll see many types of bridges along the way including some vestiges of bridges long gone. Walking among the new, and in some areas incomplete, projects we'll examine the progress on the revitalization of the area including the development at North Point and the 3 new parks that provide a graceful transition from their Olmstedian predecessors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't been through this area, we guarantee you some spectacular and unique views on Boston. We will see all the nooks and crannies people drive past, but never get out and explore. This tour is NOT a little stroll. For two hours we will WALK! Over bridges, under bridges, underneath expressways, over railroads, near prisons, over dirt &amp;amp; gravel, through grassy fields, and on top of movable locks. And it wouldn't be a Boston By Foot tour if we didn't find an excuse to toss in a touch of Charles Bulfinch and catastrophic fire along the way.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are an explorer at heart, a fan of landscape architecture, a history buff, or an engineering nerd, there's something on this tour for everyone.  Make sure to check the weather and dress appropriately (we'll head out rain, snow, or shine), wear comfortable shoes that you can get dirty, and bring along some water. They may call it the &amp;quot;lost half-mile,&amp;quot; but it's two miles around and there's no place to stop for snacks or bio-breaks. Meet us behind the Science Park/West End Green Line Station in Nashua Street Park (across from the Suffolk County Jail) before the start of the tour. Tickets are $15 per person ($5 for Boston By Foot card holders - membership information at their &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; (BBF membership gets you free admission to other nerdy events that aren't announced to the general public))&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come on down to explore this nerdiest part of Boston.  Look for me, Amy, wearing my Boston By Foot hat and my Meetup button.  The tour starts promptly at 2:00pm.  I listed 1:45pm so that everyone has time to pay and get organized.  If there are too many of us we'll have to split up into smaller groups.  After the tour, we'll probably head to Boston Beer Works for a drink and a snack.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for people with Boston By Foot badges - mine says "Amy"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>20</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256355671000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254195612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Engagement: Exploring the Charles River Basin Walking Trek</name><id>11494984</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255801500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/11494984/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/0/global_9447616.jpeg</photo_url></item>