<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351738</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Encuentro5 (fifth floor)</name><city>Boston</city><id>610414</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Planning meeting for the National Peace Conference in Albany&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, 9 June, 7:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.encuentro5.org" target="_blank"&gt;Encuentro 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;33 Harrison Ave., fifth floor&lt;br /&gt;Chinatown T stop on the Orange Line, Boylston T stop on the Green Line, Downtown Crossing T stop on the Red Line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The National Peace Conference in Albany at the end of next month will be THE most important gathering of antiwar and social justice activists in a while.  So far over 25 national organizations are co-sponsoring this impressive event with 30 workshops and speakers from across the political spectrum discussing strategy and deciding on an ambitious program of action to unify and build a movement strong enough to stop US wars, occupations, and interventions.  In addition to the focus on Iraq, Afghanistan, and Pakistan, there will be leading activists to discuss struggles around the world from Palestine to the Caribbean, Latin America, Iran, and Africa; immigrant rights; defense of civil liberties; poor people's movements; labor and student movements; and a strong emphasis on bringing our war dollars home to meet needs of health care, housing, education, jobs, and the environment; AND MORE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Albany is practically in our backyard.  We need a strong showing from the Greater Boston area.  Please come to a meeting to get the latest update on the conference and see what we can do to broadly publicize the conference and bring as many activists and people new to the movement to Albany.  We will also have an opportunity to see the proposed Action Program for the conference and discuss how we might participate in drafting a program for the next year. It will be an inspiring event, something we sorely need in this time of tragedy in Gaza and the destruction of the Gulf of Mexico by corporate greed and government collusion.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Harris</member_name><member_id>5188497</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276130188000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People for Peace</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>stopthewars</urlname><id>708558</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Antiwar</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275957635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Peace Conference planning meeting</name><id>13730922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276126200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/stopthewars/events/13730922/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/global_2184137.jpeg</photo_url></item>