<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>rt 113</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03813</zip><lat>44.236515</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Baldface Circle Trailhead</name><city>Center Conway</city><id>614763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.014620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Distance&lt;/b&gt;: 9.8 miles (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Elevation gain&lt;/b&gt;: 3600 ft (minimum)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Time&lt;/b&gt;: 6 hours and 45 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The base plan is to hike the Baldface Circle Trail over North and South Baldface. This goes over some steep ledges up to South Baldface that can be dangerous when wet. If that is the case they can be bypassed by taking the Slippery Brook Trail to the Baldface Knob Trail. This would add 1.0 miles and 137 ft, which is an additional 35 minutes of book time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several opportunites for side trips that would extend the mileage and distance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emerald Pool - 0.1 miles, 30 ft&lt;br /&gt;Chandler Gorge -  0.4 miles, 80 ft&lt;br /&gt;Baldface Knob - 0.6 miles, 100 ft&lt;br /&gt;Eagle Crag - 0.4 miles, 50 ft&lt;br /&gt;Bicknell Ridge and Eagle Cascade - 0.5 miles, 125 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is still some snow reported on these trails. It is small enough that snowshoes are not needed, but waterproof boots are needed. Gaiters may be useful also. You should expect some standing water and black flies this time of year, so bring your favorite bug repellent. There is lots of exposure on this trail so remember the sunblock also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;Disclaimer and things you must know&lt;/a&gt;. Cancellation and will be posted by 12 PM the day before. Please update any Maybe RSVPs by that time also. After that time they will be considered as No RSVPs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at trailhead parking which is 0.1 mi north of the driveway to the AMC?s
Cold River Camp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andy F</member_name><member_id>3324456</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211808196000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>This trip is described as one of the most attractive trips in the White Mountains, with about 4 mi. of open and semi-open ledge providing long stretches of unobstructed views</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211210227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North and South Baldface</name><id>7967671</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211634900000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7967671/</event_url></item>