<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>67 S Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.200634</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-227-1175</phone><name>The Draft Sports Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Concord</city><id>499480</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.533500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>There is a meeting relating to the state house gun ban taking place Tuesday evening @ 6:00 PM 12/29 at The Draft restaurant in Concord. Though men-folk are welcome, the organizers would like this meeting to be specifically for women concerned with this issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting is being organized by State Rep Jenn Coffey. Jenn is one of the good “guys”, along with Dan Itse and Jack Kimball [I have seen Jenn speak at several events at which those gentleman spoke]. This meeting is primarily meant for the ladies, as Jenn would like to emphasize the impact of this ban on women's self-defense in particular. Please spread the word of this meeting to any of the women in your life concerned about the right to armed self-defense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not familiar with Jenn, she is quite the lady.  Jenn is the National Coordinator and a Director of Second Amendment Sisters [&lt;a href="http://www.2asisters.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.2asisters....&lt;/a&gt; ]. Jenn also has sponsored a bill this session in the State House to protect your knife rights. See this nice write up in Pro-Gun New Hampshire: &lt;a href="http://www.pgnh.org/protecting_your_knife_rights_by_representative_jennifer_coffey" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pgnh.org/p...&lt;/a&gt; , and this one in Blade magazine as Jenn's bill has gotten national attention in relation to the recently defeated(!) attempt by U.S. Customs to classify all assisted open knives as switchblades: &lt;a href="http://www.blademag.com/article/the-blade-backlash-has-begun" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.blademag.c...&lt;/a&gt; .  Please help Jenn in her latest effort to protect our rights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Todd Puterbaugh</member_name><member_id>4083337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262300651000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262018289000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Women's Self-Defense and the NH State House Gun Ban</name><id>12159559</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262127600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/12159559/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>