<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**In addition to our regular book club meeting, we will also do a book swap. Please bring in a book or two to three to swap with the other members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arctic Drift by Clive Cussler&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.borders.com/ProductImages/products/00/57/93/a/57931988_a.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who love a good adventure and mystery, this book is for you! Here's a brief synopsis:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his new novel, however, the twentieth Dirk Pitt adventure Cussler may have topped even himself. A potential breakthrough discovery to reverse global warming . . . a series of unexplained sudden deaths in British Columbia . . . a rash of international incidents between the United States and one of its closest allies that threatens to erupt into an actual shooting war . . . NUMA director Dirk Pitt and his children, Dirk. Jr. and Summer, have reason to believe theres a connection here somewhere, but they also know they have very little time to find it before events escalate out of control. Their only real clue might just be a mysterious silvery mineral traced to a long-ago expedition in search of the fabled Northwest Passage. But no one survived from that doomed mission, captain and crew perished to a manand if Pitt and his colleague Al Giordino arent careful, the very same fate may await them. Filled with the breathtaking suspense and audacious imagination that have become his hallmarks, this is a tour de force further proof that when it comes to adventure writing, nobody beats Clive Cussler.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the table closest to the cafe door. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262902282000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240959548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Book Club - Arctic Drift + BOOK SWAP!</name><id>10289183</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262217600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/10289183/</event_url></item>