<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Center of Light is hosting a weekend of seminars with Mother Clare Watts. Mother Clare is a dynamic speaker, down-to-earth, with great integrity and powerful insights. She is a modern-day mystic, Teacher, national speaker, author, parent, and former homebirth midwife and psychotherapist with Jungian training. She will be giving seminars of topics of inner spirituality on Thursday and Friday nights, and on Saturday morning. I am posting these events in addition to our regular meetups since they may be of interest to some group members. There is an admission fee for these seminars. See below for a description of this day's seminar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday,   May 11th   7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Experience of the Presence of God&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a vast difference between believing something to be true and knowing that it is. It is possible to experience God so deeply that you know God is real, and to build a connection with God that is consistent and that changes you. This is the realm of the mystics. Mystics of all times and traditions have always sought to find out for themselves who God is, what God is like, and who they are as souls loved beyond measure. Join us for this seminar designed to move you beyond dogma and belief, into the realm of direct experience.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1179099230000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177962581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: The Experience of the Presence of God</name><id>5725832</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178926200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/5725832/</event_url></item>