<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-128</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03076</zip><lat>42.740836</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Muldoon Park</name><city>Pelham</city><id>799116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.345759</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Host: Claire P. cell @ 603-247-0897 &lt;br /&gt;RAIN SNOW CANCELS THIS EVENT!&lt;br /&gt;Weather permitting, I think it would be fun to go and play Disc Golf at the Muldoon Park. The park (course) is located right off Route 128 in Pelham NH. We meet at Hillside Country Store &amp;amp; Deli located at 321 Mammoth Rd, Pelham, NH.  This store is across the street from Muldoon Park. This is where we get  the discs, which are free of charge.  You can play either play 9 or 18 baskets. The game is played by tossing a disc (Frisbee) into a basket.  The first nine baskets are fairly easy, the last nine are more challenging. This is a great way to get some fresh air, a bit of exercise, and great conversations with the people from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that GPS does not work well in locating this site.   Mammoth Rd is actually route 128.  Look for the store on a hill (on your right if heading south, on your left if heading north).&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring your sunscreen, insect repellent and plenty of fluids.&lt;br /&gt;This event is at no cost! I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP or call my cell @ 603-247-0897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: &lt;br /&gt;Muldoon Park, Mammoth Rd, Pelham, NH 03076&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290281062000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289755230000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Disc Golf</name><id>15443056</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290268800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15443056/</event_url></item>