<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>345 Somerville Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.381008</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>PA's Lounge</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1213917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099039</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;OPEN MIC/Party with Free Live Music at PA's LOUNGE in UNION SQUARE, Somerville. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Singers, musicians, horns, percussionists - everyone is welcome to attend the open mic in the PA's Lounge stageroom relaxed atmosphere, to play, sing or listen.  Singers, Sax, horns &amp;amp; drummers encouraged, we have drum pads.  The Open Mic will occur Mondays starting at 8PM with rehearsals at 7:30.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a blues style open mike for all types of music, but we usually do at 1 least a jazz set inc. some well known standards.  There are at least 4 musician/singer meetup groups participating, and sometimes other social/meetups/groups.  Songs on the songlist are:  What a wonderful world, Over the rainbow, sunshine of my life, summertime, and good ideas would be songs like She’s come Undun, Blue Skies, Take Five, improvisations on great jazz/blues riffs &amp;amp; themes.  &lt;b&gt;Even if you don't play, come to check it out and meet/network &amp;amp; make friends with interesting musicians.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention Party goers,  Musicians &amp;amp; Singers!!  Come join the party at the Monday Night Open mike!  Everyone Welcome.  No cover charge - Play or sing music solo or with backing band.  All instruments and styles welcome.  Originals, covers, blues, jazz, funk, Fusion, classic rock, R&amp;amp;B, Motown, folk, etc.   Back up band with drums, bass, guitar, and Songlist for singers.  Bring your friends for the party, network, and meet interesting people.  RSVP to assure priority on the signup sheet.  If you have any particular songs you prefer, mention it in the comments when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4" on the keys.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294710572000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jazz Fans/Musicians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>jazz-190</urlname><id>1202977</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Cambridge/Somerville/Boston Jazz Meetup/Jam</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294639042000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OPEN MIC,  - Live Music, Networking, in Union Square</name><id>krnfqypcbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294705800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/jazz-190/events/15990740/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/b/global_6953227.jpeg</photo_url></item>