<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;No Limit Texas Hold 'Em&amp;nbsp;Tournament&amp;nbsp;at Mitch's in Hartford. Beginners are welcome. It's a $20 buy in with no rebuys or addons. Please bring a extra $1.00 to pass along to Nina for Meetup website fees as well. A couple of snacks and soda will be provided, but feel free to also bring along a snack. BYOB.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is&amp;nbsp;a ONE-table tournament&amp;nbsp;so PLEASE:&amp;nbsp; If you RSVP and then find you can't attend, change your RSVP as soon as possible so someone can take your place.&amp;nbsp; If we have 8 players, the payouts will be either $90/$50/$20 or $100/$60, as decided by the players prior to the beginning of the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinds will go up every&amp;nbsp;20 minutes so we should have a winner before the late news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to email me with any questions!&amp;nbsp; Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've never played before, don't hesitate to come!&amp;nbsp; First, because the best (and really only) way to get comfortable with tournament poker is to DO IT!&amp;nbsp; Second, because we're a very friendly group and we'll be patient with you as you pick up the basics.&amp;nbsp; Third, because, as a beginner, experienced players will find you very unpredictable.&amp;nbsp; This makes you a viable threat, and you may even end up winning!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Light Green House with a big cement slab for a front yard.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332202255000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328500480000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Texas Hold Em' at Mitch's</name><id>51188422</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332108000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/51188422/</event_url></item>