<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2040 Dixwell Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06514</zip><lat>41.367641</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hamden High School</name><city>Hamden</city><id>1275918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.923447</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;CANCELLED DUE TO RAIN&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that the weather is nice, I was hoping to play once a week.  I am a beginner but would love to play with anyone and everyone.  I thought I would schedule a meetup this Wednesday at the Hamden High School tennis courts.  Would love for anyone to join me to hit a few balls around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, as I mentioned to a few of you today, I am volunteering at the Special Olympics Tennis event on Sunday, June 9th from 8:30 - 12pm.  This volunteer opportunity is through ESPN.  If anyone is interested in volunteering, please let me know/contact me.  The deadline to let me know is by next Friday, May 17th.  The volunteer location will be at Southern CT State University.  You can volunteer as a ball runner, timer, counter, hugger and/or as an award presenter.  I am volunteering as a ball runner and hugger.  You can volunteer anytime between 8:30am-4pm.  I opted to volunteer from 8:30am-12pm.  Let me know if you are interested and we can always car pool or you can meet me there.  I need to know for sure by the end of next week/May 17th so I can let the volunteer coordinator at ESPN know.  Thought this would be fitting to post it on this site.  I hope to see a lot of interest from all you tennis lovers.  Thank you in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swadhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S.  It looks like it may rain on Wednesday.  If the forecast still predicts rain on Wednesday, I will update the website and cancel this meetup Tuesday evening. CANCELLED DUE TO RAIN&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368065633000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tennis Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tennisplayers</urlname><id>967168</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Tennis Meetup of New Haven and Fairfield Counties</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365436368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cancelled Due To Rain - Hamden High School - Week Night Tennis 7pm</name><id>113292342</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368054000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tennisplayers/events/113292342/</event_url></item>