<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Federal St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01109</zip><lat>42.109195</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-755-6112</phone><name>Scibelli Enterprise Center, Across from STCC, downstairs media room</name><city>Springfield</city><id>669366</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.577679</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Notice of IRN Public Meeting - Dec. 7, 7PM &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dear Innovators, &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We are pleased to announce our regular Public Meeting for December 2011. This will be the last meeting of the year so we hope many of you can make the trip - AND bring along friends and co-workers! Remember, the open meetings are now FREE to the public. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Not only is the meeting free - but you are likely to walk out with one of our many door prizes! Yes, once again we celebrate another year of IRN with some useful items to be given away. Your odds of winning are extremely good, so come on down! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please note - if any members wish to add to the door prizes (giveaway items), please email Craig at cissod@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Our Dec. speaker will be Neshan Daglian (aka "Dag") an experienced Engineer who spent much of his career at Atlas Copco, a world leader in everything from air compressors to mining equipment. He has served in various capacities from product engineer and test engineer to engineering manager. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The meeting will also feature expanded refreshments - we hear a rumor that even shrimp may be on the menu! We will also allow time for some one to one networking. &lt;br /&gt;

C'mon down and hobnob with your fellow innovators! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As mentioned previously, we record audio from our open meetings - and have started a Podcast series, which you can find on itunes at the following link: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/innovation-invention-speakers/id433329307" class="linkified"&gt;http://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/innovation-invention-speakers/id433329307&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

or, on the web at: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://hearth.com/podcast/irn/podcast.xml" class="linkified"&gt;http://hearth.com/podcast/irn/podcast.xml&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

There you will find all the episodes up to and including October, 2011 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In order to keep our members up to date with links, announcements and other such news - we have started a facebook page at: &lt;br /&gt;

h&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Holyoke-Massachusetts/Innovators-Resource-Network/210705578957971" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/pages/Holyoke-Massachusetts/Innovators-Resource-Network/210705578957971&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/67kd75w" class="linkified"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/67kd75w&lt;/a&gt; (shortened version) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please "like" us on facebook - we need to get a certain amount of people who check in to reap the benefits. You can also add your own comments and links, so we can have a continual exchange of links and upcoming events. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Sincerely, &lt;br /&gt;

Innovators Resource Network&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Craig</member_name><member_id>8480979</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Blanchard</member_name><member_id>9728219</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323357673000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322508464000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IRN December Public Meeting - Speaker, Door Prizes, extra Refreshments and more</name><id>42646102</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323302400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/42646102/</event_url></item>