<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last year we had a great turn out with quite a few people helping to hand out the enormous amount of info we had for the huge crowd for the 4th. This year we can do an even better job at informing people with fliers and DVD's! However it cant be done well without your help. If you have joined this group and have not been involved yet here is a great opportunity to make a difference on a day where we can inform thousands of people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4th OF JULY TRUTH ACTION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday July 4, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Charles River Esplanade, Boston&lt;br /&gt;9 am to 5 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Truth activists will be gathering at Boston's 4th of July Celebration on the Esplanade this year to distribute DVD's along with We Are Change info handouts. A core group of organizers will be setting up Camp on the lawn adjacent to the Stone Man Playground near the Harvard (Mass Ave) Bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there, we'll break off into groups and canvas the entire area, from and including the Longfellow Bridge to the Harvard Bridge. Even if you can come only for a couple of hours, there will be someone at the Camp at all times beginning at 9 am, who will be able to connect you with groups already out working the crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best access to the home Camp is via the pedestrian entrance to the esplanade at the Mass. Ave Bridge. From there it's just a short 100 ft. walk to a fork in the sidewalk that surrounds a strip of lawn where we're setting up camp. Look for the flag of New England we'll be flying a red flag with a green Pine tree.&lt;br /&gt;We have a total of 10,000 pieces of literature we want to distribute among the 500,000-plus people in attendance. We hope you can join us as in this huge distribution effort and for some celebration after the fireworks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(From the Mass. Ave bridge when looking towards down town along the Charles river there will be a bike/ walking path that splits in two directions. The section of grass that is in between the paths is where we will be set up.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI This is a great vantage point to watch the fireworks, so come help us hog our space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246885783000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245816451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston July 4th Charles River Espland 9/11 Truth info Handout! Help Wanted!</name><id>10722727</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246712400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/10722727/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/6/global_7665974.jpeg</photo_url></item>