<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>2009 SPRING SALE &amp;amp; DEMO WEEKEND&lt;br /&gt;April  26,  Sunday 1 pm to apx 2/2:30 pm for our group visit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CCK Directions&lt;br /&gt;From 84 (Anywhere Northeast of us)&lt;br /&gt;Take 84 West to exit 39 (Farmington/Route 4 exit). Take Route 4 West through Farmington and Unionville. In Unionville veer right-continue on Route 4 about 2 miles outside of Unionville, Route 4 runs into Route 179. Follow Route 179 North to stop sign, turning right over bridge (you're still on Route 179). CCK is just up the road on the left. Look for the big red barns and the boats outside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't plan on being here more than an hour or so, just long enough to see whats new, try a few boats &amp;amp; recommend some to our members..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;UPDATE: Then its off to the Barbie-Q spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will head out to the Barbie-Q spot after we have seen enough at Collinsville, i will guess 2:30 +/- ?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE BARBIE-Q Spot:&lt;br /&gt;GPS Users use 92 Canton Road, Burlington, CT to get you to the entrance to the  Rails to Trails entrance on rte 179 and 4 intersection .  Its about 2.5 miles south on 179 from Collinsvill Canoe &amp;amp; Kayak event and on the left just past the lighted intersection. Use caution while entering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I chose this Barbie-Q place because it won't mess up anyone's home, its outside, and sort of secluded enough for a simple gathering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for the Orange striped Traffic Cones a bit further down from the main parking area, we will be near the river bank. Walking along the river is nice here also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some food, chairs and your faviourite beverage.&lt;br /&gt;I will have the grille and fire pit loaded.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is also listed on my other site www.meetup.com/Forever-Young&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;but RSVP is only here on the Recreational-Sea Kayakers site so we can see who is going &amp;amp; to hopefully find each other&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I list this event once a year and its good for some of you to try before you buy, and buy used also check Craigs List but dont buy JUNK LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ladies, try out the Necky Eliza,&lt;br /&gt;Its perfect designed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guys, just try what fits you, just get something 14 feet or so longer with compartments..LOL&lt;br /&gt;otherwise everyone will just call it junk, but its ok i have junk too.LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The used boats tend to be a good deal, most sold are the recreational ones, this is good for you since the better ones to take on the ocean are not favored by recreational paddlers so you get a good deal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember: its prudent to get something of a better quality and further than your intended use even if you dont go to the ocean than to have something junky if the weather is like the ocean on a lake.&lt;br /&gt;You will gain confidence and skills so dont be caught up with the hype of high initial stability,&lt;br /&gt;My NDK Greenlander has ok inital stability for beginners and has plenty of go for advanced padlers,&lt;br /&gt;My bathtub boat you can stand up in and paddle..LOL..get the idea..get something just a bit above your skills and you will gain them in it.. Get a boat rated as &amp;quot;ok&amp;quot; for the ocean, then you can go out in most all normal situations with confidence that you and the boat will survive just fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommendaton: 14 feet or longer, 2 sealed compartments, name brand with long time reputation for good quality and history. ie, Necky, Impex, and others.talk to the Connyak people there if you are interested in ocean kayaks for additional recommendations.. I even posted on Connyak.org that some of you may be asking questions&lt;br /&gt;Greenland is common type among most members there..&lt;br /&gt;Many of you have tried my Greenlander as first timers and done well in such an advanced boat..&lt;br /&gt;So dont waste your money on the  fat slow ones..thinking they are better and more stable..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I or some other demonstrators will show you why later in the season..or someone else will if the fall in and we save them..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recreational boats are short, fat, heavy, slow, bald and cheap..ops sounds like some lazy bum stupid guys..LOL&lt;br /&gt;you will waste your money and energy getting them to move any faster than a crawl. They are good for relaxing sucking beer and floating on a lake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You really want 14 feet or longer, slimmer, lighter, faster, accessories, and worth the price... ops sounds like some attractive intelligent ladies..LOL &lt;br /&gt;You will be surprized at the glide and stride you will enjoy year after year.&lt;br /&gt;They are good for relaxing and moving in many conditions, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group does lakes, rivers and some limited ocean trips, all have for the past years have gone just fine even with recreational kayaks out on the ocean. We all work as a group to keep you alive and make decisions on conditions for all as we go along.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C C&amp;amp;K also will have some lectures and demonstrations things for those of you that want to learn about kayaking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;check out their site for more info..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.cckstore.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see ya soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing my flourecent orange hat at the place, hard to miss that one</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>28</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241285637000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235058658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spring Kayak Demo &amp; our  Barbie-Q 2.5 miles South @ Rte 179/4 by the River After</name><id>9775953</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240765200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/9775953/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/9/global_5044665.jpeg</photo_url></item>