<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>January we'll have a business meeting to get things off the right way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE FPA License Plate Frames for members. Purchase an additional one for a small stipend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's talk about our possible start of AOPA/EAA Airport Open House. The following is from their website. We should discuss this further.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;INTERNATIONAL “ L E A RN TO F LY D AY ”&lt;br /&gt;Announced during EAA AirVenture Oshkosh 2009, International&lt;br /&gt;Learn to Fly Day is a cooperative effort by pilots, companies,&lt;br /&gt;governments, and organizations around the world to raise interest&lt;br /&gt;in flying and encourage current pilots to get others involved in&lt;br /&gt;aviation. The inaugural event is planned for May 15, 2010, with the&lt;br /&gt;intention of making it an annual event. Specific events to punctuate&lt;br /&gt;International Learn to Fly Day are in the planning stage. More details&lt;br /&gt;will be announced after the first of the year.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, we need to figure out Oshkosh 2010. Only about 7 month and about 15 days from our meet night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We doing an Oshkosh Raffle? Let's discuss that as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm sure we'll add more to the list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, Fly Often and Fly Safe.&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe, &lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263510382000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260317423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 January Meetup</name><id>lcqqjyncbqb</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263337200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/12047596/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/b/global_12512427.jpeg</photo_url></item>