<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Summer Solstice with a sunset hike and bonfire at the lookout along the rugged Metacomet Trail in East Granby. We'll meet up at 7:00pm at the Tarriffville Gorge. You may know this spot as the whitewater canoing and kayaking area off Tunxis Avenue. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We meet just at the park's entrance and hike approximately 20 minutes up the Metacomet ridge to an overlook of the river where we'll enjoy the sunset, camaraderie, and a bonfire before heading back down. Be sure to bring a flashlight for the descent if you plan on staying after dark. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Coordinates: &lt;br /&gt;

N41.902852 &lt;br /&gt;

W72.75919 &lt;br /&gt;

Follow Tunxis Avenue to the entrance of the park. Park at the metal gate that locks the park after sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mapquest Directions: &lt;br /&gt;

38 Tunxis Ave &lt;br /&gt;

East Granby, CT 06026 &lt;br /&gt;

#38 is the last house on Tunxis (before the entrance to the park) and brings you about 40 feet from where we will meet and pick up the trail. Plenty of street parking if the lot is full. Again, we will meet at the metal gate at the entrance to the park, just past #38 on Tunxis Ave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;

By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow Tunxis Avenue to the entrance of the park. Park at the metal gate that locks the park after sunset.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340511521000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340467822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Hike / Bonfire</name><id>70407312</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340492400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/70407312/</event_url></item>