<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Silence Before Bach&lt;/b&gt; directed by Pere Portabella  Spain 2008  101 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Since this is a weeknight event, please indicate if you will be joining us for dinner and  attending our group discussion after the film when you RSVP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Real-life drama and documentary-style filmmaking blend with surrealistic whimsy in director Pere Portabella's passionate look at the ties between classical music and the construction of contemporary Europe.... this puckish, almost kitsch collection of skits takes a playful look at the legacy of a classical composer whose music still retains the power to inspire and influence. All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I didn’t find “&lt;b&gt;The Silence Before Bach&lt;/b&gt;” immediately accessible, though this is far from a complaint. The film demands engagement and a kind of surrender, a willingness to enter into a work shaped by correlation, metaphor and metonymy, by beautiful images and fragments of ideas, a work that locates the music in the twitching of a dog’s ears, in the curve of a woman’s belly, a child’s song and an adult’s reverie. Like the music it celebrates, this is a film made in glory of the world. NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Silence Before Bach&lt;/b&gt; is a mélange of genres including narrative vignettes and documentary sequences on the theme of the transformational power of great music. At one moment his camera records a subway car packed with passionate cello-playing musicians; at another he is following a guide who gives tours of Leipzig dressed in full Bach regalia; and in a third he stages Felix Mendelssohn’s discovery of sheet music for the “St. Matthew Passion” used by a butcher to wrap meat. By turns funny and serious, poignant, sexy and refreshing, &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The Silence Before Bach&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; is very nearly unclassifiable, like so much of Portabella’s oeuvre. (Film Forum) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before Bach, Portabella infers, Europe was essentially primitive. Indeed, Bach effectively redeemed this earlier stage of creation. The movie's title may then be interpreted as an expression of awe. Bach's music is &amp;quot;the only thing that reminds us the world is not a failure,&amp;quot; someone says—and not as a joke.  Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll stroll down Huntington Ave.  to a nearby eatery for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be holding a meetup sign after the film near the front row.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248221327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Silence Before Bach </name><id>10928131</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250805600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10928131/</event_url></item>