<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will park at the first  parking lot on left side as you enter park from North Street (RT 85).  Hike will last about two hours (6-8pm). We will be walking the red loop which is approximately 4.5 miles. The terrain is moderate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FRIENDLY DOGS ARE WELCOMED, Dogs must remain leashed for entire hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN CANCELS : you will be notified via email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The attendance list is printed out at 5pm on the day of the hike so be sure to remove yourself from the hike if you can't make it. Thank You.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will need water and good boots or hiking shoes. Insect repellent and sunscreen are also a good idea. I will make every effort to get us back to our cars before sunset but please bring a small flashlight for safety.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are a hiking group. That means we start together and we finish together and are only as fast as our slowest hiker. Please keep this in mind if you decide to join us. Also, keep an open mind to hikes having to be shortened on-the-fly if the group is moving slower than expected. I do not want us to get caught in the dark!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No Children: Feel free to email me or contact me through here if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;ll=41.717582,-72.440286&amp;amp;spn=0.027965,0.066047&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;msid=106880071684886446021.000489beb08559c03d945" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gay City State Park Trail Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/gaycity.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt</member_name><member_id>10084960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278100823000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277352655000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>After Work Hike - Gay City State Park  Hebron, CT</name><id>13895313</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278021600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13895313/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>