<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Lyme Rd, Hanover, NH 03755</address_1><state>Ne</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.718903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>45 Lyme Rd, Hanover, NH 03755</name><city>Hanover</city><id>8652532</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.273232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us while evening hikes are still sunlit! Another Upper Valley classic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE HIKE: We will hike ~ 1.25 miles/1 hr. up to the high point of Lambert Ridge (~2300 ft/ ~1000ft elev. gain) to take in views of Mt. Moosilauke to the north and smaller peaks to the south, and then retrace our path back to the parking lot (~2 hr total). (This is the section of the Appalachian Trail that ascends Smart's Mt, but we'll save the summit of Smart's for a full day excursion.) The out and back plan will allow for folks at different paces, though I suggest we follow the same turn around time. &lt;br /&gt;

MEETING: Meet at north end of parking lot at 45 Lyme Rd. (Rt 10 north of Hanover across from golf course &amp;amp; firestation, look for Mascoma Bank) for carpooling to the Smart's Mt. trailhead on Dorchester Rd. in Lyme. Or, if you plan to meet us at the trailhead, kindly note this on your RSVP, otherwise we will look for you in Hanover. We will depart by car from 45 Lyme Rd promptly at 5:15 and from the trailhead on foot at 5:45pm. We should return to trailhead at 7:45pm and to 45 Lyme at 8:15pm. &lt;br /&gt;

Sunset is 7:42pm. Headlamp is advisable. &lt;br /&gt;

WEATHER: Currently the weather looks good for Wed., but please check this site after noon Wed. as the hike may be canceled if chance of thunderstorms is &amp;gt;50%, or if insufficient sign up. &lt;br /&gt;

DOGS: Dogs are welcome, mine will be along. There are no streams on this hike so bring enough water for you and your dog if you are bringing one. &lt;br /&gt;

PARKING: There is ample parking at 45 Lyme Rd. and at trailhead &amp;amp; probably no cell service there. &lt;br /&gt;

CANCELLATION: If you cannot make it, please update your RSVP so you are not in the head count and we are wondering where you are. &lt;br /&gt;

AFTER HIKE SOCIALIZATION: Optional pending preference of the hikers (Ramuntos Pizza/beer in Hanover is good choice) &lt;br /&gt;

DISCUSSION: If you are interested in evening hikes, please see my thread on the Discussion Board seeking input. In the interest of streamlining planning and not inundating us with email, please limit comments here to topics related to this hike only. Thank you in advance for your help with this!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346004057000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345227581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Lambert Ridge Trail, Lyme NH (evening)</name><id>78185332</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345670100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/78185332/</event_url></item>