<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 McNamara Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05757</zip><lat>43.480911</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>802-235-1513</phone><name>Forget-Me-Not Farm</name><city>Tinmouth</city><id>958161</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.075638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;SolarFest -- July 16, 17, and 18, 2010&lt;/b&gt; -- On a beautiful July weekend, several thousand people come to SolarFest to join a weekend community. We are inspired by art and technology, by the talent and ability of all the diverse individuals who make the festival (many of the volunteers have been doing this for over a decade), to create a place where learning and fun thrive. Flyby News has been supporting this festival for more than a decade, and invites especially &amp;quot;9/11 truthers&amp;quot; for a special camping retreat to energize with great people, green energy, music, and Vermont's splendor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We are looking forward to bringing you another great year of world-class entertainment, the best workshops the Northeast has to offer, plus over 100 vendors and exhibitors showcasing a wide variety of renewable energy and sustainability products, clothing, crafts and delicious food. Tickets go on sale in April. Performers and presenters will be listed as they are confirmed. Workshop proposal and volunteer applications will be available in mid-January.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark your calendars for SolarFest 2010 - July 16, 17 and 18!&lt;br /&gt;For more than 15 years, demonstrating the power of positive energy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;KEYNOTE SPEAKER  PERFORMERS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Environmentalist Bill McKibben will be Keynote Speaker for SolarFest 2010. Internationally known as a tireless champion for a healthy planet, Bill is a prolific author and the founder of 350.org, an international climate campaign. Read an excerpt from his newest book here.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our performers this year include Barefoot Truth, Capital Zen, Caravan of Thieves, Entrain, Impulse Ensemble, The Guy Mendilow Band, Sara Milonovich and Daisycutter, Perpetual e-Motion, Prydein, Kelly Ravin, Rubblebucket Orchestra and the SolarFest House Band.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;PARTICIPATE!  TICKET INFORMATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SolarFest is still looking for volunteers!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opportunities abound in Zero Waste, Parking/Traffic, Security, and more.  We trade you the weekend ticket, plus two meals a day at the Volunteer Kitchen in exchange for nine hours and the cost of the t-shirt.  Please join us for a really great, meaningful time.  Click here.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-sale Ticket Sales are Closed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets will be available at the Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2010 Ticket Prices:&lt;br /&gt;Weekend Pass: $45&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Only: $10 (Tire Kicker Friday)&lt;br /&gt;Saturday only: $30&lt;br /&gt;Sunday only: $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn more at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://solarfest.org" target="_blank"&gt;SolarFest&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280098007000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278707057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SolarFest - New England's Best Energy-Art Festival</name><id>14054270</id><headcount>3000</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279296000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/14054270/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/8/global_16293160.jpeg</photo_url></item>