<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Sanford St. </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06824</zip><lat>41.142201</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-259-1036</phone><name>Fairfield Theater Company</name><city>Fairfield</city><id>936735</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.257874</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Shemekia Copeland not only Rocks The House, Shenekia gives it a new name :-) &lt;br /&gt;Opening is JohnnyswimGet Tix! Artist Info Video Website Share Thu 12/02 7:30 PM | DOORS OPEN AT 7:00 PM  &lt;br /&gt;TICKETS: $27  MEMBERS SAVE: $5 PER TICKET Having opened for the Rolling Stones and headlined at the Chicago Blues Festival, this daughter of legend Johnny Clyde Copeland keeps the tradition alive. Her passion for the blues, her ability to bend its rules and her clear desire to take the genre to new places make her a perfect fit for the intimate StageOne. Come welcome this repeat-winner of the Living Blues Reader Award and a repeat nominee at the Blues Music Awards, and hear songs from her latest album, Never Going Back.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She says, &amp;quot;My main goal when I started this was that I was going to do something different with this music, so that this music could evolve and grow. I got that idea from my father. He went to Africa and worked with musicians there. He was one of the first blues artists to do that. I want to be the same way. I want to be innovative with the blues.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291437527000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288673246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lady Who Knows How To Sing The Blues "Shemekia Copeland"</name><id>15307317</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291334400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/15307317/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/d/global_2165245.jpeg</photo_url></item>