<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Webster Plaza</address_2><address_1>6 Mill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02050</zip><lat>42.119158</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-837-6668</phone><name>Mug'N'Muffin</name><city>Marshfield</city><id>958766</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.766249</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Mug'n'Muffin is an old childhood favorite of mine back when they had a restaurant in Braintree Square.  Once that restaurant closed I sadly thought they went out of business.  I was delighted to find the restaurant last year in a vist to Marshfield.  In addition to sticking with our alliterative theme, dining at the Mug'n'Muffin in Marshfield in May is also good for your wallet as it's a Cheap Eat with everything on the menu under $8.  OK, so I didn't realize how much the &amp;quot;M&amp;quot; theme was being played out but did you notice how much I love alliterations?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breakfast is served all day here and there are lunch items as well.  Don't you just love being able to eat Breakfast at Lunch or Breakfast and Lunch?  In addition to the traditional Breakfast and Lunch fare they offer Desserts.  Did I mention everything on the menu is under $8?  Did I mention the beaches of Marshfield are a short drive away?  Is it Spring or Summer?  Maybe both!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're already driving to Marshfield in your mind then please plan to join us for &amp;quot;Breakfast or Lunch?  Maybe Both!&amp;quot; on Saturday, May 30th.  We are going during non-peak hours but still at a mealtime so they should be able to comfortably accommodate us.  Get ready for a nice casual relaxing meal with the SSDOMG Members and Guests at a cheap eat on the alliteration trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breakfast or Lunch?  Maybe Both!&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, May 30th @ 1pm&lt;br /&gt;Mug'n'Muffin&lt;br /&gt;6 Mill Road&lt;br /&gt;Website Plaza&lt;br /&gt;Intersection of Route 139 and 3A&lt;br /&gt;Marshfield, MA 02050&lt;br /&gt;781-837-6668&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Place: Please meet outside the front door.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer: Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: [Current] Annual Members - FREE, Members and Guests - $2 each&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Minimum of 6 Yes RSVP's by 4pm on Thursday, May 27th.  (This number must be maintained at the RSVP Deadline as well.) Currently there is no max.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: 1 per member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 4pm on Friday, May 29th (Any changes made after this time may not be seen by the Event Organizer prior to the event.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview: Webster Plaza is located at the intersection of Routes 139 and 3A in Marshfield.  For those of you who joined us at Aoyama last February, this is in the same strip mall.  For those of you in the SSFMG who have attended Fit Camps at Rob's Studio, this is located just before the last set of lights before getting to his studio.  Either way, there's a CVS across the street.  If you go thru the lights you have gone too far (unless you take the right, then you can still turn right into the strip mall).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take the Marshfield Exit (12).  Follow Route 139 East for about 4 miles passing thru numerous lights.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full directions to be posted the week before the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet outside the front door or at our table after we are seated.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244850056000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242318487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast or Lunch?  Maybe Both!</name><id>10411360</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243702800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/10411360/</event_url></item>