<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The estimable poet and translator David Ferry will be launching the Fall 2012 Poetry Reading Series at Boston University, on Monday, September 24th at 6 PM. This free and public reading will take place in the Katzenberg Center, 3rd Floor, 871 Commonwealth Avenue (BU West T-stop on the Green Line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ferry is the author of Of No Country I Know: New and Selected Poems and Translations, winner of the 2000 Rebekah Johnson Bobbitt National Prize for Poetry and the Academy of American Poets' Lenore Marshall Poetry Prize. He is the translator of Gilgamesh (1992), The Odes of Horace (1998), The Eclogues of Virgil (1999), The Epistles of Horace (2001), winner of the Landon Translation Prize, and The Georgics of Virgil (2005), all published by Farrar, Straus and Giroux. Ferry's other awards include the Sixtieth Fellowship of The Academy of American Poets, the Teasdale Prize for Poetry, the John Simon Guggenheim Foundation Fellowship, the Ingram Merrill Award, and the William Arrowsmith Translation Prize from AGNI magazine. His new book, Bewilderment, was released this month by the University of Chicago Press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books will be available for sale. Please contact Meg Tyler at (617) 358-4199 or mtyler@bu.edu with any questions. This event co-sponsored by the Center for the Humanities at Boston University and the College of General Studies.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348535144000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347550834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>David Ferry reading at Boston University</name><id>82226582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348524000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/82226582/</event_url></item>