<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Cambridge Center 6th Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362583</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>TechStars/Dogpatch to START</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>7972722</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE/CLARIFICATION;  Hi there;  everyone is invited to join our group mobile tech crawl. You don't need to create a team. Feel free to invite your friends as well. We will mix it up at 5pm when we all gather and, as needed, we'll create Team LEW, Team KEITH and Team BRUCE for a mobile marketing crawl of Kendall Square with our friends at AMA Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year the BIMM group nailed it and we all got rewarded with freebies from AMAboston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please sign up on Event brite here....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://checkin2012.eventbrite.com/"&gt;http://checkin2012.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Christina FROM AMAboston will make sure we’re all on the list for the NERD wrapup and your only cost is the $5 cost/donation when you register at eventbrite above- the NERD event is included - so no extra expenses. A savings of $25 for non AMAboston people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You HAVE to use the EventBrite Link to officially sign up - if you are not on the list, security at the NERD Center will NOT let you in!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************** &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://checkin2012.eventbrite.com"&gt;http://checkin2012.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2nd Annual CHECKInvitational TweetUP - July 11 @ Kendall Square, 5pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Event! - The Legend! - Not to mention The Beer and the Fries....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AMA Boston's Social Media team is leading the charge once again as mobile marketing meets Kendall Square. Show your savvy around that smartphone or just text your marketing pals to join us and pick up on some of the latest mobile news &amp;amp; trends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;charge your batteries and get those walking shoes out as we travel to exotic outposts around Kendall Square on a quest for the holy grail of mobile marketing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FREE PASSES to the next major AMA Event for the winning team!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worth up to 45 bucks apiece! The bigger your team, the more you WIN !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(And YES, it may involve a check-In at MeadHall too ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team Lew (ALL BIMM ATTENDEES LAST YEAR) and Team Chris slugged it out to victory last year - who can take them on and prevail?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This years challenge is open to anyone trying to figure out if Google+Local is going stomp FourSquare and which is best for checking into MeadHall or The Asgard. We'll demo some cool new apps and set out from the TechSTARS office promtly at 5pm for a fun, marketers style scavenger hunt around Kendall Square ending up at the MicroSoft NERDCenter for a Mobile Marketing presentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE $5 donation goes to the MSPCA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>lew</member_name><member_id>10673992</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>bruce jones</member_name><member_id>11668980</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>12427891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342813225000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341003250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual CHECKInvitational Mobile Marketing Crawl</name><id>71326072</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342040400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/71326072/</event_url></item>