<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Human beings are a popular and very dynamic subject to capture with your digital camera. In addition to the standard technical challenges you face in all photography, capturing images of people presents additional challenges.  Good people photography or portraiture (both formal and informal) requires an understanding of human behavior, good communication and a level of photographic skill to create.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be a combination lecture style and hands on exercises, and will cover the skills and methods for making portraits and great images of people.  We will cover the techniques to advance your photography from just taking snapshots to a more a deliberate approach too this great subject.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People/Portrait photography topics discussed will include camera and lens settings, posing ideas and how to use different lighting (available light, reflectors, on-camera flash) . Styles of portraits discussed will range from candid to formal classic images. The workshop will also feature how to connect and communicate with your subjects, how to guide their posing to make better portraits. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People are the most dynamic and often the most challenging of photography subjects. They also can present opportunity to make some truly outstanding images! This class is designed to sharpen your skills and to help get more creative in your portrait taking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a good class for beginners and more advanced photographers alike&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>f</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286062371000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281808134000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PEOPLE PHOTOGRAPHY - Making portraits workshop</name><id>14422109</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284829200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14422109/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/e/global_16414110.jpeg</photo_url></item>