<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>L'Argent de Poche (Small Change) France 1976 dir Francois Truffaut 104 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small Change is an episodic comedy drama composed of several sequences that explore childhood in director François Truffaut's signature humanistic style. Filmed in Thiers in South Central France, each vignette is seen from the point of view of a kid from two weeks to 14 years old. There is no real plot, just little scenes flowing together dealing with personal joys and pains of the children in a small town.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Literally translated as &amp;quot;Pocket Money,&amp;quot; the title of François Truffaut's 1976 film gets at something meager and precious about childhood. The baggy theme is kids' resilience and resourcefulness, seen in incidents strung across the course of a school year. Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Too long absent from the big screen (it hasn't screened at the Brattle in over 20 years!), SMALL CHANGE is one of French master Francois Truffaut's most poetic and personal films, a radiant celebration of the world of childhood. Through a series of loosely connected vignettes in a small city in southern France, a group of children, from infants to adolescents, experience the joys and trials of being young. 'Children exist in a state of grace,' as a young mother observes. 'They pass untouched through dangers that would destroy an adult.' - Brattle Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A comedy, a romance, a mystery - in a word: childhood - captured, distilled, and transformed effortlessly from sketchbook to symphony in the hands of a master named Francois Truffaut.&amp;quot; - Wes Anderson&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; A rarity - a poetic comedy that's really funny. Truffaut's deadpan, disjointed style is quicker and surer than ever before.&amp;quot; - Pauline Kael (an American film critic who wrote for The New Yorker magazine from 1968 to 1991)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An original, a major work in minor keys. It's a labor of love that ignores precedent with splendid verve ... It ambles through the lives of these children, observing them in school, at home, going to the movies, making do on a Sunday morning when parents sleep late, trying to pawn some textbooks, making painful and hilarious discoveries that, by the time we reach the end, have encompassed most of the ordinary expressions of childhood in ways not possible in the conventional fiction film.&amp;quot; - Vincent Canby, The New York Times (1976)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a really neat restaurant and  talk about stuff thats really important.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tommy&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tommy will be holding a shiny red meetup sign near the front row when the film (is finally) over. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261184960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Truffaut's Small Change</name><id>12113132</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263065400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/12113132/</event_url></item>