<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>867 Boylston Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02199</zip><lat>42.348633</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 247-3200</phone><name>Back Bay Social Club</name><city>Boston</city><id>1356210</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.083479</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Film Lovers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On several occasions recently The Back Bay Social Club's Social Burger has been the topic of enthusiastic discussion.  Just yesterday afternoon a hearty group of film lovers set out to view &lt;b&gt;All Good Things (AGT)&lt;/b&gt; together and ended up instead at the very well-done, thoughtfully provocative, lively discussion engendering, &lt;b&gt;Somewhere&lt;/b&gt;.  While enthusiastic about &lt;b&gt;Somewhere&lt;/b&gt; and also the burgers (as well as the duck and salads) being served at The Cambridge Brewing Company, we entertained the possibility that &lt;b&gt;The Back Bay Social Club&lt;/b&gt; home of the &lt;b&gt;Social Burger&lt;/b&gt; receiving raves as one of the top ten menu items in the Boston Metropolitan area, even as I write, should be our next destination.  &lt;br /&gt;How can a film meetup justify such a detour? Very simply, by gathering to discuss the defining moment(s) when we became film lovers.  Each one of us has her/his own stories of when she/he fell in love with movies.  So the idea to combine three of our favorite loves, film, food and fantastic film discussion, was born.  Just the other day, one of my friends wrote:   &amp;quot;I have never read True Grit, but the original film was the very first “adult” film I ever saw, and the girl in that film was a good feminist role model.  .  .  See you Sunday evening to see what the Coen brothers do with the story.&amp;quot;   All of us have similar stories of defining cinematic moments and I hope you'll come and share them on Sunday, January 9th.  Another topic of interest is what are your lifetime top ten films?  Possibilities are endless and there is no shortage of theaters to adjourn to. . .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at The Back Bay Social Club for a lively gathering.  Betsey &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a red card stock BIAM meetup sign at the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294679988000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294100054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film, Friends and Food at The Back Bay Social Club</name><id>15904847</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294597800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15904847/</event_url></item>