<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Kitty O'Shea's is a great spot to host this mix and mingle Meetup party across SEVEN groups with over 200 members signed up to go!  Singles and couples are all welcome as this will be an awesome event to meet people and socialize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty O'Shea's is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 &lt;br /&gt;Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyosheasboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2nd floor can hold 200 people.  There are 2 Bars upstairs, 4 huge comfy couches, AC, its own DJ area with light machine and dance floor, plus its own bathroom upstairs so we would truly have out own private party. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a cash bar event, with pre-ordered appetizers.  While the event is free, if you choose to eat some appetizers you should contribute $5 towards food.  Please note that after 9pm, the bar will charge a $10 cover, so get there before 9pm!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have problems finding the venue or group, or have any questions, please call me at 646-541-0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recommend that you go early, as the place may get crowded later on.  This should be a great night and I look forward to seeing you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have already RSVP'd through other groups then please do not respond here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP is at a maximum 30 people as this event will be at capacity.  Please note that we reserve the right to adjust RSVP numbers based on the response from other groups.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of this sight, and my phone number is posted</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226269582000</updated><rating><average>3.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223871677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Huge Boston Meetups Mixer at Kitty O'Shea's, This Friday!</name><id>8951173</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224284400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8951173/</event_url></item>