<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2nd floor Suite 6B - (take elevator)</address_2><address_1>201 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.518875</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-240-3671</phone><name>A Higher Balance </name><city>Salem</city><id>848691</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.895309</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this fun and practical workshop, you will design your desired ideal life, and then create a visual expression of it to keep you on track in achieving it. Using guided visualization, journaling, the law of attraction, and other time-tested techniques, you will take a 360-degree view of your life and identify key elements you want to include in your ideal future. Then, you will create a two-dimensional representation of your life vision on paper. We provide you with all the tools, including lots of images – no artistic skills required! Bring a journal and some favorite photos &amp;amp; magazines. &lt;br /&gt;

 Both Mia and Barb earned Bachelors degrees from Clark University, where they first became friends; since then, they have designed and led workshops on a variety of topics in the U.S. and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;$35 with advanced registration(3 days ahead), $40 at the door&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Directions to A Higher Balance 
&lt;p&gt;A Higher Balance Healing Center is located at 201-203 Washington Street, Suite #6B in downtown Salem, MA.  The center is directly above Starbucks, but enter the main building at the doorway to the left of H&amp;amp;R Block.  Above the door is labeled &lt;strong&gt;The Hawthorne Building, 201-203&lt;/strong&gt;.  Take the elevator to the second floor, and go right to Suite #6B at the end of the hall. There is parking in front of the building.  You will need four quarters for a 2-hr. meter.  For workshops or training programs that run longer than two hours, there is free parking a bit further down Lafayette Street where there is a park in the shape of a triangle.  Free parking with no meters is available on all sides of the triangle.  It is located across the street from The Art Corner.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara Ducharme</member_name><member_id>3582123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359380033000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Women Supporting Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Women-Social-Network-Group</urlname><id>1379831</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journeys</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356712823000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vision Boarding with Mia and Barb</name><id>96824812</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359309600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-Social-Network-Group/events/96824812/</event_url></item>