<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Arbor St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.759473</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.232.1006</phone><name>Real Art Ways</name><city>Hartford</city><id>717784</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.703319</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I know it's short notice, but Saturday there is a post-screening discusion of the film.  And yes, I'm one of those totally geeky people into architecture AND music, so.......&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the RAW website:  "This exuberant imagining of the real-life marriage of Gustav Mahler (Johannes Silberschneider) and his tempestuous wife Alma Schindler Mahler (the luminous Barbara Romaner) is a sensory feast of art, sex and celebrity in fin-de-siècle Vienna. Chafing under her agreement to give up her own musical ambitions, Alma seeks passion in the arms of the young, dashing architect Walter Gropius, which sends a tormented Mahler to Sigmund Freud for consultation. “Cameos” by Gustav Klimt and Max Burckhard. Moving and funny (the sessions with Freud are sly gems) the film is filled with Mahler’s sublime music conducted by Esa-Pekka Salonen. Beautifully written and directed by Percy Adlon (Bagdad Café) and his son Felix Adlon." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

(Germany, Austria, 98 mins, in German with subtitles)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.realartways.org/cinema.htm#mahler"&gt;http://www.realartways.org/cinema.htm#mahler&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1235537/"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1235537/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE:  I people prefer to go another night, let me know.  If there is enough interest, I may reschedule, or schedule an additional Meetup.  It is currently scheduled through Thursday 27 September, with NO showing on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margo Lynn</member_name><member_id>513710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348411298000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348265546000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Mahler on the Couch" @ Real Art Ways</name><id>83500362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348353900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/83500362/</event_url></item>