<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357681</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 288-1807</phone><name>Unitarian Society of New Haven</name><city>Hamden</city><id>786805</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897463</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sean Faircloth, the executive director of the Secular Coalition for America, will be visiting Connecticut on the weekend of April 2nd and 3rd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his talk, entitled &amp;ldquo;Our Secular Decade: A Strategic Plan for Secular Government,&amp;rdquo; Sean will give us the latest scoop on the priveging of fundamentalist religious groups in matters of government funding, proselytizing in public schools, exemption from child welfare laws, even matters of sex and morality, how it affects us, an dwhat we can do about it. There willl be plenty of opportunity for Q &amp;amp; A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only about five years old, the Secular Coalition for America is an organization of organizations, working on their behalf to increase visiblity and respect for nontheistic viewpoints in the United States and to protect and strengthen the secular character of the U.S. government. The coalition advocates that American politics espouse the complete separation of church and state as established by The Constitution. The Coalition holds reason and science as its guiding tenets for public policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3BZewZQfCoA"&gt;Sean Faircloth on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; or visit the &lt;a href="http://www.secular.org/"&gt;Secular Coalition for America&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301933021000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300846091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sean Faircloth: Our Secular Decade: A Strategic Plan for Secular Government</name><id>17021409</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301864400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/17021409/</event_url></item>