<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>47 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380584</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Marran Theater, Lesley University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1235475</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116506</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's some more information about the show which is actually a 10th Anniversary Celebration&amp;nbsp;Performance as well as the background of True Story.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a personal note, I've seen tons of their shows and have taken classes with them over the past year and it's just great to see theater that is so rich and rewarding!&amp;nbsp; So please do come on out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playback Theatre Performance &lt;br /&gt;featuring  &lt;br /&gt;True Story Theater&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday, February 3, 7:00-9:00pm (doors open at 6:45pm) &lt;br /&gt;Marran Theater, Doble Campus, Lesley University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free and open to the public.  &lt;br /&gt;Rooted in drama therapy, Playback began 35 years ago in New Paltz, NY and has now practiced in over 50 countries for community-building, social healing, and building understanding across differences.&amp;nbsp; The essence of Playback is simple: volunteers from the audience are supported to tell important moments from their lives, and the actors then play back the heart of the story they just heard using music, movement, and dialogue.&amp;nbsp; Yet from this simple interaction, people laugh, cry, get fresh insights and bond.&amp;nbsp; It's embodied empathetic and insightful listening; truly a theatre of compassion.&amp;nbsp; Come witness how performers use their skills of empathetic listening and creative group process to honor the voices of the audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See you in the lobby!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296781310000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Hi Incubators! This week True Story Theater is putting on a free show at Lesley University we are  invited!  True Story perfroms playback theater, a more dramatic improv perfrmance that's based on the audiences' emotions, inputs, and stories.</why><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296598221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special: 1st Free Show of the week Thursday!!  Come check True Story Theater!</name><id>16402972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296776700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/16402972/</event_url></item>