<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>13500 South Willow St</address_2><address_1>Roosevelt Room (downstairs)</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.956150</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>BEST WESTERN - EXECUTIVE COURT INN</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1202246</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.441811</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This month we are so lucky to have the women from Revitalive Health and Wellness, Newburyport MA.  Their lecture is going to focus on our incredible digestive system and the importance of cleansing and detoxifying while people are transitioning to the raw and living foods lifestyle.  They will share some simple strategies to help support that transition process.  They will also address some of the common pitfalls people encounter when incorporating more raw foods into ones diet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kristen Overlock&lt;/b&gt;, BS Nutrition, Certified Colon Hydrotherapist (CCHT), Certified Raw &amp;amp; Living Foods Lifestyle Educator, I-ACT Certified, Reiki Master&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristin graduated in 1995 with a BS in Nutrition from Penn State.  As a lifelong athlete, she developed an interest in heath and nutrition at an early age.  She also struggled with severe digestive problems and peptic ulcers for most of her life, which led her on a quest to regain her health and learn everything she could about nutritional wellness.&lt;br /&gt;Kristen studied colon hydrotherapy at the Dotolo Institute in 1999 under Brenda Watson (founder of Renew Life).  In 1999 Kristen began working at the Ann Wigmore Natural Health Institute where she taught courses on nutrition, digestion and colon health.  Over the years Kristen has developed a unique approach to colon hydrotherapy which incorporates abdominal massage, Reiki, and reflexology.  &lt;br /&gt;Since changing her diet and lifestyle Kristen has lost 65 pounds and reversed her peptic ulcers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anna Forkan&lt;/b&gt;, BSE Engineering, Certified Nutritional Microscopist, Certified Raw and Living Foods Educator&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anna graduated in 2003 with a BSE in Engineering from the University of Iowa.  While attending the U of I she became interested in global environmental issues and founded the group Engineers for a Sustainable World.  Her main focus with ESW was drinking water issues plaguing Latin America,mainly Mexico and Guatemala.  While working with local populations educating them on the importance of clean water, her passion for motivating people live healthier, happier lives was found!  Anna also worked with the Dept of Natural Resources in the Pollution Prevention Dept to help companies reduce their ecological footprint.  The link between the environment and diet was what initially interested Anna in changing her eating habits.&lt;br /&gt;In 2006 Anna began working as the Operations Manager at Ann Wigmore Natural Health Institute.  While working there Anna began to study nutritional microscopy to provide visual feedback on our inner terrain.  In 2008 she became certified in applies microscopy.  As Anna transitioned to an entirely plant based diet she began to see a major transformation in her attitude, energy, body and so much more.  Since changing her lifestyle Anna has lost 70 pounds and reversed several health challenges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2008 Anna and Kristen founded Revitalive as a community resource to help people not only cleanse and detoxify but to help clients address underlying patterns that cause dis-ease.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is going to be a great night!  Please bring a raw organic dish enough to feed 8 people.  If you are new and not sure what to bring a salad (fruit or veggie ) is always good.  Please bring your dish prepared because we have no kitchen space.  Also please list ingredients in your dish because some people may be allergic to certain things.&lt;br /&gt;If your life is as crazy as mine I will make a dish for you...cost $15 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost for the meetup is $10 per adult.  Children always free!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KO Bisson</member_name><member_id>4565632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282699659000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawfood-ManchNH</urlname><id>1292928</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280322270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Potluck Meetup Friday August 13th!!!</name><id>14239463</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281738600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawfood-ManchNH/events/14239463/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/b/global_9355803.jpeg</photo_url></item>