<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>545 Boylston St</address_2><address_1>Back Bay</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357231</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 638 -9699 </phone><name>Vlora Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>898612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066116</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Everyone, it's time for an Old-Fashioned, New England-Style Halloween Costume Party Gala at Vlora, right in the heart of Copley Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be one of Brunch &amp;amp; More's biggest parties of the year! You don't want to miss this night to remember (if you &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; remember it after). Besides, when was the last time you went to a big Halloween costume Party? Well, it's about time and here's your chance. Start thinking about what you'll wear. Use your imagination. Make it fun. Awards and prizes will be given for the best costumes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The festivities will include plenty of free hors d'oeuvres and, of course, gettin' down! We also plan to have a variety of drink specials. Vlora has a &lt;i&gt;fantastic&lt;/i&gt; menu and wine list so feel free to order additional appetizers or dinner if you want (you are responsible for your own bill).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now please keep in mind, available spots are limited and they will go quickly. RSVP as soon as possible to hold your place. Don't delay --- purchase your tickets TODAY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some important details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening starts at 8pm in the large private function room at the back of the restaurant and --- this is my favorite part --- after 10pm the entire restaurant will be opened up to Brunch &amp;amp; More for our Halloween party with a dance floor center stage!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are currently a paying member of Brunch &amp;amp; More (you've already paid your membership dues for the month of October), your cost for the Halloween bash will only be an additional $5 (as long as you RSVP and purchase your tickets online before October 20th). Just send me $5 via Paypal and I'll add you to the guest list. Or if you want, just pay $20 online, and I'll give you credit for next month's membership dues. On the other hand, if you are a member of Brunch &amp;amp; More but haven't yet paid your dues for October, your cost will be $20 (again, as long as you RSVP and purchase your tickets before October 20th; once you've paid, you can attend all October events). As an added bonus, those who RSVP and purchase tickets by October 20th will get one free drink up to $7 included with the price of admission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: all tickets purchased between October 21st and October 30th will be $20, but no free drink is provided; tickets purchased at the door on October 31st will be $25.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So are you in? Don't miss what is sure to be an amazing, unforgettable Halloween costume party. I can't wait to see how creative you get. Think outside the box. Come on, people, show me what you've got!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;Your Organizer &lt;br /&gt;Brunch &amp;amp; More&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ritesh</member_name><member_id>4789957</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jennifer </member_name><member_id>5436581</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257893601000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254937469000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Old-Fashioned, New England-Style Halloween Costume Party Gala</name><id>11572715</id><headcount>62</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1257033600000</time><rsvp_limit>80</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11572715/</event_url></item>