<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I apologize for the late cancellation of the meeting on the second part of Francis Bacon's New Organon. I hope that nobody made the trip in vain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will move onto Rene Descartes. There are so many things to read about and discuss philosophy in general and Descartes in particular. Before one of our member Dave Buehler's suggestion about Hans Jonas: Phenomenon of Life (Descartes' view on animals) we counted that we may spend as many as seven meetings on Descartes. The plan was/is Meditations on First Philosophy (63 pages 1 meeting) Objections and Replies to the work just mentioned before (340 pages 4 meetings) Principles of Philosophy (120 pages 2 meetings). The Objections and Replies to Meditations on First Philosophy seem particularly fit for discussion, they are Descartes' contemporaries' objections and Descartes' replies. (Descartes asked his peers to let him publish their objections and his replies to them with the first edition of this work!) I am sure that we will discuss how we can fit in other works by Descartes and about Descartes into our series. Please bring your suggestions! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For now we will start out with Meditations on First Philosophy from the second volume of: The Philosophical Writings of Descartes (Translated by John Cottingham, Robert Stoothoff and Dugald Murdoch, ISBN:052128807 for Vol I and ISBN:052128808 for Vol II).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to our meeting, see you on the 26th of April.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177801658000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176414467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rene Descartes: Meditations on First Philosophy</name><id>5664310</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177628400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/5664310/</event_url></item>