<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The polls have been closed and the winner for our &amp;quot;U&amp;quot; Restaurant is the Union Chowder House in South Weymouth! I checked it out online and they have a great selection of American fair specializing in their seafood.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since Lynnie was the first to suggest this restaurant, she has agreed to co-host the meetup with me. We will be charging our normal $2 event fee and free for annual members. Annual members may bring a guest free as long as you add them into the count when you RSVP. Please make sure they are definitely going to attend before signing them up, so you don't take a spot away from another member who would like to join us.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have spoken to the manager and she would like a headcount by Monday 4/12, so please make sure that you are pretty positive you can attend. We will be sitting at a few separate tables close together, so we will request separate bills for each table. That should make it a little easier to keep the checks straight. As always, please bring cash! The prices are very reasonable at this place, so there should be something for everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive on time out of courtesy to our other diners. We will start without you if you are more than 10 minutes late. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner on Wednesday, April 14th @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Union Chowder House&lt;br /&gt;26 Union Street&lt;br /&gt;Columbian Square&lt;br /&gt;Weymouth, MA&lt;br /&gt;781-335-6073&lt;br /&gt;www.unionchowderhouse.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Alison and Lynnie F.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min./Max.:  There is a minimum of 6 Yes RSVP's by 6pm on Monday, April 12th.  There is a maximum of 20 attendees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Yes. One per member allowed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: Annual Members &amp;amp; 1 Guest - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price Range: Almost all items on the menu are under $20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Accessibility: This is handicap-accessible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: The restaurant has asked for a rough count by Monday, April 12th.  Please finalize your RSVP by 7pm on Tuesday, April 13th.  Please see our RSVP and No-Show Policy on the About pages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: We will only cancel if there is a snowstorm the day of the event. TBD - Please see our Weather policy on the About page (scroll to the bottom and click on &amp;quot;weather&amp;quot;).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: To be posted prior to the RSVP Deadline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture. The reservation will be under Alison and SSDOMG. We will meet inside the entrance or at the tables if you are running late.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lynnie F</member_name><member_id>8930120</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271711378000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270343992000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"U" know "U" wanna meet us at the Union Chowder House</name><id>13079960</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271284200000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/13079960/</event_url></item>