<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>182 Hayden Rowe</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.205910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cassies House</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>1579805</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.511398</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Handlers and dogs will meet at&amp;nbsp;Cassie's house&amp;nbsp;at 12:30p for a meet-and-greet and training opportunity.&amp;nbsp;The town has given her permission&amp;nbsp;to park along Hayden Rowe as long as you don't block a driveway. Walk to commence at 1:00p, on a predetermined route through town. Once our walk is finished (expect to take about 45 minutes to an hour), we'll head back (via car or walk!) to Cassie Stock's house at 182 Hayden Rowe Street for food, drinks, and some outdoor play time with our pups; unfortunately the yard is not fenced, so bring some long leashes if you like! Some of you may have travel crates (I have a pop-up variety) if your pooch needs a break when we get back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests of any variety (human or canine!) are welcome to this event, and we will be accepting donations to the NEBBC to fund future (larger) events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PEANUT BUTTER PLUS Drive... We will take this opportunity to collect items for local shelter BayPath Humane Society, one of the only no-kill shelters in the area who routinely takes (and loves!) pit bulls. We will be accepting peanut butter, dog toys, leashes, food, bowls and even cat supplies. For a complete list, visit BayPath's Wish List: &lt;a href="http://www.baypathhumane.org/content/view/67/69/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.baypathhum...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can follow us on facebook for any updates... &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/#!/pages/New-England-Bully-Breed-Club/74020777664" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donatable items can be dropped off/mailed on or before Sunday, March 27th at 182 Hayden Rowe Street, Apt. 4, Hopkinton, MA 01748 or at Lucky Dogs DayCare at 80 Sumner Street, Milford, MA 01757. You can visit them at &lt;a href="http://luckydogsdaycare.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://luckydogsdayca...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much, and hope to see you there! Spread the word, and bring your friends. This is taking place surrounded by cities and towns that has RECENTLY passed laws promoting BSL. This is a great opportunity to show how great they can truly be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions or concerns, call Cassie at (508) 380-8853.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Punish the Deed, Not the Breed,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cassie-Leigh Stock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New England Bully Breed Club&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301314258000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>What a site!  A parade a dogs sporting demonstrating how great our beloved bullies can be on a pack walk through small-town Hopkinton.  Walk to end at my house for food/drinks and play!</why><group><who>Boxer Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boxer-340</urlname><id>1175534</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Massachusetts Boxer Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300201702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bully Parade through the center of quaint Hopkinton &amp; Peanut Butter PLUS drive!</name><id>16928703</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301243400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boxer-340/events/16928703/</event_url></item>