<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>704 Sumner Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01108</zip><lat>42.087719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Springfield Pregnancy Care Center</name><city>Springfield</city><id>10877752</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.551163</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We would like this to be a fun and entertaining time for all the ladies. It will be a regular baby shower with games, entertainment, and refreshments. It is also an opportunity to help a very good pro life organization that is walking the walk not just talking the talk. Items need not be new but must be clean and in excellent condition. Please consider joining us for this fun event with a purpose. The following is a list of items needed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. diapers - newborn, size 1 to size 6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. diaper bags&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. baby supplies: baby bottles, sippy cups, pacifiers, baby wipes, baby wash/shampoo, baby lotion, baby powder, diaper rash ointment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. baby food: cereal, toddler formula.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. gently used: bassinets, cribs (that meets current codes or a kit) umbrella strollers, regualr strollers, hi chairs, bouncy chairs, baby bath seats, baby tub seats, swings, pak-n-plays, activity seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. new or gently used: pregnancy, baby care, and parenting books, such as Dare To Discipline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7. toddler board books&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8. new or gently used: maternity clothes - small- large- and extra large&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9. new or gently used: baby clothes - newborn to size 24 months&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10. new or gently used: snow suits, hats, mittens&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11. new or gently used: receiving blankets, bassinet and crib sheets. We welcome hand made baby blankets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 store baby gift cards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;13. monetary donations, cash or check to the center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more informaton contact Denise at &lt;a href="mailto:majormomdb1@aol.com"&gt;majormomdb1@aol.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have the shower in one of the rooms at the Pregnancy Care Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Baran</member_name><member_id>9211691</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361136930000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>We Surround Them</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Western-Mass-912-Project</urlname><id>1394602</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6299972534</group_lon><name>The Original WMass 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356745735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BABY SHOWER FOR THE SPRINGFIELD PREGNANCY CARE CENTER</name><id>96895382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361125800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Western-Mass-912-Project/events/96895382/</event_url></item>