<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>How about a fun filled weekend getaway near North Conway NH ?!! For $35 you get a day pass at Attitash that gets you the alpine slide, mountain bike ride, waterslide, euro-bungy trampoline, scenic sky ride and climbing wall! The mountain biking is what I am really looking forward to. They take you and the bikes on the chairlift to the top of a trail so you just coast downhill over ramps and such. I saw it from above on the sky ride and it looked like a blast!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.attitash.com/ticketprices.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.attitash.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like something calmer, there is a nearby hike to Arethusa Falls. This hike is an easy 2 hours and can be extended by going to Frankenstein Cliff. Other possibilities are horseback riding and canoe/kayaking. We can have a campfire there, too!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be staying with our friends at Skidaddlers ski club for $20 a night each. Dormitory style with men and women in different sections, 2-4 people to a room. They have a fully equipped kitchen that we can use, complete with dishes etc, and a large living room with TV and dvd. Bring a sleeping bag or sheets and a towel. We will go to a restaurant for supper Sat night. Bring you own food or dine out, your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drive up Friday after work and return on Sunday. Please indicate in your rsvp comment if you need a ride or can offer one. Address and directions will be provided. The $40 for accomodations will be required a week in advance. More details to come.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250471590000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245425397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend getaway at Attitash Aug 14-16</name><id>10688608</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250298000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10688608/</event_url></item>