<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Metropolis, by Fritz Lang, is playing at the Coolidge Corner Cinema for one week.  Believe it or not, I've never seen it.  I think it's required viewing if you're interested in Cinema; so I'm grateful for the opportunity.  I'm scheduling this for Monday night at 7:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like, you can meet me at the Upper Crust Pizza (right next door to the theater) at 6:15 for a bite beforehand and a quick discussion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm going to try and be alert enough that we can go somewhere after the movie - at around 9:30 pm and discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what's on the theater's web site: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The definitive reconstruction&amp;quot; - The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In association with the Goethe-Institute Boston, the Coolidge Corner Theatre is proud to present a one-week only run of Fritz Lang's original vision of METROPOLIS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Coolidge is thrilled to present the New England Premiere of this new restoration, which Roger Ebert hails as &amp;quot;one of the most important film archival discoveries in history!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fritz Lang's METROPOLIS has long been a cornerstone of cinema history, influencing contemporary films such as BLADE RUNNER and STAR WARS, but it has not been viewed in its complete form since its legendary 1927 Berlin premiere. Shortly after its debut, the film's distributor ordered nearly an hour of footage to be lopped off, reels which thereafter were presumed to have been destroyed forever. All of that changed in 2008, when the curator of the Buenos Aires Museo del Cine discovered a 16mm dupe negative of METROPOLIS that included 25 minutes of &amp;quot;lost&amp;quot; footage that had not been seen since the film's premiere. The discovery of such a significant amount of material led to a full restoration which reinstated the original editing, reestablishing the balance between characters and subplots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Metropolis, a towering city of the future, society is divided into two classes: one of planners and management, who live high above the Earth in skyscrapers; and one of workers, who live and toil underground, slaves to the whistle of Metropolis’s ten-hour clock. When the only son of Metropolis' leader becomes smitten with a beautiful woman, he winds up following her to the depths of the Earth, where he discovers important truths about the city his family rules. A pioneering work of dystopian science fiction, METROPOLIS wound up fulfilling director Fritz Lang's stated goal to make &amp;quot;the costliest and most ambitious picture ever.”&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>3404432</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275673893000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metropolis</name><id>13698566</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275951600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/13698566/</event_url></item>