<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>118 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.367222</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Bodymind Integration Center</name><city>Watertown</city><id>725562</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.187240</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This will be a fun evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heard of the Enneagram? It’s a tool for understanding and developing yourself, and for understanding others (and thus improving how you relate to them). The Enneagram system sees people as being nine different psychospiritual types.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Enneagram_of_Personality" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Enneagram_of_Personality" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; gives a good overview.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this two-hour class, Herb will cover:&lt;br /&gt;• The nine types. This is fun: Herb acts out each of the nine types with hats and props. I’ve seen this twice, and it makes me think of a low-budget, one-man, off-Broadway show, with a message! Fun and educational at the same time. Quote from Paul Gerzon who is co-organizing the workshop&lt;br /&gt;• What is your core type? Herb will type some people who come to the class -- maybe all.&lt;br /&gt;• How each type relates to other types. Relationships tips!&lt;br /&gt;• How you can grow beyond the limited aspects of your type&lt;br /&gt;• How you can develop the strength of all nine types&lt;br /&gt;• How you can relate to the inner and outer worlds of each type&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To repeat, this should be a fun evening! And, possibly quite important and life-changing. Thousands of people have reported immense change in their lives do to knowing this information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb presents deep material in an educational and stimulating way, while at the same time being entertaining and light-hearted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Herb has written, “The Enneagram is an amazingly accurate system of understanding personality that groups human motivations and patterns of feeling, thought, and body experience into nine personality types. Each of us has elements of all nine types, but one is more dominant and automatic and is a stronger perceptual lens. This lens flavors how you see the world uniquely and therefore, to a large degree, how you think, feel, and act automatically. Being in a type is a great strength and gift but also limits the range of possible ways to experience life.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his private practice, Herb uses the Enneagram to define a client’s core type and explore how it limits his or her perception and ability to see the world in the strengths of all nine types. He can teach you to see the limited reality in your core filter (i.e, your type) and expand to a greater understanding of options that each type provides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you June 22!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~Herb Pearce, M.Ed., is an Enneagram expert and author of The Idiot's Guide to the Enneagram. Herb is a brilliant counselor and has taught close to two thousand Enneagram workshops in the last twenty years. Herb uses the Enneagram as a team building tool in organizations; as well as while working with relationship and communication issues (individuals, couples and families).&lt;br /&gt;Read more about Herb at www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277429167000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Arlington-Singles-Events</urlname><id>1416650</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Arlington Singles Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276180954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Enneagram Presentation</name><id>13759691</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277248500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Arlington-Singles-Events/events/13759691/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/4/global_7835444.jpeg</photo_url></item>