<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St., Suite 2</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>ArtStudio 360</name><city>Holliston</city><id>1537371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422928</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Doors open at 1 p.m. (we had said it might not start until 2, but your host can arrive by 1 after all!).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a break from the holiday madness and join us for&amp;nbsp;a relaxing day of&amp;nbsp;making art! No formal instruction today--just&amp;nbsp;a chance to&amp;nbsp;make last-minute gifts or cards or anything else you like.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; 1 p.m. to whenever. Come and leave whenever you like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Yourself, your art supplies and whatever project you&amp;rsquo;d like to work on. Bring your own beverage and, if you so choose, a snack to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; $10, regardless of how long you stay. We can accept cash or checks made to "ArtStudio 360." This fee helps keep ArtStudio 360 open, so we can't accept IOUs or partial payments. We're happy to direct you to a nearby ATM if you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.) and some supplies including acrylic paints, collage materials, etc.&amp;nbsp;Access to a microwave, toaster oven, refrigerator, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone (18+ only, please). Just sign up through the NE ATC+ Meetup Group. Membership in the Meetup group is free; joining simply allows you to reserve a space in events at ArtStudio 360.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;These smaller sessions&amp;nbsp;often fill&amp;nbsp;quickly.&amp;nbsp;Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly so that your space becomes available to someone else. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;In the unlikely event that we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Second floor. Use front door or door off parking lot; come up the stairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324314510000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321540685000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kick back &amp; make art: Pre-holiday Open Studio from 1 p.m. to ????</name><id>41502012</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324231200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/41502012/</event_url></item>