<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1874 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02420</zip><lat>42.448071</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-862-6288</phone><name>Cary Memorial Library</name><city>Lexington</city><id>1056907</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.229634</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hypnosis allows us to take advantage of the power and vast wisdom of the &lt;b&gt;unconscious mind&lt;/b&gt;. At a very deep level, the unconscious mind takes in everything you have seen and experienced since life began for you. &lt;b&gt;Automatic writing&lt;/b&gt; allows us to tap into that source and bring out information in a quite interesting manner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Automatic writing&lt;/b&gt; has been around for a long time. It has been associated with psychics and mediums. We will be doing this strictly from a hypnotic point of view. This is similar to regression in the fact that it is intended to access information from the past that is not at the conscious level. It is not mysterious or anymore dangerous than normal regression is. (Accessing traumatic events and misleading perceptions of past events are the most common dangers to watch out for with any regression.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a fascinating demonstration of the power of the unconscious mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General hypnosis related subjects will be discuss and we will start off with some stress relief hypnosis for all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call or email me with any questions or for personal sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Martin&lt;br /&gt;978-273-5905&lt;br /&gt;kenda_assoc@msn.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Learning Center - Bottom Floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin Martin</member_name><member_id>4468007</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290047719000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287720890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP Meetup - Lexington- Automatic Writing</name><id>15191160</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289865600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/15191160/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/0/global_11885328.jpeg</photo_url></item>