<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Federal St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01109</zip><lat>42.109196</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Scibelli Enterprise Center, across from STCC, downstairs media room</name><city>Springfield</city><id>9576442</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.577682</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Clemente from Startup Helping Hand will be our featured presenter for the April public, open-door event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Startup Helping Hand is a new service in the area. It offers a la carte services for startups and businesses. Those who subscribe to the service may choose a space with a cubicle at the Holyoke Mall location of the Startup Helping hand. All those who subscribe to the service have access to professional aid from experts in areas that a starting business needs the most - legal, accounting, funding, mentoring, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meeting will be in a Q&amp;amp;A informal format, so bring a list of questions about services you need help with for your own business or idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Startup Helping Hand website URL is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://startuphelpinghand.com/"&gt;http://startuphelpinghand.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Startup Helping Hand also has a Meetup group of its own:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Helping-Hand-Entreprenuer-Resources-Holyoke-Mall/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Helping-Hand-Entreprenuer-Resources-Holyoke-Mall/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IRN co-organizers wish to ask all attending to pass the word around about this great event to their co-workers, friends, and relatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Partial list of services which Startup Helping Hand provides:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Financial Services &lt;br /&gt;

Legal and Patent Advice &lt;br /&gt;

Business Concept Evaluation &lt;br /&gt;

Marketing and Brand Development &lt;br /&gt;

Design and Website Development &lt;br /&gt;

Funding Presentation Development &lt;br /&gt;

Explore Our Access to Over 500 Franchises &lt;br /&gt;

On-Demand Sales Force, Focused on Assisting Startups &lt;br /&gt;

Workshops Tailored To Address the Current Needs of Our Members &lt;br /&gt;

Hands-on Support, Guidance and Assistance On Developing a Business Plan &lt;br /&gt;

Assistance With Establishing the Necessary Funding to Launch the Business &lt;br /&gt;

Prescreening and Guidance on Exploring the Best Funding Sources For the Venture &lt;br /&gt;

Affordable Co-working Office Space, Conference Rooms, and Cubicles. All Available By the Hour, Day and Month &lt;br /&gt;

Access to the Real Estate Community to Locate and Fill Suitable Vacant Retail/Office Space &lt;br /&gt;

Collaboration With Local Resources to Assist and Nurture Our Entrepreneurial Ecosystem&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365100972000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362845834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Public meeting - Startup Helping Hand, Jack Clemente</name><id>108423222</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365030000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/108423222/</event_url></item>