<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 11</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.493217</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt. Major</name><city>Alton</city><id>3041421</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.255547</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sun will come out on Monday. So I'll hike. You are welcome to join me. You are responsible for you own well being and safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet 10:15 am at the parking lot, and start to hike at 10:30 am. Its a loop hike. We will hike Mt. Major trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Trailhead: Take I93 North to Exit 20, take US3 North to NH 11 East toward Alton, turn right into the parking lot at the Mt. Major trailhead highway sign. We will be hiking the Mt. Major Trail to the summit of Mt. Major (1,780'). Expansive views of Lake Winnipesaukee from the top. 4.8 miles round trip, 1,150' elevation gain, AMC book time 3 hours. We will stay together as our pace need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349166739000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349030767000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute-EasyHike Mr. Major.  -Alton Bay, NH</name><id>84814582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349100900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/84814582/</event_url></item>