<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.396255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-625-5700</phone><name>Somerville Theater</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669360</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122551</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We were unable to hold an actual Pow Wow, this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In its place, I'll post reviews of films that we would have discussed at the Pow Wow in order to help everyone make choices.  Those with high rating in bold.  Please feel free to add comments so that it will feel like we held a Virtual Pow Wow, and use this space to hook up with other members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;7:00 - Houston - A German corporate headhunter searches for a top CEO in Houston, Texas. Far from home, he spirals onto a dark, personal journey away from reality, fueled by his alcoholism.  No reviews.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;7:00 - Before You Know It - IMDB - 4.8 - ...a calm and straightforward documentary [that] looks at the lives of three gay men in their sunset years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;7:15 - Tokyo Waka - IMDB -4.8 - The portrait of a city: ancient yet constantly remaking itself. A poem in images: stillness, patterns, urban motion. And in words: a tofu seller, a homeless woman, a Buddhist priest, contemplating nature, the metabolism of their city, mortality. And 20,000 crows, unruly avatars of the natural world, sardonically observing it all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7:45 - The Way, Way Back - IMDB: 7.8/RT: 86% - "&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;The Way, Way Back&lt;/span&gt; is everything you want in a laugh out loud, crowd-pleasing, coming-of-age movie."&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9:15 - Wasteland - IMDB: 7.0 - &lt;span&gt;A young Englishman recently released from prison recruits his three best friends and to rob the local drug kingpin who is responsible for his incarceration. Can he get revenge and win back his fed-up girlfriend?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000080"&gt;9:30 - Crystal Fairy - IMDB: 7.4/RT: 83% - Self-absorbed American slacker Jamie (Michael Cera) goes on a quest for the ultimate high in the Chilean desert. But his plans may be derailed by the overenthusiastic hippie (Gaby Hoffmann) he and his friends pick up along the way.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"an unusually insightful look at self-imposed false identities and group dynamics"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;9:45 - The Punk Singer - IMDB: 4.2 - A look at the life of activist, musician, and cultural icon Kathleen Hanna, who formed the punk band Bikini Kill and pioneered the "riot grrrl" movement of the 1990s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;12 O'Clock Boys - IMDB: 5.9 -13-year-old Pug lives on the dangerous Westside block and has a singular objective: to become a member of the 12 O’Clock Boys, the notorious dirt-bike group in Baltimore.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please feel free to add a comment to meetup with other members, or to add information for any film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366941963000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366499925000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday's Films at BIFF</name><id>115350362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366930800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/115350362/</event_url></item>