<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>319 Todd Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06716</zip><lat>41.564697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-808-5829 </phone><name>Terri's House</name><city>Wolcott</city><id>1368806</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.972048</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tired of the mob scenes out there for New Year's Eve? Are you looking for something inexpensive, casual ,yet fun for New Year's? Well, you've found it! We're ringing in the new year at Terri's! C'mon and join us with new friends...and old!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's right, we're bidding farewell to the old year as we welcome in the new with a good old fashion house party at Terri's place. We're planning a night of fun starting with appetizers and cocktails at 7 pm , followed by dinner at 8 pm ...and from there it's party all night long. A little music...some dancing ...cocktails...dinner...perhaps some games and yes, we will do the traditional ball countdown at midnight. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just bring a dish (Terri will coordinate food,so as not to have food duplications)...bring whatever you are drinking...and we are asking for a $5.00 contribution for hats, noisemakers, party stuff and also for a champagne toast at midnight. Now where else can you go for $5.00 on New Year's Eve? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't stay home on this great night...come out and celebrate with us. If you do not want to drive home (or can't), you are welcome to stay. We will find room for you! We'll have breakfast in the morning. So bring a blanket and pillow and something for breakfast if you are staying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can pay online with your RSVP at Have Fun, Will Travel, or as usual, send a check to Terri Bruno, 319 Todd Road, Wolcott, CT 06716. All checks should be received by Dcember 24th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh, and by the way...dress is CASUAL. Dress to be comfortable, not to impress  , this time. So come have fun (no travel). LOL&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262477589000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260173699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ring In The New Year : 2010 !!!</name><id>12034562</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262304000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/12034562/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/b/global_12135323.jpeg</photo_url></item>