<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>Door Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$20 cash at the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;Happy Valentine's Day!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Ready to meet some like-minded progressives? Then you'll want to join us for Dating While Progressive, a fun and welcoming singles party!*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice&lt;/strong&gt; event is co-hosted by the &lt;strong&gt;Bisexual Resource Center&lt;/strong&gt;, the Boston chapter of the &lt;strong&gt;National Organization for Men Against Sexism&lt;/strong&gt; (NOMAS-Boston), and the Boston chapter of the &lt;strong&gt;New Leaders Council&lt;/strong&gt; (NLC Boston).&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Haven't been to a Socializing for Justice event?&lt;/em&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s time to meet the friendly faces of the group that&amp;rsquo;s grown to over 1800 members, hosted 110+ events and fostered hundreds of connections since our founding 5+ years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; $5-$20 collected at the door. &lt;br /&gt;

 (every $10 includes a raffle ticket)&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Complimentary appetizers will be provided.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BAKE SALE:&lt;/strong&gt; We are going to have an indulgent and fun bake sale with all proceeds to benefit The Network/La Red, a Boston-based anti-partner abuse organization. &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0ArB1RWVdJCJFdHFkQlJiQ0lpbEhhVXBYNFlFN0ZUOUE"&gt;Want to bake something&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; Anyone who's single and/or available is invited! Attendees are all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. Some just moved to Boston and others were born here. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As always we'll help you mix and mingle - so no worries if you're new to SoJust&lt;/strong&gt;, plus we'll have "I'M LOOKING FOR", "ASK ME ABOUT" tags and a flirty bingo ice-breaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us if you are ready to go BEYOND FRIENDS - movements are built on RELATIONSHIPS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;THIS IS NOT A MEETING - IT'S A FUN SINGLES PARTY!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 No Program. No Speaker. (No Speed Dating.) Just Us. For Justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*The venue is open to anyone over 18 (must be 21+ to enter after 7PM) and is partially physically accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue and bathrooms are big enough for manual, but not motor-powered, wheelchairs. Lir is across from the Hynes Convention Center. Parking near Lir is really hard - you could get lucky or you could drive around for 30 or more minutes. There are parking garages by Back Bay station. Best bet is to take the T to Back Bay or Hynes Convention Center (which is the closest T stop).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HELP SPREAD THE WORD!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Invite your friends to this facebook event: &lt;a href="http://on.fb.me/tEPoXU"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;[coming soon] &lt;br /&gt;

 Join the SoJust Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://on.fb.me/SoJust"&gt;http://on.fb.me/SoJust&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 On Twitter? Follow &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust" target="_blank"&gt;@SoJust&lt;/a&gt; and SoJust's Co-Founder &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/robbiesamuels" target="_blank"&gt;@RobbieSamuels&lt;/a&gt; #sojust&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust is all about building a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoJust isn't a non-profit 501(c)(3) and receives no outside funding.&lt;/strong&gt; We're a grassroots volunteer-run member-supported cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have over 1800 members, we have hosted 110+ events and we manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at www.sojust.org. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/dues/" target="_blank"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison Brill</member_name><member_id>4034719</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330041470000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325813843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dating While Progressive</name><id>46881442</id><headcount>97</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329260400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/46881442/</event_url></item>