<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Yeah, way over there... But, lucky us to have two of our friends close enough to even drive if metars act up... Not to mention our local friendly Worcester Area Pilots Association is hosting this.&lt;br /&gt;I'll drive or fly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Air traffic control for VFR and IFR traffic in the Boston Center and Approach Airspace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Worcester Area Pilots Association is hosting this exciting and educational FAASTeam program. FAASTeam Rep. and Boston Center controller, Bob Adelizzi will brief us on why &amp;quot;they do what they do&amp;quot; and answer the questions like &amp;quot;how do I get from A to B&amp;quot;. This program is for all pilots; Student to ATP, VFR and IFR. The last time we held this event, it was standing room only! FPM Jim Adams says, &amp;quot;bring a first time attendee to a WAPA-FAASTeam Event and get a extra chance at a door prize!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Bring your questions...&lt;br /&gt;-How to get your Bravo clearance&lt;br /&gt;-Do you need one for charlie&lt;br /&gt;-How should we ask for traffic advisories&lt;br /&gt;-What do they want to hear when &amp;quot;checking in&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join WAPA at the ORH Terminal on November 4. Business Meeting at 6:30 p.m. - Safety Seminar at 7 p.m.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Should we leave at 5:30 if we are flying and stop to eat someplace first? The meeting is at 7:00. We'll need to get moving before that.... Let's hear your input...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CV&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257547082000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256558918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening with Boston ATC and the FAASTeam with WAPA in ORH</name><id>11712842</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257373800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/11712842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/9/global_4880393.jpeg</photo_url></item>