<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02133</zip><lat>42.335347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Massachusetts State House</name><city>Boston</city><id>900281</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.153409</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What are you doing on Halloween? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join Nerd Fun as we explore Beacon Hill this Halloween with the best historical walking tour group in Boston, Boston By Foot! Feel free to get into the spirit of the evening and wear a costume for the event, if you so wish!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20.00 cash per person, but are only $5.00 cash per person for Boston By Foot members. You will be purchasing tickets from Boston By Foot docents at the start of the tour. Care to be a Boston By Foot member? Information can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonbyfo...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour is an hour-and-a-half long, starting at 5:30 pm, ending at 7:00 pm, and are always held rain or shine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, will be wearing a black tricorne hat, a white swashbuckler shirt, a black overcoat, and a large red MEETUP sign attached to his black satchel. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 5:00 pm to 5:30 pm T.J. was going to wait near the Robert Gould Shaw Memorial right across from the Massachusetts State House, until the BBF people tell us which group we should join. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a very large crowd gathering in front of the Massachusetts State House on Beacon Street on the edge of the Boston Common. Depending how many people sign up, we may need to be split into two groups, but we can gather together somewhere after the tour for a bite to eat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the tour, according to Boston By Foot:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Beacon_Hill_Halloween" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonbyfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our most popular event of the season! For 25 years, this walk has been the starting point for the perfect Halloween in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Walk over the dark side on All Hallows' Eve and there's no better place to do it than on Beacon Hill. Hear stories of ghosts, murders and mayhem that haunt this quiet neighborhood while walking among the Halloween decorations and the people who come to Beacon Hill every year to celebrate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;If you have never been to Beacon Hill on Halloween, this is one of those must-see events in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This tour highlights Beacon Hill's rich heritage of mystery and suspense. See the home of the murdered George Parkman and learn what happened to his dismembered body. See where the Quakers were hanged and famous men buried, and many more scenes of the macabre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Apparitions of lawyers and ministers, murderers who walk in their sleep, stranglers, and cautionary tales for lovers. Join one of our many docents on a journey through the true and morbid tales that haunt Beacon Hill this Halloween&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Boston By Foot, by Polly Flansburgh&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Founder &amp;amp; President of Boston By Foot:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/welcome/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonbyfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We welcome you to come and explore Boston's rich heritage of architecture and history in the company of dedicated and enthusiastic guides -- all graduates of Boston By Foot's highly acclaimed training program.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Since 1976 we have offered regularly scheduled tours from May through October (just show up!) and year-round custom tours for groups and private parties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Whether you are a long-time resident or just in town for the day, we hope you will lace up your walking shoes and see Boston at her best... By Foot!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I love Boston By Foot! Nerd Fun has been exploring Boston with them for over two years now. I even audited their Spring Lecture Series for their guides-in-training back in Spring 2009. I've heard about this tour for the past two years, and always have wanted to go on it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289146404000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287863705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beacon Hill With A Boo @ Boston By Foot, Massachusetts State House</name><id>15205490</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288558800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15205490/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/b/global_2222155.jpeg</photo_url></item>