<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/0/8/event_177369992.jpeg" width="106" height="162" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;If you have never seen this film on the big screen now is your chance! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;We will start to gather by 6:00 and head in for seats at 6:30. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4 ; font-size : small"&gt;Mia: "I do believe Marsellus Wallace, my husband, your boss, told you to take ME out and do whatever I wanted. Now I wanna dance, I wanna win. I want that trophy, so dance good."&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Two years after the groundbreaking debut of Reservoir Dogs, Quentin Tarantino unveiled his masterpiece, &lt;strong&gt;Pulp Fiction&lt;/strong&gt;and solidified his place among the greatest filmmakers in modern cinema.  In celebration of his legendary 20-year career, NCM Fathom Events, Miramax and IGN are bringing &lt;strong&gt;Pulp Fiction&lt;/strong&gt; back to the big screen for only one day on &lt;strong&gt;Thursday, December 6 at 7:00pm (local time)*. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Recognized on AFI’s Top 100 list, Pulp Fiction weaves three interconnected stories of seemingly unrelated people into an intricate tale of violence and redemption.  Jules Winnfield and Vincent Vega are two hitmen who are out to retrieve a suitcase stolen from their employer, mob boss Marsellus Wallace. Wallace has also asked Vincent to take his wife Mia out while he is away. Butch Coolidge is an aging boxer who is paid by Wallace to lose his next fight. These intersecting storylines are brought together in a highly-stylized way that is quintessentially Tarantino. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

In addition to bringing Quentin Tarantino’s masterpiece back to the big screen, the event will feature exclusive interviews and original trailers, handpicked from Tarantino’s personal collection, that have influenced his work. Join us in celebrating 20 years of a legendary career as &lt;strong&gt;Pulp Fiction&lt;/strong&gt; comes back to movie theaters across the country &lt;strong&gt;Thursday, December 6 at 7:00pm (local time)*. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This will definitely sell out...so don't wait too long.  For more information and to buy tickets got to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fathomevents.com/classics/event/pulpfiction.aspx?d=12/6/2012"&gt;http://www.fathomevents.com/classics/event/pulpfiction.aspx?d=12/6/2012&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  The movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355067937000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352129458000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pulp Fiction (7PM show)</name><id>90042452</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354834800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/90042452/</event_url></item>