<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Stevie from the &lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup Group&lt;/span&gt; on &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;March 29 at 1.45 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Molière&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, the &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;4th film&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; of the &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;Salve Regina French Film Festival&lt;/span&gt; held in Newport RI&lt;/b&gt; between &lt;b&gt;22 March to 2 April 2009&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films are being shown to the public for no charge thanks to the support of the French American Cultural Exchange (FACE), the Cultural Services of the French Embassy and the French Ministry of Culture (CNC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An RSVP limit of 15 will ensure we have enough seats in the theater given its freely available to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the film&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; - &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Molière&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Salve Regina French Film Festival &lt;a href="http://www.salve.edu/frenchfilm/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; shows the following details for the screening of this film:&lt;br /&gt;[b&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;]&amp;quot;Moliere&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• &lt;u&gt;Date &amp;amp; Time&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;2 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; Sunday, March 29&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Location: &lt;b&gt;Bazarsky Lecture Hall, O'Hare Academic Center&lt;/b&gt; (located on the Salve Regina Campus, Ochre Point Road, Newport RI)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Historical fiction with extraordinary cast, sumptuous production and witty script about a missing period in the life of Moliére, one of the world's greatest masters of comedy.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reception following the film co-sponsored by Alliance Française de Newport.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----&lt;br /&gt;Further details about the film (taken from the FACE Tournées Festival information at &lt;a href="http://www.facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms/moliere.html" target="_blank"&gt;FACE/tournees/fichesfilms/moliere.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;In 1644, Jean Baptiste Poquelin, also known as Molière, is only twenty two and his illustrious Theater Troupe, founded the previous year, is bankrupt. Hounded by creditors, Molière is thrown into jail. When the jailors finally let him go, he disappears. Historians have found no trace of him before he reappeared with his troupe several months later. Taking this mystery as his starting point, Laurent Tirard concocted an elaborate historical fiction in which the young Molière is released from prison by Mr. Jourdain. This wealthy bourgeois settles Molière's debt on the understanding that he will teach him the craft and art of the stage. Mr. Jourdain is infatuated with the lovely but poisonous Célimen, whose salon gathers suitors and great wits. He craves to impress her but she only has disdain for him. To ensure that his love interest remains a secret from his wife, Elmire, Mr. Jourdain presents Molière as an austere private tutor. Molière falls in love with Elmire who, at first, only has harsh words for this holier-than-thou figure who invaded her home. Trapped in this untenable situation, Molière's eyes and mind will open to life itself and to his work as an artist. It is from this tale, and from his passion for Elmire, that Molière, the great dramatist, is born.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTOR&lt;/u&gt; – Laurent Tirard&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;SCREENPLAY&lt;/u&gt; – Laurent Tirard, Grégoire Vigneron &amp;amp; Gilles Henry&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;CAST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jean-Baptiste Poquelin: &lt;b&gt;Romain Duris&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Jourdain: &lt;b&gt;Fabrice Luchini&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Elmire Jourdain: &lt;b&gt;Laura Morante&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dorante: &lt;b&gt;Edouard Baer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Célimène: &lt;b&gt;Ludivine Sagnier&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Running time&lt;/u&gt;: 120’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Production&lt;/u&gt;: France, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rating&lt;/u&gt;: Not rated&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gauge&lt;/u&gt;: 35mm, DVD (color)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;GENRE&lt;/u&gt; – Comedy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DISTRIBUTOR&lt;/u&gt; – New Yorker Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Witty, suspenseful script shows that clothing and plumbing have evolved over the past 400 years, but foibles and longing are consistent factors in human affairs. Script makes fine use of formal language as a seductive tool, with humiliation and elation ebbing and flowing on the turn of a phrase (…) Molière buffs will delight in locating bits and pieces of his plays in this imaginary venture.”&lt;/i&gt; Lisa Nesselson, Variety&lt;br /&gt;__________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being organised by Stevie Worthington as part of a &lt;b&gt;6 part Meetup event&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup group&lt;/span&gt; held in &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;NEWPORT RI&lt;/span&gt;. If you can't make this night, hopefully you can make it to at least one of the other films in the Film festival on either &lt;b&gt;22 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;24 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;26 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;31 Mar&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;2 April&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Any questions, send Stevie an email - merci! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be inside the lobby from 1.30pm wearing a pink jacket holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238713432000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236717654000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film Festival in Newport - Film 4 "Molière"</name><id>9925638</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238349600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9925638/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/6/4/global_7625732.jpeg</photo_url></item>