<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>66 Marlborough Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.353600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Church Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>11707482</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075104</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ellen Beth Siegel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a clinical psychologist and a former lawyer, with a degree from Harvard University. She began studying with Ottone M. Riccio in 1990, and has also studied at The Frost Place in Franconia, New Hampshire. Her poems have been published in Bellowing Ark (where she was a Featured Poet), The Christian Science Monitor, Concrete Wolf, Poetpourri, and The Warwick Anthology, and have been nominated for the Pushcart Prize. She was one of the co-Editors of Do Not Give Me Things Unbroken, a 2002 anthology of poems all written from one of Mr. Riccio’s assignments. She also compiled the 2009 how-to book of poetry assignments Unlocking the Poem. Her chapbooks Remembering Endymion and The Sweet Moth Kisses Never Traded have been finalists in various chapbook contests. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ezekiel "Zeke" Russell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; grew up in an artist's community in Central Maine surrounded by poets and lumberjacks. He has been writing poetry for the last 20 years, but has only been performing for the last seven or so. He helps to organize the Untitled Open Mic and Mill City Slam at Brew'd awakening in Lowell. He was a member of the 2011 Lowell National Poetry Slam competition team and was the Grand Slam Champion that year. He has self published three chapbooks, and expects no one to be impressed by that. He works for Homestart inc., trying to end homelessness. He lives in Jamaica Plain with his partner Emily and their pug PJ and usually needs a hair cut. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365699285000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365005360000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poetry Month Thursdays, April 11 -- Ellen Beth Siegel and Zeke Russell</name><id>112463852</id><duration>1800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365696900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/112463852/</event_url></item>