<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is the third of three scramble events for the 2009 season.   &lt;br /&gt;Save money by registering for all three events by Thursday, June 18.  &lt;br /&gt;Series dates are June 18, July 30, August 27.  Series price is only $60. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an evening run along the Connecticut River on shaded paved and dirt trails cut into the river bank.  After the run, participants will be treated to food and cold beer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the food while listening to the sounds of great music along the river.  All in all, an X-Treme Scramble will be a great way to spend a summer evening.&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;The X-Treme Scramble is made possible due to the partnership and terrific support by Riverfront Recapture.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every Scramble is different - you may cross over the river on Founders Bridge and take the switchback ramp down onto the path along Great River Park. You may follow the path south past the boat ramp and amphitheater. You might wade along the beach on the river and up and over the hill back to the path. &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;You might run across the bridge and down the stairs to Charter Oak Landing and follow the trail into Charter Oak Landing. You may even climb over the Park River and continue south to the finish beneath Mortensen Riverfront Plaza.  Portions of this course might get you wet, might make you curse, might make you dirty – but it will all make you smile. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear the cheering crowds, listen to the band and climb back up to Mortensen Riverfront Plaza for the best post race party of the summer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251634068000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>5K-Runners-Meetup</urlname><id>1354697</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>5K Runners Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245867614000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>X-Treme Scramble #3</name><id>10726606</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251410400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/5K-Runners-Meetup/events/10726606/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/a/global_9326170.jpeg</photo_url></item>