<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is  a great event that I have attended several times.  Let’s plan on going as a group, you won’t be disappointed!  The information below is from BVS homepage (&lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonveg....&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP for our special outing to the Peace Abbey in Sherborn with naturalist, author, documentary scriptwriter, and radio commentator Sy Montgomery!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sy has been a vegetarian for over 30 years.  In her many award-winning books for children and adults she may take readers into the world of exotic wildlife in the far corners of the globe, or into the extraordinary lives of her rescued pig and hens.  Whether her subjects are the pink dolphins of the Amazon, snow leopards of Mongolia, tree kangaroos of New Guinea, tigers of Sundarbans, or the rescued pig and chickens who have shared her daily life, Sy views animals with respect, love, awe, and fascination with their individuality, and wants to inspire readers with the same.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Called by the Boston Globe &amp;quot;part Indiana Jones, part Emily Dickinson,&amp;quot; Sy Montgomery is dedicated to reaching as wide an audience as possible.  &amp;quot;We are on the cusp of either destroying this sweet, green Earth or revolutionizing the way we understand the rest of animate creation,&amp;quot; she says. &amp;quot;It's an important time to be writing about the connections we share with our fellow creatures.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sy's books available for sale and signing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*  the fun and heart-warming national bestseller The Good Good Pig: The Extraordinary Life of Christopher Hogwood&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*  the newly-released Birdology: Adventures with a Pack of Hens, a Peck of Pigeons, Cantankerous Crows, Fierce Falcons, Hip Hop Parrots, Baby Hummingbirds, and One Murderously Big Living Dinosaur&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* her new children’s book, Kakapo Rescue: Saving The World’s Strangest Parrot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* We will try to have some other titles from her amazing list of writings:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.authorwire.com/s/s_biblio.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.authorwire...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BVS' annual event at the PEACE ABBEY in Sherborn is a highlight event of our year.  Soak in the beauty and &amp;quot;good vibes&amp;quot; of this unique place, meet the animals in the small sanctuary for rescued farm animals, stroll the grounds and view the Pacifist Memorial and Gandhi statue, the magnificent Emily the Sacred Cow Animal Rights Memorial, and explore the Abbey and its artifacts from around the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL WELCOME!  This is a family-friendly event, and we encourage you to bring non-vegetarians!  We would love them to experience the inspiration of this gathering and this speaker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 PM  VEGAN POTLUCK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a favorite dish to share that is free of meat, poultry, fish, dairy, eggs, and honey.  Dishes should be ready to serve, and please include serving implements (labeled with your name).  A card with ingredients/recipe is appreciated.  A dish serving 8-10 per person is suggested.&lt;br /&gt;Need recipes?  See:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg.org/go_veggie.html#recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonveg....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3 PM  SPEAKER PRESENTATION - SY MONTGOMERY&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll use the church next to the Peace Abbey for the speaker program.  It seats 350, so we'll have plenty of seats!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE PEACE ABBEY:&lt;br /&gt;The Peace Abbey is a center which encourages non-violence, peacemaking, social justice, and compassionate living.  It was home, until her death six years ago, to Emily the Cow, who gained worldwide celebrity with her dramatic slaughterhouse escape, and became spokescow for veg living.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;Two North Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Sherborn, MA  (next to Natick)&lt;br /&gt;Where Route 27 and Route 16 overlap&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin</member_name><member_id>7947968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279474370000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274633760000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BVS at Peace Abbey with Sy Montgomery</name><id>13569218</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276448400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/13569218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_12060127.jpeg</photo_url></item>