<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>651 Willard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.234646</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Shea Rink</name><city>Quincy</city><id>669315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.028560</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hike the entire Skyline Trail from Quincy to Canton,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Second extension or return trip to Canton.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Should take about 3 to 4 hours and is approx 8 miles. YeeHaaawwwww! We will start at the parking area at Shea Rink in Quincy and return to parking area on Rte 138 near Dunkin Donuts.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Since this is an end to end hike, we will need to setup some carpooling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE!!!!! You DO NOT have to RSVP that you are not attending. This only fills up my mailbox. Thanks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This hike does have a lot of elevation. If you have not hiked before, have a medical condition, or cannot keep pace at 3 mph or more, you may not want to consider this event. Please bring a map of the Hills with in the event you fall behind. By signing up to his hike you agree to the liability waiver below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;LOCATION: Shea Rink, 651 Willard Street, Quincy, Ma &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;RECOMMENDED GEAR: Water, snacks, food, gloves, proper shoes for hiking, proper clothing for weather conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Debra's Cell # - 508-237-4454; use email address, dlh161@gmail.com. I cannot respond to the meetup email from my smartphone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Peaks: Great Blue Hill (635 feet).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Difficulty Level: Fast and Strenuous.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Time: Approximately 3 to 4 hours..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Weather Forecast: &lt;a href="http://www.weather.com/weather/today/USMA0260:1:US" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.weather.com/weather/today/USMA0260:1:US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;CANCELLATION POLICY: Inclement weather (mainly Rain) may cancel the hike. If cancelled, it will be&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;rescheduled a few weeks later. I will not have the time to call everyone, so you'll need access to your&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;email to see if the hike is canceled. I will try to post it 4 hours before the hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;CODE OF CONDUCT AND LIABILITY WAIVER: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Weather can change quickly. Weather conditions which normally do not appear problematic can be when the body is stressed by hard exercise. You can develop hypothermia or hyperthermia very easily at any outside temperature.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Debra and a group of smiling hikers</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra </member_name><member_id>12483780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334529457000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334069019000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Hike the Entire Skyline Trail from Quincy to Canton - 2nd Extension</name><id>59970782</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334415600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/59970782/</event_url></item>