<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Where Rte 27 &amp; Rte 16 overlap</address_2><address_1>2 N Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.244972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 655-2143</phone><name>The Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>322287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.369190</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'm posting this on behalf of the Boston Vegetarian Society:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Boston Vegetarian Society,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time for our annual outing to the beautiful Peace Abbey, with a fabulous vegan potluck and a special speaker program!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY, JULY 18, AT 1 P.M. (Rain or shine)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BVS' annual event at the PEACE ABBEY in Sherborn is a highlight event of our year.  Soak in the beauty and &amp;quot;good vibes&amp;quot; of this unique place, meet the animals in the small sanctuary for rescued farm animals, stroll the grounds and view the Pacifist Memorial and Gandhi statue, the magnificent Emily the Sacred Cow Animal Rights Memorial, and explore the Abbey and its artifacts from around the world.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL WELCOME!  This is a family-friendly event, and we encourage you to bring your friends and family, **especially non-vegetarians**.  We would love them to experience the inspiration of this gathering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 PM  VEGAN POTLUCK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Share delicious vegan cuisine. Bring a favorite dish to share that is free of meat, poultry, fish, dairy, eggs, and honey.  Dishes should be ready to serve, and please include serving implements (labeled with your name).  A card with ingredients/recipe is appreciated.  A dish serving 8-10 per person attending is suggested.&lt;br /&gt;Need recipe ideas?  See our page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonveg.org/go_veggie.html#recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonveg....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3 PM  SPEAKER PRESENTATION &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll use the church next to the Peace Abbey for the speaker program.  It seats 350, so we'll have plenty of seats!  Bring friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our special program will shine a spotlight on the plight of captive parrots and the issues facing avian wildlife, which are critical concerns deserving greater broad attention in the animal protection community.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marc Johnson, Founder and CEO of Foster Parrots and the New England Exotic Wildlife Sanctuary is a pioneer in this field.  He has been involved in these issue since the early 1980s.  His drive and dedication to parrot protection and avian welfare have brought him before audiences across the country to speak on the captive parrot crisis, wild parrot conservation efforts in South America, and controversy surrounding non-native parrot species in the US.    Marc Johnson was raised in Belgium and educated a the University of London.  He was a potter and art teacher with a studio in Cambridge MA when parrots first came into, and changed the course of, his life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Foster Parrots, Ltd. is a non-profit dedicated to the rescue and sanctuary of unwanted, languishing, and abused captive parrots and other displaced exotics, and education on captive parrot issues.  A staunch advocate for parrots as wild animals, Foster Parrots has established a conservation project in Guyana in South America that has helped protect parrots and other wildlife since 2004.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The N.E. sanctuary, recently relocated from MA to a 15 acre site in Rhode Island, gives lifelong care to over 475 unadoptable parrots and other captive exotics.  Jane Goodall came to their opening day ceremonies.  They write that the site is the former location of &amp;quot;a chicken slaughter house and egg production plant, where hundreds of thousands of birds once experienced untold suffering and death. Now it is a sanctuary where birds and other animals will find peace and comfort.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT THE PEACE ABBEY:&lt;br /&gt;The Peace Abbey is a center which encourages non-violence, peacemaking, social justice, and compassionate living.  Peace and justice advocates from around the world have come here, including Mother Teresa and the Dalai Lama. It was home, until her death five years ago, to Emily the Cow, who gained worldwide celebrity with her dramatic slaughterhouse escape, and became spokescow for veg living.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Peace Abbey&lt;br /&gt;Two North Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Sherborn, MA  (next to Natick)&lt;br /&gt;Where Route 27 and Route 16 overlap&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Details on directions, free parking, car pooling, volunteering, and RSVPing will follow later.  For now, save the July 18 date and invite some non-vegetarians to come with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event is free with your potluck offering; donation requested for the Peace Abbey.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or shine. The event is wheelchair accessible; please contact me in advance for details on wheelchair access.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info:  BVS  617-424-8846&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Kimber&lt;br /&gt;Boston Vegetarian Society&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.BostonVeg.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonVeg....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248215157000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246835856000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Vegan potluck &amp; speaker at Peace Abbey in Sherborn - Annual BVS event</name><id>10808295</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247936400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/10808295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>