<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH 113A, Wonalancet</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03897</zip><lat>43.908970</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ferncroft Parking ARea</name><city>Wonalancet</city><id>410429</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353912</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mt Whiteface with rugged ledges and Mt Passaconaway are both on the AMC's list of NH 4000 footers, so here's a chance to bag two more! Mt Whiteface is 4020, and Mt Passaconaway is 4043.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the weather is warm, and the forecast is good, we will make our way up the Blueberry Ledges Trail to the summit of Whiteface and then take the Rollins Trail to Passaconaway, and complete our loop using Dicey's Mill Trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total Mileage 11.9 with 3800 feet of elevation gain.  We will take breaks as needed, since this is a long hike with significant elevation change. Keep track of the time, its a long hike down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Lat:43.91339 Lon:-71.35808)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rt 16 North, until the Chocorua region. 113 West, until Tamworth, then Rt 113-A until the trailhead. (it ends close to it).&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;the Ferncroft Rd. parking area. Ferncroft Rd. leaves NH 113A at Wnalancet Village, at a right-angle turn in the main highway; at 0.5 mi. from NH 113A, a gravel road (FR 337) turns right and reaches a parking area and kiosk in 0.1 mi. No parking is permitted on Ferncroft Rd. beyond this point.From the parking area, return to Ferncroft Rd. and follow it to Squirrel Bridge at 0.3 mi. The Blueberry Ledge Trail turns left across the bridge.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hike discription: starting at Blueberry Ledge Trailhead&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;hike 0.20 mi/7 min/+24 ft on the Blueberry Ledge Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; From the parking area, return to Ferncroft Rd. and follow it to Squirrel Bridge, where the Dicey’s Mill Trail continues straight ahead. The Blueberry Ledge Trail turns left across the bridge and follows a private gravel road, avoiding driveways, then diverges left into the woods where the road curves right to the last house. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;to the junction of Pasture Path&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.10 mi/4 min/+31 ft on the Blueberry Ledge Trail &lt;br /&gt; Here the Pasture Path to Mt. Katherine leaves left. The trail joins an old road, and soon the Blueberry Ledge Cutoff diverges right to follow the bank of the Wonalancet River. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Blueberry Ledge Cutoff &lt;br /&gt; entering wilderness area &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; hike 1.40 mi/1 hr 10 min/+902 ft on the Blueberry Ledge Cutoff&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; It leaves the Blueberry Ledge Trail, and descends slightly to the riverbank. Then the Dicey’s Mill Trail runs on the opposite bank quite near the river; an old logging road comes across the river over a footbridge from the Dicey’s Mill Trail at this point, and the Blueberry Ledge Cutoff follows this road upstream into the Sandwich Range Wilderness. The trail soon climbs a small ridge and returns to the bank high above the brook. It swings away from the brook again, meets and follows a small tributary, then swings right and climbs steeply to the bottom of the upper ledge. Marked by cairns and paint, it climbs to meet the Blueberry Ledge Trail at the top of the ledge at a large cairn. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Blueberry Ledge Trail &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 11 min/+1172 ft on the Blueberry Ledge Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The trail climbs gently through open hardwoods, then rises steeply past Wonalancet Outlook to the top of the ridge. It drops slightly into a hollow, then ascends slightly to a junction with the Tom Wiggin Trail on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; to the junction of Tom Wiggin Trail   leaving wilderness area&lt;/b&gt;  hike 0.70 mi/42 min/+695 ft on the Blueberry Ledge Trail &lt;br /&gt; Now the trail climbs moderately, then swings sharp right at an outlook, where it abruptly approaches the edge of a steep cliff and may be dangerous if slippery. Just beyond here, it climbs a steep ledge, then continues to scramble up the steep, rough, rocky ridge, with several excellent viewpoints, ending at the ledges of the lower south summit. The McCrillis Trail enters from the left, just north of the ledges, while the Rollins Trail continues north to the true summit of Mt. Whiteface and on toward Mt. Passaconaway. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; to the junction of McCrillis Trail and Rollins Trail&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.10 mi/3 min/-55 ft on the Rollins Trail &lt;br /&gt; Leaving the south ledges, the Rollins Trail passes over a wooded ledge with a glimpse ahead to the true summit, then descends sharply into the steep, narrow col between the true summit and the open south summit of Whiteface, passing the junction with the Kate Sleeper Trail at the site of the former Camp Shehadi on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; to the junction of Kate Sleeper Trail&lt;/b&gt; hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+67 ft on the Rollins Trail &lt;br /&gt; From this col, the trail climbs north then runs along the ridge crest to the wooded true summit (no marking) of Mt. Whiteface. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Whiteface &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 3.90 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 3 hr 25 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2947 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -111 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +2836 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;hike 2.20 mi/1 hr 17 min/-768 ft on the Rollins Trail&lt;/b&gt; The trail continues along the narrow ridge, with outlooks to the east across the Bowl, descending gradually with occasional steep pitches and two short ascents to the broad, deep pass between Whiteface and Passaconaway. The trail then angles slightly upward around the south face of Passaconaway to meet the Dicey’s Mill Trail. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Dicey's Mill Trail &lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.20 mi/11 min/+181 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The Dicey’s Mill Trail then climbs through a rough, wet section, crosses a small brook, and reaches the junction, where the East Loop bears right. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of East Loop &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; hike 0.70 mi/39 min/+549 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; From the East Loop junction, the Dicey’s Mill Trail bears left, passes the site of the former Camp Rich (25 yd. left on a side trail), climbs moderately via wide switchbacks, then ascends steeply to a northwest outlook. Here it turns right and meets the Walden Trail in another 20 yd. The summit is 40 yd. right on a spur path, while the Walden Trail leads ahead 90 yd. to the east outlook. &lt;br /&gt; to Mt Passaconaway &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 0.70 mi/39 min/-549 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Dicey’s Mill Trail leaves the Walden Trail and descends steeply to a northwest outlook. It then descends moderately via wide switchbacks and passes the site of the former Camp Rich (25 yd. right on a side trail). The East Loop Trail enters left. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of East Loop &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;b&gt;hike 0.20 mi/11 min/-181 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; The East Loop bears left, the Dicey’s Mill Trail crosses a small brook then descends through a rough, wet section. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Rollins Trail &lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;hike 1.80 mi/1 hr 34 min/-1306 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; The trail begins a long descent, angling down the side of a ridge, following an old logging road at a moderate grade through hardwoods with occasional glimpses of the steep-sided Wonalancet Range rising on the opposite side of the valley. It passes a large boulder and then crosses the river at the site of Dicey’s Mill—there are some remains of the old mill hidden in the woods nearby. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Tom Wiggin Trail &lt;br /&gt; entering wilderness area &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; hike 1.90 mi/1 hr 20 min/-738 ft on the Dicey's Mill Trail&lt;/b&gt; The trail meets the Tom Wiggin Trail and the descent becomes easier. The trail swings left and becomes steeper the trail leaves the WMNF and Sandwich Range Wilderness, then a marked path left crosses the Wonalancet River on a footbridge to the Blueberry Ledge Cutoff on the opposite bank. The main trail follows a logging road then leaves the woods on a gravel road. It passes a house in a large clearing, then passes a gate. The Blueberry Ledge Trail turns right and the gravel road passes Squirrel Bridge and ends at Ferncroft Rd. &lt;br /&gt; to Dicey's Mill Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 11.60 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 9 hr 16 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +4232 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -4208 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +24 ft&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet at the trailhead, please be ready to hike by meetup time for this long hike.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282239351000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269567776000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whiteface and Passaconaway</name><id>12995568</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281875400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12995568/</event_url></item>