<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 College St. </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.559044</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-346-7096</phone><name>Tuscany Grill</name><city>Middletown</city><id>886457</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.649916</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dining Room &amp;amp; Mezzanine&lt;br /&gt;Our Dining Room features window seating and a beautiful high plaster ceiling. The Mezzanine offers a great view of the Lounge and Dining Room. You can even dine in the Lounge and enjoy sporting events on our ten foot projection screen television. A quiet, private atmosphere for small to medium sized parties is available in our Side Room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bar &amp;amp; Patio&lt;br /&gt;Our spacious bar room is the perfect place to enjoy a cappuccino or cocktail before or after dining. The full Tuscany Grill menu is available at the bar where there are five televisions so you can always see what is on. In the Summer enjoy alfresco dining on our Patio.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of downtown Middletown, in the historic Middlesex Opera House building, Tuscany Grill has been serving fine Italian creations since 1995.&lt;br /&gt;We are right around the corner from Main Street, Middletown &amp;amp; minutes from the Middletown shopping center, Wesleyan University and the new Destinta Theater.  This is a great restaurant!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our specialties include chef inspired modern Italian &amp;amp; classic Italian creations. A large selection of delicious pasta dishes, unique entrees, pizza, desserts and an excellent selection of fine wine to complement your meal. Specials are offered daily for Lunch &amp;amp; Dinner - there is always something new to try!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If it is Saturday the 18th and you can't attend Please Call the Restaurant  and reduce the number.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>reservation under Sandy</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1245965823000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236818678000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ITS TIME FOR Tuscany  Grill </name><id>9935402</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240095600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/9935402/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/5/global_2981797.jpeg</photo_url></item>