<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>South Mountain Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01360</zip><lat>42.648052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>M&amp;M Trail-head</name><city>Northfield</city><id>5536982</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.441948</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A short walk (20-30 minutes) up to the top of Mt. Crag from South Mountain Rd. in Northfield, Ma. This is a tiny section of The M&amp;amp;M Trail. Sunset is around 5:10 - Moon-rise a few minutes later. Most of the walk is easy on a gentle grade or level ground. There is a short section up to the top which is moderately steep and may require a scramble or two. We plan to head back down before it becomes completely dark (unless everyone wants to stay longer) but a headlamp or flashlight is recommended. It is fairly open on top with great views to the West, South and East. The temperature usually feels 10 to 20 degrees lower up there so dress accordingly. Right now the forecast is favorable with temps in the low 30's. Parking is limited to five vehicles so attendance is limited to the first four - carpooling is encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions; From Rte 2 in Erving Center, Take North St. (becomes Gulf Rd. in Northfield) 2.7 miles. Turn Left onto South Mountain Rd, Go 1/2 mile to the top of the hill. Parking is on the street or at an adjacent cemetery. Look for my white van. Kinda hard to miss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328815238000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328453036000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset and Full-Moon rise on Mt, Crag</name><id>51109982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328648400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/51109982/</event_url></item>