<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>1.5 miles south of Rt. 130 on Rt. 13</address_2><address_1>98 Rte 13</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03033</zip><lat>42.723415</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Andres Institute of Art</name><city>Brookline</city><id>671395</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.662552</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This adventure incorporates both hiking and exposure to many works of art. Andres Institute of Art in Brookline, NH is a 140-acre sculpture park with miles of wooded trails, beautiful vistas, and peaceful settings. It is the combination of art and nature that makes a visit to Andres Institute of Art a unique and memorable occasion. Big Bear Mountain used to be a downhill ski area, but in 1996 the property was purchased by engineer and innovator Paul Andres. Paul moved into the house near the top of the mountain and decided to commission sculptures to place along the many trails surrounding his new home. In 1998 the Andres Institute of Art was incorporated as a 501(c) (3) charitable organization. The trails on the mountain are open to the public free of charge. Sculptors from Lithuania, Latvia, England, Czech Republic, Ukraine, and other countries have contributed their work to this art exhibit. As a result of the collective effort from these gifted artists, there are now over 60 thought-provoking original works of art.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance: 4 to 6 miles, depending upon trails taken. Estimated time: 3 to 4 hours Even though this is not a huge mountain, there is a fair amount of climbing involved. Trails range from easy to difficult, so appropriate footwear should be worn. You should have rain gear in case of showers. Maps are located at the trailhead behind the parking lot. The map will describe the difficulty level of each trail, as well as the location of each exhibit. The map is also available online. Dogs are allowed in the park as long as they are under the control of the owner. Driving directions: The Andres Institute of Art is located on the west side of Rte. 13 in Brookline, NH about 1.7 miles north of the Massachusetts border, and 6.8 miles south of Rte. 101 in N.H. After you enter the road to the Institute, the parking lot will be about 100 yards on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Yvonne...this is the response to my email from Andres Institute of Art...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="https://mail.google.com/mail/images/cleardot.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="https://mail.google.com/mail/images/cleardot.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="https://mail.google.com/mail/images/cleardot.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="https://mail.google.com/mail/images/cleardot.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;span&gt;Hello Cheryl!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;I'm sure we can find you a guide, more than one, if need be!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Our sculpture park is free&lt;/span&gt; of charge, though any donations are gratefully accepted! &lt;span&gt;We do not have any picnic tables, but there are plenty&lt;/span&gt; of places to relax, enjoy the view, and chow down! &amp;nbsp;One spot I might suggest is by the Phoenix, (Sculpture #1 on the map) It has views to the west, and some bowling alley chairs, &amp;nbsp;many a meal has been enjoyed there! &lt;span&gt;Also, there is the stone theater, otherwise known as "Diamond Site" (sculpture #5 on the map) It is composed&lt;/span&gt; of many seat-sized boulders which make it a favorite among picnicers at &lt;span&gt;Andres&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;nbsp;It has the added advantage &lt;span&gt;of&lt;/span&gt; being near the studio which has a bathroom! Lets keep in touch, feel free to ask any other questions! Thank you SO MUCH for your interest!! 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.andresinstitute.org/"&gt;http://www.andresinstitute.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338256650000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331739993000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Andres Insitute of Art</name><id>56325112</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336228200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/56325112/</event_url></item>