<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Folks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a great opportunity for &lt;b&gt;free voice lessons&lt;/b&gt;, which can be pretty expensive from good teachers.  I went to the first class, and it was awesome.  Unfortunately it is only for men. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I learned a lot, and it is really fun, everyone is friendly, and easy to learn to sing quartet style.  I'm going on Thursday.  Improved singing is one of the best capabilities you can add to your musicianship - a free extra instrument that you already have and don't even have to buy!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Quartet Organizer says it doesn't matter that it is the 2nd of 4 meetups, it's somewhat redundant - I highly recommend going if you want to improve singing.  There were ~25 new participants last week.  (Note - there is a $10 one time fee for a CD and materials).   I'm also planning to set up a music meetup for Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our next Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Voice Classes for Men #2&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jan 14,  Thursday 7:00 PM &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Temple Emunah &lt;br /&gt;9 Piper Rd &lt;br /&gt;Lexington, MA 02421 &lt;br /&gt;781-643-7468&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Respond yes to our meetup and then&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; go to The Barbershop Quartet Meetup and respond yes there.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/barbershop-7th/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Sounds of Concord&lt;/b&gt; will again be offering free* group voice classes for men who sing and who wish to become better singers. If you are a guy or know a guy who enjoys singing, this is a great program!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program is sponsored by Sounds of Concord, an award winning men's a cappella chorus, and will consist of &lt;b&gt;4 classes on Thursday nights beginning Thursday January 7th, and continuing on January 14, 21 and 28. Read more&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263680485000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263336491000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Voice Lessons for men at Barbershop Quartet</name><id>12302462</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263513600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/12302462/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>