<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>167 Neck Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06443</zip><lat>41.272118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mercy Center At Madison</name><city>Madison</city><id>11203052</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for something to do on a Saturday night? Try a winter labyrinth walk near the ocean! &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mercy Center at Madison is blessed with 33 acres of breath-taking, waterfront property with a beautiful, private beach. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin with a short gathering to do introductions. Then, learn about the history, tradition and purpose of labyrinths before entering into its meditative and relaxing space. A path to the center leads us in and back out while walking in quiet reflection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Labyrinths are different than mazes. There is only one winding path that leads to the center, and the walker basically retraces their steps in to get back out to the entrance/exit. Basically, it’s a way of physically reflecting on the twists and turns of life and what will bring you or has brought you to this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the labyrinth is outside, you'll need to dress warmly! Following the walk, there will be time for conversation, cookies, hot tea and apple cider indoors while people warm up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no right or wrong way to walk the labyrinth. Respond to the questions, insights, and emotions that arise from within and from the beautiful ocean beach surroundings as seen in the light of the full moon. Following your walk you are invited to remain for a shared reflection with all gathered for the evening's journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mercy Center offers this event for a free will donation which means you can pay what you like. I'm going to suggest that we all try to give at least $10 to further their mission and work...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #444444"&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Our vision is to nurture a relationship with the Sacred in self, others and creation that seeks to foster a just and compassionate world.... The profound spiritual and personal transformations experienced at Mercy Center are carried by each attendee into each aspect of their lives... These inner shifts are to be shared with the world today. If each person who has come to Mercy Center affects even just 1 other person, then our impact is truly lasting and our vision of a more just and compassionate world will be realized."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/6/6/event_196256422.jpeg" width="449" height="336" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy Center Labyrinth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you want to carpool at 6 pm - Meet at parking lot on corner of Mitchell and Willow.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359327247000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358377918000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Labyrinth Walk</name><id>99958712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359244800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/99958712/</event_url></item>