<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I got the below invitation today and it sounds like a good time.  I am assured all the food will be vegan. If we get a large group I should probably give the organizer a heads up so please respond if you are interested.  I realize this is a long ways from New Haven but Windsor Locks is a stop on the Amtrak line(only .04 miles to the event) and there is probably an opportunity to carpool.  Email me if you would like to find a ride.   Here are the direction from the Amtrak station to the event: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=S.+Main+St.+(Rte.+159),+Windsor+Locks,+CT+06096+(Windsor+Locks+Amtrak+Station)&amp;amp;daddr=41+Oak+Street,+Windsor+Locks,+CT&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FU_CfwIdrsar-yHSRyK0dIpotw%3B&amp;amp;mra=cc&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=41.929385,-72.62816&amp;amp;sspn=0.00811,0.015407&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ben&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On February 22 at 5 PM, Northern Connecticut Vegetarians want&lt;br /&gt;to invite the the New Haven Meetup Group to  the  Celtic/Irish&lt;br /&gt;Vegan Potluck and Entertainment by a lively Celtic Band.  The&lt;br /&gt;band features Lisa Furman and BlueFlys Band.  Lisa Furman on&lt;br /&gt;guitar, Irish whistle and lead vocals, Chris Teskey on guitar,&lt;br /&gt;Dick Neal on banjo and mandolin and Tahlia Furman on fiddle. &lt;br /&gt;They  play a fresh, progressive, eclectic blend of Celtic and&lt;br /&gt;Americana music and perform regularly in southern Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;and the New York City area.   Please bring a Healthy Vegan dish&lt;br /&gt;(Celtic if possible) to share along with a list of its&lt;br /&gt;ingredients and attendee’s name.   Also, attendees should bring&lt;br /&gt;their place setting.  A donation of $10 per adult is requested;&lt;br /&gt;children are free. The Carniglia Senior Center, 41 Oak Street,&lt;br /&gt;Windsor Locks is the location for this event.   For&lt;br /&gt;reservations or questions, call Harry at  (860) 623-8082 or&lt;br /&gt;email Harry at veggyharry@aol.com.  For more information, see&lt;br /&gt;www.northctveg.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ben, we do hope your group will join us.  Rest assured all food&lt;br /&gt;will be VEGAN.   The ingredients list for each dish and&lt;br /&gt;nonvegan dishes are removed from the serving table.  In fact,&lt;br /&gt;we have 2 food tables at our events--one labeled for RAW VEGAN&lt;br /&gt;and another for VEGAN.  Reservations are requested as NCVS&lt;br /&gt;yearly music program is a popular event.  The music group comes&lt;br /&gt;from New Haven area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm tall.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Martin</member_name><member_id>1315927</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236984360000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-386</urlname><id>279146</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234498378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NCVS Celtic/Irish Vegan Potluck and Entertainment</name><id>9733825</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235340000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-386/events/9733825/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/a/global_1616698.jpeg</photo_url></item>