<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>550 Winter Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.396603</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 890-6767</phone><name>Double Tree Hotel</name><city>Waltham</city><id>1061208</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.266121</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Build Wealth in Real Estate . . . Without Tenants and Toilets!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Self-storage has become the Hottest Sector of Commercial Real Estate over the past 25 years (and almost no one has heard about!)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Meyers will teach the real-world ins and outs of identifying, negotiating, buying, managing and building wealth in real estate without the hassles of tenants and toilets!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn how to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•enjoy all the benefits of owning property without all the risks and hassles of dealing with needy tenants and leaky toilets &lt;br /&gt;•acquire properties in any area with no money down, the safe way  &lt;br /&gt;•manage from afar by implementing the multitude of new technologies available in this exploding industry.   &lt;br /&gt;•maximize the 20+ Profit Centers available in Self Storage to maximize cash flow and create value that isn’t available in any other form of real estate  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Scott is the nation’s leading expert in the area of Self Storage Investing. He enjoys teaching the strategies that helped him realize his dream of becoming a self-made real estate millionaire, without all the hassles of tenants and toilets. After nearly going bankrupt while investing in single family homes and apartments, he now devotes a large amount of his time speaking to real estate and Self Storage groups on how to create wealth the old-fashioned way; slowly and safely. Scott is a Certified Self Storage Manager (CSSM©) through the National Self Storage Association and a regular exhibitor at Self Storage Industry Trade Shows and Conventions. Scott is also the author of “The Complete Guide to Finding, Evaluating, and Acquiring Self Storage Facilities”, and a frequent contributor to numerous industry trade publications.  Scott is the owner and President of his own Self Storage Investment Company, Alcatraz Storage™.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 Networking and Meet the Vendors&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Meeting&lt;br /&gt;Doubletree, 550 Winter Street, Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston AREIA members are free, visitors and meetup members pay $25&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Downstairs in the hotel.  </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269121233000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>93</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266536417000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association March Meetup</name><id>zhhdnynfbxb</id><headcount>78</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268947800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/12642325/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/global_6774288.jpeg</photo_url></item>