<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1667 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 547-0759</phone><name>Lizard Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119650</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lamine Toure &amp;amp; Group Saloum&lt;br /&gt;Lizard Lounge&lt;br /&gt;1667 Massachusetts Ave, Cambridge, MA 02138(617) 547-0759&amp;#8206;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 PM $ 10 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lizardloungeclub.com/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lizardloun...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.laminetoure.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.laminetour...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Group Saloum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Saloum is Boston's hottest Afro-pop band. Founded by world-renowned griot percussionist Lamine Touré, Group Saloum fuses Senegalese mbalax with elements of jazz, funk, reggae, and Afrobeat. Group Saloum performs original mbalax music highlighted by the infectious rhythms of Touré's sabar drums, drawing upon the collective creativity of some of Boston's most talented musicians.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;From Boston, a spectacular afropop act specializing in, but not limited to, Senegalese mbalax.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;— Afropop Worldwide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lamine Touré and Group Saloum kick out a hard-hitting dance mix that spans the percussive fury of Senegalese mbalax and the joyful uplift of Congolese soukous&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;— Banning Eyre, Boston Phoenix&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Whatever your pleasure this album has got it. Group Saloum is a tight group made of some of the best musicians in Boston. For a city boasting hundreds of music conservatory and grads, this says quite a bit. Their polished act will definitely be thrilling live concertgoers for years to come.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;— Erich Ludwig, VP Artist Relations, Calabash Music&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check us out on MySpace as well!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group Saloum is: Lamine Touré (sabar percussion and lead vocals), Yeumougor “Paa” Seck (sabar percussion and backing vocals), Babacar “Moha” Seck (sabar percussion and backing vocals), Michael Lewis (drums), Balaji Mani (guitar), Hiro Sakaba (bass), Akili Jamal Haynes (trumpet &amp;amp; backing vocals), koga rite (keyboards), Sarah Privler (trombone), and Erin Blatti (backing vocals).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The band's self-titled first album is available online from Amazon.com and www.calabashmusic.com. The CD was recorded by ASCAP-winning producer Dan Cantor of Notable Productions, and is released and distributed by Nomadic Wax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click below to enjoy the first three minutes of Mbaye Saar, from Lamine Touré &amp;amp; Group Saloum's first album!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268617340000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268338425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lamine Toure &amp; Group Saloum</name><id>12851302</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268443800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/12851302/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/6/8/global_13589992.jpeg</photo_url></item>