<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Friday: Patchy fog before 8am. Otherwise, mostly sunny, with a high near 85. Calm wind becoming south between 10 and 13 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Night: A chance of showers and thunderstorms, mainly before 2am. Mostly cloudy, with a low around 70. Southwest wind between 6 and 9 mph. Chance of precipitation is 30%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: A slight chance of showers and thunderstorms. Mostly cloudy, with a high near 89. West wind between 7 and 11 mph. Chance of precipitation is 20%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Night: A chance of showers and thunderstorms. Mostly cloudy, with a low around 68. Chance of precipitation is 30%.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 86. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TIME IS RUNNING SHORT TO GET IN ON THIS EVENT,&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE PAY UP SO THINGS WILL GO SMOOTHLY AND THERE WONT BE ANY &amp;quot;SORRY YOU CANT GO&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;see you there al-r&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Friendship at the Lake with Food, Activities and Free Boating with optional camping feature&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Get Smart, Enjoy 3 days of camping for $20.00 (which&lt;i&gt; includes&lt;/i&gt; Saturday big picnic) or $11.00 for day use alone at a pristine private campground and lake. --&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please reserve your spot now (SOONER IS BETTER) because last year some last minute people complained because they were left out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Procrastinators, complainers, and miserable people ?? EEhhhhhhhhh&lt;br /&gt;We didn't want them to come anyway......so be paid up, anticipate a great time under any conditions, and be happy with a good group of people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many times lower reality happens when ya try to hedge the bet too much, ya most likely loose out..ya stay home and WISH you could have gone..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last Years pics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/CT-Recreational-Sea-Kayakers/photos/667486/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facility:&lt;/b&gt;  Yale Univ. Outdoor Center, East Lyme &lt;br /&gt;Private pristine lake and picnic area,  Nestled on mile long Powers Lake, surrounded by 1500 wooded acres.&lt;br /&gt;Picnic Pavillion, beach front with doc and raft. &lt;br /&gt;Boating, hiking, fishing. (more details below).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yale Outdoor Education Ctr&lt;br /&gt;298 Upper Pattagansett Rd&lt;br /&gt;East Lyme, CT 06333&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAMPING --&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; FRIDAY NIGHT-Afternoon or a bit earlier (JULY 16) TO SUNDAY AFTERNOON (JULY 18) INCLUDING our Traditional POT LUCK PARTY ON JULY 17 TOTAL COST FOR ALL &lt;b&gt;IS $20.00 per person for the entire Camping weekend DEAL.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Limited to 25 persons.   &lt;i&gt;An additional camping site has now been secured.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This CAMPING FEE will cover your entrance to the facility (ALL OF THE CAMPING), paper goods, charcoal, some beverages. &lt;br /&gt;You have to bring your tent/other..and camping food..etc.. we may pot luck some of the camping meals but that's to be discussed at the site and time..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also included in price:  Rowboats, canoes, kayaks.  (life jackets are available and must be worn).  Blazed hiking trails around a wildlife marsh, pond, clay volleyball court, horse-shoe pit, small basketball court, field office, and recreation cabin with ping pong.  A spring water dispenser is located in the Pavilion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please send a check for $20.00 per person to (include a note with your name, phone and email in case there is some problem and indicate CAMPING):&lt;br /&gt;Mail to:  &lt;br /&gt;YALE MEETUP OUTING&lt;br /&gt; c/o B.G. &lt;br /&gt;3 STEPHANIE CT &lt;br /&gt;MADISON CT 06443-8112&lt;br /&gt;/b]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAMPING AND AND/OR ATTENDING THE PARTY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday we will have our Traditional  &amp;quot;Pot Luck Barbie-Q&amp;quot; so please bring either a desert, side dish to share, some good meat..etc..ok about 8 serving size worth for an idea..&lt;/b&gt;    Remember to bring a chair or blanket and the usual summer relaxing necessities.  &lt;br /&gt;Al and Barbara will bring their gas grills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will supply the additional charcoal for the real smoky meat flaviour, paper goods, ice, water and some soft drinks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kayaks/Canoes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The facility offers kayaks, canoes and rowboats.  If you care to bring your own, then you will need to put in on the state boat ramp (located around the block); Directions: out of the facility, bear sharply right, follow road for about 1-2 miles, boat launch is on the right&lt;br /&gt;gps: &lt;a href="http://www.kids.ct.gov/Dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2686&amp;amp;q=384254&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1620"&gt;http://www.kids.ct.go...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or:  &lt;a href="http://connecticutwatertrails.com/CWTA%20-%20Connecticut%20Boat%20Launches%20-%20New%20London%20County%20-%20East%20Lyme%20-%20Powers%20Lake%20Boat%20Launch.htm"&gt;http://connecticutwat...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for insurance reasons Yale can’t allow you to put in on their property.  The advantage of bringing your own is that you can go for a sunset kayak.  You will not be limited to Yale rules (IE must be in site for life guards; and time restraints).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BEHAVIOR:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a private club reserved and organized by a member who works at Yale, so please be courteous and responsible as this is where she works!  Drink responsibly and please keep your space clean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAMPING PEOPLE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to camp, then I will need $20/pp in advance as well as an RSVP to secure your spot.  Right now, I am securing 3 campsites but will add as the numbers increase.  There are only 9 sites available which tend to book up, so please, if you are interested in camping send me your $ and your RSVP by July 1.  Bg3step@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommended equipment:&lt;/b&gt;  Tent, air mattress, sleeping bag, bug repellant, sun lotion and any snacks and other things to make your stay enjoyable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BARBARA &amp;amp; STEVE R. WILL BE HOSTING THIS EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;please contact them for additional info that i may have not added yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEATHER: UPDATED WHEN AVAILABLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SINCE THIS HAS TO BE A PRE-PAID AND PRE-RESERVED EVENT/FACILITY IF SOMEHOW ITS RAINING and ya already paid, WE WILL STILL PARTY USING THE INSIDE/COVERED FACILITIES. We are planning on putting a bunch of canopies together for the camping part so that we will have some cover it it does rain.  Hopefully mother nature will cooperate as she did last year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! Oh, and please remember to RSVP. Thanks!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95 North: &lt;br /&gt;to Exit 71 (Four Mile River Rd -- East Lyme), turn right off exit ramp and continue 1-1/2 miles to end of the road. Turn right onto Route 1, continue another 1-1/2 miles, turn left onto Scott Road. (right past the SCOTT’s FARM MARKET) Continue straight two miles to front entrance (directly across the road) This is the intersection of Scott road and Pattagansett Road.   Enter property and follow dirt road (which bears to the left); 3/4 mile to check-in station and lakeside parking lot.  A list of names will be given to the guard so you will be all set if you have paid.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Driving Directions: From HARTFORD:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-84 East apx 0.5 miles to (exit # 55) rte 2 East toward Norwich.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow rte 2 for 24 miles to rte 11 (exit # 19).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take rte 11 for 7.5 miles to (exit # 4) for rte 82.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right (toward Hadlyme) onto rte 82 THEN TAKE AN IMMEDIATE LEFT onto DARLING Rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Darling Rd to its end apx 1 mile Take a Left onto GUNGY rd follow for apx 2.8 miles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a left at Beaver Brook rd go apx 1 mile and continue strait on Whistletown Rd for 2.1 miles to the intersection of Pattagansett and Scott rd,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE ENTRANCE TO YALE NATURE CENTER IS OPPOSITE  SCOTT RD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--- Follow the windy dirt road TO THE END -apx 3/4 mile to check-in station where someone is in a booth to greet you- (your name will be on a list) then park at the lakeside parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;look for my small Orange Striped Cones in the vicinity of our pickanick area.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAMPERS:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who are camping we will email you the campsite numbers so you will know where to go&lt;br /&gt;and i will put out my small Orange Stryped by the sites.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>LOOK FOR THE 6 foot tall ORANGE POLE BY ROAD OF THE CAMPSITE AREA (S)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>5197547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279561832000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271275751000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*The "SMART CHOICE" in Camping*     East Lyme - Lk Powers - Yale Ntr Ctr</name><id>13183897</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279306800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/13183897/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/6/global_14538838.jpeg</photo_url></item>