<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sally spoke with the author of the manuscript, and he graciously gave permission for us to print what we need for book club. I asked if he would like to print it, and sell it to us for a small profit (since these are sales that he loses on books, ultimately), and he said no, but if anyone wanted to bring a donation to a food pantry that night, he would see to it that it goes to whoever we choose to be recipients.(Canned goods, pasta,rice etc.) You will see why this is sort of in keeping with the theme after you read the story. He said that he is honored to have us read his manuscript.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHERE THE WILDFLOWERS GROW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emily’s time is short. This she knows; this she has accepted. &lt;br /&gt;The promise of another tomorrow broken, she has turned to the &lt;br /&gt;past, reliving her fifty-seven years through the songs that &lt;br /&gt;marked her passage from apple of her father’s eye to faithful &lt;br /&gt;wife and loving mother. With each new dawn, Emily asks Ray, her &lt;br /&gt;devoted husband and defiant caretaker, for another selection &lt;br /&gt;from her life’s songbook, the music that’ll deliver her to &lt;br /&gt;people and places previously lost to the lengthening shadows of &lt;br /&gt;time. Dipping into pools of memories long run dry, Emily doesn’&lt;br /&gt;t simply recall the spring of years past, she’s there, &lt;br /&gt;breathing deep of its lush, perfumed air. Retracing her steps, &lt;br /&gt;Emily has returned chronologically to the very moments that &lt;br /&gt;have defined her life since childhood. Now it’s their turn.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Today, waking to the sight of her wedding ring, Emily made the &lt;br /&gt;request Ray had been anticipating: the song that will return &lt;br /&gt;her to the one year from which everything has grown. The year &lt;br /&gt;they met. Transported thirty years past, to their intersection, &lt;br /&gt;Emily is again twenty-eight. Successful and secure, she’s &lt;br /&gt;haunted by the regret of a path not chosen. But in Ray—&lt;br /&gt;confident and conflicted, embattled and inspired—she glimpses &lt;br /&gt;what could have been, the life she might’ve had. Upon meeting, &lt;br /&gt;Ray and Emily are forced to confront the demons that have kept &lt;br /&gt;each from attaining what they most desire. On that one year &lt;br /&gt;their future is hinged; twelve months which reshape their lives &lt;br /&gt;and bind them to a single road.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WHERE THE WILDFLOWERS GROW is a tribute to enduring memory, the &lt;br /&gt;indelible impressions bequeathed to us by a life&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>8054589</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237853271000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233419143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club - Manuscript</name><id>9640400</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237417200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/9640400/</event_url></item>