<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>302 Wickenden Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.819674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-751-4900</phone><name>Abe's</name><city>Providence</city><id>1109470</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.397127</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We hope you can join your fellow Newcomers at this year's holiday party hosted by Abe's. There will be food, drink, and most importantly, fun!   We have the room from 2PM until 5PM when the bar opens for normal hours (we can of course stay, just won't be private anymore)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since Abe's does not offer food, we'll also be having a Potluck this year.  Unfortunately, this means that no preparation can occur onsite, so might make some things more difficult.  Participation in the Potluck is entirely optional, but wouldn't you love to show off the most awesome recipe you know with the best people in Providence to hang out with?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cost of the event is $5&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, in order to get the bar to open, we do need to pay to use the space and have Claude (the owner) spend the afternoon tending the bar for us.  To that end, I'm asking that everyone contribute $5 to cover that cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Yankee Swap (optional)&lt;/b&gt; - will start around 3:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Based on the success of last years fun, we're bringing back the exciting &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_elephant_gift_exchange" target="_blank"&gt;Yankee Swap/White Elephant Exchange&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you wish to participate in the White Elephant Exchange/Yankee Swap, bring one small gift wrapped item without labels that costs $10 or less. Everyone who brings a gift will be eligible to participate in one of the most interesting and potentially fun gift exchanges ever seen. At the end of the exchange, every participant gets one gift to take home, however, it may not be the gift that was opened, as a bit of &amp;quot;stealing&amp;quot; can occur.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Examples of good items: bad movies on DVD, amusing books, gift cards, novelty bottle openers, (almost anything from Oop!), small toys. (I won a box of condoms the first year we did this).  Need more advice for gift choices? Check out the WikiHow article on &lt;a href="http://www.wikihow.com/Buy-a-Gift-for-a-White-Elephant-Party" target="_blank"&gt;gift ideas&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.wikihow.com/Organize-a-White-Elephant-Gift-Exchange" target="_blank"&gt;organizing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the only group in the place.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292885295000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291246368000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>3rd Annual Winter Party</name><id>15613685</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/15613685/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>