<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Xen'drik Expeditions returns to Pandemonium Books &amp;amp; Games in a frantic pair of super-weekends! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noon to 5 PM at the Dining Room table of Doooom - Well of Woe, Round 1 - Host to be announced&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The prohecies of the Caldyn Fragments have pointed to the Well of Woe, and the four factions speed towards it. But can they work together to find out how to reach it? (All factions welcome.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noon to 5 PM in the Arena - The Mere of Shattered Souls - Hosted by Chris Senhouse&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A new piece of the Caldyn Fragments falls into place. Can the four factions work together to meet their goals? (All factions welcome.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 PM to 11 PM at the Dining Room of Doooom - Well of Woe, Round 2 - Hosted by Chris Senhouse&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You now hold the key to finding the Well of Woe, but can you survive long enough to claim it for your faction? (All factions welcome.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6 PM to 11 PM in the Arena - Cabal of Shadows Adventure 3: Khyber's Children - Hosted by Andrew French&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The time has come for the sahuagin of Shargon's Teeth to repay their debt to the children of the shadows. Will their aid lead to a new part of the draconic prophecy...or a watery grave? (Cabal of Shadows characters only)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can take 6 players per session, plus we take 2 alternates, who get the space if a player cancele or doesn't show. Please sign up by sending email to rpga [AT] bloopwatch [DOT] org&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540835000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1166825327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>XenEx Panic Weekend @ Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><id>5342359</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168707600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/5342359/</event_url></item>