<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1360 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-497-9797</phone><name>Au Bon Pain</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669157</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're back on track for 3 week intervals and this one is straight from the polls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4- The Emperor's Children by Claire Messud&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?isbn=030726419x" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments:&lt;br /&gt;From a writer &amp;quot;of near-miraculous perfection&amp;quot; (The New York Times Book Review) and &amp;quot;a literary intelligence far surpassing most other writers of her generation&amp;quot; (San Francisco Chronicle), The Emperor's Children is a dazzling, masterful novel about the intersections in the lives of three friends, now on the cusp of their thirties, making their way — and not — in New York City.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is beautiful, sophisticated Marina Thwaite — an &amp;quot;It&amp;quot; girl finishing her first book; the daughter of Murray Thwaite, celebrated intellectual and journalist — and her two closest friends from Brown, Danielle, a quietly appealing television producer, and Julius, a cash-strapped freelance critic. The delicious complications that arise among them become dangerous when Murray's nephew, Frederick &amp;quot;Bootie&amp;quot; Tubb, an idealistic college dropout determined to make his mark, comes to town. As the skies darken, it is Bootie's unexpected decisions — and their stunning, heartbreaking outcome — that will change each of their lives forever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A richly drawn, brilliantly observed novel of fate and fortune — of innocence and experience, seduction and self-invention; of ambition, including literary ambition; of glamour, disaster, and promise — The Emperor's Children is a tour de force that brings to life a city, a generation, and the way we live in this moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to try the Harvard Square Au Bon Pain again and I apologize for my address faux pax last time.  I think I've got it right this time around.  Regardless,&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt; head to harvard square&lt;/span&gt;!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226965552000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220958255000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meetup:The Emperor's Children by Claire Messud</name><id>8720384</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225148400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/8720384/</event_url></item>