<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is the third in a six-part series on mindfulness meditation. The first week we focused on mindful breathing and posture, the second on the body, and this third lesson will focus on emotions.&lt;b&gt; If you missed one or both of the introductory classes, you'll be fine. Each class focuses on some of the fundamental aspects covered in the first two classes and takes it from there.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will learn that mindfulness is not so much about cultivating inner peace as it is about increasing non-judgmental awareness and clarity of thought and sensory experience. We may have more peace in our lives as a result, but it is not the primary focus of our efforts. With so much distraction and stimulation in the world, it helps to have a regular practice that brings us back to the moment and increases our awareness. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course will be supported by audio instruction provided by Gil Fronsdal, primary teacher for the Insight Meditation Center in Redwood City, California. Each week for the next six weeks, we will start the group by listening to his talk, which lasts about one hour, and will follow with discussion about the content and our experiences. This will be a good refresher course for those who have been meditating for years, as well as those who are new to mindfulness or meditation. Please join us in mindful community as we seek to bring more awareness into our lives and into the world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254782012000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251155572000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup</name><id>mvtxkymmblc</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254175200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/11190653/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/0/global_10129760.jpeg</photo_url></item>