<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Bennet Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Regattabar at the Charles Hotel</name><city>Cambridge, Harvard square</city><id>3395632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122665</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the Facebook event page (&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/228347917297759/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/228347917297759/&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A very special night featuring two unique band that sound like no one else!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIMBILA blazes ecstatic African rock with an East Village edge. The trance of African spirit possession merges with the trance of free-spirited head-bangers. Surreal buzzing timbila, hypnotic dream melodies of mbira, stinging guitar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIMBILA is part of a new wave of world rock bands creating music without borders. In their sound, the trance of African spirit possession becomes one with the trance of free-spirited headbangers—all part of a rock ‘n’ roll stew that is melodious, lyrical, liberating, vibrating, fierce and free, and always danceable. The buzzing rhythmic attack of the Mozambican xylophone (timbila) and the hypnot &lt;br /&gt;

 ic thrumming of Zimbabwean thumb piano (mbira) join with the sting of guitar in grooves that are deeply funky, and an alluring bed for vocals that are sweet, sassy and feminine, and harmonized in celestial English, Chopi and Shona. No other band in the world sounds like Timbila!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;....and we all know about what Atlas Soul will bring :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet in the lobby at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be an epic show, Atlas Soul show at 7:30pm, and Timbila show starts at 10pm. Combo tix available for $22 at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2776" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.getshowtix.com/regattabar/moreinfo.cgi?id=2776&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For group seating, go ahead and buy your ticket as soon as you can, but then email me (Kenny) your full name, so I can add you to the list to submit to Regattabar, so they can seat us together. Email me by Wed., 1/16 to get on the group seating list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual, if people are up for it, we can meet afterward nearby in Harvard Sq for food/drinks/conversation. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kenny Hyde</member_name><member_id>11634784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358995646000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355287865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atlas Soul and Timbila at Regattabar</name><id>95042372</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358640000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/95042372/</event_url></item>