<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Charter Oak Landing </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.758861</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-665-9428</phone><name>HARTFORD BELLE</name><city>Hartford </city><id>970084</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.670011</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.5</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA’S SINGLES EVENTS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOSTED BY THE IRA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROUDLY PRESENTS THE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2ND ANNUAL &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HARTFORD BELLE RIVER BOAT &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CRUISE HAPPY HOUR  ( For Singles Only) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LET’S GET SO HAPPY ON THE WATER &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No Worries- There are plenty of Life Jackets)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And than afterwards, we are  heading over to the&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chowder Pot in Hartford&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING MORE HAPPY ON LAND&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; And the Party continues with Dancing/Song/Cocktails &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS WILL BE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ONE GREAT EVENING TO LOOK FORWARD TO &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(See Pictures from last year’s Cruise at:  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/photos/637394/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HARTFORD BELLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date:        Friday,  June 11 2010. Exclusive for The Ira’s  Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time:       6:00PM- 8:00PM on the Beautiful Connecticut River&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Arrival Time:  Please be at the Ship between 5:30: 5:45. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our ship will be at: Charter Oak Landing located on Reserve Road. Our dock is by the gazebo,  (Directions Below)   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost:  $26.50   For the Two Hour Narrated River Boat  Cruise. Plus   One FREE  Drink Ticket: Wine, Beer, Mixed Cocktail, Plus  Dry Munchies. ( Unless we sink, the Dry Munchies will become Wet Munchies, Lol. ) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD:  We can bring our own food aboard…….. Please be creative, and bring to share…….. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facts on the Booze: Mixed drinks $6.00, beer &amp;amp; wine  $5.00, soda/juice $2.00, water $1.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that due to space limitations we are limited to our &amp;quot;house brands&amp;quot;.  We do pour premium brands.  Just a note in case you have any &amp;quot;sophisticated&amp;quot; drinkers....not to cause any alarm..  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min and Max Details:  We need to have a minimum of 25 Happy Singles to have the boat leave,,,,,,No more than 40, unless we want to use our life jackets………&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My Motto: COME ALONE, BUT, NEVER FEEL ALONE. WARM AND FRIENDLY INTRODUTIONS TO ALL. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BASED ON LAST YEAR SELL OUT CROWD, DO ACT FAST TO SECURE YOU SPOT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Information: May 30. Sunday. All Payments of 26.50 Via Pay Pal or Check must be in house.  After this date, if there are openings, $31.50. Please let me know if you are joining, so I may send to you a Pay Pal Request. All that is needed is your email address for the above. Please send to: mistrchrming@aol.com. Subject Line: June 11. Riverboat Cruise. Questions- 860-604-5792. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or Shin the Ship Leaves. They have an area that is fully covered. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS AND OTHER INFO:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Brainard Rd/Airport Rd. exit off I 91 or Rt 5 &amp;amp; 15. (Chowder Pot Restaurant).  Left on Brainard Rd.  and follow about 3/4 mile to light.  Left on Reserve Rd. (pass Regional Market).  Entrance to Charter Oak Landing is on right at RR Crossing,  just under the Charter Oak Bridge.  Our dock is by the gazebo,  Ample free parking.   See our website at www.hartfordbelle.com for complete directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Hartford Belle&amp;quot; is a beautiful 49-passenger riverboat - reminiscent&lt;br /&gt;of simpler times. She has a mahogany-trimmed enclosed cabin, but we &lt;br /&gt;like to keep the windows open to enjoy the warm summer breezes. &lt;br /&gt;A full bar is available to serve your favorite drinks and light snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is ample seating or you can stand on the bow to get the best views&lt;br /&gt;of your trip along the majestic Connecticut River. It is not uncommon to &lt;br /&gt;see great blue herons, red-tailed hawks and an occasional bald eagle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave Moran of the Hartford Courant said &amp;quot;This was a different part of Connecticut's capital city, even a different aspect of life, than I &lt;br /&gt;was used to seeing...&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Large River Boat. Signs. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1276359054000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269808492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira. Happy Hour on the Water and Land. Hartford Belle/Chowder Pot. </name><id>13016559</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276292700000</time><rsvp_limit>42</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/13016559/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/4/global_13967940.jpeg</photo_url></item>