<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Durkee Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.525336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-263-7165</phone><name>Bobby's Ranch</name><city>Westford</city><id>985659</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431796</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let's get out into nature and ride the scenic trails on horseback.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bobby's Ranch in Westford has a vast trail system offering scenic views of the woods, rivers and &lt;br /&gt;a pond. They ride through narrow trails and wide open spaces and often see wildlife.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ever been horseback riding?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry - they'll offer a variety of experiences if we have a group with different level riders.  Beginners will go for a slow guided walk through the trails, and people who have ridden before will have the opportunity to trot and canter if they desire.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; It will be $35 per person for a one hour trail ride&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Plan:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9am - meet in the Boston area (place TBD) to get into a couple vehicles to carpool to Westford.  (it's about a 45 minute drive)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10am - arrive at Bobby's Ranch, get an orientation, choose a horse and saddle up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:30am - go for a one hour trail ride&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30am - pack up and find a place to have some lunch on the way back&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Long jeans/pants - NO SHORTS&lt;br /&gt;- A hat&lt;br /&gt;- Sunblock&lt;br /&gt;- Cowboy boots are best, but sneakers are OK &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP's&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are limited to 14 people and will need to finalize the Thursday before, so there will be no waiting list.&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP you'll see a question about whether you're willing to be a driver and how many your car fits.  I'll drive one car and I can carry 5 people comfortably in my SUV.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the Boston area and then carpool.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stacy Goodman</member_name><member_id>3216337</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275778667000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Couples</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostoncouplesmeetup</urlname><id>1053816</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Couples Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271083467000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Horseback Riding at Bobby's Ranch in Westford</name><id>13158218</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1275224400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncouplesmeetup/events/13158218/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/c/global_14330604.jpeg</photo_url></item>