<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me for Billy Wilder’s 1948 black romantic comedy with political overtones still relevant for today -- &lt;i&gt;A Foreign Affair&lt;/i&gt;.  A &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; Critics’ Pick and listed as one of &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/pages/%u201CThe_Best_1%2C000_Movies_Ever_Made%2C%u201D"&gt;“The Best 1,000 Movies Ever Made,”&lt;/a&gt; this is a film you don’t want to miss!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Writer/director Billy Wilder (in collaboration with producer/writer Charles Brackett) earned his first critical condemnation with &lt;i&gt;A Foreign Affair&lt;/i&gt;. Reviewers accused Wilder (as they would so often in the future) of moral bankruptcy, challenging him to prove what could possibly be funny about the Nazi war guilt, the bombed-out city of Berlin, the postwar European black market or attempted suicide. All of these elements are in &lt;i&gt;Foreign Affair&lt;/i&gt;, and all are very funny. John Lund is an American army captain carrying on a casual affair with Berlin songstress Marlene Dietrich, who accepts Lund's attentions so long as there are contraband cigarettes and nylons added to the bargain. Iowa congresswoman Jean Arthur is sent as part of an American fact-finding delegation to Berlin, and Lund is compelled to clean up his act--or at least pretend to. Despite her initial shock at the corruption all around her, straitlaced Arthur eventually falls for Lund, but Dietrich has been at this game a lot longer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read the original 1948 review at: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?res=9D01E7D81230E23ABC4953DFB1668383659EDE"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it’s off for a quick bite to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236576985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Foreign Affair</name><id>9913289</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237503600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9913289/</event_url></item>