<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Lee Circle</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03038</zip><lat>42.910095</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Layon Residence</name><city>Derry</city><id>3585142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.259384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NOTE PLEASE BRING UNDECIDED VOTERS TO THIS! DERRY SKYDIVERS TO PRESENT PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE RON PAUL, HOUSE SPEAKER O&amp;amp;acirc;&amp;#128;&amp;#153;BRIEN 9/29/2011 6 p.m. Undecided Republican presidential voters, please come to an evening garden party hosted by Michael &amp;amp; Erica Layon at 1 Lee Circle in Derry. Light snacks will be available. Starting at 6 p.m. with an aerial display from skydivers jumping into a residential yard, the event will feature speeches and a Q&amp;amp;A with Presidential candidate Ron Paul, House Speaker Bill O'Brien and State Rep. Andrew J. Manuse. SKYDIVERS TO PRESENT PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE RON PAUL, HOUSE SPEAKER OBRIEN Leap for Liberty event will feature speeches from New Hampshire reps. and a Q&amp;amp;A with Dr. Paul DERRY, N.H.Skydivers will jump from a helicopter over Derry on Sept. 29 for an aerial display and then land in a residential yard, highlighting a special question-and-answer session about the future of the nation with Presidential Candidate Ron Paul. Derry homeowners Michael and Erica Layon will host the Leap for Liberty garden party event at their home, hoping to attract undecided presidential primary voters from Derry and the surrounding communities to hear from Ron Paul. Dr. Layon will be among several skydivers jumping into his neighbors field, weather permitting. He will then proceed to his own property where he will introduce State Rep. Andrew J. Manuse, a Derry Republican, to begin the event. Rep. Manuse will introduce New Hampshire House Speaker William OBrien, who will summarize the economic and personal freedoms advanced by the State Legislature this year and what changes still need to be made to continue the return of common sense to a limited, affordable government. Speaker OBrien will then introduce Presidential Candidate Ron Paul, who will discuss how the nations founding principles can be restored to reinvigorate an America that supports both liberty and prosperity for all people. Following the speeches, Congressman Ron Paul will take questions and field concerns from undecided Derry-area voters with Erica Layon moderating to ensure that the top questions from those in attendance are answered in detail. To better address the areas of greatest interest, attendees will have the opportunity to fill out a brief survey upon arriving or submit questions in advance. Congressman Ron Paul, a Texas Republican and a physician by trade, is running for president in 2012. Dr. Paul is coming to Derry to garner support from New Hampshire voters in the First in the Nation Primary. The Leap for Liberty event will be specifically tailored to address the questions and concerns of undecided voters and be a fundraising-free zone. The media is welcome to attend the event for local coverage. Leap for Liberty will begin at 6 p.m. on Thursday, Sept. 29, at 1 Lee Circle in Derry, N.H., with skydivers dropping from a helicopter, followed by speeches from state representatives and a question-and-answer session with Presidential Candidate Ron Paul. The skydiving jump and aerial display will only take place with good weather, but the event will commence rain or shine. Those who expect to attend are asked to R.S.V.P. with Erica and Michael Layon by calling 603-470-9464 or by checking-in at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=249914521720106" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook....&lt;/a&gt;. To get to Michael and Erica Layons home, take Rte. 102 from Exit 4 off I-93 to the Derry traffic circle and then follow Hampstead Road out to East Derry. Take a left on Adams Pond Road, a right Walnut Hill Road, a left on Halls Village Road and then a left on Lee Circle. The Layons home is the first on the right. Park on the side of the street. Address The home of Michael and Erica Layon 1 Lee Circle Derry, NH 03038 Contact Erica Layon ericalayon@me.com 603-470-9464&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317337869000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316467049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ask Ron Paul, with Leap for Liberty</name><id>34173612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317333600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/34173612/</event_url></item>