<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Audubon Way</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03032</zip><lat>42.983557</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 668-2045</phone><name>Massabesic Audubon Center</name><city>Auburn </city><id>762116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.365221</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lake Massabesic is a great place for low intensity hiking.  Some of you will remember we did snowshoeing here last winter.  We will start at the Audubon Center off Spofford Road and head to Battery Point where there should still be colorful foliage.  The trails are easy with a small section moderate.  Round trip from the Audubon to Battery Point is 2 1/2 miles.  As an option, if everyone is willing, we can take a side trail to the Osprey Viewing Hut that adds about 1/2 mile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you bring your dog, the Audubon asks that you do not bring the dogs through the fields behind the center.  At the parking lot you can go a short distance to the end of the road and enter the trails there or, there is a fire road gate on Spofford Rd that also accesses the trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;NH RT 93 North to exit 5 State Hwy 28 (Rockingham RD)&lt;br /&gt;Take a right at the end of ramp&lt;br /&gt;go 300 feet and take a left turn onto Auburn Road (by the Poor Boy Restaurant)&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles then continue on Beaver Brook Rd&lt;br /&gt;Turn left at Londonderry Turnpike (By-Pass 28)&lt;br /&gt;go 2.6 miles and right turn at Spofford Rd&lt;br /&gt;Aububon Way is on the left, we will meet at the NH Aububon Lake Massabesic Audubon Center&lt;br /&gt;26 Audubon Way&lt;br /&gt;Auburn, NH 03032&lt;br /&gt;603-668-2045&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For early birds, I will be at the Ye Old Post Restaurant at 8:45am for what I consider to be the best breakfast in Southern NH.  It's a small restaurant that I frequented when I lived here in the area, they should have room at this time of the morning.  If I get many responses I will call to make sure they can accommodate us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Ye Old Post Restaurant in Chester, NH:&lt;br /&gt;NH RT 93 to exit 4, State Hwy 102&lt;br /&gt;East on RT 102 toward Derry&lt;br /&gt;Travel three miles and at the traffic circle, take the 3rd right off the circle, Chester Rd, (this is a continuation of RT 102 East)&lt;br /&gt;Continue to follow RT 102 6 miles from the traffic circle and at the intersection of RT102 and RT 121 (blinking yellow light) take a left&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Ye Olde Post&amp;quot; is on the left next to the hardware store.&lt;br /&gt;We will be 15 min. to Lake Massabesic from there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1256249982000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254492566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lake Massabesic Auburn, NH/ Ye Old Post Restaurnat</name><id>11528537</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255788000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11528537/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/b/global_11010795.jpeg</photo_url></item>