<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Macy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01913</zip><lat>42.846649</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>CarriageTown Marketplace</name><city>Amesbury</city><id>13510152</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.913300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Host: Claire P cell 603-247-0897 &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT &lt;br /&gt;

 Weather pending, I plan on checking out a number of rail trails on the coast. There are four short trails in the three coastal towns of Salisbury, Amesbury and Newburyport MA. I would like to bike and walk some of the trails. &lt;br /&gt;

 The first trail to bike would be the Amesbury Pow Wow River Walk which is 1.3 miles, then we would drive to get to the Salisbury Point Ghost Trail which is 1.8 miles then we would drive to Salisbury Eastern Marsh Rail Trail which is 1.4 miles, then off we would go to finish the afternoon by walking or biking (depends on how long we took for the other trails) with the Newburyport Clipper City Rail Trail which is 1.1 miles and has beautiful sculptures to view. &lt;br /&gt;

 1) AMESBURY’S POW WOW RIVERWALK: The Pow Wow Riverwalk in Amesbury, MA, is a paved 1.3 mile trail that will accommodate wheelchairs, in-line skates and handicap scooters. &lt;br /&gt;

 It begins at the Carriagetown Marketplace (Stop &amp;amp; Shop) on Route 110 (GPS use 100 Macy St Amesbury MA). It runs all the way to downtown Amesbury ending at the parking garage on Water Street. &lt;br /&gt;

 2) SALISBURY POINT GHOST TRAIL: Currently 1.8 miles, the Salisbury Point Ghost Trail provides a peaceful walk or bike ride through the woods on a very well-maintained stone-dust trail. Sharing railroad history with the Amesbury Riverwalk, the Salisbury Point Ghost Trail got its name because the train cars transported carriages and early auto bodies covered with white muslin shrouds. The trains passed through Salisbury with their "ghostly" freight on their way to Boston, Detroit and New York. Passenger service was also popular on the Salisbury rail line, and people could travel throughout New England, or even make a transcontinental journey from Salisbury. In 1936 passenger service was discontinued. This entrance to the Ghost Trail is on Bartlett Street. This street is next to the Dairy Queen on Elm Street/Route 110. &lt;br /&gt;

 3) SALISBURY EASTERN MARSH RAIL TRAIL: This 1.4 mile paved trail extends from the Merrimack River to Mudnock Road. It passes through the Great Marsh with wonderful views the marsh with a newly constructed bridge over Town Creek. Use the parking area on Friedenfels Street just before the Newburyport Bridge on Route 1. &lt;br /&gt;

 4) NEWBURYPORT’S CLIPPER CITY RAIL TRAIL: The Clipper City Rail Trail was completed in 2010, and is a 1.1 mile multi-use pathway running between the Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (MBTA) commuter rail station and the shoreline of the Merrimack River near downtown Newburyport. &lt;br /&gt;

 See link for more information &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.seabrookrailtrail.org/neighbors" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.seabrookrailtrail.org/neighbors&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I recommend Hybrid or Mountain bikes since not all trails are paved. You should also have a helmet, dress in layers for comfort, bring plenty of fluids and snacks and wear sunscreen. &lt;br /&gt;

 After all of this hopping around, let’s plan on having dinner at one of the restaurants in the area. &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no need to RSVP no. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 DRIVING DIRECTIONS FROM BIKE TRAIL TO BIKE TRAILS: &lt;br /&gt;

 The Amesbury Pow Wow trail is located at the Carriagetown Marketplace 100 Macy St (Route 110), from this trail we will go to the paking at Bartlett St in Salisbury. Head west on Macy St to Rocky Hill Rd (397 ft), turn right onto Rocky Hill (0.3 mi), turn left on MA 110 E/Macy St (1.5 mi), turn left on Bartlett St. Then after our ride there we will then go to the parking area at Friedenfels Street. Head south on Bartlet St take left on Elm St (Rte 110) (0.8 mi) continue on to School St (397 ft), turn right onto Bridge St (Rte 1 &amp;amp; 1A) (1.6 mi) turn right onto Friedenfels St. And from there we will drive to Newburyport MBTA lot located at 25 Boston Way off of Parker St. Head back to Route 1 &amp;amp; 1A, take right onto Newburyport Turnpike (Rte 1 &amp;amp; 1A) (1.3 mi), turn right onto Hill St (331 ft), turn right onto Parker St (459 ft), and take first left onto Boston Way (0.2 mi). Let’s meet in the lot by the trailhead. &lt;br /&gt;

 Liability Release - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claire P</member_name><member_id>7906902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369512602000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368972163000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easy biking and hiking at the seacoast</name><id>120131832</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369501200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/120131832/</event_url></item>