<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hello This is Anthony J Pasquale and Mike Sobus teamed&amp;nbsp;up to create a new Business Networking Luncheon Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will reserve time to Network before and after this meetup. You bring your lunch and notebook, and we will have guest speakers here to pass on what we are calling "The One Big Thing" that you can work on for a lenth of time each month that will generate a result in your business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mike Sobus,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over 28 years as a successful business executive with proven experience in marketing, sales, team leadership, management, training, product development, HR, business startups and business turnarounds. Managed multi-million dollar customers including, GE, Miller Brewing, Abbott, Asahi. SAB, and DuPont to name a few and opened new $multi-million markets in Japan, Korea, South Africa, and Eastern Europe including Hungary and Bulgaria. Managed new product development and market roll out of $7 million beverage additive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Anthony J Pasquale,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;24 Years experience as a leadership speaker and entrepenuer. Anthony and his wife Rita Rose have&amp;nbsp;owned multiple successful businesses. A Successful Motivational speaker through the Mindful Wealth Group one of the businesses&amp;nbsp;being AJP Enterprise (A Mindful Wealth Group) and&amp;nbsp;DITR/SIFU Real Estate Partnership&amp;nbsp;and also has string of online franchises through SHOP.com. He and this wife also run a very successful martila arts school in Danvers Mass.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Come join us for this ongoing Bussiness Netwotrking Luncheon the second Wednesday of every month.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ready to Learn "The One Big Thing For This Month!"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328795590000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs,Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1824</urlname><id>1133728</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>The NorthShore Business Support Network meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323783121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northshore Business BYOLN  (Bring Your own Lunch Networking)</name><id>qfnrccyqdblb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328721300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1824/events/44307012/</event_url></item>