<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3260 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02631</zip><lat>41.773640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cobie's</name><city>Brewster</city><id>1629991</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.038864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We will meet at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cobie's Clam Shack&lt;/strong&gt;, located on Cape Cod in Brewster, Massachusetts, has been a Cape Cod tradition since 1948. Cobies serves fried clams, fried seafood, burgers, hot dogs, french fries and ice cream. Cobies Restaurant is located right off 6A and the Cape Cod rail trail, easily accessible to cyclists, motorists, and tourists. &lt;br /&gt;3260 Main St | Brewster, MA | (508) 896-7021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then go to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brewster Ladies Library for a Free talk by Joan Anderson &lt;/strong&gt;author of A Year by the Sea. She will be talking about "Writing Your Own Story".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a bit about Joan Anderson's book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Curling up with this autobiography will refresh readers' souls and adjust their attitudes. With their two sons grown and married, Anderson and her husband decided to take a "vacation" from their long marriage. Her husband moved on to a new job hundreds of miles away, while Anderson cocooned herself in her rusting Volvo and drove to her family's cottage on Cape Cod. During the year-long separation, Anderson reestablished her connection to nature and was able to discover new hope. She swam with seals, ran a marathon, worked in a fish market, and earned extra income clammingAactivities that gave her the opportunity to shed her image as family nurturer and allowed her to grow as an independent woman. After a Memorial Day reunion, her husband retired from his job to live with Anderson on Cape Cod. Anderson's story reminds readers not to overlook their personal needs when providing for family members. This is a good choice for discussion and a companion piece to Anne Morrow Lindbergh's classic Gift from the Sea.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barbara will be wearing her Girls Just Wanna Have Fun Pin!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310410276000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We want to learn more about ourselves as interesting, strong, talented and independent women!</why><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304284385000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lite Bite and Self Help Talk (Writing your own story) Joan Anderson (Free!)</name><id>17502249</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310074200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/17502249/</event_url></item>