<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you ever wanted to know what it felt like to be a Knight or Warrior Princess?  If so this event is for you!  During this afternoon of play we will learn how to sword fight and then our adventure will beginning....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brawl at the Ball  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is invited to a one of a kind ball. Bored with how most fancy-smancy balls are normally conducted, we have added our own twist...sword combat! Ice-breaker games, open combat against everyone, and a team game to compete to win the favor of the King and Queen of the Ball. Nothing livens up a party like an excuse to &amp;quot;cut&amp;quot; loose. Join us at the Brawl Ball '09  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be playing from 3:30 to 5:30.....  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After our brawl is complete we will head over to Lesters Roadside BBQ for a buffet of authentic southern bbq.  This will be listed as a separate event so if you want to join us you need to sign up for that as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a prepay event since I will need to pay for this in advance and the Cost will be $25. Since the cost is partially determined by the number of people who sign up if we have extra funds you will be issued a refund in cash on the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you pay via check it can be mailed to us at the following address:  &lt;br /&gt;The Fun Singles   &lt;br /&gt;P.O. Box 1382  &lt;br /&gt;Westford, MA 01886  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you choose to pay online there will be a small fee so the price will be $26.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can also choose to pay us directly if you see us at an event.  If you choose to do that please put the payment in an envelope marked with your name and the name of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One last note: If we have not received your payment 3 days before the event we will need to change your RSVP to a No.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judie</member_name><member_id>5431837</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281130664000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237926270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swordplay for all you "Knights" and "Warrior Princess" wannabe's...</name><id>10026496</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240772400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/10026496/</event_url></item>