<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>187 Podunk Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03275</zip><lat>43.096092</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Hall Mountain Parking Lot just before</name><city>Candia</city><id>3990812</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.342980</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/8/8/event_63513672.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/1/8/event_63514072.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/8/6/event_63514182.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Podunk Road starts off of North Road very near to this mailbox for 672 North Road, Candia, NH. Once on Podunk Road proceed 0.8 miles to the sign for the parking lot. &amp;nbsp;At 0.6 miles Podunk Road intersects with Currier Road. and becomes a dirt road for the last 0.2 miles to the parking lot sign. The parking lot will be on the left side of Podunk Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting at the Hall Mountain Trailhead Parking Lot we will hike to the start of the upper Lynx Trail (750') and descend 250' to the lower end of the Lynx Trail (500') where it intersects with the Beaver Pond Trail. We will then hike around Beaver Pond doing a relatively flat 2 mile loop (there is still some uphill and downhill). We will then hike back up the Lynx Trail to our starting point ascending 250'. The Lynx Trail is 1.3 miles long so the total hiking distance is about 5 miles as the Lynx Trail doesn't start at the parking lot. Our starting point is a "back entrance" into the park.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Check out the first 6 pictures in the photo album of the broken or missing planks Christine's comment was talking about. &amp;nbsp;When I checked out the Beaver Pond Loop Kaitlyn had not trouble with the holes what so ever. &amp;nbsp;But &amp;nbsp;decide for yourself. &amp;nbsp;Depending on what the group decides we can avoid that part of the trail and hike around only half of the pond. &amp;nbsp;The parks department has still not answered my email about when it would be fixed..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will park in the Hall Mountain Parking Lot which is 0.8 miles from the start of Podunk Road off of North Road.  The parking lot is just 0.2 miles past where Podunk Road and Currier Road intersect and Podunk becomes a dirt road.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321721542000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318630324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bear Brook State Park -  Lynx Trail and Beaver Pond Trail (5 miles)</name><id>37431822</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321110000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/37431822/</event_url></item>