<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Central Connecticut Drupal Meetup Group will be meeting to create a resource to help grow Connecticut's Drupal community. Come meet fellow Drupalists, come learn what Drupal can do for you and the best practices to apply when using Drupal, and come help steer our group to become an invaluable source of information and networking opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: Introductions, User Presentations, Sharing of Needs and Resources, and Organization of the Group&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Tuesday, March 16th, 7:00pm to 9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: University of Connecticut Law School, Library 202 *, Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * When entering the library, you will find yourself on the 3rd floor, so you will need to go down one floor to find the meeting room. A map and directions to the campus are online at &lt;a href="http://www.law.uconn.edu/content/map-school-law-campus" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.law.uconn....&lt;/a&gt;. A map of the second floor of the library is online at &lt;a href="http://www.law.uconn.edu/school-law-library/information-policies-and-pro..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.law.uconn....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;User Presentations:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anne Murray-Randolph is the Assistant Vice President of Communication and Strategic Projects at Yale University. She will talk about SimpleSite, a front-end Drupal application developed at Yale, that makes Drupal so easy to set up and use that an administrative assistant can do so – through the selection of established feature sets (versus modules), themes, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aldon Hynes is an independent consultant who has helped various organizations use Drupal as part of their online social media outreach. Starting with his work on DeanSpace in 2003 and leading up to the current day, he will explore how individuals and organizations can use Drupal in conjunction with other social media tools to get their message out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Drupal:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drupal (drupal.org) is a powerful, free and open source content management system (CMS) that allows an individual or a community of users to easily publish, manage and organize a wide variety of content on a website. Tens of thousands of people and organizations are using Drupal to power scores of different websites, ranging from small personal blogs to large corporate and political sites, including whitehouse.gov and data.gov.uk. Drupal is used for ecommerce, podcasting and photo galleries, social networking sites, knowledge management, business collaboration and much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.drupal.org/node/53948" target="_blank"&gt;More info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dr. Mark A. Friedman</member_name><member_id>6940951</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268953456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268409743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Central Connecticut Drupal Group</name><id>12858579</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268780400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/12858579/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/a/b/global_11475755.jpeg</photo_url></item>