<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>From I-93 exit 32, follow NH Route 112 W about 6.7 miles to Kinsman Notch, parking area on L </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03262</zip><lat>44.040096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kinsman Notch Trailhead</name><city>North Woodstock</city><id>1939491</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.791534</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we doing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Like National Trails Day that is in June, National Public Lands Day brings awareness to trails and thanks many people and partners for their support and hard work, including volunteers, land agencies, and outdoor minded businesses. It is also a day to introduce people to the many joys and benefits of trails.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Let's join in celebrating National Public Lands Day by doing some trail maintenace on our adopted section of the&amp;nbsp;historic 2,175-mile long&amp;nbsp;Appalachian Trail - the 3.3 mile section of the Kinsman Ridge Trail from Route 112 to Gordon Pond.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to spend about 5 hours out on the trail - at the most we would be hiking about 6.6 miles round trip but would likely do much less since we will be stopping to perform trail maintenance activities along the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/a/c/9/event_23199625.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. &amp;nbsp;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it&amp;nbsp;prior&amp;nbsp;to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Sturdy hiking boots.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Long sleeved shirts, long pants and leather work gloves. Cotton clothing for this trip is OK. Safety glasses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: You should also bring weather appropriate clothing since we will be working on the trails rain or shine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Plastic whistle. Personal first aid kit. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack. Extra socks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;: Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Some interesting information from&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Jim Schmid's "&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.americantrails.org/resources/info/tools1.html"&gt;compendium of trail tools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;These are the tools that we will be using:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loppers:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Loppers are designed for clearing heavy vegetation from trails. With their long handles, a sturdy pair of loppers has the mechanical advantage to cut cleanly through all sorts of brush and branches (most cut limbs of 1 to 1-1/2 inches in diameter).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hand Pruner:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Handier and lighter to carry than a lopper when only minor pruning is needed. Used to cut small branches encroaching on the trail. Also useful for cutting protruding roots that are tripping hazards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bow Saw:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A bow saw with a blade 16- to 21-inches in length is handy for cutting brush out of the trail and trimming small branches.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Axe:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Axes can be used to chop deadfall from trails, shape stakes for turnpikes and waterbars, and cut notches for structures made of timber. The axe is best reserved for cutting jobs too thick for available saws.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pick Mattock:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A mattock is a heavy sturdy grubbing tool with an adz blade that can be used as a hoe for digging in hard ground. The other blade of a mattock may be a pick (pick mattock) for breaking or prying small rocks or a cutting edge (cutter mattock) for chopping roots.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.061686270356724&amp;amp;lon=-71.76741600036621&amp;amp;site=gyx&amp;amp;unit=0&amp;amp;lg=en&amp;amp;FcstType=text"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will begin this event by meeting in the parking area on the southwest side of Route 112 at 9:00 AM. &amp;nbsp;According to Google Maps this meeting spot is about 140 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 40 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=44.040808,-71.791763(Kinsman+Ridge+Trailhead+%5Bsouth%5D)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFWgCoAIdbYu4-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=44.040808,-71.791763&amp;amp;sspn=0.009008,0.013797&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; the link below for driving directions to the meeting spot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351730291000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332107608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Public Lands Day Work Party on our Adopted Trail</name><id>56868192</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348923600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/56868192/</event_url></item>