<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362095</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kendall Press</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1523815</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079887</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us in April when our very own Jon Gosselin presents The Art of Influencing Consumer Behavior. Join Jon, Innovator For Change, as he discusses what it takes to faster press the "why they'll buy" hot buttons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon has been a BIMM member since August 2011 and he is both a very experienced and sophisticated Internet marketer. Those of you who know him know that you can expect an informative presentation and a spirited discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He will talk about the need to be more fascinating from a buyer's perspective and will share tools and techniques for syndicating your specific value-adds and help us understand and measure the all-important measurements for the success of your actions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon is a Director of TheAllyAdvertisingGroup.com a multi-media marketing company. Their primary focus is in helping local business owners utilize various tools of technology to automate customer acquisition and retention, while simultaneously implementing referral marketing strategies that significantly cut the cost of new business acquisition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find more background on the Team Ally Advertising Group here &lt;a href="http://www.theallyadvertisinggroup.com/meet-team-aag/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.theallyadvertisinggroup.com/meet-team-aag/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope you'll join us for this informative and spirited evening&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Keith</member_name><member_id>12427891</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365770528000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup</urlname><id>1506882</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>Boston Internet Marketing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362791820000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Art of Influencing Consumer Behavior</name><id>108357642</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365634800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Internet-Marketing-Meetup/events/108357642/</event_url></item>