<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Zero Harvard Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Out Of Town News</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12557432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120163</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;What: A demo against Harvard for the International Day of Mourning for Animals in Laboratories &lt;br /&gt;

 When: Sunday, May 26th, from 1:00-3:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Where: At the Out of Town Newsstand in Harvard Square.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring: Your Own Fruit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a day of mourning, but we are choosing to try and convince Harvard to release the primates they have to sanctuaries versus other laboratories. There have been 4 primate deaths in their laboratories so we will definitely be in mourning as well. We have a great victory with the closing of their primate lab. &lt;span&gt;Let us win another battle by convincing Harvard to do the right, and humane thing, to release their primates to sanctuaries! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Be sure to wear your best mourning clothes. A simple black tee shirt and pants will do. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 All signs, and posters will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please review the below link on how to be the model protester: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www2.peta.org/site/R?i=4KM0ytmgiSECDKAznWudHA" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www2.peta.org/site/&lt;/span&gt;R?i=4KM0ytmgiSECDKAznWudHA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please see the article below that was in the Boston Globe for our last demo. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Animal rights group to protest at Harvard Saturday &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 By Brad Petrishen, Daily News, Friday, April 26, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An Ohio-based animal rights group will protest at Harvard University Saturday, demanding that the school relocate the monkeys from its Primate Research Center in Southborough to sanctuaries. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 “Due to Harvard’s negligence, Harvard’s profiteering from primate experimentation, and the pain and suffering inflicted on primates by Harvard, Harvard has an obligation to release these victims and provide for their care,” Michael Budkie, executive director of Stop Animal Exploitation Now! wrote in a letter to the school. “The primates who have already suffered so much at Harvard’s Southborough facility will now endure additional agony through further experimentation is simply unacceptable. These primates deserve a future free from any future pain, suffering, deprivation, or neglect.” &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Harvard announced earlier this week it plans to shutter the facility, which the federal government was investigating following the deaths of four monkeys in the last several years. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 School officials have said the approximately 2,000 primates there will be transferred to other research facilities. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Budkie’s organization is demanding the school instead pay to release all the primates to sanctuaries and pay for their lifetime care. The protest will be held at 1:30 p.m. at Harvard Square in Boston, Budkie said. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 “It is clear that Harvard has received hundreds of millions of dollars for primate experimentation over the years,” Budkie wrote. “Harvard’s profits from primate exploitation have been monumental, and so Harvard’s bill has now come due.” &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 See also: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Harvard Medical School, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 Harvard Announces Closure of Primate Research Center; Watchdog Group Applauds Move; Calls for Retirement of Primates &lt;br /&gt;

 Press Release&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://fbcdn-sphotos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash4/260384_10151367830187703_1144064190_n.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/f/8/event_235640472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for people holding signs and wearing black. :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</member_name><member_id>55605982</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369594925000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368691889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvard Demo &amp; Fruitnic</name><id>119666852</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369587600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/119666852/</event_url></item>