<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;THIS EVENT IS HAPPENING IN MANCHESTER&amp;nbsp; address to be annouced to rsvps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be getting together at a members house to learn the ways of Authentic Indian Cuisine. This will be a limited engagement. Our host has graciously offered to cook and to show anyone who's interested , how to do it themselves.. and promises to get everyone "involved" in the cooking process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neha will begin cooking at 5. Anyone who is interested in really watching learning can come at that point. Everyone else is encouraged to&amp;nbsp;arrive closer to 7pm when the cooking will be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the menu:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Appetizer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samosa: this consists of a fried triangular pastry shell with a savory filling, which includes spiced potatoes, onions, peas, and coriander. This will be served with green and brown chutney&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entr&amp;eacute;e:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Channa Bhatura: it's a mouth watering dish. Chole Bhatura is a fried puffy bread made out of All purpose flour.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s usually served along with channa masala, a spicy and tangy chickpea dish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vegetable Biryani: is a rich and exotic rice dish with spicy vegetables. The saffron aroma makes this dish very inviting. Biryani is a popular Mughali dish that has been adapted by Indians. Vegetable Biryani makes a great dish for a formal dinner or can be served as main meal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dessert:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payasam: is a rice pudding, which is a traditional South Asian sweet dish. It is made by boiling rice or broken wheat with milk and sugar, and flavored with cardamom, raisins, saffron, cashew nuts, pistachios or almonds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the number of people RSVPing I can increase the number of &amp;nbsp;dishes. Do let me know if you are allergic to anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And&amp;nbsp;yes, its going to be a BYOB event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brett</member_name><member_id>6413149</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neha</member_name><member_id>6552224</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320883633000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319074887000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enjoy Home Cooked Authentic Indian Cuisine</name><id>38040822</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320526800000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/38040822/</event_url></item>