<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>291 Gray Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04105</zip><lat>43.764313</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Winslow Farm</name><city>Falmouth</city><id>452535</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.296715</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The Winter Cache Project hosts a weekly work party at their farm plot at Winslow Farm on Route 100 in West Falmouth. &amp;nbsp;All are invited to join for all or part of the weekly work party from 10am to 2pm. &amp;nbsp;Bring a water bottle and lunch as well as "dress for the weather and the work." &amp;nbsp;Bring&amp;nbsp;farm tools if you have any, work gloves and (if it's wet) rubber boots.&amp;nbsp; Car pool leaves from the parking lot behind Local Sprouts @8:45 am every Sunday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Sue McCormick from this meetup is also active in Winter Cache and will be able to update these recurring events with any date-specific details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More About Winter Cache:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mission:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;

&amp;nbsp;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The mission of the Winter Cache Project (WCP) is to free ourselves from a dependence on industrial agriculture and to increase our community food security by developing sustainable local food systems. By growing and storing our own food to last throughout the winter and educating ourselves about agricultural issues, we aim to create a working example of how we can come together as a community to provide for our basic needs by employing the principles of mutual aid, equal access, and self-determination. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&amp;nbsp;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Goals:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increase year-round food security&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Implement sustainable agricultural practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Raise awareness around agricultural issues by educating ourselves and our community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Preserve food for the winter by storing, canning, drying, and freezing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Make nutritious, fresh food more accessible for all Portland residents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Connect as a community to provide for our own needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;What We Do:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://sites.google.com/site/wintercacheproject/_/rsrc/1270318354609/home/carrot%252520box.jpg?height=300&amp;amp;width=400" width="400" height="300" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The WCP grows, harvests, and preserves fruit, vegetables, and herbs to build a food cache for the winter months. The bulk of our cache is grown by members of the project at Pleasant Valley Acres Farm in Cumberland. Gene Weir, the farmer at Pleasant Valley Acres, allows the WCP to grow food on their land in exchange for help with tasks such as planting, weeding, harvesting, and cleaning out the goat barn. The WCP also participates in work-trade relationships with other local farmers--exchanging labor for an opportunity to glean their fields.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;The majority of the work is accomplished during Sunday work parties from April to November. Work parties serve a dual purpose: first, to carry out the necessary labor to grow our own food, and second, to build community and share knowledge with neighbors and friends. At the end of October, many vegetables, such as potatoes, onions, carrots, cabbage, and squash, are put into storage in a basement root cellar in Portland. This food is then re-distributed to project volunteers on a bi-weekly basis throughout the winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The second major component of the WCP is our educational campaign. We offer workshops throughout the harvesting season for community members to teach each others how to preserve food in various ways, including canning, freezing, and drying. Educational events feature speakers, panel discussions, and educational videos to spark discussion around food security, sustainable agriculture, and social justice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/wintercacheproject/home"&gt;Winter Cache Web Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sue McCormick</member_name><member_id>3284483</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314544473000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306336883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Cache Weekly Work Party</name><id>pwqcsyplblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314540000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/30226321/</event_url></item>