<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 100</address_2><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360794</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>857-453.6000</phone><name>Microsoft New England Research &amp; Development Center (NERD)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1054297</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>6:30-7:00pm - Food and Socializing&lt;br /&gt;7:00-8:00pm - Presentation&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by Friday Nov 5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have all heard that the best developers are lazy. But what does that really mean? One thing that is clear is that good developers are able to accomplish more by doing less. Many development teams tell us they end up spending lots of time doing things on wasteful tasks whose results don’t matter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their are many best practices, check lists, methodologies, processes, and tools out there. Some don’t work while, others just take a lot of work, and still others can very easily be done wrongly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vineet Sinha, Founder of Architexa, has been working with numerous teams to understand practices that work and those that have challenges. In this talk we will go through a number of simple ideas that some of the more effective coders use, and discuss some of the details of applying them to your work. Whether you are new or the most experience developer to a project, we show how most of these allow you to be more lazy and not worry about coding details all the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beyond just being an effective lazy developer, we also talk about the simple things you can do today to increase your chances of being lazy in the future. We discuss effective ways to get started with unit tests, documentation, code reviews, and many others. Vineet's talk will be interactive, and will be designed so that you can be lazier and work more on fun coding projects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vineet is the Founder (President &amp;amp; CTO) of Architexa (www.architexa.com) and is passionate about helping improve developer productivity, and has been doing so since 1999 when building tools at Microsoft.  He has more recently tackled these problems as part of his PhD work at the MIT Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Lab (CSAIL), which along with work done in collaboration with Accenture Research Labs has lead to him building a tool designed to help software developers understand, document, and collaborate about important aspects of their code. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vineet has been speaking at EclipseCon regularly since 2007, and has been building tools on Eclipse since 2003. Beyond Eclipse and using Java with Rest, ORM, Google App Engine, etc, Vineet has been working with Flex and Ruby/Rails&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292285284000</updated><rating><average>3.6400001049</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Java Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-java</urlname><id>87071</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Java Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>39</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275969408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Effective (Java) Development By Being Lazy And Staying That Way</name><id>smqtnynpbcb</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289259000000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-java/events/14688860/</event_url></item>