<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hailed by everyone from Dave Van Ronk to Doc Watson, from the Washington Post to downbeat, Dakota Dave Hull’s guitar style spans a wide musical geography to create an infectious, uniquely personal blend of jazz, ragtime, folk, blues, Western swing, and vintage pop. Dakota Dave is a restlessly curious, adventurous traveler along the broad highway of America’s music. In his playing the masters speak, but in a vocabulary that is Dave’s alone: alternatively mirthful and moving, always melodic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A gifted composer as well as a strikingly original interpreter of older tunes, Dave calls what he does “classic American guitar.” Folk legend Van Ronk called Dave “one of the best guitarists in the world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of all, Dakota Dave’s music is great fun. As Douglas Green (Ranger Doug of Riders in the Sky) puts it, “There is an imp within Dave Hull that always expresses itself on the fretboard; a witty, intelligent yet respectful imp who frolics in his music, an imp Dakota Dave neither fights nor lets take control, but simply absorbs into the heart of his style.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On stage or in the recording studio Dave has performed with Utah Phillips, Doc Watson, Robin and Linda Williams, Dave Van Ronk, John Renbourn, Paul Geremia, Spider John Koerner, Cam Waters, Sally Rogers, Butch Thompson, Peter Ostroushko, Garrison Keillor, and Norman Blake, and many others. His albums include three with early performing partner Sean Blackburn and six solo efforts (the acclaimed Hull’s Victory and Reunion Rag, both on Flying Fish) with four more, New Shirt, Sheridan Square Rag, The Loyalty Waltz and Time Machine on Arabica Records. Airship, a duo album with singer/guitarist/fiddler Pop Wagner was widely praised. His three albums with guitar and mandolin ace Kari Larson (also on Arabica) have become legendary. Most recently, Dave recorded an album of mostly traditional music duets with the noted guitarist Duck Baker, When You Ask a Girl to Leave Her Happy Home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dave is a recipient of a 2013 Traditional Arts grant from the Minnesota State Arts board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website - &lt;a href="http://www.dakotadavehull.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.dakotadavehull.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"One of the best guitarists in the world." &lt;br /&gt;

—Dave Van Ronk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Hull is something of a guitar god in his native midwest, where he's been dazzling audiences for over 30 years with his lush finger-picking and quicksilver flat-picking. He is also a sly raconteur with an encyclopedic knowledge of vintage American music." &lt;br /&gt;

—Scott Alarik, Boston Globe, March 2004&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There's a million good things I could say about Dave Hull but I'll narrow it down to two: He's an excellent picker, both flatpick and fingerstyle, he collects some fine instruments, and we've been at a lot of good places to eat together." &lt;br /&gt;

—Norman Blake&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Dakota Dave brings a modesty and tenderness to the old classics he plays - qualities that are rare among guitarists of his stature and experience." &lt;br /&gt;

—Sarah Craig, Manager, Caffe Lena, Saratoga Springs, NY, March 2004&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Hey Dave, thanks for sending me your Loyalty Waltz album. I just put it on to use as background music for something I was reading. Damn you, I never read a thing. Listened to the whole album straight through. Nice album, my good man. Keep on." &lt;br /&gt;

—Geoff Muldaur&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WORKSHOP: "The Art of Making Arrangements" workshop: $30 (less 20% JPTC members). RESERVATIONS REQUIRED. Arrive 6:30, workshop 6:45-7:45pm. &lt;br /&gt;

CONCERT: Doors 7:30, concert 8-10pm. $20 at the door, $15 in advance - email notlobreservations@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

20% discount for JPTC members &lt;br /&gt;

+ $1 preservation fee. &lt;br /&gt;

$10 discount for concert + workshop. &lt;br /&gt;

email notlobreservations at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

In your reservation request please specify you are reserving for the workshop, the concert, or both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info at the notloB website - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please sign up for our concert announcements - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee from JP Licks &lt;br /&gt;

Pastries from Fiores&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366426968000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363196345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dakota Dave Hull</name><id>109081392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366416000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/109081392/</event_url></item>