<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come join in the adventure. Living Forgotten Realms events at Pandemonium continue with three more adventures. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Table 1 &lt;br /&gt;CORE1-2 The Radiant Vessel of Thesk &lt;br /&gt;Rumors of a great item, touched by divinity, have traveled across Faerûn. Those with an interest in possessing the item and benefiting from its power have sent agents to find it, but no one seems to know what or where it is. A Living Forgotten Realms adventure set in Thesk for characters levels 1-4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Table 2&lt;br /&gt;LURU1-1 Slivers of Eaerlann&lt;br /&gt;Luruar is a haven of peace and culture surrounded by howling wilderness studded with lost ruins, hidden temples, and the lairs of foul, vicious creatures. Things that are lost, however, do not always stay so and some things hidden refuse to remain in darkness. A Living Forgotten Realms adventure set in Luruar for characters levels 1-4.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Table 3 &lt;br /&gt;MOON1-1 Nature’s Wrath &lt;br /&gt;Faith in Chauntea runs strong amongst the Ffolk, and the village of Warlsbry is no exception. The village appears to have fallen from favor, and now the beasts of field and sea bring their wrath against the village. You must return the village to the gods' good graces or it may not survive the coming winter. A Living Forgotten Realms adventure set in the Moonshae Isles for characters levels 1-4. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must provide a character based on the Character Creation rules found at &lt;a href="http://www.wizards.com/default.asp?x=rpga/news/lfrcharacters" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wizards.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Muster begins at 6 PM. Adventures begin promptly at 6:30 PM. You can only sign up for one of the adventures, and you must sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.warhorn.net/BostonLFR/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.warhorn.ne...&lt;/a&gt;  Please note that RSVPing here does not guarantee you a space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 6 players per table. Sign up for information on LFR Pandemonium games by joining our Yahoo Group at &lt;a href="http://games.groups.yahoo.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://games.groups.y...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221171038000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220450581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>More Living Forgotten Realms @ Pandemonium</name><id>8678452</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220997600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/8678452/</event_url></item>