<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>November 18, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HI! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time is really flying and our next meeting is just around the corner. My impression is that people really like the book we are now reading &amp;quot;LIVING BUDDHA, LIVING CHRIST.&amp;quot; It challenges us to widen our horizon and to let &amp;quot;mindfulness&amp;quot; guide every moment of each day: to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; beauty, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; we are walking, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; we are eating, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; we are enjoying the company of family and friends, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; music, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; creation, to &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; we are united with the Divine... &amp;quot;Mindfulness&amp;quot; points to meaning in our daily life...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since our last meeting, in my own reading, I found these lines I wish to share with you:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+ When you enter deeply into the present moment, you, too, become a living Buddha... &lt;br /&gt;+ To me mindfulness is very much like the Holy Spirit. When you are mindful, you see more deeply... and when you touch deep understanding and love, you are healed.&lt;br /&gt;+ We also have the see of the Holy Spirit in us - the capacity of healing, transforming, and loving.&lt;br /&gt;+ The most precious gift we can offer our loved ones is our true presence. &lt;br /&gt;+ Mindful speech brings real happiness. Unmindful speech can kill. It doesn't cost anything to use loving speech. Choose your words carefully and you will make many people happy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy this wonderful book. See you this coming Sunday at 4:00PM at Peace Abbey - Sherborn.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Have a Wonderful Week,&lt;br /&gt;                                                &lt;br /&gt;PEACE&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Joe Matteucig&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on Route 16, close to the Library and Town Hall Complex of Sherborn.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fr. Joe Matteucig</member_name><member_id>4994956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232913509000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225055576000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club November Meetup</name><id>9035607</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227474000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/9035607/</event_url></item>