<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3444 Little River Rd.</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05676</zip><lat>44.389835</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Little River State Park Campground N44° 23.392' W72° 46.041'</name><city>Waterbury</city><id>8353222</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.767281</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;General Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Our objective is to bag three peaks on the New England 4k list (Ellen, Abraham, and Camels Hump) with car camp weekend. $20 Cost (bring cash) includes site fee for camping only - all food is participant responsibility. We will Car Camp Friday and Saturday night at a group site. Plan to cook breakfasts at the group site, leader will provide hot water. Plan for restaurant Saturday evening. Saturday we will climb Mt Abraham and Mt Ellen (4K list). Sunday we will climb Camels Hump Mountain (4K list). Both hikes have beautiful views when the weather cooperates. Participants may hike either or both days. If hiking/camping only part of email Pam at &lt;a href="mailto:phwilmot@gmail.com"&gt;phwilmot (at) gmail.com or post comment here. If not camping, you do not have to pay the $20. You do have to sign up with the AMC per below.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;SIGN UP:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;T&lt;strong&gt;his hike is a cross posting with an AMC trip. To join you must also RSVP/Sign up on the AMC website: &lt;a href="https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/274" class="linkified"&gt;https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/274&lt;/a&gt; and answer ALL the questions there. This will not take long and you do not have to be an AMC member. I will call to talk with you about the hike. The signup at AMC has carpooling info.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Campsite:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Little River State Park Campsites T13 and T14 see Map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vtstateparks.com/pdfs/littleriver.pdf"&gt;http://www.vtstateparks.com/pdfs/littleriver.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This campground has showers and flush toilets. It also has a swimming beach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; From Jct. Hwy 100 and U.S. 2: Go 1-1/2 mi. W on U.S. 2, then 3-1/2 mi. N on Little River Rd. Located 30 miles southeast of Burlington just off I-89. &lt;strong&gt;This is about 3 ½ hours from Boston without much traffic.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;N44° 23.392' W72° 46.041'&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;time=&amp;amp;date=&amp;amp;ttype=&amp;amp;q=little+river+State+Park,+United+States&amp;amp;sll=43.480577,-73.206174&amp;amp;sspn=0.007894,0.014591&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=44.391046,-72.779875&amp;amp;spn=0.031096,0.058365&amp;amp;z=14&amp;amp;iwloc=addr&amp;amp;om=1" target="_blank"&gt;Directions/Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Routes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (Subject to change) &lt;span&gt;Abraham/Ellen: The plan is to park in Lincoln Gap and hike north on the Long Trail to Abraham, Ellen and return.  It’s a 12.6 miles round trip.  Up 1600 ft the first 2.6 mi, some up and down along the ridge and then reverse.  Since there is a sustained steep section the time is estimated at 8 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For Camels Hump we will drive into the state park to the trailhead for the Monroe Trail.  This trail goes 3.1 miles to the Long Trail and another 0.3 to the peak (6.8 rt) and up about 2100ft.  RT book time advertised as about 5 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here is a map of trails on Camel’s Hump: &lt;a href="http://www.vtstateparks.com/pdfs/camels_hump_trails.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.vtstateparks.com/pdfs/camels_hump_trails.pdf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Participants should be prepared for late Summer hiking. Everyone should have all the appropriate individual gear including rain pants &amp;amp; jacket, spare, warm (dry) clothing, bug spray, sunscreen, hats &amp;amp; gloves. Our worst case scenario, if someone gets seriously injured, is for one or two of us to have to spend an uncomfortable (but survivable) night in the woods. Everyone should have a whistle and a headlamp. There may be additional group gear that we will share. Don't forget a bathing suit! If you are camping, bring a tent if you have one.  If not, you can bunk with someone else (and for space reasons may have to anyway-- depending). You must bring a sleeping bag and pad if staying over with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday Breakfast: by individual at the campsite, leaders will provide hot water. &lt;span&gt;Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday Lunch: on the trail by individual&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Saturday Dinner: At a local restaurant in Waterbury. Ben and Jerry's factory is nearby and we will visit at least once!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us and want to head off on your own. We will hike at a moderate pace and you must have previous 4K experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Don’t forget to RSVP/Sign up on the AMC website: &lt;a href="https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/274" class="linkified"&gt;https://hbbostonamc.org/regi/274&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>C</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>6419698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343592884000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343079444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>VT Peaks: Ellen, Abraham, Camel's Hump Car Camping Weekend</name><id>74595162</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>162000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343430000000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/74595162/</event_url></item>