<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 King Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.320358</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hotel Northampton</name><city>Northampton</city><id>3298292</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631332</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A fun opportunity to network and hang out with other people in a variety of professional fields..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Outside Patio of Hotel Northampton if weather is good or inside at the upper level bar if not...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free for NAYP Members&lt;br /&gt;$5 for guests&lt;br /&gt;5-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some background info about Hotel Northampton and the featured non-profit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The history of the Hotel Northampton begins with Lewis Wiggins, an entrepreneur who had a great interest in preserving the Colonial Revival theme when constructing the Hotel Northampton in 1927. An integral element of Wiggins' concept was to achieve museum status for the hotel's furnishings, and to this end he acquired antiques both for the hotel and for his own collection. Many of these antiques still grace the hallways, restaurants, and lobby. The collection was added to daily, and by 1937 Wiggins employed a full-time antiquarian curator with a staff of up to 15. Two staff members were assigned only to mingle with the guests and discuss the hotel and its antiques.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The featured non-profit at September's event is Best Buddies. Best Buddies is a nonprofit organization dedicated to establishing a global volunteer movement that creates opportunities for one-to-one friendships, integrated employment and leadership development for people with intellectual and developmental disabilities.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>2960740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284070500000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282842206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NAYP Party with a Purpose (Northampton Area "Young" Professionals)</name><id>14551052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284066000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/14551052/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>