<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>There's nothing better to help you wake you up in the morning than a little exercise so let's meet at the Gantcher Center for a nice walk before work.  If the weather is outstanding, we may walk outside such as at the Ellis Oval.  Otherwise, we will do a few laps of talking &amp;amp; walking around the indoor track in the Gantcher Center.  So what do you say we get together to meet some of our colleagues, compare notes about work, burn a few calories, and get a jump start on a productive day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I probably need to say that you should check with your doctor before exercising, you are encouraged to walk at whatever pace is comfortable for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you work up a sweat, the Cousens Athletic Complex has changing and shower facilities on the basement level.  If you intend to use the lockers, you are strongly encouraged to bring a lock and to avoid leaving valuables in the locker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: the entrance to Gantcher is through the Cousens Facility and &lt;b&gt;requires a Tufts ID&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, if you have any questions, feel free to shoot me an email at rich.kelley@tufts.edu.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Tufts hat and a goofy name tag.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288789988000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288042352000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wake-up Walk</name><id>15225639</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288783800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/15225639/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/4/global_14831588.jpeg</photo_url></item>