<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/e/a/event_181788362.jpeg" width="267" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;From boardgamegeek.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the same as the basic Clue game, but with more of everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The publisher's description: &lt;br /&gt;

 Was it Madame Rose in the Carriage House with the Poison? Monsieur Brunette in the Trophy Room with the Horseshoe? Or was it our old friend Colonel Mustard whodunit in the Library with his trusty service Revolver?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll need your sharpest detective skills to solve the ever-changing CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE mystery, because in this expanded version of our classic game of detection, there are more rooms, more weapons, more suspects -- more mayhem!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The late Mr. Boddy's country manor has a total of twelve possible Murder Locations, both outdoors and indoors, with secret passages, plus new "Snoop Spaces" that let you broaden your investigation. A vial of Poison and a Horseshoe bring the number of Weapons up to eight. And the devious bunch of Supsects has grown to ten with the addition of Miss Peach, Monsieur Brunette, Madame Rose and Sergeant Gray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With all these additional people, places and things to unravel, your most expert powers of interrogation and deduction will be called into play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So shuffle the Suspect, Weapon and Murder Location cards, slip one of each into the Confidential Case File envelope -- and start sleuthing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn by turn you probe, collecting evidence and pinpointing certain culprits, means, and rooms. Then, when you think you've got it, make your accusation: Whodunit? Where? With which weapon?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE ... it's so entertaining, it's criminal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send out my house number the day before the event to those who have RSVPed 'Yes'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1357618878000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353467057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Clue: Master Detective</name><id>92261422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357605000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/92261422/</event_url></item>