<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi gang,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry about last month - there was a power outage at Z Square so the restaurant was closed at the last minute. My apologies to those who tried to attend but were shut out. We can discuss the topic &amp;quot;How can naturalism save the world?&amp;quot; another time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next month we'll join forces with the Humanist Chaplaincy at Harvard and other groups to celebrate Darwin Day (his 200th birthday!). From 8-10:30 pm there will be a big party open to the public at the Queen's Head Pub at Memorial Hall in Harvard Yard, plus other events earlier in the day, see the Harvard Darwin Day &lt;a href="http://darwinday.fas.harvard.edu" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.  Anyone wanting to help decorate should contact me at 617-625-5156. Hope to see you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org  &lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month):   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring and promoting a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>in the basement of Memorial Hall, entrance closest to Harvard Square</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236727339000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231808940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Darwin Day 2009 at Harvard!</name><id>9509542</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234486800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/9509542/</event_url></item>