<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>51 Sandy Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.429840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 259-8355</phone><name>deCordova Sculpture Park &amp; Museum</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>954923</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.314025</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Here's a chance for you to come out with/without your kids and meet the single parents of Parents Without Partners. We are opening up this event so you can check us out before attending an orientation. Looking forward to meeting you!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet outside the museum store. If you are arriving later let me know and I'll give you my cell phone # to call and find us. &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: Adults: $14, Seniors (65+): $12, Students: $10, Children 12 and under: FREE. Members, Lincoln Residents, and Active Duty Military Personnel and their families receive FREE admission. Many libraries have museum passes available. Check your local library and reserve your pass today. &lt;br /&gt;

 Pack a lunch, water, camera, sunscreen and a blanket we are going to explore the grounds of the deCordova Sculpture Park and Museum. &lt;a href="http://www.decordova.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.decordova.org&lt;/a&gt; The park was established in 1950 and covers 35 acres of beautifully landscaped lawns, forests, fields, gardens, and terraces on a rolling site along the shore of Flint’s Pond. There are more than 60 works to explore outside. One rule to let your kids in on: (No touching the art or climbing indoors or out, and no running in the indoor galleries). These rules are to protect the art. The museum has just completed the summer exhibitions. At the top floor the outside deck offers views the grounds and the lake, very picturesque. Rain cancels event. &lt;br /&gt;

 Located at: 51 Sandy Pond Road, Lincoln, MA 01773 &lt;br /&gt;

 RSVP if you are attending!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>8198815</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340471598000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Single Parents</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>pwp817</urlname><id>1298426</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Parents Without Partners- Single Parents</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338990076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>POSTPONED due to rain. DeCordova Sculpture Park and Museum + Picnic</name><id>67983882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340460000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/pwp817/events/67983882/</event_url></item>