<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349509</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>bpl.org</phone><name>Rabb Auditorium at Boston Public Library in Copley Square</name><city>Boston</city><id>883985</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079466</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Have you seen this dog-n-pony-n-orc show? Now with slides? It's&lt;br /&gt;a visual and verbal tour through geekdom!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come see &amp;quot;a heartbreaking work of staggering geekiness&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;Ethan Gilsdorf?s FANTASY FREAKS AND GAMING GEEKS comes to&lt;br /&gt;Boston Public Library&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wed., Oct. 20&lt;br /&gt;6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Boston Public Library, Central Library&lt;br /&gt;700 Boylston St.&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As part of the Boston Public Library’s Author Series, Ethan Gilsdorf presents a visual and verbal tour through his book “Fantasy Freaks and Gaming Geeks: An Epic Quest for Reality Among Role Players, Online Gamers, and Other Dwellers of Imaginary Realms” (now available in paperback).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The award-winning travel memoir investigates fantasy and gaming subcultures – from Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons players to World of Warcraft addicts, from Harry Potter fans to live-action role-players. “Fantasy Freaks and Gaming Geeks” also recounts the author's quest to make peace with his geeky past and accept his &amp;quot;inner geek.&amp;quot; In a slide-lecture, the author will discuss his book and the appeal of fantasy and gaming, followed by a Q&amp;amp;A and book signing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;National Public Radio described the book as &amp;quot;Lord of the Rings meets Jack Kerouac’s On the Road.&amp;quot; Wired.com proclaimed, “For anyone who has ever spent time within imaginary realms, the book will speak volumes.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gilsdorf publishes travel, arts, and pop culture stories regularly in the New York Times, Boston Globe, Washington Post, Christian Science Monitor, and other magazines and newspapers worldwide. His blog &amp;quot;Geek Pride&amp;quot; is seen regularly on PsychologyToday.com and he has also been a guest on talk radio as a fantasy and escapism expert. “Fantasy Freaks and Gaming Geeks” was named a &amp;quot;Must-Read&amp;quot; book by the Massachusetts Book Awards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Incriminating press photos (including the author in chainmail, wielding a sword) can be downloaded here: &lt;a href="http://www.ethangilsdorf.com/pressroom/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ethangilsd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info: &lt;a href="http://www.fantasyfreaksbook.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fantasyfreaksbook.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fantasyfre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/news/author_series.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bpl.org/news/author_series.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bpl.org/ne...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287702822000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286945378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"a heartbreaking work of staggering geekiness!"</name><id>15093183</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287612000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/15093183/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/0/global_6942656.jpeg</photo_url></item>