<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sanders Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>738747</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114285</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;An Evening with Jane Goodall&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Richard Wrangham&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Ticket information below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Jane Goodall, DBE, is founder of the Jane Goodall Institute.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Professor Richard Wrangham, PhD, is a Harvard College Professor &amp;amp; Board member of Jane Goodall's International Advisory Council.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The famous primatologist and conservationist will discuss the 50-year chimpanzee behavioral research she pioneered and her message of hope for the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The conversation begins at 8:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Book signing and merchandise sales to follow&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The year 2010 marks a monumental milestone for the Jane Goodall Institute (JGI) and its founder, Dr. Jane Goodall, DBE. Fifty years ago, Goodall, who is today a world-renowned primatologist, conservationist and UN Messenger of Peace, first set foot on the shores of Lake Tanganyika, in what is now Tanzania's Gombe National Park. The chimpanzee behavioral research she pioneered there has produced a wealth of scientific discovery, and her vision has expanded into a global mission to empower people to make a difference for all living things. For more information about JGI please visit www.janegoodall.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Professor Wrangham has been studying chimpanzees for over 30 years. He started his work at Gombe under Dr. Goodall. Today, Professor Wrangham continues to collaborate with Dr. Goodall and the Jane Goodall Institute and is the director of the Kibale Chimpanzee Project in Uganda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A book signing with Dr. Goodall and Professor Wrangham will follow the presentation. Dr. Goodall’s books, JGI merchandise and memberships will be available for sale on site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Purchase tickets at the Harvard Box Office or on-line, &lt;a href="http://ofa.fas.harvard.edu/cal/details.php?ID=40925" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;HERE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard University - Sander Theater&lt;br /&gt;45 Quincy Street &lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;United States&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Info: John Trybus – jtrybus@janegoodall.org&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308098169000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270346440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goodall, Wrangham &amp; Chimps</name><id>13080232</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272931200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/13080232/</event_url></item>