<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/0/0/e/event_73193262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showtime is at 7:15PM.&amp;nbsp; I will be at the theater by 6:15PM and we will be heading in for seats at 6:45PM.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is showing upstairs, so look for me at a table near the windows at the top of the escalators.&amp;nbsp; I will have on my Meetup Pin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember it's opening weekend and Mark is a Boston Boy so it is a good idea to buy your tickets ahead of time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are planning to attend the after event, please plan and bring cash.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; January 13, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; Universal Pictures &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Baltasar Korm&amp;aacute;kur &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; Aaron Guzikowski &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Mark Wahlberg, Kate Beckinsale, Ben Foster, Giovanni Ribisi, Caleb Landry Jones, Lukas Haas, Diego Luna, J.K. Simmons &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; R (for violence, pervasive language and brief drug use) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.contrabandmovie.net/" target="_blank"&gt;Contrabandmovie.net&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/contraband" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; Mark Wahlberg leads the cast of "Contraband," a fast-paced thriller about a man trying to stay out of a world he worked so hard to leave behind and the family he'll do anything to protect. Set in New Orleans, the film explores the cutthroat underground world of international smuggling -- full of desperate criminals and corrupt officials, high-stakes and big payoffs -- where loyalty rarely exists and death is one wrong turn away. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Chris Farraday (Wahlberg) long ago abandoned his life of crime, but after his brother-in-law, Andy (Caleb Landry Jones), botches a drug deal for his ruthless boss, Tim Briggs (Giovanni Ribisi), Chris is forced back into doing what he does best--running contraband--to settle Andy's debt. Chris is a legendary smuggler and quickly assembles a crew with the help of his best friend, Sebastian (Ben Foster), to head to Panama and return with millions in counterfeit bills. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Things quickly fall apart and with only hours to reach the cash, Chris must use his rusty skills to successfully navigate a treacherous criminal network of brutal drug lords, cops and hit men before his wife, Kate (Kate Beckinsale), and sons become their target. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=59839#ixzz1duCLnUex" style="color : #003399"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326810997000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321478664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Contraband (7:15PM Show)</name><id>41430892</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326582900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/41430892/</event_url></item>