<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte 185</address_2><address_1>130 hartford rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06070</zip><lat>41.842920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Hike to top</phone><name>Heubelin Tower/Talcott Mountain</name><city>Simsbury</city><id>333458</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.792090</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A Warming Event Prior to Going To Tina's New Years Party..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an old favourite place for many of us, Yes we have gone here a lot, but the Feature is well worth it,&lt;br /&gt;We dont plan on goin up to the tower but plan on stopping at the first ledge for the event..&lt;br /&gt;Yeh, if its sunny...&lt;br /&gt;still a few days away..ah so what... its good to think of it going to be nice...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway.... It will be a good reason to try a swig of warming Brandy, a warming drink of Kalua and chocolate or something like that mixed in..Dont drink too much yet...LOL...but for the non drinkers..warm cider, or some things that are really good will start our evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So there you have it..a socializing/walking event for those going or not going to Tina's Party later..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Pictures view is where we will kayak in the spring... Get Ready &amp;gt;..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other info:&lt;br /&gt;SO instead wouldn't it be nice to have a short hike to a nice flat area near the first set of open area at the top path of the Heublin Tower (Talcott Mountain) for a small PRE WARMING UP EVENT  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can't stay up there too much past sunset since im not sure how strict the rules are enforced for a park closing at sunset? &lt;br /&gt;We can find out im sure?.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;From Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;Find rte 185 on your maps..take that..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for the signs for Talcott Mountain/Hebulin Tower State Park area (south side of rte 185), its right across from Penwood State Forest if you missed it.. &lt;br /&gt;Go up the entrance way for a short distance, you will see the parking area off to the right across from the trail head on the left. I will have the Blue Toyota Avalon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this is in an odd location for most of your routs of travel.. &lt;br /&gt;Please check your maps. &lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS or others, 130 Hartford Road (rte 185), Simsbury, CT will get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199305260000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>This is a simple reason... its not good warm kayaking weather yet...</why><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198508262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Sunset Event Of This Year and New Year of Future Events</name><id>6962803</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199132100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6962803/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/5/7/global_2851879.jpeg</photo_url></item>