<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Kingston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353490</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-2622 </phone><name>Good Life</name><city>Boston</city><id>669027</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This one is for those who want to try a beat with their brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good Life in the downtown crossing area hosts El Barrio, brunch, beats and bebidas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comidas:&lt;br /&gt;El Barrio Executive Chef Antonio Guerrero has created a menu which combines classic home-style Latin dishes with comfort food such huevos rancheros (sunny-side up eggs and black beans) or the lighter vegetarian option of Ensalada Fresca made of mixed greens, avocados and cilantro vinaigrette, as well as Chicharron and coconut-crusted French Toast topped with cinnamon whipped cream. There will be other options and the entree range is $6 to $14.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bebidas:&lt;br /&gt;Coco piratas (a cinnamon and rum drink), Caipirinhas, and bloody mary as well as the usually drink fare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Musicas:&lt;br /&gt;Latin grooves from the 60s, 70s and 80s spun by Bradford James.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Party:&lt;br /&gt;Play Nintendo's Wii which simulates real-life sport and translates the player's motions onto a screen or watch football on one of the big screens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.goodlifebar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Good Life Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/rider_tools/trip_planner/" target="_blank"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to plan your public transportation route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DRIVING DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to plan your route.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;You should find ample free parking nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as restaurant staffing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me on my cell (617) 445-7549&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to me, &lt;a href="http://brunchclub.meetup.com/107/members/3389565/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email me about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260120578000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258458337000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Good Life Brunch Sunday November 22nd at  11 AM</name><id>11893694</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258905600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/11893694/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/f/d/global_11879885.jpeg</photo_url></item>