<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>23 Depot Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03032</zip><lat>43.018082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Parking Lot Just Past</name><city>Auburn</city><id>2785171</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353149</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/b/2/event_97844722.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If on I-93 heading North or South in Manchester get off at exit 7 getting onto  NH-101 heading East.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If heading east on Route 101 get off at Exit 2 in Auburn and turn right at the end of the ramp:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If heading west on Route 101 get off at Exit 2 in Auburn and turn left at the end of the ramp:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proceed south on Hooksett Rd. for 0.8 miles passing Holidays Bar and Grill. Just after cresting the top of a hill and staring downhill again turn left onto Depot Rd. and proceed 0.2 miles passing 23 Depot Rd. There is a dirt parking lot on the left.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be hiking a couple of the FOMBA - Friends Of Massabesic Bicycling Association trails (mountain bike trails) for an approximately 5.5 mile hike. Old fire roads connect the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the trials are winding it is possible to take shortcuts at times if one is getting tired to make the hike shorter and head back sooner or simply take a rest till the group not taking the shortcut catches up to you. At times you will see places where you realize the trail loops back on itself and you are only a few feet away from another trail section.  So if you get the feeling didn't I just pass that tree, rock, etc. a little while ago you will probably be right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the terrain is somewhat hilly the hills are smaller ones so there isn't any real significant elevation gain or losses.  We will be hiking the Fireline and Long Trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to a trail map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fomba.org/files/trail-map.pdf"&gt;http://www.fomba.org/files/trail-map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also 2 pictures in the photo album so you can see a larger version of the trail map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338661362000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337304939000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FOMBA Trails- 5.5 Mile Hike</name><id>65282042</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338642000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/65282042/</event_url></item>