<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>149 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02341</zip><lat>42.006462</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 380-8853</phone><name>Burrage Pond</name><city>Halifax</city><id>1195541</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.884483</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hopeful for spring, everyone? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This location has been recommended by several members...  Grab your friendly bully and come join us for an on- or off-leash walk and play date Saturday, March 6th at 11:00a!  We're meeting at the Halifax entrance, at 149 Elm Street in Halifax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is, of course, a pond here, so if your pooch likes to get wet, you may want to bring a towel and/or a blanket for the car :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is about a 2-3 mile walk for those of you who are up to it!  Hopefully, the weather cooperates with us and our short-coated bullies this time!  Non-bully dogs are welcome, as well!  Remember, you need not have a bully to be part of our activities: only a love and support of them :)  One of our most excellent members has two labs! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions or comments, feel free to email me! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can find more information on the pond and its trails at &lt;a href="http://www.everytrail.com/view_trip.php?trip_id=68711" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.everytrail...&lt;/a&gt;.  Visit www.newenglandbullybreedclub.com and submit your membership app if you haven't already!  Also, we are compiling a Board Member Committee to help with event-planning , emailing, site-updating, manning booths at events, and major-decision-making regarding the NEBBC.  The club has grown exponentially since its inception in 2008, and we need some reliable, enthusiastic, dependable, energetic individuals to help run the show!  There is so much more I want to do, and just don't have the manpower for right now.  Please email me if you are interested... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Punish the Deed, Not the Breed, &lt;br /&gt;Cassie-Leigh Stock &lt;br /&gt;President &lt;br /&gt;New England Bully Breed Club &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>NEBBC Attire</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270307259000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266619516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Burrage Pond Dog-Walk &amp; Play Date!</name><id>12651100</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267891200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/12651100/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/d/global_13197005.jpeg</photo_url></item>