<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1245 New Britain Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06110</zip><lat>41.731354</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-561-0180</phone><name>Szechuan Tokyo</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>823910</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742638</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SZECHUAN TOKYO DEBUT OF THE TONY HARRINGTON 5: Soul Jazz, Funk, R&amp;amp;B. A special holiday concert - bring the family! Showtime is 8:00. There's no cover for this show. We recommend reservations as demand for Tony's shows is heavy. Backup personnel to be announced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ABOUT THE ARTIST:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A native of Hartford , CT Tony Harrington developed his love for all forms of music at an early age. Tony?s love of music and desire to perform was inherited from his father Sam Harrington. At age 11 Tony and his cousin formed a gospel group named ?The H &amp;amp; H Singers? and began performing at churches throughout Connecticut and Massachusetts . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony?s passion for performing blossomed, and his interest in the arts grew along with his desire to compete athletically. Upon entering Hartford Public High School Tony joined the concert choir and became a featured soloist under the direction of Ms. Edith Campbell. Tony?s talent demanded other forums and he was selected to join the Greater Hartford Youth Chorale for his junior and senior years in high school. The Greater Hartford Youth Chorale?s classical repertoire provided Tony with a strong foundation that allowed him to continue performing with other ensembles. He soon joined the Sounds of the North End and assumed the role of lead-vocalist performing at weddings fashion shows and banquets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Tony continued to perform as he continued his formal education. Tony Harrington graduated from the University of Hartford in 1977 with a Bachelor of Arts in Sociology alongside his Mother Anna Harrington. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The years after graduation brought Tony a myriad of experiences some jubilant and some tragic. His family was a constant source of encouragement and inspiration. His cousin Rahni collaborated with Tony on two songs dedicated to Tony?s father Sam. Tony?s Aunt Evelyn paid for the production of the songs ?A Good Friend is Hard to Find? and ?I Owe You?. And in 1978 before Sam Harrington?s passing he heard his son?s songs on the radio. Sam Harrington was proud of his son?s musical talent and knowing this became one of Tony?s greatest musical accomplishments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony sings another fan favorite! Over the years Tony always found his way back to music. Tony began recording more frequently in 1978. He recorded ?Six Million Steps? with Ollie RasPberry in 1978. The single was released by Inspirational Sounds to correspond with Any West?s run from Maine to Florida in support of Muscular Dystrophy. ?Six Million steps went all the way to #2 on the London disco charts in the summer of 1978. Following that success Tony worked with two groups. Inner Fusion from 1979-1982. And in 1984 he formed the group ?Tony Harrington and Touch Band?. The seven piece ?Tony Harrington and Touch Band? continues to perform all over New England and New York and have made recent appearances at Mohegan Sun and Foxwoods resort casino. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; As Tony Harrington and Touch was taking off Tony began performing as an anthem vocalist. Tony?s anthem repertoire includes the Russian National Anthem and Canadian National anthem. He is best known for his rendition of the National Anthem sung before Hartford Whaler?s games. Tony has also performed the National Anthem for Hartford Wolf Pack games, New England Blizzards, Boston Celtics, New York Knicks, at the World Cup in Montreal, WBC World Welterweight Boxing Championship between Marlon Starling and Too Su Kim, and for three years at the September 11th Memorial Remembrance Ceremony. As well Tony also performs at Hartford Hellcats (CBA), CT. Pride (CBA), New York Rangers, and New Jersey Devils games. Tony?s anthem renditions are so in demand that he has even performed at local professional arena football games in the 90's and a professional soccer team in Central Connecticut in 2000 &amp;amp; 2001. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony?s broad background extends from gospel to R&amp;amp;B to jazz. His high energy performances have made him a favorite in his home state and beyond! Tony Harrington and Touch can be seen performing at some of the most well attended events in the region. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tony Harrington has developed a smooth melodic style that is all his own. His talent remains in demand, and will be heard on the single ?Spend My Life? on the upcoming album by world renowned saxophonist, Marion Meadows.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll make a reservation under  Meet up</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212363651000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Because we are Fun</why><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210648250000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> SZECHUAN TOKYO DEBUT OF THE TONY HARRINGTON</name><id>7926949</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212190200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/7926949/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_2930168.jpeg</photo_url></item>