<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Huh?!? Totally puzzled?  What's this TAPPING gotta do with LoA?  That's how we felt when we first heard about this tapping - EFT - thing.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When combined with LoA principals, &lt;b&gt;Emotional Freedom Technique (EFT)&lt;/b&gt; has been advocated by LoA experts like Jack Canfield, Joe Vitale and Bob Proctor (who were featured on The Secret) and Michael Losier &lt;i&gt;as a powerful way to tap yourself out of “blocks” that stop you from attracting more of what you want.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate Beeders, our presenter, is a certified EFT/MTT practitioner and a Success Coach.&lt;/b&gt; The technique Kate uses, which is called Meridian Tapping Techniques (MTT)- which includes Emotional Freedom Technique (EFT), combines two well known sciences: mind/body and acupuncture (without the needles). &lt;b&gt;We'll be learning to combine this technique with LoA to tap yourself into attracting more financial abundance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we know, it's impossible to attract and keep an abundance of money if we have negative emotions around it. Very often it is the fear of lack of money and all of the stress that goes with that. As we remove the blocks that are in our way with EFT, then the abundance will flow more easily to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are examples of some of the negative thoughts we'll be &amp;quot;tapping&amp;quot; on:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Are money worries keeping you up at night?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Are you noticing more money is going out than coming in?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Do you feel there's no end in sight?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Have you been grinding your teeth at night? Or getting other symptoms as a result of stress and anxiety?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The power to decrease greatly your stress is literally in your fingertips.&lt;/b&gt; Watch your tension levels drop dramatically in a very short time, and replace the stressful thoughts with more positive ones. This quick and pain free technique typically provides lasting results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Kate Beeders:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;email: Kate@successcoachingwithKate.com&lt;br /&gt;website: www.successcoachingwithKate.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kate is a certified EFT/MTT practitioner and a Success Coach helping people eliminate whatever obstacles are blocking their success. She has several tapping certifications that have been awarded only to several hundred people in the world. Kate's radio show, &amp;quot;Tapping to Success&amp;quot; can be heard live over the Internet. Many of her articles have been published on www.selfgrowth.com and www.emofree.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The powerful technique Kate uses is Meridian Tapping Techniques (MTT- which includes Emotional Freedom Techniques- EFT). These tapping techniques have been popular in California and Europe since the early 1990s. It's often referred to as &amp;quot;emotional acupuncture&amp;quot;. Although, it's not a miracle drug, the results are typically fast, pain free and lasting. Negative emotions, behaviors and pains are usually eliminated quickly and then replaced with the positive behavior and emotions the person wants. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This technique is so strong that it was used to help many Vietnam veterans get over many of their PTSD that they have been living with for decades. The vets were able to eliminate many of these severe problems in several sessions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; ONLY if you know you are coming.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually provide handouts and have appetizers &amp;amp; refreshments. So, to keep &amp;quot;green&amp;quot; &amp;amp; cost down, please RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; only when you can honor your commitment &amp;amp; show up. Many of you have been wonderful with this and we very much appreciate your understanding and support!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;For &lt;b&gt;parking and directions (via T or driving)&lt;/b&gt; info to Dave's loft : &lt;br /&gt;(1) Go here: &lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/files/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) Sign in &lt;br /&gt;(3) Scroll down and open file &amp;quot;Directions &amp;amp; Parking_BostonLOA Meetup&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270768603000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267578592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tap Yourself into Attracting More Financial Abundance</name><id>jxfdnyngbjb</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270594800000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/12763450/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/3/global_13736803.jpeg</photo_url></item>