<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 WASHINGTON STREET</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.773164</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>George's Restaurant</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>1021866</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084864</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Table is reserved for 10-12 under Meetup Group. Band starts at 9 and manager says it will be hopping because the band is great! See you there around 8:30! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's try a new dance location. MAL'S Blues and Jazz Lounge at George's Restaurant is in Historic Downtown Haverhill. (Two miles off of Rte 495.-Directions below) Mal's Lounge is located on the third floor of the Restaurant. (We offer an amazing surround sound in our new lounge.) The Love Dog's are scheduled for this event. Come on over to meet some new friends, dance and have fun.&lt;br /&gt;There is a $10.00 cover charge...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO GEORGE'S&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE NORTH: From I495 North, merge RIGHT from EXIT 49, River Street. Travel approximately 2 miles to train overpass (River Street becomes Washington Street). GEORGE's restaurant is the four-story, marble building on the LEFT-HAND side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE SOUTH: From I495 South, merge LEFT from EXIT 50, River Street. Travel approximately 2 miles to train overpass (River Street becomes Washington Street). GEORGE's restaurant is the four-story, marble building on the LEFT-HAND side.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251242541000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248707404000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Love Dog's - New Dance Location</name><id>10967466</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250985600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/10967466/</event_url></item>