<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Redstone Hill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01564</zip><lat>42.436197</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>:(978) 422-8888</phone><name>Davis Farmland</name><city>Sterling</city><id>682939</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.726173</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us Starry, Starry Night Mazing.  Enjoy viewing the stars in the big sky of the country. The maze will be open from 10am to 9pm, weather permitting. Last admission is at 8pm.  Bring your flashlight, telescope (if you like) and your courage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Davis Mega Maze:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The concept for Davis' Mega Maze began across the street at Davis' Farmland in 1995. The idea at the time was novel, providing an exhibit for children in a small plot of corn. The area designated for this children's maze was only 40 by 60 feet in size and it was more of an experience than a challenging puzzle. When the maze opened, children flocked through the entrance and trampled the corn. The exhibit was destroyed. What seemed like such a great concept, now appeared to be an impossible one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sixth generation farmer, Larry Davis, relayed the traumatic maze experience to a good friend who also loved the concept and recommended finding a way to make it work. He knew of a gentleman in England named Adrian Fisher, who was the world's most famous maze designer and recommended Larry contact him to try and make this exhibit become a reality. However, the Davis farmers believed the challenges were too great and filled the empty exhibit space with a fence maze. A year later, Larry's friend found out Adrian Fisher who was interested in designing a corn maze in New England. The Davises jumped at the opportunity, calling Adrian immediately. Two things would need to change to make the maze a success. First, the maze would be designed for adults instead of children; and secondly, it would not be located at Davis' Farmland, instead it would be across the street and act as it's own farm park. It would be huge with over 3 miles of winding pathways and each year would have a different theme. Theming options were endless, from dinosaurs to aliens and pirates. Adrian chose the first theme and designed the maze based on a famous Celtic frieze of two entwined dragons. The maze design was spectacular, combining both geometric angles with long sloping curves. With a project of such magnitude and detail, the Davises quickly found that building the maze was near impossible. But this ended up being the least of their worries. After planting the initial crop of corn, for the next month the farmers watched the plants slowly shrivel and die. Not only had the crop of corn died, but it was too late in the season to re-grow corn. This meant the maze would need to wait another year before it could be built. The plans seemed unattainable until their crop specialist, recommended using a crop called sorghum instead of corn. The idea worked. In the right weather, sorghum can grow as much as 8 inches in a day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This years maze:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.davisfarmland.com/megamaze/2008maze.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.davisfarml...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost:&lt;br /&gt;Adult (13-59) $16.95&lt;br /&gt;Senior (60+) $12.95&lt;br /&gt;Kids (5-12) $12.95&lt;br /&gt;Under 5 Free&lt;br /&gt;WGBH/ AAA/MTA $2.00 discount (max 6)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.davisfarmland.com/megamaze/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.davisfarml...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car Pool From Nashua:&lt;br /&gt;We will be leaving the Exit 6 (Off Route 3) Welcome Center at 5 PM. If you are not familiar where the welcome center is, look for the large blue signs that say welcome center. If you are planning to carpool, please indicate so in your RSVP. Otherwise, I'll see you in Sterling. Go to the ticket booth. I will have a meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223752738000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220298180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Starry, Starry Night at Davis Mega-Maze</name><id>8664242</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223157600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8664242/</event_url></item>