<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I've always wanted to experience a corn maze! Plus I won't have to worry about getting lost on the walk!&lt;br /&gt;Meet in front of the ticket booth at 11:00.  Tickets are $14.95.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the website:&lt;br /&gt;There is more than one solution to the Mega Maze and there are several different levels of intensity at which the maze can be completed. All offer varying degrees of difficulty and a new maze experience every time you attempt them. We have developed X-treme MazingSM for the most adventurous cowboys and cowgirls who are truly looking for the ultimate mazing experience. If you have time, spend the day and complete all levels or stay on the same level and see how many different ways you can complete it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basic Mazing&lt;br /&gt;Level 1: Intensity Level 25%&lt;br /&gt;Receive your lucky star and exit the maze at the halfway point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level 2: Intensity Level 50%&lt;br /&gt;Complete the entire maze and exit over the victory bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;X-treme Mazing&lt;br /&gt;Level 3: X-treme Intensity Level 60%&lt;br /&gt;Complete the entire maze AND each of the games of chance and challenge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level 4: X-treme Intensity Level 70%&lt;br /&gt;Complete level 3 AND find all 5 Lucky Charm rub-ons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level 5: X-treme Intensity Level 80%&lt;br /&gt;Complete level 4 AND piece together the Map of the Lost Vegas Strip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level 6: X-treme Intensity Level 90%&lt;br /&gt;Complete level 5 AND go over all 8 bridges.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Level 7: X-treme Intensity Level 100%&lt;br /&gt;Complete level 6 AND fill out all 12 Quiz Questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maze Courtyard&lt;br /&gt;Begin your a-maze-ing adventure in the Mega Maze Courtyard! &lt;br /&gt;International Collection of 6 Minute Mazes&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy our International Collection of 6 Minute Mazes. These mazes are all different and popular in different areas around the world. Some mazes are more comfortable for children and others are more enjoyable for grandparents. Each maze requires different faculties to complete. They are an awesome warm-up for your next step-the Mega Maze. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out pictures of past mazes on their website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.davisfarmland.com/megamaze/pastmazes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.davisfarml...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to Heather for recommending the Maze and to Trish for recommending the restaurant!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will go for lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;Finders Pub&lt;br /&gt;171 W Boylston St&lt;br /&gt;West Boylston MA 01583&lt;br /&gt;508-835-3707&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188831926000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187628960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Corn Maze</name><id>6212314</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1188658800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6212314/</event_url></item>