<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>8th Floor</address_2><address_1>100 Milk Street Entrance (Ten PO Sq Bldg)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-542-7400</phone><name>Exemplar Law Partners, LLC</name><city>Boston</city><id>129307</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054977</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**PLEASE NOTE**: This group is a part of Revolve Nation, but has been specially formed for entertainers and professionals &lt;i&gt;actively&lt;/i&gt; involved in the entertainment industry. Artists, writers, filmmakers, musicians, please come and share your ideas, questions and concerns with other like-minded professionals and receive valuable advice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, I am pleased to announce our guest speaker, Jay Sweet.  Jay is man who wears many hats in the music industry; he runs his own music consultancy agency, Sweet &amp;amp; Doggat, is an Editor at Large for Paste Magazine, and a Producer @ the Norfolk Folk Festival.  I'm sure Jay will have some seriously valuable advice for both musicians and other professionals working in the industry.  The topic(s) are still being refined, &lt;b&gt;so if you have a specific topic or question you would like to see addressed, PLEASE email me in advance at sjamieson@exemplarlaw.com&lt;/b&gt; It's always about YOU GUYS, the members, so let's make sure we have the best program we can!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks, and I hope to see you all on Nov 10th @ 6 pm @ our offices in Ten Post Office Sq, 8th Floor, Boston.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very Best, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shannon&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258067607000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256224322000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Revolve Nation ENTERTAINMENT Meetup &amp; Roundtable Discussion Group</name><id>11686162</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/11686162/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/2/global_8029234.jpeg</photo_url></item>