<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey Roller-fans, Next meetup will be Sept. 20th, 2009 at 10:00 am. on the Blackstone River Bike Path in Cumberland, R.I. The address is 51 Front St., Cumberland, RI. this street is off Store Hill RD. in Cumberland and it is an entrance to the bike path at  a apartment builing called the mill, it is an old brick building made into beatuful apartments. A member lives there, and we can use the lounge and bathrooms there, so you can bring  a drink or sandwich, it is a very cool place to relax after rolling. I rolled this a few weeks ago, my plan is to head south 2 miles,no major obstacles, a small wooden bridge but in good shape, then turn back and go about 2 miles north where things get hairy, train tracx , steep hill, not good for people on blades unless your real comfortable in stopping and slowing ability. As always with this group, it's about having FUN and getting out to get some excercise with other people, no stress, do as little or as much as you want to, come and go as you wish. There is 2 parking lots as you come to Front St. stay to the right as you come down Store Hill Rd., you will see iron fence , stay right, you will see train tracx, and the nice building. Park in the left lot , there will be a lot on your right also, but I will be in left lot, and that will be our starting point. You can use map quest for directions, I did they are very good. Any questions or comments please email me as soon as possible. This will be a wheather permitting meetup. I really don't care about rsvp and such, if your there, your there!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in parking lot on left, I'll be looking for you</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254099125000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252451529000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roller-blade Blackstone Riverway Bikepath, Cumberland,R.I.</name><id>11322390</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253455200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/11322390/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/global_5864541.jpeg</photo_url></item>