<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mountain Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.475981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-464-2987</phone><name>Wachusetts Mountain State Reservation</name><city>Princeton</city><id>761189</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.883362</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Updating the post with the full details for our fun trip to learn to Snowboard at Wasschusetts Mountain :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting there&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets meet at 8am at North station to get our tickets and get the train together - I will update this post with the exact position of the meeting place on Saturday morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Ski train” service will &lt;strong&gt;leave North Station at 8:30 a.m&lt;/strong&gt;. and arrive at the Fitchburg commuter rail station at 10:06 a.m where&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Wachusett Mountain will pick us up and shuttle us directly to the mountain, approximately 20 minutes away.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Wachusett will then shuttle us at &lt;strong&gt;4:45 p.m. back to the Fitchburg&lt;/strong&gt; station for a train departing at 5:35 p.m. &lt;strong&gt;arriving in Boston at 7.05pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;train costs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;USD20&lt;/strong&gt; return and includes the shuttle up and down the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Class&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a special class start time for those that take the ski train.  Once off the bus we will be kitted out for those who do no have their own boots and boards and the &lt;strong&gt;lesson will be for 1.5 hours&lt;/strong&gt; they will group people based on ability, however, as many of us will be taking the beginner class we just need to let them know and they will make sure that we get to stay together :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;cost of the lesson is USD89, and includes snowboard and boot rental and a day pass on the mountain&lt;/strong&gt; so we can practice what we learned for the rest of the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment &amp;amp; Clothing &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As mentioned for those taking the class your boot and board hire is included int he class price.  For those not taking a  lesson you can hire equipment at the shop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you skate / skateboard and have &lt;strong&gt;knee pads and wrist guards&lt;/strong&gt; I would strongly recommend that you bring those with you.  Again these are available for hire at the shop if not, for an extra cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't have a ski jacket / celopets / gloves Wachusetts Mountain has recommended that both the Salvation Army and Goodwill has tons of good quality gear at this time of year, so its easy to get kitted out at a very low cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few different options for food and drinks on the  on the mountain for lunch quick breaks etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think that all the details.....if you need to reach me please text me on 305 905 6910.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So looking forward to hanging with you all this weekend :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wendy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wendy F</member_name><member_id>14430808</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359217879000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358943117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ski / Snowboard - Wachusetts</name><id>100976742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359207000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/100976742/</event_url></item>