<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We picked the theme a long time ago and I am told we picked magic but I don't remember that at all. Sounds like a good theme though so what the heck? Pesto Chango Magic is the theme!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TuiNtC4kURk"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TuiNtC4kURk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love this song, it always makes me smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This month no muggles allowed! Let's work some magic in the kitchen, stir those cauldrons, add those snippets of puppy dog tails and newt eyes to make your dish savory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there a dish you've cooked that worked magic to win a heart or sooth a troubled friend? Share with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magic comes in many forms, sometimes it is just wishful thinking, sometimes a spell woven of mystical origins lost in the depths of time. Where do you find magic in your life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kk5xfK0ovrk"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kk5xfK0ovrk"&gt;v=kk5xfK0ovrk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One more music video for magic...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rgUrqGFxV3Q" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rgUrqGFxV3Q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every month a new crazy theme! Lots of fun and lots of food and drink. RSVPs open 30 days prior to the event and these dinners fill up quickly. Remember there are no rules. Caryl will email the address to those attending the Wednesday before the dinner. Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>park on the lawn if possible</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362952139000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357322808000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Do You Believe in Magic?</name><id>qxhmlcyrdblb</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362787200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/97899172/</event_url></item>