<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1356 Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.341990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 566-3330</phone><name>Party Favors</name><city>Brookline</city><id>762879</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Cupcakes are all the rage, so let's have a taste-testing EXTRAVAGANZA! We'll hit four of the most popular cupcake purveyors in Boston, followed by a casual, choose-your-own lunch from the vendor stands in the Quincy Market Colonnade at Faneuil Hall Marketplace. Can't handle so much sugar in one morning? Well, then, split 'em with a friend, save 'em for dessert, or have 'em boxed up to take home! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt; Rest assured that a good variety of flavors will be available: each establishment has been notified that we're coming. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll hop on and off the T to reach the different neighborhoods, and will be &lt;b&gt;walking up to 4 miles at a fairly brisk pace&lt;/b&gt;. Wear comfortable shoes and bring enough cash for your cupcakes (&amp;quot;designer&amp;quot; ones can be pricey!), T fare, and lunch. &lt;b&gt;RAIN OR SHINE&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet outside our first stop, Party Favors in Coolidge Corner, Brookline, at 9:30 a.m. sharp. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address: 1356 Beacon Street, Brookline, 02446. Phone: (617) 566-3330.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA directions: From Boston, travel outbound on the &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; (Cleveland Circle) train of the Green Line to the Coolidge Corner stop. You'll be let off at the intersection of Beacon Street and Harvard Ave. Cross to the right hand side of Beacon Street (Landmark: S.S. Pierce Building/Walgreen's), and proceed up Beacon Street one block to Party Favors at number 1356.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;~ ITINERARY ~&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Bakery addresses and corresponding T stop info will be provided the day of the event, in case we get separated during the tour.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop 1, 9:30 a.m.: Party Favors, Coolidge Corner (partyfavorsbrookline.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop 2, approximately 10:15 a.m.: South End Buttery, South End (southendbuttery.com/cupcakes.html). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop 3, approximately 11:00 a.m.: Sweet, Back Bay (sweetcupcakes.com). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop 4, approximately 11:45 a.m.: Lulu's Bakeshoppe, North End (lulusbakeshoppeboston.com). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch, approximately 12:30 p.m.: Quincy Market Colonnade at Faneuil Hall Marketplace. Pick whatever strikes your fancy from one of the many vendor stands:  (faneuilhallmarketplace.com/dining3.html). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Because this particular event is so informal, the group's customary MEMBER GUIDELINES pertaining to last-minute cancellations and No Shows, etc. will not be in effect.&lt;/u&gt; Again, THIS EVENT ONLY. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, I do request that you please RSVP so that I can get an accurate idea of how many people are coming.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so rate the event by completing the survey afterward. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet outside our first stop, Party Favors in Coolidge Corner, Brookline.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223830011000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221417145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Sweets and the City": cupcake walking tour &amp; lunch!</name><id>8756105</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223127000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/8756105/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/b/c/global_5506796.jpeg</photo_url></item>