<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 63 </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03451</zip><lat>42.829506</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Pisgah State Park - Kilburn Trailhead</name><city>Hinsdale</city><id>3187781</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.482990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;Directions for this hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;If coming from East or West on Route 2, head north on Route 63 in Erving and travel a little over 10 miles until you enter "downtown" Hinsdale NH. At the intersection of Route 119, head east (right) about a quarter mile and Route 63 will take a left and head north once more. Follow this road (Chesterfield Road) north approximately 3.7 miles. On your right will be a brown sign with an arrow which says "Pisgah State Park, Kilburn Loop Trail". This is at the entrance to the parking area, which accommodates 20+ vehicles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Plan on wearing something bright if possible. I do not expect hunters to be close to this trail, but better to be safe than sorry.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The map that you get when you click on the above link for "Pisgah State Park - Kilburn Trailhead" is WRONG!!!  If you click on the above location it will show you the red marker on Rt 63 just north of Rt 119.  That marker should be about 3 miles north of that spot, in the area where Kilburn Pond is noted on the map.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Regardless of how many times I chose to (edit map), it won't save the correct location.  Hopefully this glitch can be corrected! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kilburn Loop is listed as a 5.4 mile loop around Kilburn Pond, It appears to be a mostly flat terrain with a total elevation gain of about 200 feet. This trail is part of the many trails located in New Hampshires Pisgah State Park, which occupies the towns of Winchester, Chesterfield, and Hinsdale New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Map here:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.chesterfieldoutdoors.com/plands/pmap.html"&gt;http://www.chesterfieldoutdoors.com/plands/pmap.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Our trailhead will be at the intersection of Rt 63 and Kilburn Road in Hinsdale. This trailhead is about 4 miles north of Route 119, or about 5 miles south of Route 9. From the trailhead, the Kilburn Loop trail is about a half mile walk. Our total hike should be about 6.5 miles and should take 4 hours plus or minus with a break at the mid-point for snack/lunch. &lt;br /&gt;

 You will need to watch the weather and dress appropriately for the season. Layers if it's cold, and layers if it's warm! Bring plenty to drink and a snack if you wish. &lt;br /&gt;

 I've never done this hike myself, so it'll be an exploratory pace. I'm told that other groups finish this hike with a dip in Kilburn Pond. Any of you daring enough should bring a towel!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Terry Rooney</member_name><member_id>43555442</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355013599000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352238951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike the Kilburn Loop in Pisgah State Park*** NOTE*** Date changed!!!</name><id>90265802</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354978800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/90265802/</event_url></item>