<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The New Haven County Bar Association, Young Lawyers Section is hosting a Young Professional Networking Happy Hour at Bottega Lounge in New Haven on Wednesday, June 25, 2008.  The event is from 5:30 till 8:00.  Bottega Lounge will be providing drink specials and free appetizers.  Additionally, Club Getaway a camp for young professionals in upstate Connecticut is going to be giving away a free weekend vacation to Club Getaway valued at over $400 dollars and will also be providing $25 dollars off to anyone who books a weekend at Club Getaway and mentions our event.  This event is a great opportunity for young professionals from Connecticut to meet each other, share ideas, contacts and referrals.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drink Specials and Free Food: Bottega Lounge will be providing half price (two for one) draft beer, wine and martinis.  Complimentary food includes cheese and crackers, veggies &amp;amp; dip, and hot assorted hors d?oeuvers (pigs in blanket, potato puffs, spring rolls, etc?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your contact for the event is NHC'er and Events Chair of the New Haven Young Lawyers, Josh Hecht. If you have any questions, he can be reached at (203) 772-0070&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214602790000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213707225000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weds. 6/25 - Young Professional Networking Happy Hour at Bottega Lounge </name><id>8157997</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214429400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8157997/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/7/b/global_4486987.jpeg</photo_url></item>