<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>268 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02351</zip><lat>42.100518</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-871-5800</phone><name>Mia Regazza</name><city>Abington</city><id>949050</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.950145</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join me for a last minute dining option at Mia Regazza.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mia Regazza has been named best restaurant south of Boston. Great Italian and American cuisine served with pride by John and Kristen Martin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John &amp;amp; Kristin Martin have three wonderful daughters which gave them the inspiration to name their new restaurant Mia Regazza which loosely translated means 'my girls'. After many years as a head chef at the old  Hingham Bay Club and more recently the general manager of  DiNeros Restaurant  in Cohasset and  The Ocean Club  on Nantasket Beach, John has a well deserved reputation for bringing the highest standards to every restaurant he has been involved with. Kristin has also been involved for many years in the business operations taking care of the day to day details of running a restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In January of 2008, John &amp;amp; Kristin decided to finally open their 'own' restaurant and purchased the old Mexican restaurant known locally as Carmen's. After some minor and major renovations, Mia Regazza took on a warm and comfortable look of an old Italian restaurant. A small full service bar also features the latest technology in high definition televisions. The atmosphere promises to be fun and causal, but emphasizing the highest quality of food. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.miaregazza.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.miaregazza...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my photo, ask for hostess for Lisa's table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242344204000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241394838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Dining Out - Mia Regazza in Abington</name><id>10328986</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241478000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10328986/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/9/f/global_8468719.jpeg</photo_url></item>