<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Kirk Street</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.646255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>St Anne's Episcopal Church</name><city>Lowell</city><id>4713912</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.311447</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a fundraising event for which all proceeds go to Living Waters Center of Hope and Merrimack Valley Food Bank.&amp;nbsp; This event is also being posted on our other sites "Connections and Friends" and also "Improving Our Communities Together".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entrance to this event costs a small donation plus a non-perishable food item.&amp;nbsp; The write up by Living waters is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us to HELP FIGHT HUNGER! For a small donation you will pick out a unique bowl that has been made/bought/recycled and keep that bowl as a reminder of all the empty bowls in this world. You will enjoy some homemade soups &amp;#150; made/donated and served by the Culinary St&amp;#133;udents of Greater Lowell Tech, Lowell HS&amp;#146;s Hospitality Academy, Nashoba Valley Tech., Nashua Tech Center, Chowder Factory and more&amp;#133;&amp;#133;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will also have a presentation, music and a raffle that includes local artist&amp;#146;s pieces, local business gift certificates, etc. This continues to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;ALL PROCEEDS FROM THIS EVENT TO BENEFIT &amp;#147;LIVING WATERS CENTER OF HOPE&amp;#148; and they in turn will be sharing a portion of the proceeds with the Merrimack Valley Food Bank!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This year, as well as a tax-deductible donation, you will be asked to bring a non-perishable food item for Merrimack Valley Food Bank&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So come on out and meetup with us for a great cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would also like to make a bowl to donate, the following stores are participating, just mention the Empty Bowls for a special price:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magic Brush Pottery of Tewksbury&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time to Clay of Nashua&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fire Your Desire of Acton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ancient Echos of Art of Chelmsford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Artwood Studios of Dracut.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you all at this event.&amp;nbsp; Remember to bring the Meetup cell phone number in case you get lost or can't find us (978-304-2811).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Near the Entrance of the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327327343000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323223709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Lowell Empty Bowl</name><id>43647122</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327253400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/43647122/</event_url></item>