<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hopkinton, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><lat>42.225433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hopkinton State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>3554392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.548653</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Here's a spot where those who need to rent a kayak can do so.  More info at:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://boatinginboston.com/locations/hopkinton-state-park.html"&gt;http://boatinginboston.com/locations/hopkinton-state-park.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd recommend calling ahead to confirm they are open for business if you need to rent.  I'd also consider getting there nice and early so you can take care of your rental business and be ready to paddle with everyone as soon as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopkinton State Park is not a fabulous place to paddle.  It's a good place to try out a new kayak to see how you do, or to rent if you don't have one.  We'll keep it simple and paddle  slowly while exploring the area.  We can talk about safety, good stroke technique and posture so you can get the most out of your paddling experience.  It's a small enough place for people to stay as long as they like, or leave when they have had enough.  Pack a lunch and we can find a spot to sit and eat after we have paddled for a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a $5 fee to enter the park.  Besides kayaking, there are hiking trails and picnic areas.  It's a nice place to spend the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at the boat launch next to the kayak rental area.  Please arrive by 10:00 and we'll start paddling when everyone is ready.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Nancy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336874276000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334582915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginner's Paddle at Hopkinton State Park</name><id>60770002</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336831200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/60770002/</event_url></item>