<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>96 Winthrop Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tommy Doyles Irish Pub &amp; Restuarant Harvard</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1532939</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come out and meet other Boston area Science Fiction and Fantasy fans in a comfortable setting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the regular social meetup for the Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group, which always happens on the First Tuesday of every month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE - We're back at Tommy Doyle's Irish Pub &amp;amp; Restaurant in Harvard Square. The entire downstairs is available for us, but seats still go quickly! If we have a big regular turnout, they're willing to consider blocking off the upstairs for us, so please, come out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our group meets DOWNSTAIRS, so if you find yourself sitting upstairs next to people who aren't interested in BSG or LOTR, you are in the wrong place. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their website is here: &lt;a href="http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.tommydoyles.com/blog/harvard-square/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're taking the T, Harvard Square is on the Red Line, and Tommy Doyle's is a short walk south (just beside the Winthrop Square park). If you're familiar with Harvard Square, Tommy Doyle's is on the section of Winthrop Street that is closed to cars, but open to foot traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a map:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=96+Winthrop+Street+Cambridge,+MA&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.010019,0.013518&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=96+Winthrop+St,+Cambridge,+Massachusetts+02138&amp;amp;ll=42.373205,-71.120199&amp;amp;spn=0.002513,0.005423&amp;amp;z=18" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=96+Winthrop+Street+Cambridge,+MA&amp;amp;sll=42.566534,-71.539188&amp;amp;sspn=0.010019,0.013518&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=96+Winth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're driving in, there are several parking lots nearby:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a pay lot (Harvard Square Parking Garage) at 20 Eliot St, Cambridge, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Evening Rates Entering After 5 PM are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1/2 Hour or Less $4.00-1 Hour or Less $8.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1 1/2 Hours or Less $14.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;-1 1/2 Hours to Close $15.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;- Lost Ticket: $30.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;- $2.00 Validation When Stamped By Affiliated Vendors (Not sure if Tommy Doyle's validates or not)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is another pay lot at the Charles Hotel at One Bennett St. Cambridge, MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$7.00 1 hour &lt;br /&gt;

 $16.00 2 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $19.00 3 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $21.00 6 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 $25.00 12 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 Daily Max: $34.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there is yet another pay lot at 124 Mount Auburn St, Cambridge, MA. Details for that lot are here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston.centralparking.com/Cambridge-124-Mount-Auburn-Street-Parking.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://boston.centralparking.com/Cambridge-124-Mount-Auburn-Street-Parking.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is metered parking in Harvard Square, but it usually goes very quickly. I personally park at the Alewife T stop (7 dollars a day) and take the Red Line to Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll probably talk about the books, television, movies, comics and games that we like (and those we don't like, and even those we may be ashamed to admit that we like), but there is no set agenda!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're can't come on time, that's fine, there is usually still a critical mass of people until 8:00 PM (or later). If you want to come a bit early, that is fine too, I try to get there around 6 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have SciFi/Fantasy Books or DVDs that you don't want anymore? Feel free to bring them to the meetup and give them away (please, no sales here), but be sure that you take home anything that is left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, as a reminder, we don't charge for our meetup, but the restaurant that hosts our social meetups greatly appreciates your business (and doesn't charge us a room rental fee as a result), so please come hungry (or at least buy a drink).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>All the way downstairs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318707900000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315417187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Social Meetup 2011</name><id>32615762</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317767400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/32615762/</event_url></item>