<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've reserved the Screening room at 360 State Street for another Movie Night! Come see a film for free at this great location!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees: I will need your &lt;strong&gt;FULL NAME (and that of any +1) for the Concierge&lt;/strong&gt; to let you in. Please Provide when you RSVP. (Event Comment, Email, or Text me.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, there should be &lt;em&gt;NO&lt;/em&gt; Maybe's for this event.  Only RSVP if you're going to come, and change accordingly if something comes up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Events Film Is...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Children of Men&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (2006 - Drama / Sci-Fi - 109 min. - R)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0206634/"&gt;Link to the IMDB Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Staring: Clive Owen, Julianne Moore, Michael Caine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description: In the somewhat near future, the human race ceases to be able to procreate.  No child has been born for 18 years.  The first pregnancy for over a decade occurs in less than politically desirable circumstances, and a former activist must help transport the mother to safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roger Ebert gave this film 4 Stars and it received a 93% fresh rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;AJ's Comments: It's been years since I've seen this film.  In limited release it was part action chase, part Art, part drama.  While I'm sure many will pick up on or champion a message related to children and life from it, I remember enjoying an artistic Emphasis on Sounds throughout the film.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1b29"&gt;Event start time is &lt;strong&gt;7:00 for the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;social&lt;/span&gt; portion&lt;/strong&gt;, so you can start showing up then &lt;em&gt;but please no earlier&lt;/em&gt;. We will not &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;start the film until &lt;strong&gt;7:30&lt;/strong&gt; or shortly there after, but don't plan to be any later&lt;/span&gt;.  (There are restrictions on room time.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3f57a4"&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. If someone else backs out you can be automatically added, just provide your full name for the concierge as a contingency.  (I recommend RSVPing individually rather than using +1's if wait-listing.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just Please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are &lt;span&gt;instructions with a phone number on the door and&lt;/span&gt; a call box with bell button. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call/text AJ at 315-345-9348&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street (some with Credit Card slot available.), obey the posted limits on the meter.  If you don't mind the longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evening/weekends. (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street.) 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only, the entrance is on State Street just to the Right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring the Bell Button or Call the concierge on the cell phone number on the door, they will Direct you. If you have added problems, call AJ at 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336333341000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335305968000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: Children of Men</name><id>61971492</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336258800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/61971492/</event_url></item>