<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In June we'll meet at Chaibo in Fitchburg to discuss &lt;em&gt;Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother&lt;/em&gt; by Amy Chua. Cool off with one of Chaibo's yummy smoothies or gelatos while our discussion heats up over this controversial book! As always, we'll be at the first set of comfy couches by the door. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Note: In June we're meeting the fourth Thursday of the month rather than our usual last Thursday of the month.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of the book by Publisher's Weekly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chua  imparts the secret behind the stereotypical Asian child's phenomenal success: the Chinese mother. Chua promotes what has traditionally worked very well in raising children: strict, Old World, uncompromising values--and the parents don't have to be Chinese. What they are, however, are different from what she sees as indulgent and permissive Western parents: stressing academic performance above all, never accepting a mediocre grade, insisting on drilling and practice, and instilling respect for authority. Chua and her Jewish husband (both are professors at Yale Law) raised two girls, and her account of their formative years achieving amazing success in school and music performance proves both a model and a cautionary tale. Sophia, the eldest, was dutiful and diligent, leapfrogging over her peers in academics and as a Suzuki piano student; Lulu was also gifted, but defiant, who excelled at the violin but eventually balked at her mother's pushing. Chua's efforts "not to raise a soft, entitled child" will strike American readers as a little scary--removing her children from school for extra practice, public shaming and insults, equating Western parenting with failure--but the results, she claims somewhat glibly in this frank, unapologetic report card, "were hard to quarrel with."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be sitting at the first set of comfy couches by the door. See you there!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1308926759000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306798533000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother by Amy Chua</name><id>20285001</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308870000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/20285001/</event_url></item>