<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our own Ginger Asel will be holding a post sunrise Easter service at the top of Wachusett Mountain on Sunday for anyone interested in joining her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.wachusett.com/EventsActivities/CalendarofEvents/EasterDayCelebration/tabid/750/Default.aspx"&gt;http://www.wachusett.com/EventsActivities/CalendarofEvents/EasterDayCelebration/tabid/750/Default.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 EASTER DAY CELEBRATION&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, March 31st&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Easter Sunday at the mountain with a variety of activities for the whole family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7am Sunrise Service &lt;br /&gt;

 Join us atop the mountain for a morning service just after sunrise. Reverend Ginger E. Asel will preside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get to the service please take the Polar Express Chairlift, which begin taking people to the summit at 6:30am. A valid (FREE) lift ticket will be required to access the lift. This can be picked up at Customer Service starting at 6am. In the event of inclement weather, the service will be conducted inside the base lodge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8am-10am Easter Breakfast &lt;br /&gt;

 Join us for an Easter Breakfast served up hot in the cafeteria. Plenty of options to choose from and a great way to start to the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10:00am &amp;amp; 10:30am Easter Egg Hunt &lt;br /&gt;

 Two Separate Easter Egg Hunts: The first will be a hunt for the little ones - ages 4-8 who will gather off the granite room deck. The second will be for the older kids, ages 9-14 and will take place near the Easy Rider lift. (we will temporarily be closing this area to skiing and riding during the hunt).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11:00am Orson's Easter Parade! &lt;br /&gt;

 Keep your eyes peeled for Orson, who will be handing out special prizes and lead kids around the base area! A great photo opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Easter Day Deal! &lt;br /&gt;

 Dress like an Easter Bunny or wear your best Easter Bonnet and receive a 1/2 Price Lift Ticket! (outfit must be visible while skiing or riding).&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Atop the mountain via free lift</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ginger asel</member_name><member_id>10242894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364754252000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364255105000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Easter Service Atop Wachusett Mtn/Hike?/Ski/ Egg Hunt/ Breakfast</name><id>111044472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364727600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/111044472/</event_url></item>