<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Game night has been a fan favorite for the last few years. This is a fun way to break up the long nights and to socialize with other hikers. This year the December game night will be held at a new venue, the Stone &amp;amp; Paddle Restaurant in Rocky Hill, CT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/1/8/event_187352792.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;We&lt;/span&gt; plan on having a private dining room all to ourselves with the doors closed for privacy. The cozy dining room with electric fireplace for a rustic accent will warm our souls as we dine and later socialize and play games. This year we are not asking for a donation for facility costs or a pot-luck item. You will order what you would like to eat from the varied menu. Parking is sufficient at this plaza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also have a white elephant gift exchange after dinner where if you bring a wrapped gift worth about $5-$10, you can participate. Participation is optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will run from 6:30 PM to 9:00 PM. Dinner is planned to start at 7 PM but there is some flexibility in when you order your meal. RSVP's close on Wednesday, December 19th at 8 PM so please register!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can order your own meal or you can order together with your friends. Everyone will have separate checks unless you wish to combine with others. &lt;span&gt;There will be a cash bar for sodas or alcoholic beverages.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The menu with prices&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.stoneandpaddle.com/pdf/Stone%20&amp;amp;%20Paddle%20RH%208112.pdf"&gt;http://www.stoneandpaddle.com/pdf/Stone%20&amp;amp;%20Paddle%20RH%208112.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No&lt;/strong&gt; outside food or drink is allowed by the restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donations&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, but &lt;strong&gt;no&lt;/strong&gt; donations will be sought this year for the December event. In previous years food was pot-luck and donations were sought to pay for the meeting hall but we are trying something different now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gift Exchange:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be doing a &lt;strong&gt;Naughty Santa&lt;/strong&gt; (a.k.a White Elephant) gift exchange (&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_elephant_gift_exchange"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_elephant_gift_exchange&lt;/a&gt;) for those who wish to participate. All you need to do is bring a wrapped gift worth roughly $5-$10 (you can spend more if you like but don't expect something worth more). P&lt;span&gt;aper bag wrapping is fine for the eco-conscious. Follow the link above to learn the basics of how the exchange works. The Naughty Santa version of the White Elephant can get a bit "spicy" over the plain White Elephant version of the game as some gifts may be a little sexy. You just don't know what may be in the next gift... all in the interest of fun! Rules will be set at the start of play. If you want to go all out, go ahead and dress up for the Naughty Santa exchange (holiday themed attire).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;An example of a Naughty Santa meetup event (photos): &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Winos-R-Us/photos/1193991/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Winos-R-Us/photos/1193991/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Games&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a restaurant, the table space and layout is somewhat limiting for game play but we will try the best we can to make do. You can always stick to eating and socializing, especially by the fireplace!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the games we have already:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;* Picture Picture &lt;br /&gt;

 * Worst Case Scenario &lt;br /&gt;

 * Scrabble &lt;br /&gt;

 * Fact or Crap &lt;br /&gt;

 * Jenga (well a knockoff version) &lt;br /&gt;

 * Cards (for various card games)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'd like to see someone bring these as well as anything else:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;* Bolderdash &lt;br /&gt;

 * Cranium &lt;br /&gt;

 * Pictionary &lt;br /&gt;

 * Bring any other game you might think 4 - 6 people at least could play at the same time. Team games would be great too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all hope you can attend and enjoy a warm evening with great people. Last year this was a hit with 50 - 60 people going each time! Because of being so close to Christmas this year and in competing with the Mayan "end of the world" the day of the event, our gathering is a bit smaller this time around but let's not let that detract from the fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you RSVP "yes" and later can't go, please remember to change your RSVP so someone else can go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We plan to have a birthday party/game night event in January, 2013 back at the condo complex just like last year. In February, we hope to be back at a restaurant for the final game night of the winter season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Stone and Paddle Italian Restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.stoneandpaddle.com/index.cfm"&gt;http://www.stoneandpaddle.com/index.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the dinning room which is to the back-right through the establishment.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356812029000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353395624000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Dinner &amp; Game Night in Rocky Hill CT</name><id>92146382</id><duration>9000000</duration><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356132600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/92146382/</event_url></item>