<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>332 Riverside Drive</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10025</zip><lat>40.801903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New York Buddhist Church</name><city>New York</city><id>3702072</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.970024</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jodo Shinshu Boot Camp &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday, November 3, 2012 | 10:00 AM – 4:30 PM &lt;br /&gt;

American Buddhist Study Center &lt;br /&gt;

331 Riverside Drive (between 105 and 106 Streets) &lt;br /&gt;

New York, NY 10025 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Power of Shin Buddhism &lt;br /&gt;

And the Buddha’s Call to Awaken NOW! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

With Camp Master &lt;br /&gt;

Reverend/Professor Mark Unno &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you are a Buddhist or have an interest in Buddhism, this one-day Shin Buddhist boot camp is just for you. Prof. Mark Unno will take us through Buddhist essentials concepts and teach why Shin Buddhism is so relevant to today’s global society. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

A basic precept of Buddhism is that we are all interconnected. Join the boot camp to experience this firsthand. We will come away with a deeper awareness of who we are and how each of us is connected to all things in life. Mark will open our hearts and minds, helping us to look deep within ourselves to realize (even though this may seem to be a cliché) that we are not alone. Where our western society is so focused on self and ego, an eastern and Buddhist perspective can show us that our true significance is based on our interconnectedness with the universe through Amida Buddha. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Dress comfortably and be prepared to come with an open mind to engage with Mark’s fearless compassion and wisdom. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Mark Unno is Professor and Head of the Department of Religious Studies at the University of Oregon. He received his Ph.D. from Stanford University and continues his research in Classical Japanese Buddhism focusing on Shin and Zen Buddhism. He is the author of Shingon Refractions: Myoe and Mantra of Light as well as other Buddhist books and papers. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

RSVP: 212-864-7424 or email &lt;br /&gt;

Admin@AmericanBudddhistStudyCenter.org &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Donation: $20 for ABSC members, students, and seniors; all others $30 contribution is requested. A light lunch is included. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://americanbuddhiststudycenter.org/ambuddhist.org/programs/" class="linkified"&gt;http://americanbuddhiststudycenter.org/ambuddhist.org/programs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside around 10 a.m.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351975522000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351525831000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Power of Shin Buddhism event in NYC with Dr. M. Unno</name><id>89036512</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351953000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/89036512/</event_url></item>