<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Spring Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06040</zip><lat>41.759903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Highland Park Recreation Area</name><city>manchester</city><id>1739891</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.502731</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come explore the Case Brothers historic district and take a 3-mile history hike from the trailhead to the summit of Case Mountain in the Highland Park section of Manchester. We will see a waterfall, stone walls, carriage path, and Case mansions, as well as forest and ponds. Wear sturdy shoes or sneakers and expect some wet spots, very steep climbs, and bumpy terrain. The hike and commentary will take about two hours. Participants in this moderately paced (and SLOW at the beginning, but FASTER and strenuous as we go along) hike will learn basic hiking skills and, depending on the weather, view the Hartford skyline from the summit of Case Mountain. We will view property owned by the Town of Manchester and by the Manchester Land Conservation Trust. Led by Susan Barlow. Hike starts at the Spring Street trailhead: From Hartford, take I-84 eastbound to I-384, exit 4, right off exit ramp. Follow Spring Street down a curve and then down a steep hill, over a one-lane bridge. Parking along one side of Spring Street, with a little parking at the trail head. Extreme weather cancels. No dogs, please. Co-sponsored by the CT Forest and Park Association Family Ramble Program, but open to all, including singles. No dogs, please. The reason this hike starts out slow is that we talk about the history of the area, view the old paper mills and the Case brothers' mansions, before picking up the pace to go up to the summit. The Case Mountain Recreation Area has over 600 acres of forest, brooks, rock formations, and trails. Come find out more. Let me know if questions! &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/d/7/event_24784311.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue backpack</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan B</member_name><member_id>7644854</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357055281000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>68</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349095690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Highland Park History Hike</name><id>84912622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356804000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/84912622/</event_url></item>