<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>94 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348351</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass Ave Tavern</name><city>Boston</city><id>5496632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088005</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to get some new books for free? Do you have some books that you enjoyed and would like to share with others? Or perhaps you have some books that don't match your interests. Then join us for dinner and a book swap. The Tavern will also be providing us with some complimentary appetizers. We've done book swaps in the past and they have been a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; Once you swap a book, your original book will NOT be returned to you. Please only bring books that are in excellent condition. NO textbooks, young adult books, damaged/ripped books. You are welcome to bring as many books with you as you would like. Each guest swaps for the same amount of books that they brought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each member pays for their own food/drink. &lt;strong&gt;We must have an accurate headcount, so please only sign up if you can definitely attend the event. If your plans change, please change your RSVP as soon as possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) at our tables. If you have trouble finding us, please call 774 232 0000.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333753325000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331147801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Book Swap at Mass Ave Tavern</name><id>55388872</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332370800000</time><rsvp_limit>37</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/55388872/</event_url></item>