<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>661 Main Street, Holden</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.324123</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>508-829-4566</phone><name>The Blue Plate Lounge</name><city>Worcester</city><id>591303</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.834250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Several people have indicated an interest in getting together earlier for dinner, so we'll be meeting at Vivian's Market Style Cafe, 184 West Boylston Street in West Boylston. (508)835-6100. This is the plaza where Planet Fitness and The Salter School are located. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vivian's is brand new, so I haven't eaten there yet, but I have been told by several friends that the food is good and the prices are reasonable. We should meet there by 7PM, which will give us plenty of time to have dinner and get over to the Blue Plate early. Jason usually fills up the &amp;quot;Plate,&amp;quot; so the earlier we get there, the better the chances we have of getting a table or two. Either way it will be a great show.  If you can't make dinner, but plan to see and hear Jason, then plan on getting to the Blue Plate at least a half hour early. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you plan to eat out with us by 6PM if possible.  I'd like to have a head count so that I can call ahead and make sure they have some tables together for our group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cover charge is usually only $5 - the best deal in town!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you tonight!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a meetup sign in plain sight, and I'll grab a table for us if I can.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209951142000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Ask any one of the 11 people from our group who saw Jason last month and they'll all tell you that he was a blast to hear as well as to watch.</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209344343000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jason James and the Bay State House Rockers</name><id>7824640</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209778200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7824640/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/8/b/global_3945467.jpeg</photo_url></item>