<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Financial District Faneuil Hall area</address_2><address_1>160 Milk Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-451-9460</phone><name>Jose McIntyre's</name><city>Boston</city><id>326634</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052719</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE, TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP It's time for another Mix +Mingle cross Meetup Private Party for 200+ members at Jose McIntyre's (near Faneuil Hall) at 160 Milk St Boston, MA 02109. Tel. (617) 451-9460 Website: www.irishconnection.com/jose.html Jose McIntyre's 2nd floor holds 200 people. We&amp;#146;ll have our own DJ, dance floor, bathrooms, appetizers, bar area, couches, 2 bartenders, etc. so this will truly be a private party. I pre-buy $400 in appetizers (wings, veggie platter, etc.) in advance, since their kitchen is too small to accommodate food for 200 members. There will be NO refills on food. A good reason to get there early and enjoy some great food while it lasts. Note: Background music will be at low levels upstairs from 7 to 9PM so members will have a a quite time to chat. After 9PM the dancing + loud music starts. Please do not complain, since members come to dance to music after 9PM. When you get there just head upstairs, there should be a private party sign up. Then meet/greet Biagio, your host for the night. Please introduce yourself, say what group you are with, and have a $5 bill in hand at the top of the stairs (no $1 bills, please). We cannot block the stairs and security will make members to go back downstairs if you take too long. 1. Everyone, but the invited Meetup Group Head Organizers, pays $5 cash. 2. After 9 p.m. you might have to pay another cover charge to the bar, so stretch your dollar and come before 9PM. If you get in before 9PM you ONLY have to pay $5 to Biagio. 3. It will be packed. Get there early to ensure you can get in. 4. If you come after 8PM you might not get in right away and you will have to wait in a long line downstairs. This has happened before and another reason to come elary! 5. They have good AC unlike that last place we went to so it should not get hot upstairs. The Meetup Groups that are invited to come: Social Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Biagio) The Boston Volunteer Meetup &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/"&gt;http://www.bostonvolu...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Josh) Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meetup.com/421/"&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Tonya) Girls just want to have FUN &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/FUNgirls/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Sarah) The Boston Euro Social Meetup &lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.com/76/"&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt; (not Confirmed by Noelle) The World is Our Playground Meetup &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-World-is-Our-Playground/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Ralph) The Boston Culture Club Meetup &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Culture-Club/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; (Confirmed by Joanna) Single Geeks, Nerds And Professionals (30-49) &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Professional-Geeky-Si.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Alison) We normally have over 150 members at these Mix and Mingle parties. I hope you can all join us for this blast of a party. It should be fun! Ciao, Biagio&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332769411000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>45</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331075040000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mix &amp; Mingle</name><id>55264212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332543600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/55264212/</event_url></item>