<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Buffalo Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03266</zip><lat>43.814055</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rumney</name><city>Rumney</city><id>807315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.858176</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;: Climbing gear, sleeping bag, tent, clothing suitable for climbing and variable weather, swim suit for the initiation dive in the river, towel, toiletries, water, food, snacks, Camp chair, fire wood and liquor its an essential part of the crag pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we'll be camping at Rattlesnake Mtn campground&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that are staying over, it’s $12.00 per person per night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner:&lt;/strong&gt; pot luck dinner, bring something and eat hearty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday we'll meet at Wellington train station at 7pm to carpool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;:  for those that are going to be driving up on Saturday, we’ll meet you at the main parking lot at 900 am. the directions are, rt93 north to exit 26 take rt25 west to Rumney, follow rt25 to the rotary stay on rt25 west, the polar caves will be on the left. follow rt25 till you see the sign for Rumney village (double blinking yellow lights over head) take that right onto main st, go over a bridge take that left at the church which is Buffalo rd, about 1 miles on the right you will come to the parking lot for climbing at Rumney.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you have a GPS use this address 410 buffalo rd Rumney NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;for those that are coming up saturday morning, WE"LL MEET AT THE PAY STAION PICNIC TABLE...... WAIT TILL I GET THERE....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>main parking lot at the pay station there is a picnic table meet there</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>bob griffin</member_name><member_id>9493844</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1344266507000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335898942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Climbing n Camping with the Moonshine sippers</name><id>ddgsbdyqlbgb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344085200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/62953632/</event_url></item>