<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>SOUTH END </address_2><address_1>1277 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.342229</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peter's Park - Joe Wex Dog Run</name><city>Boston</city><id>152593</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067787</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per meetup</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>First French Bulldog meetup this Spring!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's welcome the warm weather and get the kids out to play!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is my first meetup as organizer so I'm going to switch things up a bit.  I've heard from so many members already about venues etc (I'm trying to answer everybody)-THANKS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I decided to forge ahead and plan the first meeting at our old favorite Peters Park in the South End.  I know the gravel is not ideal but can be much better than mud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few changes:&lt;br /&gt;Meeting dues is $4 per meetup payed via paypal on the site. This is to cover meetup fees, and other goodies.&lt;br /&gt;My biggest issue with the Peters Park is trying to hold onto Simon's leash, my bag, and a cup of java and open the gates.  SO, I will have with me a few boxes of Java from DD.  Bring a mug or I'll have cups.  Also, I'll have name tags for everybody so we can remember names.  Additionally, every meetup will have goodie bags for the kids to take home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing everybody! Let's keep our fingers crossed for good weather&lt;br /&gt;Terri &amp;amp; Simon&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a meetup name tag on and meetup name tags for all who rsvp YES.  You won't be able to miss the group!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206449329000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Who needs a reason? If you own a frenchie you JUST know...put 20 of them together and you can't stop laughing. It's great to discuss behavioral or health issues specific to the breed.</why><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205249813000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's revive this Frenchie meetup! First Spring meetup.</name><id>7510428</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206194400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/7510428/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/1/global_381217.jpeg</photo_url></item>