<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We did this walk last Sunday both the humans and the dogs had a blast. With the weather supposed to be so beautiful this Sunday we figured we'd do it again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group of us will be meeting at The ML Donovan Elementary School at 123 Reed Street in Randolph, MA Sunday, January 13th at noon for a leashed "pack walk" with our bullies. The ML Donovan Elementary School backs up to trails in the Blue Hills reservation and offers plenty of parking for all of us to meet. The trails are not cleaned so snow boots are probably a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are actually two parking lots for the school. We will be meeting in the lot that is technically at the front of the building, not the one with the playgrounds in it. If you are running late you can message me on here or on Facebook, it will go directly to my phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come socialize yourself and your pup with a responsible group of breed enthusiasts :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just a friendly reminder regarding etiquette at NEBBC-hosted/sponsored events, but nevertheless needs to be taken very seriously and is expected to be followed, especially considering the size of the club and all the newbies!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dog/Handler Etiquette:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ NO flexi-leashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Avoid head-on greetings between dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Until you are familiar with individual dogs AND handlers, contact between dogs must be kept to a minimum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Prevent your dog from lunging on leash, whether it is in play or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Dog(s) must be kept under owner control at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Do not allow your dog to surprise, or "sneak up on" other dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ A VERY important note: Just because two dogs are friendly, does not necessarily mean they are going to be friendly with each other. Make no assumptions and DO NOT LET YOUR DOG GREET ANOTHER DOG until you have asked and BEEN GIVEN PERMISSION by the owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ If your dog is reactive, use your good judgement. (Be up front, and give everyone their space. Do not "test" if your dog will be ok by letting him go up to unsuspecting dogs/handlers if you've known him to be aggressive toward either.) Muzzling is an option and an opportunity to still expose your dog while keeping everyone safe. Take all necessary precautions. You are still representing our club and our dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Dog must be wearing a securely fitting collar/harness or combo thereof with NO chance of slipping it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not intended to sound harsh, but with the size of the club and with our emphasis on raising awareness &amp;amp; promoting responsible ownership, it is very important that this etiquette be taken seriously&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

ALL BREEDS WELCOME!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358783351000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357830606000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Hills Reservation Bully Walk</name><id>98912872</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358096400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/98912872/</event_url></item>