<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Bonjour à toutes et à tous,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suite au succès de la première Boston French Party de 2008 le 15 Janvier à Caprice (vous avez vraiment mis l'ambiance!) et aux nombreuses demandes que nous avons reçues depuis, les Boston French Party deviennent bi-mensuelles! &lt;br /&gt;Et oui, une soirée toutes les 2 semaines! Prochaine soirée le Mardi 29 Janvier à Caprice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus de musique française, plus de rencontres et toujours plus de fête!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ce rythme plus régulier nous permettra de faire des soirées à thèmes, de varier davantage les bars et de continuer à faire vibrer Boston le mardi soir! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bientôt!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the success of our first Boston French Party of 2008, held on January 15th at Caprice and the numerous requests we have received since then, we have decided to have a party every 2 weeks! &lt;br /&gt;Yes, every 2 weeks! The next party will be held on Tuesday, January the 29th at Caprice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More French music, more people to meet and more party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This frequency will give us the opportunity to organize parties with themes, to try new places and to continue to be the rhythm of Boston on Tuesday nights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julien</member_name><member_id>1573841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201831855000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>voulezvous</urlname><id>541017</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Voulez-vous français Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200452985000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Party January Meetup - number 2</name><id>7125859</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201658400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/voulezvous/events/7125859/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/b/6/global_3049974.jpeg</photo_url></item>