<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>141 Green St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.310730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Axiom Gallery</name><city>Boston</city><id>905506</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107583</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Matt Boynton is a new member of creative peoples and turns out he and I have similar roles in the creative community. Matt runs creative networking events at galleries in the Boston area - basically inviting a bunch of artists and creative professionals to come have some wine and network with &lt;br /&gt;each other and promote their work in a comfortable environment while checking out the gallery exhibitions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His next event is next Friday, May 1st from 6-9ish at Axiom in Jamaica Plain, Matt indicated that Creative peoples were welcome to come, so I am posting it as an event here. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to contact Matt or check out his profile you can see it here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/creativepeeps/members/9418514/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From the Axiom Site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Creative Contact [ &lt;a href="http://www.creativecontact.com"&gt;http://www.creativeco...&lt;/a&gt; ]at Axiom for an enjoyable and productive evening of art, networking, refreshments, and great conversation. Learn about Art Technology New England, Axiom's latest project in Creative Economy Development, sponsored by the Massachusetts Cultural Council. ATNE is a consortium of four sectors working in art and technology: business, non-profit, academic, and individuals/clubs groups/collectives. Come discover how Axiom, ATNE, and Creative Contact can help you further your creative career. Feel free to stay for as long as you like. Please bring business cards or samples of your work if you have them. We will provide nametags and writing materials. Everyone is looking forward to getting to know you, so don't be shy about starting up a conversation with someone new! Creative Contact (www.creativecontact.com) helps artists become successful doing what they love. Creative Contact makes it easier for artists and creative professionals to promote themselves and their work, find jobs and other artists to work with, and collaborate online on creative projects. We have formed partnerships with a number of art institutions across the US and offer free enhanced accounts for all art students. We also run monthly creative networking events at progressive art galleries in the Northeast, inviting artists, creative professionals, employers, and businesspeople to network and promote talent within the creative community. You can check out our blog at blog.creativecontact.com. If you're interested in coming to one of our events or learning more about us, feel free to email info@creativecontact.com.  Free and Open to the Public but please RSVP -- Refreshments served &lt;br /&gt;RSVP at &lt;a href="http://creativecontactataxiom.eventbrite.com"&gt;http://creativecontac...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The Gallery is located in the Green Street T Station</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241406458000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240526431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creative Networking with Matt Boynton &amp; Creative Contacts</name><id>10254549</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241218800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/10254549/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/global_8388093.jpeg</photo_url></item>