<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Franconia Ridge Mts Lafayette/Lincoln/Little Haystack and Liberty&lt;br /&gt;Approximately 11 miles 5,000’ elev gain/allow  9+ hours - Strenuous&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Meeting location listed on the meetup is AFTER the carspot so the time is 7:45 at the&lt;br /&gt;Whitehouse Trailhead carspot from where we will travel to the meetup location.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting at Skookumchuck Trail and then onto Garfield Ridge Trails to Lafayette and across the Fanconia Ridge Trial to Lincoln, Little Haystack, and Liberty.  We will descend the Liberty Springs Trail to the Whitehouse Trailhead parking area.  This hike includes (3) offical 4,000 footers.  All should meet to carspot at Whitehouse Trailhead (directions below) at 7:45 AM where we will drive up to Skookumchuck Trail to begin hiking at about 8 AM.   This route does not include a hut so it will be important to bring adequate water (a gallon or more) for a strenuous hike.  We can replenish water shortly after descending Liberty along the Liberty Springs Trail near the campground. You need to be an experienced hiker in good physical condition. The Skookumchuck Trail has very good footing but is steep and a bit long and so it will be the toughest part of the journey.  It will take about 3 to 4 hours to reach Lafayette where we will have lunch.  Things will get easier after that especially if we have a clear day along the ridge.&lt;br /&gt;If you are traveling a long distance, you may wish to consider camping at Lafayette Place Campground either the night before or the night of the hike.  No dogs or children please.  I will have a cooler for the end of the hike with liquid refreshments and some munchies for when we finish (probably between 5 and 6 pm).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions To Whitehouse Trailhead Parking Lot NH Route 3:&lt;br /&gt;I-93 to Franconia Notch State Parkway take Exit f34A or the Flume Visitors Center and follow signs to exit the Visitors Center onto Route 3 and then proceed  0.2 mi. north along Route 3.  Take right after sign &amp;quot;Trailhead Parking&amp;quot; - once in lot, take left at the fork and park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 AM/Departure Exit 14 off I-93 Concord NH in the Hannaford’s parking lot near the highway.  &lt;br /&gt;If carpooling from Concord NH, please indicate so in your rsvp comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GEAR:  A gallon or more water, sunscreen, sunglasses, bugspray, rain jacket/rain pants, and fleece.  We will be hiking several miles along an exposed ridge which typically is windy.   It is recommended to bring a headlamp although daylight is on our side in June.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WEATHER: forecast of downpour or high probability of thunderstorms will cancel.  &lt;br /&gt;If the forecast is not good but not horrid, we could tackle just one peak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Disclaimer: As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, including those caused by negligence and or other reasons. You also agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for New England Hiking Meetup at Whitehouse Trailhead parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>4KDiane</member_name><member_id>7411900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277604294000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273345557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Franconia Ridge Traverse Advanced</name><id>13423963</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277466300000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13423963/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/2/global_14898706.jpeg</photo_url></item>