<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There will be a change in the location for stargazing this night if time permits for it. The change should prove to be a benefit to all the members of the astronomy group. Its a much closer location, 5 minutes from Oxford center. And there is a safe paved parking lot for the cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; After contacting the head of the Army Of Engineers at Buffumville Dam Charlton Mass, i have acquired permission to set up the telescopes on the premises after all. This area is very nice, the grounds behind the dam (where we will set up) is a little low to the horizon. It never was an issue to past astronomy groups that have set up there, so it should not interfere for us at all. There are very dark sky's there also!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If everyone likes this location we could have regular scheduled meetings there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Charlton police have been notified and all officers should have been notified of the group being there by are first meeting date.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Norm and his wife has invited The Oxford Astronomy Group to view a DVD on the Basics of Astronomy at there home.                 &lt;br /&gt;The DVD is about an 1 1/2, depending on if there is a lot of discussion during and about the video we may not be able to view in its entirety? If the weather is not favorable this will not be an issue.      &lt;br /&gt;I have purchased 3 of these learning videos and we will get a chance to view all of them in time, each advancing a little more into astronomy. But not to worry because all of the DVD's are based for the new backyard astronomer.             &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather permitting and time allowing after the video we will set up the telescopes in Conn. If members prefer we may be able to set up in Sutton Mass instead, from what i have seen this area looks very nice and its much closer for all the members. We are working on acquiring permission for this area and should know in a few days if permission was granted. I will post when i know for sure if we can use this area. Bug spay may be a good idea for April 18.      &lt;br /&gt;             &lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if location is a factor for attending the next Meetup, Woodstock Conn or Sutton Mass.             &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                                      I am looking forward to this Meetup.             &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                          thank you,             &lt;br /&gt;                                                                                                     Bill     &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Norman's address will posted to members soon.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3613014</member_name><member_id>3613014</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243204935000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238103775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>View The Basics of Astronomy Cd and Observing in Conn</name><id>10044136</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240092000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/10044136/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/b/global_7814683.jpeg</photo_url></item>