<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>194 Cranberry Road</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.839191</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Carver</city><id>4508802</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.691452</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Buffett and I invite those with or without dogs to join us on our weekly outings.&amp;nbsp; I am experimenting with this idea so bear with me as I develop a system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buffett and I go out nearly every Sunday and welcome company.&amp;nbsp; These are informal hikes and can be flexible but details won't be firmed up until the day before depending on interest expressed.&amp;nbsp; We welcome suggestions as to type or location (ie. something flat, hilly, long, short, new or established trail.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The starting time will be late morning to early afternoon (so I don't have to rush and the day has a chance to warm up...unless rain is predicted late) and can be modified within that range to meet the needs of anyone who responds, in time, with a specific request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If no one expresses interest for a particular Sunday, Buffett and I will probably just go exploring new territory or trying out routes for future hikes.&amp;nbsp; I will try to post a time and place on Sunday morning.&amp;nbsp; If someone has replied that they want to join us, we'll set up a time and meeting place and I will try to post by early Saturday evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is impromptu hiking and may or may not be workable but let's give it a try.&amp;nbsp; Your needs and suggestions are welcome.&amp;nbsp; Post to the hike or email me through the website.&amp;nbsp; I believe I have turned off the reminders so no one will be flooded with emails cluttering their mailboxes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&amp;nbsp; If someone emails me with a request, I will try to accommodate.&amp;nbsp; ALWAYS CHECK TIME AND PLACE BEFORE HEADING OUT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326121007000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325610355000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's get the dogs out!</name><id>dwxhhcyqcblb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326043800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/46448262/</event_url></item>