<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Company Valuation Metrics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; – How is it Done? Is it negotiable? How is it Improved?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s all about the Valuation - Stupid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are raising capital, selling your company, attracting key talent, making a new investment or just trying to cash out; the company valuation is critical. It is the real world measure of the value of the company on the open market. Ultimately the valuation is what you can defend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the next EntreTech Forum Our panel of experts will discuss the various ways a company’s valuation can be determined including the key components entering into the equation. They will describe their experiences in determining a valuation and negotiating the valuation with buyers, investors, etc. Finally they will discuss ways to improve the valuation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are new to determine a company valuation, need pointers on how to best determine a company’s valuation or are considering a new business opportunity, join us for an exciting and interactive discussion on company valuation lead by our panel of experienced practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panelists include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Oct2012Mtg/bond.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Chris Bond, Area Director, Murphy Business&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris Bond is Area Director for Murphy Business in Franklin, Massachusetts. He is a business broker with over 15 years of experience consulting with small business owners in manufacturing, distribution, technology and business services. Chris specializes in helping businesspeople fully understand market conditions which allow them to make intelligent decisions as they transition forward. &lt;br /&gt;

Prior to joining Murphy, Chris was Partner with Next Level, Inc., a sales management consulting firm and an affiliate of Sandler Training. Chris is a key part of Murphy’s growing team and lives its unifying mission: To assist New England’s businesspeople in the valuation, sale and/or purchase of businesses through incomparably fair, honest and expedient service. &lt;br /&gt;

Chris earned his Bachelor of Arts degree in Marketing from Stonehill College.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Oct2012Mtg/Blyzinskyj.jpg" width="100" height="130" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John Blyzinskyj, Consultant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Blyzinskyj was President of Avotus, a software and IT services company, and has had P&amp;amp;L leadership of IT businesses to $700M in annual revenue. He has significant global operating experience across the High Tech industry with both public and private companies. This has included living and working extensively throughout 3 continents. He has broad experience of Board of Directors, Private Equity investors, and M&amp;amp;A / Joint Venture transactions. This includes both negotiating agreements, as well as leading the post transaction integration of companies. In addition to his multi-national experience John also works with smaller tech companies through the Beacon Angels, a Boston based investment group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John holds a BSc in Electronic Engineering from Kings College, University of London, and an MBA from the Cranfield Institute of Management. He is a dual US / UK National.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeff Lucas, Managing Director, Neptune Advisors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff is a CFO who has led rapidly-growing public and private technology companies ranging in size from $20 million to $800 million in revenues. He has developed and executed strategic initiatives to achieve growth and profitability objectives, raised debt and equity capital and led the acquisition and integration of a variety of businesses. Most recently, Jeff was a managing director of Neptune Advisors, a strategic consulting firm focused on improving operational performance of closely-held companies in preparation for being sold. In addition to his operating experience, Jeff is a CPA and a Chartered Financial Analyst, has worked on Wall Street and in public accounting (PwC) and received his MBA from Harvard Business School. Jeff is a member of the Board of Directors of the Association for Corporate Growth and The CFO Alliance and is a past president of the Harvard Business School Association of Boston, the School’s alumni organization for its 6,000 local members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Oct2012Mtg/lent.jpg" width="100" height="113" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Bob Lentz, Northeastern University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob is currently Chairman of the Board of Northeastern University’s IDEA Venture Accelerator and EIR for NU’s Center For Entrepreneurship Education. Prior to joining the University he was a consultant serving as interim CEO for technology companies. He has extensive executive management and entrepreneurial experience in the technology industry having been involved in the growth and eventual sale of a number of successful technology ventures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob served as CEO and President of PermissionTV, an innovative online video platform company. Bob also held senior executive positions at OATSystems, Inc.; the recognized leader in radio-frequency identification (RFID) frameworks, now part of Checkpoint; and at eRoom Technology; a Web-based collaborative workspace that enables distributed teams to work together more efficiently; sold to Documentum Inc. and now part of EMC Corp. Additionally, Bob serves on the Board of Directors of Monotype Imaging Corp. (Nasdaq: TYPE) as well having served as a board member and advisor to a number of technology companies in the greater Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He holds an MBA from Babson College and a BS in Business from Northeastern University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfoct2012.eventbrite.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/register.jpg" width="115" height="24" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350437686000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348155290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Company Valuation Metrics</name><id>83282772</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350426600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/83282772/</event_url></item>