<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>315 Market Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.080454</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-431-5500</phone><name>Isles of Shoals Steamship Co</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>969928</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.760547</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Don't miss the 35th annual Market Square Day today! Food!  Live bands and entertainment! Artisan booths and lots more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created to celebrate the renovation and beautification of downtown Portsmouth - and, in particular, Market Square - the festival has grown in size along with the growth and popularity of Portsmouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An estimated 60,000-80,000 people will walk through downtown Portsmouth, enjoying the entertainment, products and food offered by artists, craftspeople and merchants - many from the Seacoast area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On average, 100+ vendor applications are approved/accepted for inclusion in the festival. Three performance stages feature local and regional musicians. The day 'kicks off' with the Market Square Day 10K Road Race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of Downtown Portsmouth will be vehicle-free and pedestrian-friendly from 9am 'til 5pm on the second Saturday in June each year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.proportsmouth.org/MarketSquareDay.cfm"&gt;www.proportsmouth.org/MarketSquareDay.cfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FROM THE CITY OF PORTSMOUTH FOR 2011:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"No parking will be allowed on several downtown streets between 4 a.m. and approximately 6 p.m. A $5 flat-rate parking fee will be collected from each vehicle entering the High-Hanover Parking Facility between 6 a.m. and 1 p.m., and a $3 rate will be collected from 1 p.m. until 4 p.m. Access the garage by turning from Market Street onto Hanover. Payment upon entry to the facility is expected to reduce delays for those leaving after the Market Square Day events. Free shuttle bus service will be available from the Festival’s parking overflow lot at Fox Run Mall. Event details are at www.proportsmouth.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"MARKET SQUARE DAY CLOSURES The following streets will be closed from 4 a.m. until approximately 6 p.m. Saturday (June 11) for Market Square Day: Congress Street; Pleasant Street from State Street to Market Square; Market Street from Bow Street to Market Square; Daniel Street from Chapel/Penhallow Streets to Market Square; Fleet Street; Ladd Street; Chestnut Street (Congress to Porter); Porter Street; Church Street; Penhallow Street; Ceres Street from Bow Street to Private Way; High Street from Congress Street to Ladd Street; and Hanover Street between Market Street and Maplewood Avenue except for access to the Parking Garage by turning from Market onto Hanover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"MSD RACE TRAFFIC INTERRUPTIONS The Market Square 10K Road Race, which begins promptly at 9 a.m. on Saturday (June 11), may cause periodic and significant traffic interruptions. There are 2,000 racers registered. The race begins at the North Church, travels up Congress to Islington, to Summer to State to Bow to Market to Hanover to Maplewood to Dennett to Woodbury to Bartlett to Islington to Essex to Middle to South to Middle to Miller to South to Marcy. A map of the route may be found at www.proportsmouth.org/MSDRoadRace.cfm."&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the Isles of Shoals at 10:30 a.m.  -- Don't be late, once we leave it may be hard to find the group!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339263587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337008317000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join 60,000 people: Meet Trailblazers, walk through Portsmouth Market Square Day</name><id>64727062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339252200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/64727062/</event_url></item>