<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;One of my favorite films from last year's French Film Festival was The Lighthouse, directed by Philippe Lioret. Don't Worry I'm Fine is his latest-here is the description from the MFA: &lt;br /&gt;Don?t Worry, I?m Fine (Je vais bien, ne t'en fais pas) by Philippe Lioret (France, 2006, 100 min.). Returning home from a vacation in Barcelona, 19-year-old Lili (a wonderful performance by newcomer Melanie Laurent) discovers that her twin brother has disappeared after a fight with their father. When repeated messages to his cell phone go unanswered, Lili can?t understand her parents? reticence to get involved in the search for their son. The fears and pressure begin to take their toll, forcing Lili to question herself and her relationship to her parents as she sets out to track down her brother. Lioret perfectly calibrates the growing sense of shock and awareness that begin to transform Lili?s life. What begins as a seemingly normal suburban family is gradually revealed to contain surprisingly dark secrets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the link to one of the only English-language reviews:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.variety.com/review/VE1117931502.html?categoryid=31&amp;amp;cs=1&amp;amp;p=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.variety.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row at the film's end. Since there is not a true restaurant nearby, we will go to a Northeastern Commons area( the group has used this before)  to knosh and discuss. The event will probably be limited to 15, but this might be updated. Group member Frank has suggested a Thai restaurant that isn't that far away and so I'm increasing the limit to 20.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there, &lt;br /&gt;Tom &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185305724000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182303223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Don't Worry, I'm Fine- French Film at the MFA</name><id>5911285</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185132600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5911285/</event_url></item>