<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Palmer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374378</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cardullo's Gourmet Shoppe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1225252</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120158</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us in Harvard Square at it's best, a warm sunny day! An outdoor tour of outdoor beer gardens and cocktail patios...Dressed in 50s ..wear jeans, white, red or Red Sox T shirt and a bandana around your neck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Main Happening and Gathering Place: Joint meetup with Boston Red Sox Natives &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/natives/calendar/12964104/?from=list&amp;amp;offset=0]This"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; event takes place on Sunday, April 4 from 4:00 pm - 7:00 pm in Harvard Square on the sidewalk at Palmer and Brattle Streets and in the Cardullo's Gourmet Shoppe. This is the famous location where fans regularly gather to watch Red Sox games while pulling up a chair or standing along the sidewalk.&lt;br /&gt;Around 4:30 PM we'll heading one block to Legal Seafood Outdoor Patio @ the Charles Hotel on Mt Auburn St;  5PM across the street to &amp;quot;Charlie's Beer Garden&amp;quot;; 6PM(after sunset)we will head indoors to &amp;quot;Borders Cafe&amp;quot; two blocks Church St for a Margarita. The game will be on TV in each of those places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Harvard Square Business Association and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education have teamed up to celebrate one of America's Favorite Pastimes in one of America's oldest gathering places, next to Cardullo's Gourmet Shoppe - the home of the illustrious &amp;quot;Chair Club&amp;quot; where fans from across the world gather to share their love of Baseball.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrate Opening Day with an Open Mic and an open invitation to step up to the plate and speak one's mind about baseball, opening day, the season ahead and those that have come before. There will be a few celebrity guests welcoming opinions, trivia, well wishers, stories, poems, facts, prayers, readings, and clean knock-knock jokes etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be ballpark treats - some to sample, some to purchase and a few other surprises.&lt;br /&gt;Special 1950 style prices for a Coke. Hot Dog, and Cracker Jacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In honor of their anniversary Cardullo's will tune their world-famous Window TV to the game and will turn back the clock to the decade when they first opened. They will feature music from that period, offering special &amp;quot;remember when&amp;quot; pricing on select items and a staff dress code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information and updates can be found at www.harvardsquare.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lauren's cell 617-233-5927</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270584796000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269693372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Opening Day! Open Mic in Harvard Square</name><id>13006703</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270411200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/13006703/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/0/global_13935712.jpeg</photo_url></item>