<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Central Sq.)</address_2><address_1>492 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 864-3278</phone><name>The Middle East Restaurant and Nightclub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>257177</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Show info:&lt;br /&gt;Tue 11/3 @ Middle East (downstairs)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/thaomusic" target="_blank"&gt;Thao with the Get Down Stay Down&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/celloproject" target="_blank"&gt;Portland Cello Project&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/davidshultz" target="_blank"&gt;David Shultz &amp;amp; The Skyline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;18+, &lt;a href="http://www.ticketmaster.com/venue/8547" target="_blank"&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; $12, doors 8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm absolutely in for this show (especially having missed her being here over the summer) and have met and read on the Message Board plenty of other people who are just as excited as me.  So go get a ticket!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll plan on meeting at about 9 for pre-show drinks either at the Middle East or somewhere near by (I'm open to suggestions).  Details will follow closer to the day of the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From allmusic:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Indie folk singer/songwriter Thao Nguyen crafts delicate but memorable songs tinged with country and blues, and her rich voice and thoughtful lyrics draw comparisons to Fiona Apple and Cat Power. She began writing and playing songs when she was 12; when she was in high school, she worked at her mother's laundromat and played guitar when she wasn't helping customers. She moved on to playing local shows while attending Virginia's College of William &amp;amp; Mary. There, she met bassist Adam Thompson and drummer Willis Thompson, who became the core of her band, the Get Down Stay Down. In 2006, Nguyen released her debut album, Like the Linen, on the Trust Me imprint and played a few Washington, D.C., and New York City dates. She also sent a copy of Like the Linen to Laura Veirs, who liked it so much that she not only had Nguyen open for one of her dates at the Mercury Lounge, Veirs also took her on a European tour and introduced her to Slim Moon, Veirs' former manager and owner of Kill Rock Stars, as well as producer Tucker Martine. Nguyen made her debut on the label by contributing a song to the 2007 compilation The Sound the Hare Heard; the Martine-produced We Brave Bee Stings and All arrived in early 2008.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Text/call my cell @ 617-549-8453</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257611956000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253298725000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thao with the Get Down Stay Down @ Middle East (downstairs)</name><id>11407272</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257300000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11407272/</event_url></item>