<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>11 Garden Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375960</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-396-0734.</phone><name>First Church in Cambridge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>824219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120958</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Whether you celebrate Christmas or not, if you enjoy choral harmonies , take time out to reflect on the season and relax to some beautiful music with the Blue Heron Renaissance Choir! Tickets are normally $30 BUT ONLY $20 but if you book quickly on the Mayor's holiday special website:  &lt;a href="http://www.artsboston.org/mhs/index.html:" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artsboston...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: IF YOU'D LIKE TO COME, PLEASE BOOK YOUR OWN TICKET ASAP, SEATING IS UNRESERVED BUT SPACE IS LIMITED! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seating is unreserved so if we get to the church by 7 pm to attend the lecture, I'm hoping we'll all be able to sit together. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NEW: If you'd like to meet earlier to get to know each other a bit pre-lecture, please come to Finale on Dunster St at 5. 45 pm for a drink or a snack (or dessert!) &lt;b&gt;Please let me know if you plan to do that.&lt;/b&gt; If not, we'll see you outside the church which is only about 7 mins walk away.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Program: Perotin / Josquin: Christmas in French-speaking lands, 1200 &amp;amp; 1500&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 20, 2008 • Lecture at 7. 15 pm, performance at 8 pm&lt;br /&gt;First Church in Cambridge, Congregational&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, we love the Messiah and The Nutcracker, too—but once you’ve heard them, come celebrate a Heron Holiday! The first half of our concert offers Christmas motets by Josquin Desprez and his Franco-Flemish contemporaries from around 1500, including motets by Mouton, Brumel, and others. In the second we turn to the astonishing sounds of polyphony by Master Perotin and others heard at Notre Dame de Paris around the year 1200, as Western polyphony was being invented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free pre-concert talk at 7:15 by Sean Gallagher (Harvard University) — sponsored by the Cambridge Society for Early Music  - Professor Gallagher is a specialist in 15th-century Franco-Flemish music and the author of a new study of the composer Johannes Regis, due for publication next year.&lt;a href="http://www.blueheronchoir.org/events/event_081220.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Outside church (or inside if it's freezing) - look for multicolor stripy scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1231455055000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228094844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Heron Renaissance Choir - early music from France</name><id>9253745</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229817600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/9253745/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/global_5526982.jpeg</photo_url></item>