<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Quincy St, </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373179</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>944537</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114908</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;I will try to save as many seats as possible but this may prove impossible for 30+ people.  Coats et al only cover so much territory.  If sitting with the group is important, get there as early as you can.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE NOTE: THIS EVENT HAS BEEN CONFIRMED WITH THE BARKER CENTER&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;It isn't posted on Harvard calendars because it is being sponsored independently. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What happens when a novelist and philosopher talks to a cognitive neuroscientist about faith, reason, fiction, and God? Listen in as Rebecca Newberger Goldstein and her husband, Steven Pinker, explore what Spinoza would say about Darwin, what role fiction should play in intellectual life, whether any of the arguments for the existence of God are any good, and other topics at the interface of literature, science, and philosophy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Steven Pinker is Harvard College Professor and Johnstone Family Professor of Psychology at Harvard University.  Pinker is one of the world's leading authorities on language and the mind, and the the author of seven books, including The Language Instinct, How the Mind Works, Words and Rules, The Blank Slate, and The Stuff of Thought.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Newberger Goldstein is a philosopher, scholar, and award-winning novelist.  Her latest novel is 36 Arguments for the Existence of God: A Work of Fiction.  Her books include the novels The Mind-Body Problem, Properties of Light, and Mazel, and nonfiction studies of Kurt Gödel and Baruch Spinoza.  A recipient of a MacArthur Foundation Fellowship in 1996, Goldstein has also received Guggenheim and Radcliffe fellowships and is a member of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Getting there:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Barker Center is on the Harvard campus, a few minutes' walk from the Harvard Sq. T stop. There is a clear, detailed map &lt;a href="http://www.fas.harvard.edu/~humcentr/contact/directionsparking.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The Center is just off Mass Ave on Quincy St. If you're driving (though, of course, this being Harvard Square you would probably be happier if you don't), the link above says free parking is available for those who identify themselves as &amp;quot;Humanities Center seminar participants&amp;quot; to the parking attendant at the Broadway Garage on Felton St. (go &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?client=firefox-a&amp;amp;channel=s&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;source=hp&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=broadway+garage+cambridge&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=ost4S4SINJzCywSs3fGHBQ&amp;amp;ved=0CBMQpQY&amp;amp;view=map&amp;amp;geocode=FeGVhgIdiufC-w&amp;amp;split=0&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=Broadway+Garage,+Cambridge,+Middlesex,+Massachusetts+02138&amp;amp;ll=42.374937,-71.112549&amp;amp;spn=0.007165,0.01545&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for a Google map of the garage's location). Who knows if that will actually work in practice, but with the price of parking in Harvard Square, it's worth a try! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will try to arrive 15-20 minutes early. If you'd like to come but think you'll be getting there closer to 6:30, let me know when you RSVP and I'll save a seat for you! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristie</member_name><member_id>11334710</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>27</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266622699000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266207768000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mind-Body Problems: A Conversation About Science, Fiction and God</name><id>12606552</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266449400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12606552/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/e/e/global_12706334.jpeg</photo_url></item>