<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Library Dr</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04032</zip><lat>43.862060</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>207-865-3307</phone><name>Freeport Community Library</name><city>Freeport</city><id>680195</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.100628</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggest Donation at Door</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join Wolfe's Neck Farm for the kick-off event in their Winter Forum Series entitled Sustainability:  Transition to Resilience.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Community Forum starts with Lisa Fernandes’ discussion entitled “Permaculture for Local Resilience.” Her talk will introduce permaculture and examine how Maine can design resilient communities that have sustainable sources of food, water, and energy.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“Practitioners of permaculture (permanent + culture) envision human societies that know themselves as co-creative participants in natural systems.  Permaculture aims to regenerate healthy, productive landscapes and communities by consciously applying ecological principles to the design of human habitats,” says Fernandes, the founder of Portland Permaculture.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;She will speak November 19, at 6:30pm at the Freeport Community Library. There is a suggested donation of $5.  A short reception featuring food provided by local restaurants will follow Fernandes’s talk.  Interested community members will be encouraged to participate in facilitated break-out discussions led by our speaker. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;*Note that this presentation is an &amp;quot;evolved&amp;quot; version of one you may have seen earlier this year; This version includes more imagery and examples and will be followed by small group breakout sessions with targeted brainstorming.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;More About the Winter Forum Series:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Community Forum Tackles New Ideas, Encourages Community Participation”&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Freeport, ME (November 2009).  You eat locally, turn the heat down, and carpool.  You are an informed citizen, and you donate to local charities and volunteer your time.  What more is a thoughtful Mainer to do?  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;One option is to take part in a new model for learning about and participating in social, environmental and economic change.  The Wolfe’s Neck Farm Foundation will hold a Winter Community Forum focusing on the theme of “Sustainability: Transitions to Resilience.”  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Forum is noteworthy for two reasons, says Wolfe’s Neck Farm Interim Education Coordinator, Heather Foran.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“First, the Community Forum tackles important social issues by taking a holistic look at Maine and its communities, and how we can be resilient to crisis and genuinely sustainable.  Second, it emphasizes community participation by giving community members a space to come together to face challenges and problem solve.”&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Wolfe Neck Farm Foundation has held a Winter Lecture Series the past two years, bringing leaders in the fields of renewable energy and food systems to speak.  This year’s Forum adds a participatory, community element: not only speakers and films, but also space for informal dialogue and facilitated break-out discussions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The speakers and films will address different aspects of resiliency and sustainability, specifically food, energy, and water systems and economics.  They will also examine hopeful and innovative models of sustainable and resilient communities, both past and present.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The community dialogue will build on these ideas and aim to create a vibrant and purposeful community dialogue about Maine’s future. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259100301000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258384839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wolfe's Neck Farm Winter Forum Event: Permaculture for Local Resilience</name><id>11885299</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258673400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/11885299/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/3/global_255395.jpeg</photo_url></item>