<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-723-2500</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>731371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070306</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Solving the Stradivarius Secret&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Talks by&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;William F. &amp;quot;Jack&amp;quot; Fry, physicist and professor emeritus, University of Wisconsin-Madison&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rose Mary Harbison, violinist and artistic director of the Token Creek Chamber Music Festival.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This free presentation is part of the Museum of Science's &amp;quot;When Science Meets Art&amp;quot; series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Museum of Science &lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;: Since the early 1700s, &amp;quot;Golden Age&amp;quot; Italian violins have been revered for their superior tone. Scores of scientists, artisans, and musicians have sought answers to the mystery of their sound, but none has been able to duplicate the magic created by these coveted instruments. Characterizing varnish, wood, and geography as secondary factors, William Fry has revived the 17th-century science of levers, focusing on the violin's inner graduations. Listen as he and Rose Mary Harbison rediscover the legendary sound. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets: Seating is limited. Seating passes for free programs are available to the general public in the Museum lobby beginning at 5:45 p.m. on the evening of the program. First come, first served. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Museum members may reserve a limited number of seating passes for free programs in advance; first come, first served. Availability is limited to the number of Exhibit Halls admissions permitted with your membership level. For member reservations, call between 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. on Monday and Tuesday of the week of the program only: 617-589-3169 . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Science Meets Art examines the ingenuity of those who are shattering the boundaries between science, technology, engineering, and art. This program is free thanks to the generosity of the Lowell Institute. Additional funding for adult programs is provided by the Barbara and Malcolm L. Sherman Fund for Adult Programs and by the David and Marion Ellis Endowment Fund. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;A comment from your organizer on the notes above: It is interesting that the MoS seems to be celebrating &amp;quot;the ingenuity of those who are shattering the boundaries between science, technology, engineering, and art&amp;quot;, while at the same time noting that &amp;quot;none has been able to duplicate the magic created by&amp;quot; Stradivarius (and so many other great craftsmen and artists) who worked, not with scientific instruments, but with their five - and maybe a sixth sense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is this trend toward reliance upon science (and away from reliance upon one's own senses) a good thing? Has art improved? Or is &amp;quot;art&amp;quot; simply being re-defined. And if so, why?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ ~ ~&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Email me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238955906000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230906620000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stradivarius (Lecture)</name><id>9425246</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238022000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/9425246/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/9/global_6800425.jpeg</photo_url></item>