<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 1/2 Hampshire Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365814</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outpost 186</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>8520002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090134</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;John Mailander &amp;amp; Molly Tuttle are individually renowned musicians currently residing in Boston, MA. Both hailing from California, they are current students at the Berklee College of Music. They will be joining together to perform two special sets of original, fresh and dynamic acoustic music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Mailander is a San Diego based musician, and is in demand throughout the California and Boston areas for performance, instruction and studio work. Playing in a variety of styles on the fiddle, mandolin and various other stringed instruments, he has become known for his soulful voice as a soloist, improviser and writer. John has shared the stage with acclaimed artists including the Alison Brown Quartet, Victor Wooten, Tony Trischka &amp;amp; Territory, Tim O’Brien, Christopher Guest and Darol Anger. He appears regularly with Chris Stuart &amp;amp; Backcountry, and in 2012 released an instrumental EP with Boston group the TriMountain Sessions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With nearly two million viewers on YouTube and features in Bluegrass Now, Flatpicking Guitar and Acoustic Guitar magazines, Molly Tuttle is making a name for herself in the acoustic music scene. A virtuoso multi-instrumentalist and award winning songwriter with a distinctive voice, Molly has turned the heads of even the most seasoned industry professionals. In just 2012 alone, she was awarded best female vocalist and best guitar player by the Northern California Bluegrass Society, and 1st place in the prestigious Merlefest Chris Austin Songwriting Competition. Molly has been performing on stage since she was 11 and recorded her first album at age 13. She has appeared on the Prairie Home Companion,The Hardly Strictly Bluegrass Festival, The Strawberry Music Festival, The Freight and Salvage and countless other festivals and venues across the country. She now balances her classes at the Berklee College of Music with an active performance schedule across the U.S. and Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, John &amp;amp; Molly create an honest and soulful mix of original and traditional music, with a respect for the past while also looking toward the future of acoustic music. They have performed at the Grey Fox, Joe Val and Summergrass Bluegrass Festivals, as well as many other venues throughout Boston and California.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;8-10pm - concert - reservation suggested, $10 in advance, $15 at the door. $5 students.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Reservations/Questions - lordgeoffreypresents at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

 Event - &lt;a class="linkified" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/161863650634931/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/161863650634931/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 LG page - &lt;a class="linkified" href="https://www.facebook.com/LGPresents"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/LGPresents&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 LG web - &lt;a class="linkified" href="https://sites.google.com/site/lordgeoffreypresents/"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/lordgeoffreypresents/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.johnmailander.com/"&gt;http://www.johnmailander.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://mollytuttle.net/"&gt;http://mollytuttle.net/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367377647000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363196497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>John Mailander &amp; Molly Tuttle</name><id>109081932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367366400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/109081932/</event_url></item>