<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last time we looked at Dr. David R. Hawkins Map of Consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's continue with this topic by exploring the levels of the Map, estimating our own personal level (this will be done silently- we will not be sharing our personal levels of consciousness), and identifying what qualities epitomize our next higher level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is fascinating to note that that people operating at the higher levels of consciousness counterbalance the negative effects of lower level people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;However, this does not happen on a one-on-one basis.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;One individual who lives and vibrates to the energy of optimism and a willingness to be nonjudgmental of other counterbalances the negativity of 90,000 individuals operating at lower levels.&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;  (For those of you who attended our last meeting or have a copy of the Map, this is a level 310.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Wayne Dyer says &amp;quot;By raising your own frequency of vibration only slightly to a place where you regularly practice kindness, love and receptivity, and where you see beauty and endless potential of good in others as well as yourself, you counterbalance 90,000 people somewhere on this planet who are living in the lower levels of shame, anger, hatred, guilt, despair, and depression and so on.&amp;quot;  He further says &amp;quot;Nothing to do.  No one to convert. No goals to accomplish.  Nothing more than raising your own consciousness level to the creative, kind, loving, beautiful, ever-expanding, endlessly abundant and receptive-to-all-without-judgment frequencies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be doing several exercises to positively affect our own consciousness levels and consequently our own level of happiness and effectiveness.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Hawkins writes &amp;quot;In this interconnected universe, every improvement we make in our own private world improves the world at large for everyone.  We float on the collective consciousness of mankind, so any increment we add comes back to us.  We all add to our common buoyancy by our efforts to benefit life.  It is a scientific fact that what is good for you is good for me.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315421340000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232667770000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raising Your Level of Consciousness</name><id>9581139</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233619200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/9581139/</event_url></item>