<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>793 Iyannough Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02601</zip><lat>41.668963</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 778-1424</phone><name>Not Your Average Joe's</name><city>Hyannis</city><id>875083</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.296033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Not Your Average Joe's, located at the Cape Cod Mall, offers what's called: &lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;&amp;quot;Take the Happy Hour Taste Tour&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; offering sampler plates for $2.99 up until 6:00 p.m. (Thanks Janice for your suggestion!)  Sounds like a great place to meet before a movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sample a wide range of Joe's legendary tastes without ruining your budget. Buffalo–Caribbean Chicken Tenders, Rhode Island Style Calamari, Forno Baked Chicken Quesadilla, Short Rib Slider, Mini-Pizzas and many more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;We'll first meet at the bar/lounge&lt;/span&gt; at Not Your Average Joe's for light bites, or choose to enjoy a full dinner. Whatever your preference! The Movie to follow is at Regal Cape Cod Mall Stadium 12, 793 Route 132, Hyannis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Janice's suggested movie to go see is: &amp;quot;Confessions of a Shopaholic.&amp;quot; It starts at 7:15 p.m. Runtime:1 hr. 52 minutes. Movie price: $8.50&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Bloomwood is a sweet and charming New York City girl who has a tiny, little problem that is rapidly turning into a big problem: she's hopelessly addicted to shopping and drowning in a sea of debt. While Rebecca has dreams of working for a top fashion magazine, she can't quite get her foot in the door-that is, until she snags a job as an advice columnist for a new financial magazine published by the same company. Overnight, her column becomes hugely popular, turning her into an overnight celebrity. But when her compulsive shopping and growing debt issues threaten to destroy her love life and derail her career, she struggles to keep it all from spiraling out of control--and is ultimately forced to reevaluate what's really important in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Isla Fisher, Hugh Dancy, Krysten Ritter, Joan Cusack, John Goodman&lt;br /&gt;Genres: Comedy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;NOTE:&lt;/span&gt; If any of you ladies would prefer to see a different movie for yourself, I'll bring a movie list with show times to Not Your Average Joe's, or you can look it up on the internet at: &lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;NOTE&lt;/span&gt;: If you want to just make the lite bites at TGI Fridays and not attend a movie that's fine too!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a button that says, "Girl's Just Wanna Have Fun!"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharon</member_name><member_id>8235187</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236381199000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234292028000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour Bites at Not Your Average Joes with a Movie to Follow!</name><id>9713929</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235080800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/9713929/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/f/4/global_5975620.jpeg</photo_url></item>