<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mt. Auburn St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.371338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-699-1221 </phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>363595</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116469</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lord Farce Labor and the Humorless Galactic Empire are building a new, indestructible Teeth Jar that threatens to bring an end to the improvisors (not to mention their teeth). Meanwhile, Jason has been imprisoned, and Gio has sent Nikki and Alex to try and free him. The princess - disguised as a role of bounty paper towels - and ChooChoo go along as well. The final battle takes place on the moon of Endor, with its natural inhabitants lending a hand to the improvisors. Will Lord Farce Labor and the dark side overcome the improvisors and take over the universe, stamping out laughter everywhere?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We certainly hope not! That's why we need you to come join our improvisors in the fight against Lord Farce Labor to restore levity across the universe. So come join us for a night of improv enjoyment. No experience needed. Just bring yourself and your willingness to try some short-form improv games just like you may have seen on Whose Line Is It Anyway? or comedy shows around Boston. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Giovanni</member_name><member_id>2402708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273930917000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273471740000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Improv Incubator: Episode VI: Return of the Gio</name><id>13434834</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273793400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/13434834/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>