<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>321 Washington St # D</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.379559</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Washington Street Art Center</name><city>Somerville</city><id>7318552</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101044</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come and celebrate with me! I'm exhibiting at the Washington Street Art Center in Somerville. Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 visions:snoisiv&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paintings and prints by Spiridoula Politis, Bartosz Majczak, and Mauro Reategui Perez &lt;br /&gt;

 June 9–30, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OPENING RECEPTION: Saturday, June 9, from 6–10 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ON VIEW: June 9–30, Saturdays 12–4 p.m., and by appointment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“[visionary art] attempts to show what lies beyond the boundary of our sight. Through dream, trance, or other altered states, the artist attempts to see the unseen—attaining a visionary state that transcends our regular modes of perception. The task awaiting [the artist], thereafter, is to communicate [the] vision in a form recognizable to 'everyday sight.' ~L. Caruana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Spiridoula Politis, Bartosz Majczak, and Mauro Reategui Perez as they share their experiences through visionary art. After travelling to the Amazon jungle of Peru to learn about plant medicine, Spiridoula brings her memories of her transformational work with a shaman into contemporary mixed media paintings using color, pattern, and mark making. Spiridoula believes “...the act of creation is a bridge to the Divine. These paintings are my version of a Yantra. I can recreate and meditate upon that deeply transformative experience I sought (and was granted) during the making of these paintings.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While in Peru, she met Mauro Reategui Perez, a painter from Pucallpa working in the style of Pablo Amaringo, his teacher and mentor. He creates lush, magical landscapes of the jungle and of the spirits within, and has graciously accepted our invitation to exhibit in the United States for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bartosz Majczak (bartomon), spirit brother of Spiridoula, brings with him printed compositions about the meta-metaphorical language of circular and spherical topologies. “Geometry is the method and medium by which we come to know anything, everything, non-things, and nothing,” he says of the inspiration behind these works. “It is the one powerful key to unlocking whole brain function—the holy grail that resolves all apparent divisions and dissolves all artifice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.spiridoula.com &lt;br /&gt;

 www.bartomon.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attend the Event: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/426912000653855/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/426912000653855/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339294279000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337652522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Visionary art exhibit reception</name><id>65792562</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339279200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/65792562/</event_url></item>