<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Valley Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.608825</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-777-1245 </phone><name>Connors Farm</name><city>Danvers</city><id>750154</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.937395</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;2010 Connors Farm Strawberry Festival&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, June 19, 2010 - 9am to 6pm&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s go pick some strawberry’s at Connors Farm Strawberry Festival!  They will have entertainment featuring The &amp;quot;Hankaholics&amp;quot; Classic Country Band (Hank Williams cover songs!) &amp;amp; featuring The &amp;quot;Boston Rockabilly Band&amp;quot; BOSTON ROCKABILLY has been performing the local circuit since 1980. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little help on how To Pick Your Strawberries:&lt;/b&gt;  Large or small -- every red berry is ripe, luscious and ready-to-eat. So pick all the red ones you can find in your aisle. Green berries will not ripen after being picked.  To find the berries -- look under the leaves of each strawberry plant.  When picking berries from the plant, pinch or pull stem from plant and be sure to leave the stem on each berry.  Our delicious, red strawberries are just waiting to be picked. So everybody get ready for a fun time in the strawberry patch! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; We contacted Connors Farm to find out approximately what the cost per quart will be at the time of this event and they are thinking that the cost per quart will be approximately $3.25 to $3.50.  Please note this may change the day of the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; Connors has a really big parking lot, find a parking spot and meetup with us to the right as you are walking into the store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to dress appropriately seeing that we will be walking around their strawberry patch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not sure if we will be there in time for their delicious BBQ but it will be running full force this day and as always the BBQ is provided by Champions BBQ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Also we will be looking forward to some:&lt;br /&gt;Strawberries Dipped In Chocolate&lt;br /&gt;Homemade Strawberry Shortcake&lt;br /&gt;Costume Characters&lt;br /&gt;Hay Rides&lt;br /&gt;AND MUCH MUCH MORE!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain if it rains on Saturday then the new date for this event at Connors Farm is on Sunday June 20th, not sure if the time will stay the same seeing that is Father's Day, please remember to check back either way for updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little information about Connors Farm: Connors farm was established in 1904.  Connors has a great Farm Market and a great bakery.  The Connors family followed generations of farmers who had been farming the land for over 300 years.  Connors Farm began as a &amp;quot;truck farm&amp;quot; meaning that all of the crops grown at the time were trucked into Boston to be sold wholesale.  During this time the main crops grown were root crops such as, parsnips and carrots.  In the mid 1950's sweet corn became the major wholesale crop. Unfortunately, wholesale prices for corn began to fall and the farm was unable to make a profit selling corn this way. As an alternative, the Connors family decided to try selling the corn on their own by creating a small roadside stand on part of the property.  This became a tremendous success and people from all over the North Shore came to buy Connors Farm corn.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late or not able to find us call the Meetup Cell phone at 978-304-2811.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be to the right of the door as you walk into the store.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276968440000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276138127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go strawberry Picking</name><id>13756408</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276956000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/13756408/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/global_15619089.jpeg</photo_url></item>