<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:45 on Saturday, so let's meet inside the theater doors at 7:15 (or right outside them if it's nice out).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP up to date. It helps me figure out who to wait for!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks and hope to see you Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Dana&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809752801/info" target="_blank"&gt;Star Trek&lt;/a&gt; is a must-see for this group, methinks. If you agree, come with us! It'll be a Saturday night shindig. Ah, I heart the summer blockbuster season!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;The fate of the galaxy rests in the hands of bitter rivals. One, James Kirk, is a delinquent, thrill-seeking Iowa farm boy. The other, Spock, was raised in a logic-based society that rejects all emotion. As fiery instinct clashes with calm reason, their unlikely but powerful partnership is the only thing capable of leading their crew through unimaginable danger, boldly going where no one has gone before.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The usual stuff:&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet inside the theater doors (or outside if it's nice out) and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.50 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update the exact time of the meeting about 2 days before the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Star Trek!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243632754000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241578406000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Star Trek</name><id>10348162</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242514800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/10348162/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>