<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We have posted these events in that past and our members that participated seemed to like them a lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While I am sure there are some men in our group that could benefit from a program like this - this one is just for the women.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Feel free to use this posting to coordinate travel and lodging with other randomites, but in order to register for this program you need to visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.nhbow.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.nhbow.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or call (603) 271-3212.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Women who want to be prepared to survive in an outdoor emergency situation can sign up for a one-day "Becoming an Outdoors-Woman" (BOW) Wilderness Survival workshop taking place on Sunday, April 22, 2012, from 8:00 a.m. to 4 p.m. at the Owl Brook Hunter Education Center, at 387 Perch Pond Road (off Route 175) in Holderness, N.H.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Space is limited, so please register soon if you are interested in attending.&amp;nbsp;To sign up, fill out the application available at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.nhbow.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.nhbow.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or call Lisa Collins at 603-271-3214 to request an application. Workshop fee of $25 is due with registration and includes program materials, use of equipment, and lunch. Participants must be 18 years of age or older.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Taught by New Hampshire Fish and Game Department Conservation Officers, the wilderness survival course will help participants learn survival techniques such as how to find wood and build a fire; protect yourself from hypothermia; build a shelter for protection against the elements; signal for help; use knives and tools safely; find and purify a water supply; prepare a meal in the outdoors; and know what should be in your survival kit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This workshop is a "Beyond BOW" course. These in-depth workshops are designed to expand on the offerings of traditional Becoming an Outdoors-Woman fall and winter programs, helping women gain the skills to participate in outdoor activities on their own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;N.H. Becoming an Outdoors-Woman programs are co-sponsored by the New Hampshire Fish and Game Department (&lt;a href="http://www.wildnh.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.wildnh.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) and the New Hampshire Wildlife Federation (&lt;a href="http://www.nhwf.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://www.nhwf.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;For more information, contact Tina Davenport at (603) 271-0495 or Lisa Collins at (603) 271-3214.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343662487000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331337475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Becoming an Outdoor's Woman - Wilderness Survival Workshop</name><id>55717582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335096000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/55717582/</event_url></item>