<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPRG Exclusive Open House&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;KRI Center for Consciousness Studies is opening its doors to SPRG May 1st, 2011! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To celebrate nearly 250 members in the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group, KRI will be hosting an open house meet-and-greet for this longstanding Meetup group.&amp;nbsp; If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended a Meetup yet, you can&amp;rsquo;t miss this one!&amp;nbsp; This is the culmination of what SPRG has been moving toward for the last few years and we want to see you get involved.&amp;nbsp; Presentations, Q&amp;amp;A sessions, light snacks and refreshments... and plenty of room to socialize and connect with your fellow SPRG members!&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1:00 - 1:45 PM - Valerie Roy presents Searching for Spirit: The How, What, Where, and Why of the Human Soul.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; A look at theories regarding the soul, from science to different cultural perspectives.&amp;nbsp; What is the soul?&amp;nbsp; Where is it located?&amp;nbsp; Join Val as she discusses some of history&amp;rsquo;s beliefs.&amp;nbsp; A question and answer session will follow. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:00 - 2:45 PM - Mike Stevens presents Night Stalkers.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Are we alone? What's lurking in the night sky?&amp;nbsp; Join Mike as he takes you through the alien abduction phenomenon through open discussion and slide presentation.&amp;nbsp;Take advantage of this&amp;nbsp;unique opportunity to discuss one of society&amp;rsquo;s most fringe topics. A question and answer session will follow. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:00 - 3:45 PM - Isabeau Esby presents An Examination of the Process of Death.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A deep and direct discussion on how death is viewed, managed, and emotionally processed in our Western culture.&amp;nbsp; As a psychic medium, Beau will bring her direct experiences with spirits to explain the process one goes through upon dying as well as the purpose of death.&amp;nbsp; A question and answer session will follow. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:00 - 4:45 PM - AJ Kitt presents What is Paranormal, Anyhow?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If things happen at all, they're normal... aren't they? &amp;nbsp;Psychical phenomena, paranormal, metaphysics, parapsychology - how are they the same and how are they different? &amp;nbsp;Join AJ Kitt, founder of the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group and the KRI Center for Consciousness Studies, as he discusses the state of the art and science of some of the things that happen all around us that remain unexplained.&amp;nbsp; A question and answer session will follow. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:00 - Open discussion.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What is the future of the SPRG?&amp;nbsp; As the SPRG moves forward, what type of activities would you like to be involved with and how would you like to see it grow?&amp;nbsp; This is your chance to get involved! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By donation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie Roy</member_name><member_id>4599203</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>andy</member_name><member_id>5342211</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike </member_name><member_id>6862973</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304378296000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Don't miss this event!</why><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302989671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPRG Exclusive Open House</name><id>17329322</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304269200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/17329322/</event_url></item>