<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>159 Nantasket Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02045</zip><lat>42.267902</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The C Note</name><city>Hull</city><id>10508112</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.852470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Swing to the band that was offered a chance to perform at JFK Jr's wedding. They turned him down because they had a previous engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jazz, Gospel, Blues and Soul. Swing on top of Rock 'n Roll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone will arrange carpooling for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bellevuecadillac.com/"&gt;http://www.bellevuecadillac.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cover charge: $10.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/e/0/event_189621472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE HISTORY &lt;br /&gt;

 Bellevue Cadillac is celebrating its 19th year playing various stages around the world. Shanghai, china, moscow russia, athens greece and toyko japan, san juan puerto rico, abaco bahamas,and ashford castle, ireland, lincoln center nyc and the palace, hollywood. You've heard Bellevue's music in major motion pictures like Shallow Hal, Me Yyself and Irene and Delta Rising and the tv shows The Sopranos, Las Vegas, Crossing Jordan, Brotherhood, Ed, Sex and the City, Touched by an Angel, Brimstone, and Good and Evil. Bellevue Cadillac performances have been seen on Access Hollywood, CNN Showbiz, Hard Copy, and VH1. To date, Bellevue Cadillac has songs on 17 compilation cds with such artists as Duke Ellington, Ella Fitzgerald, Louis Prima, Louis Jordan, Sammy Davis Jr., Peggy Lee, Brian Setzer, Joe Jackson, Cab Calloway, Mel Torme, Rita Coolidge, Eva Cassidy, Big Bad Voodoo Daddy, and others. The reviews have been raves in cover stories in Rolling Stone, Jazziz, Blues Review, and People magazines. Bellevue Cadillac has appeared with Jack Nicholson, Bill Murray, Joe Pesci, Aerosmith, Kenny Rogers, Matt Damon, Tara Reid, Shannen Elizibeth, the New England Patriots, and The Boston Red Sox 1999 Allstar Game. They've played with Ray Charles, James Brown, Tito Puente, Patty Austin, Kool and the Gang, Ruth Brown, Percy Sledge, Keith Richards and Bo Diddley. Surely, their place in history as the band that turned down the JFK Jr secret wedding had to start somewhere.in 2006 Bellevue Cadillac's cd Love Allways was nominated for 7 grammy nominations, best cd, record of the year, song of the year in the pop music category. The Bellevue Cadillac sound, "Jazz, Gospel, Blues and Soul, Swings on top of Rock &amp;amp; Roll" had to have a beginning, and that was 1991.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356297971000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355878715000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Swing to Bellevue Cadillac at the C Note in Hull.</name><id>95844052</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356224400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/95844052/</event_url></item>