<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 Main St #14</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.346626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Earthsong Yoga</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>1510084</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.549316</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #7030a0"&gt;September’s FREE Community Evening of Guided Meditations at Earthsong Yoga, our gift to you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #7030a0"&gt;Connecting to your Inner Power to Create&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Friday evening, September, 14th, 7:30 – 9:00 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #002060"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Did you know that you’re creating through your thoughts and words every moment?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style="color : #002060"&gt;&lt;span&gt;And did you know that when you deeply relax your mind, you can more effectively create what you want? Maybe you do know this; but are you able to easily do this on your own, or are you making the time to do this?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #7030a0"&gt;Come join us; and powerfully connect to and learn about your inner power to more effectively create what you want, instead of what you don’t want, through a series of deep guided meditations and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #7030a0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;discussions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0070c0"&gt;“Your meditation was awesome! I was really stressed out today, worried mostly about my job and home hunting. This helped me to calm down within the first few minutes. I felt at peace before it was even finished. Thanks!”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Melissa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0070c0"&gt;“It was a very meaningful evening.  I found Ann to be extremely effective in creating a wonderful presentation and an atmosphere that allowed me to experience more than I had hoped for.  In the world we live today, the peace, relaxation, and happiness that come with her techniques are not to be missed.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Lee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt;Treat yourself to this wonderful free event for you. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please invite others to sign up and join you.&lt;/span&gt; Share this with your friends, family and groups. The class is appropriate for everyone, and all are welcome!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required. These events often fill up very quickly, and we sometimes have a waiting list!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Please be considerate, and if you sign up, please show up or let us know of your change in plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Please plan on arriving around 7:25 to get settled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Hope you'll join us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt;Ann Ide, New Possibilities Coaching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner and trainer in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to become their greatest, best selves, to live with more ease and joy, and to more easily create the happiness they want.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #002060"&gt;This &lt;em&gt;public&lt;/em&gt; event is co-sponsored by Earthsong Yoga and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and is being shared with you because of it's applicability to effectively using the law of attraction.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>186 Main St. is the Corey building (old historical building), Earthsong Yoga sign is on sidewalk in front, studio is on second floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347677451000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345077490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deeply connecting to your inner power to create</name><id>77935682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347665400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/77935682/</event_url></item>