<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Yard</address_2><address_1>Harvard College</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374528</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>John Harvard Statue</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>710042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The August book is going to be Dead Souls by Nikolai Gogol.  Yes, this is an 18th century Russian novel, but def give it a chance; it's surprisingly light and not a slog at all.  Plus, while you're reading it at the pool, the people around you will be totally impressed by your very serious summer reading.  Then again, they'll probably be thinking &amp;quot;Wow, that person must be totally stuck-up, because otherwise they couldn't possibly be that good looking *and* intelligent.&amp;quot;  So those are the angles as I see them; I hope you're excited about the book now.  Also, some things named after Nikolai Gogol are the character from &amp;quot;The Namesake&amp;quot; and the pretty kickin' band Gogol Bordello.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/1-9781593080921-1" target="_blank"&gt;Powell's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dead_Souls" target="_blank"&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Dead-Souls-Novel-Nikolai-Gogol/dp/0679776443/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1278160722&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are multiple translations of the novel; I don't think that there's any reason to worry about which one you pick up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll try outside in Harvard Yard again (and probably for the last time for the year) for August.  Meet at the John Harvard statue at 7, and then we'll find somewhere to plop (last month we ended up sitting at the chairs and tables just outside the north gate of Harvard Yard).  I honestly can't recall if Wednesday August 4th is the day we chose at the last meeting, but let's roll with it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The July Meet-Up for Middlesex by Jeffrey Eugenides is Wednesday next week.  Please update your RSVP's; on the off chance that the weather is crappy, it would be really useful for me to know how many people to plan on for alternate inside arrangements.  Also, as we talked about at the last meeting, the free-ride for the meet-up group is over (Lisa was really great to carry the cost of doing the Meet-Up website for so long, but I am less really great).  The cost is going to be totally nominal,  though.  Please bring $1 to the first Meet-Up you attend, and then you're set forever.  That's right, $1 buys you a lifetime of book club; that's almost sweeter than getting it for free.  I'm not going to be keeping track of who pays, and if you don't want to pay for whatever reason, just don't worry about it, but I do appreciate the dollar because it will offset a decent chunk of the monthly cost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nick&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick</member_name><member_id>10094294</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281020116000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278161537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: Dead Souls by Nikolai Gogol</name><id>13990855</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280962800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/13990855/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/0/f/global_16150623.jpeg</photo_url></item>