<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Salut, tout le monde!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notre amie Susanna (Sus) a bien voulu nous inviter chez elle le mercredi 26 septembre a 8:00 du soir.  Nous en profiterons donc pour organiser une soiree speciale a l'intention des amateurs de jeux de vocabulaire, comme promis le mois dernier.  Meme si vous ne jouez pas vous pouvez toujours venir.  Tou ce qui peut arriver c'est que nous repartions avec un mot ou deux que nous ne  connaissions pas! J'y compte bien quand meme.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comme d'habitude, ceux qui comptent y participer voudront bien amener quelque chose a manger ou a boire: biscottes, vin, fromage, pain, saucisson, etc..&lt;br /&gt;Amenz aussi vos jeux, si vous en avez.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                              ***********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our friend Susanna (Sus) was so kind to invite us at her home on Wednesday, September 26, at 8:00 P.M.  We'll take that opportunity to organize a special evening for word games fans, as promised last month. You can come even if you don't play. All that can happen is we will leave wih a word or two that we did not know! I, for one, am counting on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, for such eevents, those who come will be so kind to bring something to eat or drink: crackers, wine, cheese, bread, etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your games also, if you have some.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                             ********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sus a fourni les informations suivantes: &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Here's my address:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;275 Boston Ave&lt;br /&gt;Medford, MA 02155&lt;br /&gt;(c) 617.335.7328&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There are two buses that leave from Davis Square: 94 and 96 (Medford Sq. direction)- Get off at Piggott Street (which crosses Boston Avenue). Bus 80 also stops there. Once you get off the bus, cross over to the opposite side of the road, which has a Pasta Pisa/Cafe de Crepe/laundromat/barbershop/salon, walk toward the salon and 275 is the first house (greyish/blue).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If driving from Boston, take 93N to exit 31 (MYSTIC VALLEY PKWY / RT-16 toward Arlington, stay left), stay on Rt 16W for 1.7 miles, then turn left onto Boston Ave (at the lights, there will be a U-Haul and gas station to your left). 275 is about a quarter mile up on the right. If there's parking in the mini-lot next to the house, feel free to park there, otherwise, it's street parking.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venez et amusons-nous!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frantz&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frantz P</member_name><member_id>1701364</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191374585000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchConversationGroup</urlname><id>63770</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190171517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Chez Sus!</name><id>6386550</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190851200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchConversationGroup/events/6386550/</event_url></item>