<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 Washington St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>43.979324</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-447-1001</phone><name>Conway Hostel</name><city>Conway</city><id>493948</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118510</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will do this awesome loop in the White Mountains. It is one of the most beautiful crazy long day hikes you will ever do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is NOT A TRIP for BEGINNERS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will be hiking on your own or with someone who hikes at the same pace as you for the most part and relying on your own sense of direction and map reading skills. It is very hard to keep a group together through 32.3 miles so we will split up and the fast ones will probably be finish a few hours ahead of the slower ones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My plan is to start hiking at 1am so that at the slowest we should be done by 8 or 9pm. It is going to be a very long day and you will&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The altitude gain will be probably about 8,000 to 10,000 feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My plan is to go to a campsite near Lincoln, NH and get a few hours of sleep. Get up at 12am and be on the trail no later than 1am. I cross-posted this with my NY group and most of us are driving up for 6 hours so if you leave close this doesn't apply to you unless you want to stay with us at the campsite. We will get a motel for Saturday night to have a hot shower and warm bed to relieve are aches and pains. If you want to stay with us at the motel, just let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equipment (not optional):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO COTTON!!! COTTON KILLS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hiking Pants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A fleece&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain and windproof jacket&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headlamp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Map (My favorite map is the White Mountains map from Map Adventures available at the EMS Soho Store and in Lincoln, NH.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food with lots of calories. You will need it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At least 2L of water to start and either water purification tablets or a water filter. Gatorade in powder form is great, you can add it to the water when you refill. I buy a tub at the supermarket and fill a plastic bag with it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For camping Friday night:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camping cooking stove for Friday night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sleeping bag&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tent (optional, we have lots of tents usually so if you don't have one we can share.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My NY group is driving up to NH so if anyone need a ride on the way up, let me know especially those of you who are in Boston. We are leaving NY either Thursday night or really early Friday morning to try to get some sleep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any question or comments, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;metope@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we get within two weeks of the trip, I will ask everyone who is staying at the motel with us to send me the money for the motel via PayPal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Francisco&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Francisco</member_name><member_id>822470</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277532961000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269236047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>One Day Pemigewasset Loop Hike 32.3 miles (Franconia Range)</name><id>12953294</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277528400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12953294/</event_url></item>