<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>577 Crawford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.557716</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>FCA Flight Center</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>10212102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.754265</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looks like we have a large group going to visit The Lady on the following day. &lt;br /&gt;

 So, how about we meet at the FCA Flight Center for a thorough pre brief?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll have Helo charts available based on signups. This should include not only pilots flying the following days flight, but anyone interested in knowing how to fly the corridor safely. I will provide a slide show and have asked Doug Stewart to join us. As of this writing, I'm not sure of his attendance yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your questions... There's a few things to go over.. My plan is to go south down the corridor then north but up the East River and over Central Park to rejoin the Hudson. Here's a couple must links. Print out the kneeboard and take the test if you're PIC. Print out the certificate as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.faasafety.gov/files/gslac/courses/content/79/776/kneeboard.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.faasafety.gov/files/gslac/courses/content/79/776/kneeboard.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.faasafety.gov/gslac/ALC/course_content.aspx?pf=1&amp;amp;preview=true&amp;amp;cID=79" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.faasafety.gov/gslac/ALC/course_content.aspx?pf=1&amp;amp;preview=true&amp;amp;cID=79&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When flying in the SFRA, effective 0901 Zulu on Nov. 19, pilots must fly at 140 KIAS or less; turn on anticollision and position/navigation lights (landing light recommended); self announce aircraft position on the appropriate frequency; and carry a current New York Terminal Area Chart or New York Helicopter Route Chart and be familiar with the information on it. Pilots should include the aircraft type, current position, direction of flight, and altitude at each mandatory checkpoint indicated on the back of the chart. Because of input from pilots at the Air Safety Foundation’s safety seminar, the FAA will not require the report to include the aircraft’s color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, pilots must fly along the west shoreline of the Hudson River when southbound and along the east shoreline when northbound. Those who are transiting the area—flying the entire length of the Hudson River Class B exclusion—must fly between 1,000 feet msl and 1,299 feet msl. Local operations for sightseeing, electronic news gathering, and law enforcement must be conducted below 1,000 feet msl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The FAA also has modified the New York Class B airspace, creating a standard Class B floor of 1,300 feet msl over the Hudson River exclusion zone. Previously, the floor of the Class B airspace in that area varied at 1,100 feet msl and 1,500 feet msl.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362863445000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362327379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>pre flight a pre flight for the Hudson River trip</name><id>107360092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362852000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/107360092/</event_url></item>