<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This hike is going to be led by &lt;strong&gt;Diana&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;imanaturegirl@yahoo.com) and &lt;strong&gt;Dwight&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;/span&gt;dphette@metrocast.net) who kindly stepped up after I had to bow out due to a work-related conflict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dwight  has done hiking in Bear Brook before and knows the trails!&amp;nbsp; Diana is  just getting back into it and will bring up the rear!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please  contact Dwight with any questions about meeting place and weather!&amp;nbsp;  Also, please update your RSVP as it gets closer to the date!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will send Dwight and Diana an up-dated list of people going the day before!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THANKS!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loop hike in Bear Brook State Park, Allenstown, NH.  Depending on the weather and the temperatures, it could be as short as 2.5 miles RT, or we could do a longer loop, going +/- 5 miles.  Rolling terrain, some climbing, elevation gain of 450 feet.  Nice views and will be a pretty hike if there is snow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is for people who are just getting into it, getting BACK into it or just want a less-strenuous hike! I have taken the AMC Beginning Winter Hiking course and want to hike with some of my newer gear and see how things go in colder conditions. Even though this is a short hike, please be prepared for cold weather!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This should be a great hike for snowshoes...but even if there isn't too much snow, you will want some kind of traction (like microspikes!)  I am a &lt;strong&gt;very&lt;/strong&gt; slow hiker, so if you're just starting out, please don't be worried about keeping up!  I just plod along, one foot in front of the other!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear &lt;strong&gt;layers&lt;/strong&gt;, gloves or mittens, insulated boots, a hat and bring snacks, extra socks and at least 2 liters of water. No cotton! Dog friendly, kids welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description of the hike and a trail map here:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/BearBrookStatePark090101.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikeneweng" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read about the park here:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.com/bearbrook.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstatepar" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions     &lt;br /&gt;The parking area for this hike is located in Bear Brook State Park in Allenstown, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Rt. 4:  &lt;br /&gt; * From the Epsom Traffic Circle, take Rt. 28 South.  &lt;br /&gt; * Travel on Rt. 28 South for 5.6 miles.  &lt;br /&gt; * Turn left onto Bear Brook Road which runs through the state park and is marked by a large sign. This road is also knows as Allenstown-Deerfield Road or State Park Road.  &lt;br /&gt; * After about a mile you will reach the park's tollbooth on the right.  &lt;br /&gt; * Park in the large parking lot on the left immediately past the tollbooth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 3:  &lt;br /&gt; * From the junction of Routes 3 and 28 in Suncook, take Rt. 28 North.  &lt;br /&gt; * Travel on Rt. 28 North for 3.0 miles.  &lt;br /&gt; * Turn right onto Bear Brook Road which runs through the state park and is marked by a large sign. This road is also knows as Allenstown-Deerfield Road or State Park Road.  &lt;br /&gt; * After about a mile you will reach the park's tollbooth on the right.  &lt;br /&gt; * Park in the large parking lot on the left immediately past the tollbooth.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298938632000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294883833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It! Winter Hike up Catamount Hill!</name><id>16030048</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298732400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/16030048/</event_url></item>