<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61-63 Chatham Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wild Rover Bar Boston - 1 Block from Faneuil Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>9694002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053970</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and gals, Matt Adams (Organizer of Boston Singles) has launched a new group and I'd like to invite you out to the awesome social mixer to kick it all off! There are 61 people coming from all the invited groups already. Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top 3 Reasons Why This Is Awesome:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Arrive between 7:00 and 8:00 pm get you a drink ticket good for any soda, beer, wine and most mixed drinks. (no shots or top shelf liquor) Tickets expire at 8:15 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Hors d'oeuvres will be provided between 7:00 and 9:00 pm and, yes, there will be refills. The food is all made fresh and it's very tasty!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. The DJ provides an awesome palette of music, perfect for dancing and enjoying the company of new friends, as the volume will be just enough to talk and just enough to dance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All that for just a $10 cover. (Hey, we gotta pay for it somehow...)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Friends &amp;amp; Connections&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best reason for coming out is all of the new people you'll meet and make friends with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you arrive, proceed to the second floor where you'll find Alex, the door guy and pay with a $10 bill (no 1's, 5's or 20's please, 10's only, saves time and is easier when there's a line). Everyone pays $10 cash, so come prepared!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please find introduce yourself to me, as I love getting to know new people and making new friends. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do You Have A Group You'd Like To Invite?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone has their own Meetup group that they'd like to share this event with, get in touch and we'll work out the details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Invited Groups:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Awesome In Boston&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Happy Hour - Invited By Isabel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Singles - Invited by Matt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston Professional Networking - Invited by Matt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Fun - Invited by Matt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking For This Event:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Street parking is possible but it can be tough. Try your luck if you come early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise there is a parking garage nearby at 47 Broad Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking the T:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The closet T stop is the Aquarium stop on the Blue line, and you would take the State Street exit. The next easiest T stop would be State Street stop on the Orange line.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sailor</member_name><member_id>9477823</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359774571000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359488978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In Boston Kickoff Mixer (w/Drink &amp; Food)</name><id>102001542</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359763200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/102001542/</event_url></item>