<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>CALENDAR OF TOPICS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2/24. Transforming the Storyteller. Learn how to diminish the self-centered ego. How do we all get stuck in our storylines? How do loosen its power over us? Combines Toltec and Zen spirituality. From Don Miguel Ruiz's book The Voice of Knowledge. Presented by Juliane Dean. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3/02. The Voice of Truth. What is a Buddha? Why does true entrusting come from ignorance? What kind of truth can we realize? From the book The Evil Person by Shuichi Maida.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3/09. Airplane First Aid.  First in a series of discussions exploring the Noble Eightfold Path. This talk focuses on Right Action &amp;amp; Right Speech. Are there any prohibitions in Buddhism?  How can we make our speech truthful, gentle and helpful? From the book It?s Easier than You Think: The Buddhist Way to Happiness by Sylvia Boorstein. Presented by Yvette Law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit our MAIN WEB SITE e at &lt;br /&gt;www.bffct.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We practice quiet sitting meditation, sacred chants, and mindfulness. Includes lively discussions on the practical daily application of Buddhism. Open to all seekers of wisdom and compassion from beginners to the most advanced. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We meet on most Sunday mornings from 10 - 12:15 p.m. at the Mansfield Freeman Center for East Asian Studies at Wesleyan University in Middletown, Connecticut. Google us, &amp;quot;Buddhist Faith Fellowship&amp;quot; for schedule, philosophy and directions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our group was established in 2001 with a Mahayana orientation, focusing on Shin Buddhism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have two local Affiliated Chapters:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SOUTHINGTON BUDDHIST FELLOWSHIP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://southington.bffct.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://southington.bf...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUDDHA GAIA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://buddhagaia.bffct.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://buddhagaia.bff...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Consider others as yourself&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;-- the Buddha&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>35 - 40 people attend. We are a friendly and warm community. You'll love the chanting, meditation and especially the insightful discussions.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205244487000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Good reasons to attending? 1) practice oriented 2) friendly and like-minded people 3) practical discussions 4) social networking 5) courses available 6) Learn from certified teachers  7) Learn to calm the mind and open your heart 8) free of charge</why><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202054758000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middletown Buddhist Meetup Group at Wesleyan Meeting</name><id>7253953</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205071200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/7253953/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/4/global_3037668.jpeg</photo_url></item>