<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>274 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371369</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center for Digital Imaging Arts at Boston University</name><city>Waltham</city><id>723446</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236903</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Understanding pricing and fees-&lt;br /&gt;How to figure out what to charge for your photography services&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;Monday April 12th, 2010, 6:00–9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This talk is not about WHAT to charge, but HOW TO FIGURE OUT what to charge. How many times have you just guessed at the price of a potential job and realized afterwards that you left money on the table? Knowing your costs and understanding this will help lead you to being a better paid photographer. Todd May of May’s Photography will help you look at your costs so you will know what goes into pricing a job. Todd is always an excellent source of business information for the working photographer, and this is a great opportunity to get up to date in an area vital to any successful photography business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Todd May started May's Photography with his wife Chun Ae May soon after leaving military service in 1990. After Graduating from NESOP in 1992, Todd and Chun Ae worked to develop their studio into a Commercial Advertising Studio. Moving through three studios along the way as the business grew, to their current 2600 Sq. Ft. studio located 20 miles south of Boston. Servicing clients from around the country Todd has photographed a wide variety of products for their clients. From computer chips to food, from people to shoes. The studio has maintained a steady stream of work through most of the years. Part of the growth of the studio has been in knowing the cost associated with running a business. That has helped Todd and Chun Ae determine what to be able to charge their clients. In this tough economic situation each photographer has to determine what it takes to do the job for their clients and what the market is willing to pay. Faced with these situations Todd and Chun Ae are redesigning how they approach work and pricing to enable themselves, and the studio, to go on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Center for Digital Imaging Arts&lt;br /&gt;274 Moody Street&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02453&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration: 6:00–7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Program: 7:00–10:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: CIPNE Members, Free; Non-members; $35, Full-time students, $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-registration is required for this program.&lt;br /&gt;Click here to register (Non-members may pay by PayPal) &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Walk-Ins Welcome&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Baker</member_name><member_id>5043048</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271286411000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270915580000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Understanding pricing - How to figure out what to charge for your photography!</name><id>13142992</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271113200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/13142992/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/b/global_14248107.jpeg</photo_url></item>