<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This evening we invite Sri Pingali and Ben Williams who will offer a provocative analysis and critique of Integral theory around the themes of cultural development and awakening. First, Integral theory posits a universal validity of cultural structures that animates its narrative of evolving worldviews. In part, the Integral map is largely derived from a rather narrow assessment of the emergence of cultural development among Western civilizations, without truly integrating the necessary historical reconstruction of cultural stages of development among Indic and other non-western civilizations (as well as their concomitant embodiment of "Modern" or "Mythic" worldviews). This creates the very real liability of generalizing cultural and historical idiosyncrasies from the West, often eclipsing alternative realities and trajectories of cultural development. It will be shown that the current representation and application of such structures does not even begin to capture the cultural life of the complex traditions that populate civilizations such as India. &lt;strong&gt;Using this rich culture as a case study, Sri and Ben will make clear the need for a much more holistic engagement with such cultures in the project of organizing and enacting a truly global and evolutionary Kosmopolitanism that actually enfolds, or at least accounts for, the insights and intelligences of non-western traditions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The second part of this talk will look into the ways Integral theory's model of awakening, in particular its articulation of state-stages and non-duality, is inadequate for tracking the emergent modalities and phenomenological contours of intersubjective awakening. &lt;strong&gt;In light of recent understandings and embodiments of panentheistic evolutionary non-duality, it will be shown how these evolutionary cosmologies and forms of awakening can potentially inform the robust purpose and meaning that is generated from all four quadrants in ways that even the most sophisticated premodern contemplative traditions do not.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sri Pingali&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;met Andrew Cohen in 1993 and has been a student ever since. He oversees all of EnlightenNext's initiatives and programs in his native India. He has organized several highly successful multi-city trips to India by Andrew Cohen to facilitate deep dialogue about the evolutionary perspective at the leading edges of education, philanthropy, media and spirituality. He has himself conducted multiple seminars on Evolutionary Enlightenment and the evolutionary worldview in India over the past decade. Sri brings a particularly informed inside-out perspective to cultural nuances as shaped by his own bi-cultural life experience and contemplative pursuits stretching back three decades. His abiding interest lies in applying the fundamental themes of Evolutionary Enlightenment to further cultural development at a global level. Sri leads an active professional life as Principal Consultant at a leading international IT and business-consulting firm. He holds a bachelors degree from the Indian Institute of Technology (Madras) and a doctorate in computer systems from the University of Massachusetts. He currently resides in Lenox, Massachusetts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ben Williams&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;is currently a PhD student and teaching fellow in the South Asian Studies department at Harvard University. His focus is on forms of argumentation in medieval Shaiva and Vaishnava text traditions during a transitional period in the Indian intellectual landscape when sectarian theologies and religious cosmologies began to emerge as important discursive elements in pan-Indian analytic philosophical treatises. Ben is also a long time devotee and student of Hip Hop music and culture and helped create a conference at Harvard on the social and political ramifications of grassroots Hip Hop movements in the Middle East region and Africa.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349490819000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347288232000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Subtleties of Cultural Development and Awakening</name><id>81711362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349478900000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/81711362/</event_url></item>