<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1000 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.368809</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge College</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10412732</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.110863</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every season, growers across Massachusetts plant and grow food for us. We have the opportunity to spend our food dollars &lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/5/a/event_200598522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;exclusively in Massachusetts, and buy direct from local farms. Buying direct from farmers is good for the local economy and the environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So in order to understand the various Farm Share programs available to consumers, we’ve invited farmers from across Massachusetts to join us in Cambridge for a one-evening Farm Share Fair, to explain to us all about their Farm Share programs with distribution spots in the Greater Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come meet the fantastic farmers from across our state on Thursday, March 14. 15% of the proceeds from the 2013 Farm Share Fair will be donated to theMOVE, a Cambridge non-profit dedicated to bringing youth and adults from urban Boston out to farms for work days, to learn about where food comes from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are expecting upwards of 40 farms and vendors! Veggies, fruit, flowers, dairy, and meat farm shares! Some of the farms include Neighborhood Farm, Red Fire Farm, Enterprise Farm, Farmer Dave's, World Peas CSA, First Root and Shared Harvest.....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy some great food and sustainable vendors. Kids station with games and activities. Special prizes and giveaways for anyone who signs up for their Farm Share (CSA) on site, with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FREE and OPEN to the PUBLIC&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.farmsharefair.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/9/6/event_200598582.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>6980975</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363308256000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359698503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Farm Share Fair</name><id>102466562</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363296600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/102466562/</event_url></item>