<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>205 Broadway</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821148</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 -331-2450</phone><name>Broadway Bistro</name><city>Providence</city><id>1386121</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.424403</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: Broadway Bistro - on Broadway over on the West Side, a couple of blocks up from Route 95 - look for the black lab on the side of the building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You've driven by it a million times and you've thought, "that looks like a cute place, look at the twinkly lights and I love the black lab on the side of the building". Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live on the West Side, you've undoubtedly been there already and know how cute and fabulous the food is! You're probably also keeping that to yourself too, since the place is such a nice neighborhood spot, why crowd it up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's really true, Broadway Bistro is a cozy, warm and casual neighborhood bistro complete with twinkly lights, black bead board, thonet-style chairs and the food is absolutely fabulous! It's been over 2 years since we've been for a MNM and recently they've expanded a bit and created a lovely bar section perfect for our chatty group. I'm excited and I hope you are too! Its a great spot and once you know about it, you'll be back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, If you've ever driven by and said "Hey I need to check that one out"......here's your chance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever. Except Hurricane Sandy and NYE 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the scarf or hat in the picture, but we're not hard to find!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363142447000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>49</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362761440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Broadway Bistro!</name><id>108279602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363039200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/108279602/</event_url></item>