<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Michael Skok (North Bridge Venture Partners) and Jay Batson (Founder of Acquia, Inc.) as they discuss what's needed to turn your PHP/OSS idea into a living, breathing business....in other words, the things that are important to have in place in order to fund your open source software technology company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will explore what's necessary (beyond simply building a better mouse trap) to get your idea to the altar and how to live happily ever after...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * What do investors look for;&lt;br /&gt;    * how do you build a team; &lt;br /&gt;    * where do you find talent;&lt;br /&gt;    * methods of validating business models;&lt;br /&gt;    * What else is needed, and&lt;br /&gt;    * where do you find it?&lt;br /&gt;    * ...and a whole lot more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Skok, General Partner, North Bridge Venture Partners&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Skok joined North Bridge Venture Partners in 2002. Prior to this Michael had been an entrepreneur and CEO in the software business for over 20 years. Michael founded, led and attracted over $100m in private equity to his investments in several successful software companies ranging from CAD/CAM, Document Management, Workflow, Imaging and Collaboration, Security to Analytics and spanning the Mini Computer, Workstation, PC, Client Server and Internet eras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Six of these companies were successfully acquired by Siebel, Platinum, Filenet, Banyan and IBM and two went Public, including Symantec for whom he built Symantec UK into their most profitable international business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael has served on many private and public company boards as well as supported various software industry groups such as the Software Publishers association where he was Chairman for a number of years in Europe. He is currently active on the boards of all his recent investments including Acquia, Active Endpoints, Demandware, Lumigent, MyPerfectGig, rPath and wis.dm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jay Batson, Founder of Acquia, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acquia, Inc is a venture-backed open source software company recently launched in the Boston area.  Prior to Acquia, Jay was the founder and CEO of Pingtel, an open source voice over IP PBX software company, which was financed by leading venture firms and strategic partners.  Jay has over 20 years experience in the software and hardware technology business.  He has held various management and technical positions including BBN, Cayman Systems, and ON Technology, as well as working as the leading analyst for Forrester Research into IP internetworking and Internet industries in the mid 1990's.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194651502000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191454630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>November User Group:: How to get your OSS venture off the ground.</name><id>6482478</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194478200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/6482478/</event_url></item>