<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>131 State St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358955</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 725-0100</phone><name>Kitty O'Sheas</name><city>Boston</city><id>709575</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057854</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a joint event held by a number of meet-up groups.  Basically we pack Kitty O'Sheas and have a few drinks, socialize and dance.   It's a good time, and Biagio invited Boston Live Music to join the event so I will let him tell it like he calls it -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Biagio of Social Fun says:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE, TRIPLE OR QUADRUPLE RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its time for another Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party for 160+ members at Kitty O’Sheas. This is not a Singles Party. Meaning anyone can come, including couples. All are welcome to Party and Socialize.biggrin&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Kitty O’Sheas is in Boston (near Faneuil Hall) 131 State St Boston, MA 02109 617-725-0100 Website &lt;a href="http://www.kittyoshea.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kittyoshea...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2nd floor holds 160 people its own DJ area + dance floor, plus its own bathrooms so we truly have out own private party. 3 Bartender covering 2 bars upstairs. I paid $300 for appetizers (Wings/veggie platter, cheeses etc) in advance since their Kitchen is too small to accommodate food for 160 members. There will be NO Refill on food so what we put out at 7PM will be gone by or before 8PM so yet another reasone to get here ealry to enjoy some food while it lasts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Music will medium levels in main room upstairs. Music will be tuned very low in the back room so members will have a separate area to chat. Till 8:45Pm then Jodi a member and a talented musician with play 3 live song til 9PM then the Dancing + Loud Music starts. Pease do not complain since people came to dance after 9PM + hear music.&lt;br /&gt;To get in tell Security at the stairs you are with Social Fun to get in (Even if you are with a different group). If you say ANY other group they will not let you in. Then walk upstairs to meet and greet Biagio your Host for the night. Please say your name and what group you are with. Then please give Biagio&lt;br /&gt;$5 to covers the cost to rent the whole 2nd floor, 3 bartenders +the DJ so its not all just to cover the food. Please no one dollar bills. Please have $5 ready in hand at the top of the stairs if you take too long Security will make members to go back downstairs. Sorry we cannot block the stairs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Everyone, but the Invited Meetup Group Head Organizers pays $5.&lt;br /&gt;2. After 9PM you will have to pay another $10 as a cover charge for the Bar Entrance fee to get in so that $15 total. $10 to bar and $5 to cover the cost for Biagio to rent the 2nd floor.&lt;br /&gt;3. If you get in before 9PM you ONLY have to pay $5 to Biagio to cover the cost to rent.&lt;br /&gt;4. It will be packed. get there early to ensure you can get in.&lt;br /&gt;5. If you come after 7:30PM you might not even get in right away and you will have to wait in line downstairs to go upstairs. There was one time late comers had to wait over half an hour to get in! NO Joke!&lt;br /&gt;6. Tell Security you are with Social Fun to get in -Even if you are with a different group.&lt;br /&gt;With all that aside and if I have not scared you away then please join us for all this fun Friday starting at 7 PM till the cows come home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 5 Meetup Groups that are invited to come:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Social Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Biagio)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Happy Hour &lt;a href="http://nightlife.meet.."&gt;http://nightlife.meet...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Tonya)&lt;br /&gt;    * Girls just want to have FUN Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com.."&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Sarah)&lt;br /&gt;    * The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://euro.meetup.co.."&gt;http://euro.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Noelle)&lt;br /&gt;    * Inquisitive Minds Meetup Group &lt;a href="http://www.inquisitiv.."&gt;http://www.inquisitiv...&lt;/a&gt;. (Confirmed by Indy)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe RSVPs will be moved to NO RSVPs 1 week before the event with no exception.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had over 185 members at last Mix and Mingle cross Meetup party .&lt;br /&gt;It should be fun and I hope you can all join us for this blast of a party!&lt;br /&gt;Ciao Biagio&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Biagio</member_name><member_id>3847345</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274486968000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272657037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joint Mix and Mingle - Kitty O'Shea's Boston</name><id>13342861</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274482800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/13342861/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/7/global_9580775.jpeg</photo_url></item>