<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;li&gt;Do you feel an inner “tug of war” over some things?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do you feel stuck in some part of your life you wish you could get on with?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;These are often signs of inner conflict – when a part of you wants one thing, but another part wants something else.  For example: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;“I want to be thinner, but I also want to eat what I want!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;I want more business, but I also want more time with my family.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;I want to save money, but I also love to spend it.&amp;quot;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I wish –x-, but I also want –y-.”  You fill in the blanks.  What conflicting desires do you have? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's very confusing to the Universe!  What kind of vibration is that? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wouldn’t it be nice to end the suffering and resistance caused by that “inner battle”?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this month's experiential meetup, you’ll learn a process for reaching a satisfying and comfortable resolution to your inner conflicts.  You’ll learn how to more easily and spontaneously act in ways that fit with who you want to be as a person, honoring &lt;u&gt;all&lt;/u&gt; parts of yourself, without any need for will power or discipline, but with easy, flowing allowing!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to arrive early and stay later for extra social time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun.  Please join us!  (Note our new, lower fee.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Note: It's very important to us that if you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;, to please show up. People have been getting better about this, and it is so helpful. Remember, if you need to change your plans, please change your rsvp or let us know. It really helps us with our planning, having less waste (handouts and food), and in being able to start on time. Thank you so much for cooperating with this!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258764396000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255817039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Resolving Inner Conflict and Resistance</name><id>hwpzkympbwb</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258502400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/11650173/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/global_7566143.jpeg</photo_url></item>