<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;one trail head, a few options. The question is do you want to hike on Sunday? this one is an easy to moderate class &amp;nbsp;rated hike.&amp;nbsp;depending on trail and hiker conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the class 3 cliffs are icy, turning around and retracing is an option, Even though this is a short hike, proper clothing is still required. Dress in warm layers and footwear. Trekking poles and microspikes may be helpful if the trail is icy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/f/6/event_84142262.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRAILHEAD:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;From the North I-93 Exit 24 onto US Rte 3 S about 4.6 miles to Holderness. Turn left on NH Route 113 and continue about 5.6 miles to trailhead on left. After &amp;nbsp;the Morgan trailhead parking lot, you will end up at the Percival trailhead on the left 1/8 mile down the road but we are starting from Percival trailhead. On a nice day the parking lot will likely be full when we get there, so plan to park on the side of the road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[div]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Hike New England:&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/MorganPercival080217.html"&gt;http://www.hikenewengland.com/MorganPercival080217.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This moderate loop hike over Mount Morgan and Mount Percival offers great lake and mountain views from each summit as well as the option to experience ladders and caves.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start at the Mount Percival Trailhead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow Mount Percival Trail for 0.2 mile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bear left onto the Morgan-Percival Connector and follow it for 0.5 mile to its end.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn right and follow Mount Morgan Trail for 1.6 miles until it meets with Crawford-Ridgepole Trail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn right and follow this path for about 0.4 mile. Mount Morgan Trail and Crawford-Ridgepole Trail coincide for this section. After about 0.2 mile you will walk past a series of ladders on the left leading up to a boulder cave that must be passed through before reaching Mount Morgan's cliff-top viewpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.hikenewengland.com/images/MorganPercival080217-05-SquamLake.jpg" alt="Squam Lake from Mount Morgan (photo by Mary Sheldon)" width="350" height="262" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The better option for winter is to continue about 0.2 mile farther on the main trail and then turn left to tackle the last part of Mount Morgan Trail, leaving Crawford-Ridgepole Trail behind. After 90 yards you will reach a fork. Bear left/straight to reach the cliff-top viewpoint in just 50 yards; or veer right to reach the true summit of Mount Morgan after 50 yards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to Crawford-Ridgepole Trail, turn left, and follow this route for 0.8 mile which will bring you to the summit of Mount Percival.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the descent, follow Mount Percival Trail. After less than 0.1 mile you will reach a trail junction, where on the way up one could opt to take a very rough route up to the summit by way of a boulder cave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue descending on Mount Percival Trail for 1.9 miles which will return you to the Mount Percival Trailhead parking area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>gold cr-v   603477-5116   TRAILHEAD: From the North I-93 Exit 24 onto US Rte 3 S about 4.6 miles to Holderness. Turn left on NH Route 113 continue about 5.6 miles to trailhead on left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326638242000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325679809000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last minute hike! Mt Morgan  Easy to Moderate rate</name><id>46596142</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326034800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/46596142/</event_url></item>