<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 1A</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.083500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jenness State Beach</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>937615</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.795936</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alright it's that time of year again. We are going to meet at the beach again for some great volleyball. We will be putting up the net at 5:30pm and starting soon after setup.&lt;/span&gt; Negative behavior is not permitted. We should all help putting up the net if we are available. We should all be having fun! Please everyone that can help putting up the net it would be much appreciated.&amp;nbsp; It would also be great if a couple people could bring a rake. If it does rain I will cancel by 5. If you are new to this we would love you to join.&amp;nbsp; Let's hope the weather is nice and sunny! New people are always welcome and don't hesitate to email me with questions. &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;We will also be having a bonfire this week after volleyball. &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;All are welcome to the bonfire. Those that are not playing volleyball can meet us at Jenness Beach at around 8:15pm and follow us to Sawyer Beach. We have a great time cooking and enjoying the summer night sky. We need someone to bring wood, some kind of food(ie. sausage, hot dogs, pasta salad, marshmellows, anything you can cook over a fire unless someone brings a grill or some kind of salad.) It would also be good to have plates, napkins, forks and skewers. Please post a comment about what you will be bringing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be there setting up the volleyball net! Let us know you are there and we will welcome you!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sarah</member_name><member_id>9389653</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310073978000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309280716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beach Volleyball and The After Party</name><id>23833091</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309987800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/23833091/</event_url></item>