<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>64 Market St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077868</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-430-9122 </phone><name>Portsmouth Gaslight</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>750121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757330</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/9/2/event_218192402.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new all female comedy show “High Heels Comedy Tour” takes the audience &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;through a hilarious 75 minute walk in the pumps of Bostons TOP female comedians. These laugh inducing women show off their unique points of view as they engage the audience with their offbeat life stories and opinions on &lt;span&gt;gossip, sex, men, family, friends and the pursuit of happiness. You’ll leave the show wiping your eyes and holding your sides.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The High Heels Comedy Tour hosted by &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Stacey Kendro&lt;/span&gt; has competed in several comedy festivals including the &lt;em&gt;Boston Comedy Festival and was a finalist in the Marshall's Women of Comedy Show.&lt;/em&gt; The show also features &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Andrea Henry&lt;/span&gt; who won Best Regional Film and The Audience Award for Best Comedy at the SENE Film Festival and her stand up credits include- Comedy Central's &lt;em&gt;Open Mic Fight,&lt;/em&gt; Nickelodeon's &lt;em&gt;Search for America's Funniest Mom 3&lt;/em&gt;, NBC's &lt;em&gt;Last Comic Standing&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Yuk Yuk's Great Canadian Laugh Off&lt;/em&gt; . Newcomer to the scene Dana Cairns has performed in &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333132"&gt;Beantown Comedy Riot, the Rhode Island Comic Throwdown, Boston Comedy Festival.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style="color : #333132"&gt;Dana also recently won the Closet Comics Big Break contest, for which she was given the opportunity to open for Rob Schneider at Boston’s famed Wilbur Theatre.&lt;/span&gt; The comedy tour brings a lineup of three female comics and celebrates the unique styles of women in comedy. The tour is refined yet quirky. &lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;The women all bring something different to the stage, proving that not only can females be funny; they can deviate from predictable penis punch lines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There will be a table for meetup members</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365436814000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Men and Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-527</urlname><id>501015</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Cocktail Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364315081000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>High Heels Comedy Tour</name><id>111142012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365202800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-527/events/111142012/</event_url></item>