<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>219 Elm St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.394418</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-776-5300</phone><name>Gargoyles On The Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>688517</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121317</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I have spent hours trying to find both a movie theater showing &amp;quot;Julie and Julia&amp;quot; and a French restaurant serving brunch in close proximity and it just isn't doable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, I have found a restaurant that will have some quasi-French items on its brunch menu, was able to give me a reservation for 8 people and is within walking distance of a movie theater (the Davis Square theater in Somerville) that is currently showing &amp;quot;Julie and Julia.&amp;quot; I cannot guarantee that it will still be doing so next Sunday, but if not, I will come up with some sort of Plan B (most likely dinner after the movie rather than brunch before it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I spoke with the nice people at Gargoyle's today, they weren't quite sure whether they were still going to be running their Restaurant Week lunch on the 23rd but they assured me that their regular brunch menu would be available and that the music is not loud enough to get in the way of conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: I am going to edit this meetup on Thursday night  or Friday morning, when the movie schedule for Sunday should become available.  I'll change the location/restaurant venue/meal then if necessary. On Friday evening I am going to change the RSVP setting to disallow Maybe RSVPs, so I hope that everyone will be able to firm up their plans by that time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would  really like to allow people to keep things flexible but the problem with allowing Maybes is that they take up a place and push people who might be otherwise willing to commit onto the waiting list. So you have until Friday evening to decide one way or another. After that the Maybe option will go away and anyone on the waiting list at that time will find themselves &amp;quot;upgraded&amp;quot; to a Yes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given the uncertain nature of this meetup, I am not charging the usual reservation fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservation is in my name</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252105303000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249686844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch and a foodie movie!</name><id>11061497</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251043200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/11061497/</event_url></item>