<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fairfield, CT 06824 Tel 203-292-8190</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06605</zip><lat>41.168293</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Catch A Healthy Habit Cafe 39 Unquowa Rd </name><city>Fairfield</city><id>1569632</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.215652</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;April 13, Wednesday &lt;br /&gt;7 to 9 pm &lt;br /&gt;Fairfield, Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;Catch A Healthy Habit Cafe &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free Talk by Ken Rohla: How to Make Your Own Nutrient-Dense Probiotic Antioxidant Superfoods for Pennies &lt;br /&gt;at Catch A Healthy Habit Cafe &lt;br /&gt;39 Unquowa Rd &lt;br /&gt;Fairfield, CT 06824 &lt;br /&gt;Tel 203-292-8190 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Think eating organic, vegan, or raw/living food is all you need in our diet to stay healthy? Think again! Even organic food is sadly lacking in nutrients these days, and most raw food supplements and "superfoods" contain mold. Ken Rohla TeachingKen Rohla will show you how to test your own food in your own kitchen to see for yourself what you are actually eating, or rather, what you're not! So what can you do about it? If you have the time and the land, you can grow your own food. You can grow sprouts to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can buy food-based supplements and superfoods, but in sufficient quantities, that can get quite expensive. Or you can make gallons of your own fresh supplements and superfoods for pennies, including probiotics, enzymes, and antioxidants, with high amounts of extremely regenerative ORMUS minerals, and imbue them with very healing ORMUS Brewsubtle scalar and other energies. Ken will also tell you how to use the same techniques to make your own kombucha (healing tea), pet supplements, plant food, plant growth accelerator, compost accelerator, nontoxic household cleaner, odor eliminator, mold and mildew remover, and more. Bring paper and writing instrument, Ken always gives out a ton of very specific useful info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Catch A Healthy Habit Cafe 39 Unquowa Rd Fairfield, CT 06824 Tel 203-292-8190</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302740297000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Learn how to Make Your Own Nutrient-Dense Probiotic Antioxidant Superfoods for Pennies.</why><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300572977000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE TALK: Ken Rohla @ Catch A Healthy Habit Cafe in Fairfield, CT</name><id>16980545</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302735600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/16980545/</event_url></item>