<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This Hike is FULL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;RSVP's are Closed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Before signing up for this event, please read and understand the entire Write-Up and the Liability Waiver. By signing up for this event you agree to the terms of the Liability Waiver.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rating: Moderate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance: 6.5 Miles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time Duration: 4 Hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blaze Orange: Recommended&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike begins on the Escoheag Trail which is the white blazed path and is a 3 1/4 mile loop that wanders through a rocky forest. We will follow this trail to where it intersects with the blue blazed North South Trail which we will take briefly to the Falls River. Just before the bridge on the left side of the road is the start of the Ben Utter Trail. This trail is blazed in the blue of the North South Trail as well as yellow, which we will follow to where it splits and we will continue to follow the yellow blazed trail along the river. Soon we will veer off on the white blazed trail which will take us to the Stepstone Falls. At Falls River Road we will reverse direction and head back on the woods road, blue blazed trail to our intersection with the Escoheag Trail where we will return to our cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hike is about 6.5 Miles and should take 4 Hours to complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring Drinking water (1 Liter), Snacks, Hiking Boots and bug spray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Address: 216 Escoheag Hill Road, Exeter, RI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: Route 95 exit 5A, take RI 102 South to RI 3 South. Follow RI South to RI 165 West ( Ten Rod Road ). Follow RI 165 West 5 1/4 miles and take a Right onto Escoheag Hill Road and after about 1 mile you will see a grassy area with a Red Cabin on your Right. This is where we park. Note: Escoheag Hill Road is across from Woody Hill Road on RI 165.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety First!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John N</member_name><member_id>11460346</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370818936000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1370545411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Escoheag Trail (Weber # 15) and Ben Utter Trail (Weber # 16) Combined Hike</name><id>123302662</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370784600000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/123302662/</event_url></item>