<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>472 Mass Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363930</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7013310920</phone><name>Middle East Downstairs</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>577669</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101230</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you hadn't heard of Deerhoof, you're welcome! This is an undefinable band, just as capable of producing sugary gems of catchy pop as they are at delivering intricate and challenging prog-rock passages. :-) They are as talented and simultaneously unpredictable as I've come across. And their fans include Radiohead, Sufjan Stevens, Beck, the Flaming Lips, the list goes on and on...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those interested in checking them out, my personal favorite CDs are probably Friend Opportunity, The Runners Four, Apple O' -- oh heck, I don't know, all of them. But their very early stuff was a little raw and not yet ripe, so don't go back past Apple O' in my humble opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, let's all go see them! -- I saw them once before and it was fun as all get-out!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Update: There are actually two openers tonight.  Here are the bands and set times:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doors at 8:00...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Big Big Bucks:  9:00&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Buke and Gase:  10:00&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Deerhoof: 11:00&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually listened to Buke and Gase on their page and they sound amazing, so I do want to hear them, however I don't need two opening bands, so my thinking now is to meet at 9:30?  Hope the show isn't too late for folks, it should be well worth it!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mitch</member_name><member_id>7862947</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348023908000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347506825000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deerhoof!</name><id>82175312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348012800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/82175312/</event_url></item>