<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*Come join us this Saturday night to help celebrate Charlotte's bday in Cambridge!  She's a cool girl who is a new arrival to the Boston area.  All members are welcome to join in on the festivities.  The plan is to meet up at the lounge area in Om Restaurant, and then head around the corner to Redline, a nice venue for drinks and dancing.  This is a great event to meet new people and to get your groove on!  New and current members welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8pm at the lounge inside Om Restaurant (92 Winthrop St, Cambridge).  This is a cozy, upscale lounge, so finding the group should not be difficult.  We will head over to Redline around 10pm.  Please meet us at Om, and get there early as to have time to meet folks.  Cover:  Should be a cover-free night...  see what I do for y'all?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as these are upscale venues.  If traveling by T, Harvard Square is the closest T stop on the red line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220057197000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Should be a great night out!</why><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216612749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come Celebrate Charlotte's B-Day!  Nightlife Mixer + Dancing on Sat, July 26!</name><id>8379434</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217116800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8379434/</event_url></item>