<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>911 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.845997</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-871-9300</phone><name>New England Pizza Restaurant</name><city>Vernon Rockville</city><id>318964</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.454155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As of this posting CT for Liberty members have obtained voter information for two towns, those are our targets (Vernon and Simsbury) for the time being. Door knocking is generally not done on Sundays, so to make auspicious use of our time we are scheduling a Sunday literature drop. While going door to door and spending time with voters to find &lt;em&gt;their&lt;/em&gt; issue is the ideal way to go, we simply do not have the time or resources required to make a significant impact in this manner. Sunday should be a nice quiet day traffic-wise, and we won't be disturbing anyone. I can see some folks surprised Monday morning when something is hanging on their mailbox but other than that the lit drops should go smoothly. Since time is short the plan is to selectively target groups that will yield the biggest net effect for us. I.E., the groups known to turnout for Ron Paul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have thousands of handouts ready to go, and I have bags on the way as well. This whole process works very fast. One person drives, the other hangs the literature. Most mailboxes in this area have the hook for the Reminder, and the one's that don't we just hung on the mailbox flag when we lit dropped for Ron Paul in 2008. If there's enough people we can take more than one car. We'll meet at New England Pizza, I'll have everything we need ready to go map / brochure / bag-wise.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334510337000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333729498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Literature Drop</name><id>59524512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334505600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/59524512/</event_url></item>