<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>News:  The Weather Bumblers are predicting very wet weather from Friday night to &lt;br /&gt;Sunday night with the worst weather being on Saturday night.  I live only a few blocks &lt;br /&gt;Away from Look At Me Now driving a SUV so I can get there in very wet weather.&lt;br /&gt;I will keep an eye on the weather this weekend.  If it is too bad then&lt;br /&gt;I will encourage anyone who is not local to consider the weather risk and&lt;br /&gt;Stay home if it is too dangerous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can have more Unknown Zone Only Meet Ups at other times and at other&lt;br /&gt;Locations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather might also be a factor for Sunday's Meet Up.&lt;br /&gt;I might not have time to send a memo on that until later on tonight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sandra, poetry author, said that she is coming on Saturday&lt;br /&gt;She will show me a cover of her most recent book so I will&lt;br /&gt;Write something about it when I know more about it.&lt;br /&gt;End of news memo.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday the 6th now - Change in Date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unknown Zoners will have a night of discussing various &lt;br /&gt;Conspiracy Topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the topics will be TWA 800 Air Craft Crash,&lt;br /&gt;Secret Societies,   different assassinations&lt;br /&gt;New World Order and a few other topics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I tape Coast to Coast shows, so in my SUV right now&lt;br /&gt;Is a tape of George Noorey talking to authors of&lt;br /&gt;TWA 800 Books on the 10 year Anniversary in &lt;br /&gt;JULY 2006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coasttocoastam.com/shows/2006/07/17.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coasttocoa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.coasttocoastam.com/shows/2006/07/17.html&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members are encouraged to bring their own curiosity and&lt;br /&gt;Some topics of their own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will mention events on the current calendar and do members&lt;br /&gt;Want other events in the up coming weeks and months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have not had a real Unknown Zone meeting for a long&lt;br /&gt;Time because no one has been showing up for anything.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the change from Wednesday to Saturday.&lt;br /&gt;There was hardly any interest in Wednesday.&lt;br /&gt;Lori - Look at Me Now&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;Glen - Catch a Healthy Habit&lt;br /&gt;will be more available on Saturday the&lt;br /&gt;Sixth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Car pooling is encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am not putting this Meet Up on any other Meet Up&lt;br /&gt;Calendars.  I have mentioned it briefly as a UZ Only Meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope that we can have more Unknown Zone only Meet Ups&lt;br /&gt;So that we can discuss Conspiracy, Paranormal and Current&lt;br /&gt;Event Topics in more Private Settings (Not members houses).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glen from Catch a Healthy Habit said that he will be &lt;br /&gt;available so that members can&lt;br /&gt;buy his smoothies and other types of Healthy Food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Being from West Haven, I am aware of the parking &lt;br /&gt;Problems on Campbell Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;I am also aware of parking areas&lt;br /&gt;That others might not be aware of or use.&lt;br /&gt;Most of the time, I use the large parking area that is behind&lt;br /&gt;Loris store.   I was using that parking area over a decade ago &lt;br /&gt;Long before Lori even moved into that store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, turn into the side street&lt;br /&gt;Of Curtis Place next to&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s Pizza Italian Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;(Restaurant has had a few different names over the years &lt;br /&gt;But this is its latest name.&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony workers/owner has invited us to have some&lt;br /&gt;Meet Ups there as well.).&lt;br /&gt;There is a large parking area behind there.&lt;br /&gt;Going to Campbell Avenue, you can walk over towards&lt;br /&gt;Marc Anthony s.&lt;br /&gt;Then turn right on Campbell Avenue to Lori s store.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I walk over toward the right from the parking lot. &lt;br /&gt;There is an alley between the buildings.  &lt;br /&gt;On Campbell Avenue, I turn left.  Loris store is a few stores in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you all, not counting those out of state or far away, do not &lt;br /&gt;Attend any events, then why should I even have a Meet Up Group?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike B&lt;br /&gt;Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lori Larsen and myself will be POCs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>maribeth</member_name><member_id>2893690</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220915165000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216957252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What Do You Want To Know? on Sept. 6</name><id>8408354</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220742000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/8408354/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/f/global_2489375.jpeg</photo_url></item>