<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Real Estate Investor&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you seen this exciting newspaper headline? “US Homes Facing Foreclosure Surged to 58% in the First 6 Months of the Year”. These headlines are reinforcing the facts that I have been telling my students for months! The best foreclosure market in 30 years is coming like a tidal wave and the smart investors are going to make a fortune on the Tsunami of overleveraged homes that are behind on payments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Banks will be begging investors for discounted offers on these overleveraged properties so they can get the bad debt off their books. So my question to you is, do you know how to do short sales effectively so you can make a fortune from the Tsunami of foreclosures?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you answered NO, then you are missing out on some of the fattest and easiest checks you could ever get.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not actively discounting mortgages in default to create huge profits in your real estate busines right now, you are missing the hottest pre-foreclosure market in the past 30 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here’s Just A Short List Of The Content That Will Be Covered:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Why This Is The Best Time In History To Invest In Foreclosures And How Foolish You’d Be NOT To Get Involved.&lt;br /&gt;    * How To Capture The Huge Tidal Wave Of Pre-foreclosure Deals Over The Next 12 Months.&lt;br /&gt;    * How To Find GREAT Deals Every Single Time &amp;amp; Where You Can Get Other People’s Money To Fund These Deals.&lt;br /&gt;    * The Step By Step Process To Negotiating Huge Profits On Discounting Mortgages.&lt;br /&gt;    * What Are The Different Types Of Loans To Avoid.&lt;br /&gt;    * How To Sell Short Sales For Huge Profit In A Down Market.&lt;br /&gt;    * and much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who is Steve Dillon?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve Dillon is an ex-loss mitigator who worked in the banking industry for several large lending institutions. Steve negotiated over 8,000 short sales while in the banking profession. He left loss mitigation to do real estate and has been helping hundreds of real estate investors negotiate bigger profits on short sales for several years now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=126" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=126" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctreia.com/eve...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233155454000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230530223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting with Steve Dillon</name><id>9400416</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232406000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/9400416/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/5/global_6764389.jpeg</photo_url></item>