<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Shore Rd</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>11766</zip><lat>40.943713</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>631 642 2200  ext 0</phone><name>Pathways To Health</name><city>Mount Sinai</city><id>939059</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.032907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #006600"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join Dr. Bezmen for&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #006600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hypnosis 1&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #006600"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Creative Visualization&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;October 24th 25th &amp;amp; 26th&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #006600"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wednesday 7:30p.m. Thurs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;day &amp;amp; Friday&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;9:00a.m.-5:00p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #990099"&gt;Did you know everyone can learn how to use Hypnosis and Creative Visualization to help change their life as well as others? Hypnosis and Creative Visualization can be use for relaxation, pain management, to help people reach their goals and much, much more!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #990099"&gt;Come learn all about how Hypnosis and Creative Visualization can change your life!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #006666"&gt;Creative visualization is a stand alone course for those that want to learn how to use imagery and the deeper mind to help themselves and others. It is also the first module for the 100 hrs required for certification. Pathways To Health believes that this class is a must for anyone that wants to improve their life or if an individual works with people. Participants learn a philosophy and powerful system of healing; how to communicate effectively with the inner mind; how to set effective goals and how to word suggestions for yourself or others, misconceptions surrounding hypnosis; functions of the subconscious mind; levels of trance, powerful induction techniques, pacing and leading to establish rapport, behavioral approaches in treatment; and supervised practicum experience. .&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #006666"&gt;Dr. William Bezmen, co-director of Pathways To Health is a Certified Hypnotherapy Instructor and creator of the healing paradigm, HypnoSynergistic Healing. he is teaching the Hypnosis certification series starting in August and running through November. This is a 100 hr program that leads to certification by The American Board of Hypnotherapy. It is also a requirement for certification as a HypnoSynergistic Practitioner. This 4 module sequence takes Dr. Bezmen's 35 years of clinical experience, in working with the deeper mind and puts it into a format that is easy to learn. Beginners as well as advanced practitioners, will be able to use these new skills immediately in their practice as well as to enhance their own life. Don't Miss this opportunity!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #006666"&gt;This is a great opportunity for people to learn this powerful method to help others change their lives, and provide a wonderful way to increase their own income. Many people believe that there is no other course that teaches as complete a healing paradigm to help people make the changes in their lives that they desire. Note: Creative Visualization may be taken alone for those who just want to learn the most effective methods to utilize imagery and goal setting in their lives or practice.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #009900 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #009900"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff3300"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Pre-requisite. Fee for this module is $350&lt;/strong&gt; if taken alone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #660099"&gt;Pathways to Health&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #660099"&gt;77 Shore Road&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #660099"&gt;Mount Sinai NY 11766&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #660099"&gt;&lt;span&gt;631-642-2200 ext. 0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Call to reserve your spot!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #006666"&gt;For individuals that wish to become Certified Hypnotherapist Tuition for the 100hr,  4 module program is $1700.  &lt;br /&gt;

 There is an Early Registration Discount of $200 for those who register and pay in full for the program before October 1st  Total price after discount will be $1500&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>William Bezmen</member_name><member_id>8774813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351285675000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People Making Life Changes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Spiritual-Journey-Transformation-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1440337</id><group_lat>40.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-73.0100021362</group_lon><name>The Mount Sinai Life Transformation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347827945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hypnosis 1 "Creative Visualization"</name><id>82673282</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>163800000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351121400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Spiritual-Journey-Transformation-Meetup-Group/events/82673282/</event_url></item>