<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;We did it!  We manifested a laptop projector and we're having a movie night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You’ve most likely heard us say many times that we believe we all create our experiences through the power of our thoughts and emotions.  Given this, we all have the capacity to heal and to determine our health.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How strongly do you believe in your capacity to heal and create?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would a boost of easy to understand scientific evidence be helpful and interesting to hear?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;What if you had the scientific basis to not only explain “miracle cures”, but the means to also deliberately initiate them?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt; “The Living Matrix – The New Science of Healing”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;reveals that energy and information fields, not genetics, drives human physiology!&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will hear scientists, psychologists, bioenergetic researchers and holistic practitioners who have discovered and proven that we are far more than biochemical machines. You’ll also hear real people tell their stories of making remarkable recoveries with energetic “information-based” therapies&lt;/span&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;We found the movie totally inspiring and belief affirming, and can’t wait to share it with you!  After the movie, we can have a great discussion with people from our very own community who practice some of the healing therapies mentioned in the film.  If you practice or have had positive experiences with any kind of alternative healing therapy, please come and join us!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;We’re showing this at our January Law of Attraction meetup, but are opening it up to anyone who wants to view this powerful film. Please invite whoever you like and share this info.!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The movie is 83 minutes long; so please arrive on time, as it will be important for us to start promptly. We also encourage everyone to linger afterwards to socialize, etc.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you RSVP, &lt;u&gt;please&lt;/u&gt; let us know if your plans change, so we won’t be waiting for you unnecessarily.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun.  Please join us!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264118866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260925927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Metro West Law of Attraction/"Good Vibrations" January Meetup</name><id>hwpzkyncbzb</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263945600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/12093130/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/f/global_7566143.jpeg</photo_url></item>