<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As a web developer, have you ever wished you could develop applications for desktop, phones and tablets but were intimidated by the steep learning curve associated with developing native applications?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Boston PHP member and Microsoft Technical Evangelist Chris Bowen to discuss how Windows 8 will attempt to bridge the development gap between web developers and native application developers. Chris has been attending our Boston PHP meetups for years and we are excited to have him take the podium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;This meetup will be a Look at Windows 8 and Using HTML5, CSS3 &amp;amp; JavaScript to Create Windows Store Apps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This session is an introduction to Windows 8, from the user experience to developer opportunities and options, including using your existing web skills to create Windows Store apps. Much of the time will focus on demos, showing how to use HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript skills to leverage Windows 8 capabilities such as live tiles, notifications, sharing, search, and more. We'll also look at what's new with Internet Explorer 10, Visual Studio 2012, and Blend to help make development and design easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Chris:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Chris Bowen (&lt;a href="http://blogs.msdn.com/cbowen"&gt;http://blogs.msdn.com/cbowen&lt;/a&gt;) is a Principal Technical Evangelist with Microsoft, specializing in web and client development technologies and working with companies and developers in the northeastern US. An architect and developer with over 19 years in the industry, he joined Microsoft after holding senior technical positions at companies including Monster.com, VistaPrint, and Staples. He is coauthor of two books (with Addison-Wesley and WROX) and holds an M.S. in Computer Science and a B.S. in Management Information Systems, both from Worcester Polytechnic Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be serving free pizza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30 - 7 Pizza and networking&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7 - 7:15   Announcements and intros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15 - 8:30 Main presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:30 - 8:50  Q&amp;amp;A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9 - ??? Beers at Champions Bar?&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be on the first floor at the NERD Center. Check in with security then go up one level in the elevator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Bowen</member_name><member_id>4551463</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Murphy</member_name><member_id>4790321</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347588620000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>79</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346725990000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Developing Windows 8 Apps with Your Existing Web Skills</name><id>80717982</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347489000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/80717982/</event_url></item>