<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street, 2nd Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1065386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183899</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In this experiential workshop you will learn simple yet powerful Tantra Yoga practices to revitalize the body, quiet the mind, replenish the heart and enliven the soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will learn to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ground and connect to Source&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deepen your connection with yourself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become aware of your energy field and how it interacts with others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activate the flow of kundalini in your body&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a safe space for exploration, we will use the modalities of movement, breath and sound  to access untapped aspects of you ~ to increase your vitality and expand your capacity for pleasure and joy! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring your curiosity and join us for an enlivening, playful evening with other like-minded souls!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open to singles and couples of all genders and sexual orientations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please refrain from wearing fragrances. It is suggested to wear comfortable clothing to move in and to bring a water bottle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$30/each at the door&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EARLY BIRD DISCOUNT: $20/each for the first 10 people to register by May 10!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brynn Bishop&lt;/strong&gt; is a Tantra Educator and Holistic Sex and Relationship Coach with over 25 years experience in the fields of body-mind integration and conscious relating. Her passion is guiding people on the path of intimacy, freedom and fulfillment. Brynn is known for her down-to-earth, welcoming presence and her contagious enthusiasm. She maintains a private practice in Boston and internationally via phone and Skype.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Great class, it was my first experience with Tantra but everyone was nice and I felt comfortable being there. It really does raise energy, and I even had an emotional release because energy got unblocked in my system. I'm so glad I went. Great teacher! ” -Anna&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A wonderful way to get in touch and regain some of our lost parts. Brynn led us into the world of everyday intimacy in a very safe and fun environment. She will definitely help you open up to new possibilities.” -Rob &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368896181000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367461241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Tantric Intimacy: For Curious &amp; Open Beginners!</name><id>117278552</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368833400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/117278552/</event_url></item>