<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Orris Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03215</zip><lat>43.904044</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>WELCH-DICKY TRAILHEAD PARKING LOT</name><city>Waterville Valley</city><id>924714</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.591208</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Trailhead: Take I93 North to Exit 28, make a right onto NH49 East, travel about 5 miles and make a left onto Upper Mad River Road, make a right onto Orris Road. We will hike the trail counter clockwise over the summits of Welch (2,605') and Dickey (2,734'). 50% of the hike will have views, a rarity in the wooded Northeast. 4.4 miles round trip, 1,800' elevation gain, AMC book time 3 hours, 5.5 hours estimated time for our group.No dogs. ----Steve---- Disclaimer: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Black Colorado pick up truck NH2431202</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve A</member_name><member_id>6009756</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309196700000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1413769</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>New England Over 50 Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307455806000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MODERATE HIKE - WELCH AND DICKEY</name><id>21302971</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309093200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Over-50-Hiking-Group/events/21302971/</event_url></item>