<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>HBA Boston – Take Charge of Your Career with HBA Development Programs&lt;br /&gt;When:              Thursday, January 27, from 6:00 p.m. to 9:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Genzyme Corporation&lt;br /&gt;                        500 Kendall Street&lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge, MA 02142&lt;br /&gt;Register:&lt;a href="https://netforum.avectra.com/eweb/DynamicPage.aspx?Site=HBA&amp;amp;WebCode=EventList&amp;amp;FromSearchControl=Yes" target="_blank"&gt;https://netforum.avec...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We hear about the importance of “career development” all the time, but what does it really mean Attend this event to learn how to drive your own career growth by taking advantage of mentoring experiences and other training opportunities from MLSC Board member, Abbie Celniker, PhD, CEO, Taligen Therapeutics. Dr. Celniker is an industry leader known for her inspiring mentorship and generosity in advising the careers of others. The Leadership Success Series (LSS) and HBA Boston Mentoring Group programs will present “model sessions” to give you a taste of how these Healthcare Businesswomen's Association (HBA) Boston resources can enhance your personal growth. This program is designed to help participants identify steps to help translate their self-reflection into a meaningful career development program, regardless of career stage. Enjoy the inspiring words of Dr. Celniker and to learn about how the HBA Boston Chapter can support your professional skill building.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296173293000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292990414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HBA Boston – Take Charge of Your Career with HBA Development Programs</name><id>15796145</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296169200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15796145/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>