<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1686 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.341407</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-277-1002</phone><name>Beacon Hill Athletic Club</name><city>Brighton</city><id>1188475</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.145991</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join Tracy Rodriguez, Ali Weinberg, Pat Donaher, Morgan Gottfried and Nicole Burrill, The Sassy Yogini herself, for a 90-minute Vinyasa yoga class with tons of assisting to benefit The Alzheimer's Association. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

DETAILS Date: 9/16 Time: 1-3PM (15 minute welcome and thanks, 90 minute class, raffle time!) Location: Beacon Hill Athletic Club Cleveland Circle Location - 1686 Commonwealth Avenue, Brighton, MA Tracy's Info: 203 984 0013, &lt;a href="mailto:tracyhrodriguez@gmail.com"&gt;tracyhrodriguez@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

A word from Tracy:&lt;/span&gt;    Many of you know that I grew up with my grandfather as a second father to me, spending my summers in Daytona Beach with my Liti and Lito, learning how to swim and a proper Spanish accent. (My oldest sister couldn't say abuelita and abuelito so she coined the nicknames) But not many of you know that my Lito is suffering from Alzheimer's. It's harder to go through than I can put to words, conversations cut short and repeated to an extend that brings you to tears and inspires you to fight back... My middle sister, Lexi, left her corporate job to work for Alzheimer's Association to make a difference working to cure this disease so that others don't suffer like my Lito, and caregivers like my Liti and Dad have the resources they need. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This month I will walk with my family in our first Walk to End Alzheimer's in our hometown in CT. I am hosting this class to raise funds for our walk team. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Class is a suggested $10 donation - that will get you class + 10 raffle tickets. Splurge by donating $25 and get 100 raffle tickets. Items are off the hook, trust me. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

You can pay online by donating to my team (Lito, Te Amo) or pay day of. (&lt;a href="http://act.alz.org/site/TR/Walk/CT-Connecticut?px=6302097&amp;amp;pg=personal&amp;amp;fr_id=1365" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;http://act.alz.org/site/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;TR/Walk/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;CT-Connecticut?px=6302097&amp;amp;p&lt;/span&gt;g=personal&amp;amp;fr_id=1365&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

So mark your calendar, tell your friends and don't forget ;) - 9/16 1-3pm BHAC Cleveland Circle location!!&lt;/p&gt;
RSVP on Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/?ref=logo#!/events/401470353250729/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/?ref=logo#!/events/401470353250729/&lt;/a&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Veena</member_name><member_id>2875214</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347826146000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Yogis</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonyoga</urlname><id>169595</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Yoga</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346934648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charity Yoga Class for the Alzheimer's Association</name><id>81114732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347814800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonyoga/events/81114732/</event_url></item>