<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Nate is just returning from the &lt;a href="http://openplans.org/projects/sorrento-sprint" target="_blank"&gt;Sorrento Sprint&lt;/a&gt; in Sorrento, Italy where he worked to improve the &lt;a href="http://openplans.org/projects/sorrento-sprint/multimedia" target="_blank"&gt;multimedia&lt;/a&gt; capabilities of Plone. Nate will discuss the new features of the &lt;a href="http://plone4artists.org" target="_blank"&gt;Plone4Artists&lt;/a&gt; suite of products and other products that were developed/enhanced at the sprint. Read Reinout Van Ree's &lt;a href="http://vanrees.org/weblog/topics/sorrentosprint2007" target="_blank"&gt;blog posts about the sprint&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your interested in knowing what what's the latestest and greatest in the Plone world, this meetup is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.bostonplone.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonplone.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonplon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The entrance is in the center of the long building next to the reflecting pool. Tell the security guard you are here for the Plone Users Group meeting. Call me on my cell if you have trouble. If coming by T, closest stop is green line Symphony T stop. Hynes Convention Center is also very close, as is Mass Ave (Orange line). Parking at the Christian Science Center underground parking garage available, but will cost $5. Please let the parking attendant know that you are here for the Plone Meetup hosted by Danny Robert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that while the official location of the church is 1 Norway Street, the meetup location is in the Christian Science Church Park and is closer to Huntington Ave. See this &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/yegprt" target="_blank"&gt;Google map&lt;/a&gt; for clarification.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180930415000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Plonista</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonplone</urlname><id>207992</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Plone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174608490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Plone April Meetup</name><id>5595996</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177628400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/events/5595996/</event_url></item>