<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Building E25, Room 119</address_2><address_1>45 Carleton St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>714153</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086334</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In addition to the normal "bring what you want to play" games that are the usual structure for the evening, we will also section off a part of the room for "Minute to Win It" games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do not know what "Minute To Win It" is, it is a game show where people have to perform a task in under a minute to move on to the next tier of gaming.&amp;nbsp; Games played here will be likely to include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;A Bit Dicey&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The contestant must stack six dice on a popsicle stick held in their mouth and balance them for three seconds.&lt;/dd&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;em&gt;
          &lt;strong&gt;Back Flip&lt;/strong&gt;
        &lt;/em&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The contestant must flip and catch a set of pencils from the back of their hand, starting with two for level 2, four for level 4 and six for level 7 and adding two more after each successful catch until they reached the specified number of pencils. 
&lt;em&gt;Level: 2 (12 pencils)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Chop Stack&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Using a pair of chopsticks, the contestant must stack four lip balm containers on top of each other. The tower must stay standing for three seconds in order to count&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Face the Cookie&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The contestant, using only their face, must move two Oreo cookies individually from their forehead to their mouth. Also see "Face the Gingerbread Man" in Christmas Challenges. This game is known in Australia as Bite the Bickie&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Field Goal&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The contestant must build a tower of six cups, alternating between right-side up and upside-down, on the suspended ends of a yardstick balanced on a cup.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Get Forked&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The contestant must roll quarters a distance of 16 feet (4.9&amp;nbsp;m) in an attempt to land one between two prongs of an upside-down fork&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Oh Nuts!&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this spin-off of The Nutstacker, the contestant must slide eight nut and bolt pairings from a metal ruler to stack them on top of each other. The tower must be freestanding for three seconds to count&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Stack Attack&lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The contestant must stack&amp;nbsp;28 cups in a pyramid form and then deconstruct it by sliding the cups down diagonally, and stacking the resulting piles into one giant stack, as it started in&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will not be able to play all the games as my budget at the moment can't handle all the supplies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**the door to the building gets locked somewhere between 6:30-7:00, but for the 1st 15 minutes we will have someone posted at the door to let people in. If you arrive later than that, it should be easy to get in as there is a lot of foot traffic of people coming and going. If you can't get in just call Ben, at 617-997-3545 or Becki at 818-523-2518 From the T: Take the red-line to Kendall Square station. If you're coming outbound (from Park Street), exit at the gates at the front of the train. Cross the street. (The street will be behind you if you take the escalator.) Proceed behind the T entrance on the other side to the street behind. Building E25 is the brick building across the street. If you're coming inbound (from Central Square), exit at the gates at the rear of the train. Take the stairs or elevator straight up. Proceed to the street in front of you. Building E25 is the brick building across the street. Driving directions from Mass Ave.: If you are coming from Boston or Memorial Drive, take a right at the first right past Memorial Drive. This is Vassar Street. If you are coming from Cambridge and points west, take a left onto Vassar Street. This will be past Central Square about 2 blocks before the river. If you get to the river, you've gone too far. From Vassar, take the first right onto Main Street. Go through two signals then turn right onto Hayward. You may park in the parking lot on the right side of Hayward. A MIT parking permit is NOT required in the evening, but please do not park in the spaces marked Medical. Exit the parking lot at the rear (opposite from where you entered). Building E25 will be directly across the street. Once you enter, Room 119 is just past the stairs on the right. There is a suggested donation of $1.00 that goes towards site fees.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are the only ones in the room at that time.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314058694000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269868843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Minute to Win It Edition</name><id>kpshnyplbdc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314054000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/27458431/</event_url></item>