<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South Moat Mountain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a hike on Moat Mountain Trail to the summit of South Moat Mountain, elevation 2,749 feet. Easy to moderate in difficulty,with some ledge scrambling at higher elevations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in the heart of the White Mountains, barren Moat Ridge parallels and overshadows North Conway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/a/3/1/event_8251281.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;South Moat offers a great view of Mt Washington, just outside the town of Conway.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Length 5.26 mi Elevation Gain 2,080 ft   Hike  difficulty:  Easy to moderate. Trekking poles are helpful on the upper trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring enough food,water and sports drinks for the event and your &lt;strong&gt;Hike Safe Essentials&lt;/strong&gt; listed on our Meetup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 South Moat Mountain provides 360-degree views from its ledgy summit. This hike approaches the peak from the south via Moat Mountain Trail and returns by the same route.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start at the Moat Mountain Trailhead on Dugway Road in Albany.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/7/4/event_144379572.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/2/c/event_144378732.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Follow Moat Mountain Trail for 2.7 miles to the summit of South Moat. We will return via the same trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/d/0/event_144379152.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TRAIL SURFACE Dirt, rock, and ledges&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My event is a casual paced hike. A little slower, everyone is encouraged to come along. Our objective is to have fun and get to know our fellow hikers. If the Meetup is large, we may break into 2 comfort groups, but you must stay in your group for trail support. Anyone can twist an ankle or need assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well mannered dogs are welcome and loved, but need to be leashed when other dogs are approaching. It is so awkward to see the dogs clash and this does upset the group. Make sure you have the extra food and water for your pup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ATTENTION ROCK HOUNDS: Moat Mountain Smoky Quartz Collecting Area    Geology: The Moat Mountain range is located 4 miles west of North Conway. The east side of the mountain range is a contact between the Moat volcanic rocks and Conway granite. This contact is known for an abundance of miarolitic cavities (pockets) of smoky quartz and feldspar, with some samples of topaz, fluorite, reibeckite, cassiterite, and some other minerals in very small abundance. Location: From West Side Rd. in Conway turn onto Passaconaway Rd. Travel 1.2 miles and turn right on High Street (dirt). The road leads into the White Mountain National Forest, passing a gate at 1.4 miles. At 1.7 miles, bear left at the sign pointing to the mineral site and drive 0 .7 miles to the parking area. Hike 0.9 miles to the Moat Mountain Smoky Quartz Collecting area.Mineral Collecting Tips: The most common finds in this area are small smoky quartz crystals embedded in the Conway granite. Look for minerals in the rock fragments. Make sure to bring Ziplock baggies or newspaper for specimens collected. Other recommended items include safety glasses, gloves, geologist’s hammer and cold chisel, hand trowel for loose dirt and a field guide to rocks and minerals.  Recreational Rock and Mineral Collecting Conditions: A rock and mineral collecting use permit is being developed. The public will be notified when these permits become available. Surface disturbing rock and mineral collecting activities will require a use permit. Hobby mineral collecting without a use permit is allowed as long as there is no surface disturbance. i.e. picking up a rock.  Surface disturbance is defined as digging, excavating, prying, destroying, or similar activity that results in the removal, displacement, or destruction of rocks, minerals, soil, or vegetation. Surface disturbing rock and mineral collection activities must follow the Forest Plan standards and guidelines below. General Standards and Guidelines   Only small hand tools are permitted. The use of power, mechanized equipment, or explosives is prohibited.   Maximum excavation at any one site is limited to one cubic yard. Only one site may be disturbed at a time.    Excavated holes must not be dug deeper than three feet as measured from the bottom of the hole to a projected horizontal line drawn between the bases of trees or plants adjoining the hole. In areas where the entire site is already disturbed and the original ground level altered, an estimated projection will be made of the earth’s surface for the purposes of monitoring and enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the trailhead or I93 exit 23 park and ride. These park and rides are patrolled and a good way to save on gas. Request ridesharing in your RSVP and email each other to make arrangements.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344474732000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341442876000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Moat Mountain    casual paced  all welcome/photo/dogs</name><id>qwlzpcyqlbhb</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344169800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/71977542/</event_url></item>