<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello Everyone, This is Anthony Pasquale from AJP Enterprise I wanted to let you know that you are invited to attend our North Shore Business Support Network (NSBSN) meeting in Danvers, Mass, at the Ideal Business Center, 20 Locust Street, this will be held on the second Monday of every month 800am for one hour and a half (If this falls on a holiday we will do the first Monday of the month). This event is FREE, Don't miss out! We are all here to help each other. Here are some of the yearly issues that will be covered: ~gaining referrals from your current client base ~working your neighborhood market ~getting repeat business/faithful customers, easier than getting all new people? ~advertising that works ~marketing that works ~advertising and Marketing together ~technology De-mystified ~grundgy basics like health insurance or other benefits, for you or employees of a small business ~focusing yourself ~making a mission statement to define your business ~making a 1 year and a 5 year plan ~speakers on economy/taxes that effect small business ~expanding your business ~hiring ~time management ~the importance of personal health, sleep, diet on productivity ~learning basic accounting/P&amp;amp;L statements ~using the internet to advertise &amp;amp; promote your business ~making websites ~create business 'partners' who keep each other accountable for implementing your own business goals We are looking for Business owners, Entrepreneurs, Managers, CEO's that what to see new business and help new business grow. Anthony Pasquale AJP Enterprise Team 'Live with purpose and passion everyday' ! www.umachealth.com 20 Locust Street, Suite 100 Danvers MA 01923 (978) 836-6501 'It's remarkable, how much mediocrity we live with, surrounding ourselves with daily reminders that the average is acceptable. Our world suffers from terminal normality. Take a moment to access all the things around you that encourage you to remain 'average'. These are the things that keep you powerless, unable to go beyond a limit you have arbitrarily set for yourself.'&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will personally greet them. Come and meet some of North Shore's most creative business people. We are here to help each other in today's business needs. Be apart of this great network.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1365429838000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs,Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1824</urlname><id>1133728</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>The NorthShore Business Support Network meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NorthShore Business Support Network meetup Monthly Meetup</name><id>hhldnyrfbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363003200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1824/events/104927442/</event_url></item>