<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join for a repeat of a fun event we did 2 years ago! A walk in the wood to explore Dogtown, lunch on the Gloucester waterfront, and then apple picking as a second event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 11:00 in the Dogtown parking lot.  Please use the map link below. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need a ride?  Please ask for one in your rsvp saying what area you are in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogtown is an area in central Gloucester of about five square miles, or 3600 acres, stretching from the Riverdale section of the city, north of Route 128, into Rockport, and including the Goose Cove and the Babson Reservoirs.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, since Dogtown is a ghost town, visitors can touch the lives of those who once lived there by finding numbered boulders marking cellar holes as well other boulders emblazoned with inspirational messages. In this fashion, all residents of the Commons Settlement and Dogtown whose cellar holes are marked have become legendary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogtown is known for its woods and for its boulders and rock formations left behind when the last glaciers melted. The poetry of Dogtown is about both its rocks and natural beauty and the lives of its former residents. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The famous American artist and poet Marsden Hartley described Dogtown as a cross between Stonehenge and Easter Island. Gloucester?s Roger Babson, the ?creator? of modern Dogtown loved both its boulders and forsaken cellars. Today, a network of abandoned roads and trails enable walkers to discover Dogtown.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Dogtown&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To reach Dogtown?s outskirts by automobile, from Grant Circle on Route 128 (exit 11), take route 127 North. Within the first mile, take a right on either Dr. Osman Babson Rd. or Reynard Rd. and proceed up to Cherry St. Take a left and look for Dogtown Rd. on the right. Drive up the paved road to the parking area, and then walk to the end of the paved section of Dogtown Road, past the rifle club and the public works area. Follow the unpaved Dogtown Road to Dogtown Square, and the bear right for the Babson Boulder Trail which is on the right soon thereafter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogtown info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://myweb.northshore.edu/users/ccarlsen/poetry/gloucester/dogtownhistory.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://myweb.northsho...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;q=Dogtown+Rd,+Gloucester,+Essex,+Massachusetts+01930,+United+States&amp;amp;layer=&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;sll=42.248979,-70.875077&amp;amp;sspn=0.057435,0.1157&amp;amp;z=12&amp;amp;ll=42.617286,-70.693932&amp;amp;spn=0.114197,0.2314&amp;amp;om=1&amp;amp;msid=106907836438136583019.00000111f1db8360edab0&amp;amp;msa=0" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lobster-express.com/featured_luncheons.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.lobster-ex...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gloucester House Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;Seven Seas Wharf on Route 127&lt;br /&gt;Gloucester, MA 01930 USA&lt;br /&gt;Tel. 978-283-1812&lt;br /&gt;Tel. 888-283-1812&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253718378000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250910159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>return to Dogtown</name><id>11169939</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253458800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/11169939/</event_url></item>