<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2969 Lake Morey Road</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05045</zip><lat>43.936089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hulbert Outdoor Center</name><city>Fairlee</city><id>10892312</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.142578</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A Winter Retreat for Adventurous Women at the Hulbert Outdoor Center. Fairlee, VT - Announcing a Winter Retreat for Adventurous Women! Vermont Outdoors Woman has begun registration for its Annual Winter Doe Camp at the Hulbert Outdoor Center, March 1-3, 2013. Participants can camp out or stay in heated cabins at night and play in the snow all day. Spend the weekend learning winter outdoors skills while staying near the shores of Lake Morey! Classes such as dog sledding, fire making, traditional winter camping, cross country skiing, orienteering, spring turkey hunting, ice fishing and many more will be offered. Don't miss the opportunity to receive affordable outdoor education in a stress-free, supportive environment. The minimum age is 15 and minors must be accompanied by an adult. Cost for the all inclusive weekend program is $290. Gift certificates and day fee's are also available. Visit the website for more information: www.alohafoundation.org/hulbert-outdoor-center/adult-programs/vermont-winter-doe-camp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.voga.org/winter_doe_camp_classes.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.voga.org/winter_doe_camp_classes.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also one scheduled for June 21-23, but they do not have the place listed yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've heard this is a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362187028000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356876946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Doe Camp</name><id>97055282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362175200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/97055282/</event_url></item>