<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Walk-In Registration</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Turning the Key:  Apartment House Riches with Dave Lindahl&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having been involved in more than 550 deals over the last decade and currently owning more than 3,200 units, Dave Lindahl has fine-tuned his techniques for investing in apartments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefit from his experience; save yourself the time and trouble, not to mention expense, of learning for yourself the hard way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave will be discussing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     *How to profit from apartments - without the hassles of dealing with tenants&lt;br /&gt;     *Ways to invest in apartments without a down payment - even if your credit is less than spectacular&lt;br /&gt;     *How investing in apartments is a faster, safer path to wealth &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are experienced in investing in multi-family housing, you'll also learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     *How to defer all the tax on your profits from the sale of a property&lt;br /&gt;     *9 creative ways to increase your profits&lt;br /&gt;     *Tips for using contractors - where to find them, how to train them, how much to pay them, and key points that should always be in your agreements &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave will also be sharing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     *How to determine which of the 4 stages a market is in - anywhere, anytime&lt;br /&gt;     *3 keys to successfully owning apartment houses&lt;br /&gt;     *3 keys to successful renovations &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for an evening of education and networking, and let Dave Lindahl share his wealth of experience with you. His systems and strategies will help you find the confidence to take what you learn and use it to get out there and earn more money, faster and easier than you ever thought possible! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foreclosuresmass.com/education/view/readmore/eid/6/" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-Register for Turning the Key&lt;/a&gt; and save $5.00!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 3372062</member_name><member_id>3372062</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186268644000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183680269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turning the Key:  Apartment House Riches</name><id>5980365</id><headcount>253</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186095600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/5980365/</event_url></item>