<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Four Thousand Footer Club 2012 Annual Meeting aka Awards Dinner Saturday, April 14, 2012 Cooperative Middle School, 100 Academic Way Stratham, NH 03885 (near Exeter) Join fellow finishers, past finishers, future finishers, friends and family for this year's event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schedule: 4:15pm Doors open to the public 4:30pm - 5:30pm Social Hour with exhibits by trail maintenance organizations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:30pm - 6:30pm Pizza Dinner (vegetarian pizzas will be available) in the cafeteria, with salad, coffee and milk, and chocolate chip cookies for dessert&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:15pm Auditorium opens 6:15pm - 6:30pm Outdoor Presentation of canine awards (see note on next item) 6:30pm - 8:00pm Awards Ceremony in the auditorium Welcome and introductions Announcement of donations Brief talk on trail maintenance Special media presentation Presentation of awards (to facilitate presentations, please check in at the door if you are receiving an award, as we mark the award envelopes of folks in attendance and do not announce those that are not marked!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What next? More peakbagging lists. 8:00pm - 9:00pm Further opportunity for socializing The dinner and all other functions are open to award recipients (past and present), family members and friends, and all other interested parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of the dinner is $13 for adults and $7 for children under 13.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who do not wish to join us for dinner are welcome to attend the Awards Presentation and stay to chat afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A donation of $2 per person is requested to help defray the auditorium rental cost; this can be paid at the door and does not require pre-registration The Dinner Reservation Form is available online but must be sent by regular mail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four Thousand Footer Club FAQ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General Information 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#info1"&gt;Where can I get official information about the Four Thousand Footer Club?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#info2"&gt;I mailed an application or request for information a long time ago, why haven't I heard back from anybody?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Mountains and Lists 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#list1"&gt;Where can I find the lists?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#list2"&gt;Do all of the 4000-footers have trails to them?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#list3"&gt;Why are some 4000-foot peaks not on the lists?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#list4"&gt;What are the recent changes to the lists?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#owlshead"&gt;Is there a new summit on Owl's Head?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/redington.htm"&gt;How do I get to Mt. Redington (Maine)?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#appw"&gt;Where do I get a winter application?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#info100"&gt;Where can I find information on the trailless peaks on the Hundred Highest list?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Rules 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#rules1"&gt;What are the rules for climbing the peaks?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#winter"&gt;What determines a winter ascent?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#rules2"&gt;Can I use a mountain bike while bagging a peak?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applications and Awards 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#app1"&gt;How do I apply for a membership?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#app2"&gt;How do I get an application?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#fee"&gt;How much is the application fee?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#whichaddy"&gt;Where should I send the completed application?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#app3"&gt;How can I check the status of my application?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#app4"&gt;Can my dog be admitted to the club?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#awards1"&gt;When is the Awards Dinner?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#awards2"&gt;How do I sign up for the Awards Dinner?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#numbers"&gt;Does the Four Thousand Footer Committee assign numbers to its members (like the ADK46ers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#numbers"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#multi"&gt;How does one apply for a second patch (e.g. for a second completion of the list)?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Questions 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/tshirt.htm"&gt;Where can I get a 4000-Footer T-shirt?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#patches"&gt;How can I get a replacement patch or extra patches?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#finish"&gt;How many people have finished the lists?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Four Thousand Footer Club was formed in 1957 to introduce hikers to some of the less well-known sections of the White Mountains of New Hampshire. At that time, such peaks as Hancock, Owl's Head and West Bond were trailless and practically never climbed. The problem of overuse was unknown, except in the Presidentials and Franconias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today the Club is composed of actve hikers whose travels in the mountains have made us familiar with many different areas of the White Mountain backcountry, and with the problems that threaten to degrade the mountain experience that we have all been privileged to enjoy. We hope that this experience will encourage our members to work for the preservation and wise use of wild country, so that it may be enjoyed and passed on to future generations undiminished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, we recognize three lists of peaks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/wm4.htm"&gt;White Mountain Four Thousand Footers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/ne4.htm"&gt;New England Four Thousand Footers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/ne100.htm"&gt;New England Hundred Highest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Separate awards are given to those who have climbed all of the peaks on a list in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/faq.htm#winter"&gt;winter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also have information about the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.amc4000footer.org/ne111.htm"&gt;Northeast 111 Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions to the Cooperative Middle School: From points North or South: From I-95, take Exit 2 to NH-101 West (toll on ramp). West on NH-101 for 1.2 mi. to Exit 12 (NH-111). Turn left (west) on NH-111 Bear right at junction with NH-27 West on NH-111/NH-27 for 0.7 mi. to Guinea Rd. Right on Guinea Rd. for 0.4 mi. Right onto Academic Way (school driveway) From points West: Take NH-101 East to Exit 12 (NH-111). Turn right (west) on NH-111 Bear right at junction with NH-27 West on NH-111/NH-27 for 0.7 mi. to Guinea Rd. Right on Guinea Rd. for 0.4 mi. Right onto Academic Way (school driveway) For the GPS-addicted, the parking lot is at 42&amp;deg;58&amp;rsquo;55&amp;rdquo; x 70&amp;deg;54&amp;rsquo;05&amp;rdquo;. Please note: This is a school, so no alcoholic beverages may be consumed on the grounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>6:15 PM Meet at Dog Awards or in the lobby if its raining.  alternate: restaurant chosen before ceremony</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334490650000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328574260000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Four Thousand Footer Club  2012 Annual Award Night</name><id>51316432</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334434500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/51316432/</event_url></item>