<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please ignore the &amp;quot;Nowhereplace&amp;quot; location above and use the directions below.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Founded in 1881, Lynn Woods Reservation, a 2,200-acre municipal forest park located in Lynn, Massachusetts, is the second largest municipal park in the United States.&lt;br /&gt;This park has come a long way from the neglect of the 1970s and 1980s. Most importantly for new visitors, the park map and the park have grid-coordinated trail intersection markings, making the park a pleasure to explore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3 large ponds help shape the park and buffer it from the outside world. The Undercliff Path, with its unexpectedly lush vegetation, is worth a trip by itself. Bring a flashlight for the nearby &amp;quot;cave&amp;quot;. Open part time, it was blasted out of solid rock over many years in the 1800's, in search of pirates' treasure. The view from the stone lookout tower, currently shut for repairs, is exceptional. The area north of Walden Pond (not the pond in Concord!) is less used and a bit wild. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in parking lot by the eastern entrance at 10:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Eastern Entrance:&lt;br /&gt;From the 128, exit 44B, take Lynnfield Street (Route 129) to Great Woods Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a map of the park at the link below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ci.lynn.ma.us/Public_Documents/LynnMA_Resources/woods" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ci.lynn.ma...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Need a ride?  Please ask for a ride from another participant in your rsvp, indicating what area you are in.  If you still need a ride, send me an email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch place to be determined.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207579294000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206319711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lynn Woods walk</name><id>7589047</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207405800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7589047/</event_url></item>