<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will walk through the historic part of Chestnut Hill, admiring all the fine homes and expensive cars!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will get a taste of nature by walking through Hammond Pond Reservation. &lt;br /&gt;Park in the parking lot of &amp;quot;The Mall at Chestnut Hill&amp;quot;.  Meet inside the mall in front Cafe Vanille.  &lt;br /&gt;Need a ride? Please ask for a ride from another participant in your rsvp, indicating what area you are in. If you don't find a ride that way, send me an email and I will pick you up at the Chestnut Hill T station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hammond Pond, a wooded reservation with a large, scenic pond, is located in the Chestnut Hill section of Newton adjacent to the city's Webster Conservation Area. It is a natural forest with wooded trails and large geological formations. Nearby Lost Pond has a quaking bog and system of natural trails. Deer Park!! - Mrs. Webster brought a couple of dozen deer into the area many years ago. Today, a small herd occupies an enclosed area of six acres.  Rich and famous...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newtonconservators.org/16webster.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newtoncons...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;afterward you can choose from either the brunch or lunch menus at Papa Razzi's, I have a reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bbrginc.com/paparazzi/papaboslunch.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bbrginc.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Chestnut Hill Mall, 199 Boylston Street, Chestnut Hill, MA (617) 527-6600&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175610801000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174250527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lifestyles of the rich &amp; famous walk</name><id>5581778</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175437800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5581778/</event_url></item>