<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Walkers Brook Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.518658</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>781-944-9090</phone><name>Comcast IMAX Theatre at Jordan's Furniture - Reading</name><city>Reading</city><id>437919</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Your friendly neighborhood organizer here with an update: the movie starts at 7:10. I will be in the lobby by 6:40, and I'm thinking I'll just get in line. The line is in the lobby; I should be easy to spot with my red meetup hat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I didn't realize this before but I am Legend is based on the same novella as the great Charlton Heston picture Omega Man. And there's another movie version, Last Man on Earth starring Vincent Price. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I haven't heard from anyone about rides - if you need one speak up. And I see another attendee has offered rides. So fire up that email if you don't have wheels! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And here is review by Roeper and that guy from the Chicago Tribune: &lt;a href="http://bventertainment.go.com/tv/buenavista/ebertandroeper/index2.html?sec=1&amp;amp;subsec=5561" target="_blank"&gt;http://bventertainmen...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And now back to our original description...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I love IMAX, and now the Boston Movie Group is offering a choice of venue for the new Will Smith film &amp;quot;I am Legend&amp;quot;: the AMC Boston Common opening night Dec. 14 (&lt;a href="http://movies.meetup.com/280/calendar/6517479/)"&gt;http://movies.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;, or, the Jordan's IMAX in Reading on Dec. 21. This is the IMAX meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can give people a ride up from the Sullivan Square T stop, but since I'm the organizer I really need to get to Jordan's on time so, I may not be able to wait for you if you're late. Generally I want to leave Sullivan 45 minutes before the meeting, which is 1 hr and 15 minutes before showtime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can take 3 people, it's first come first serve, just message me directly by clicking on the little email icon next to my picture. If other folks want to offer rides that would be great. Just put in your comment that you can offer a ride, how many, where and when you'll pick up. And anyone who's looking for a ride from another location that Sullivan Square should post that in their comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's always a good idea to buy your tickets ahead of time: &lt;a href="http://www.jordansimax.com/"&gt;http://www.jordansima...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official movie website: &lt;a href="http://iamlegend.warnerbros.com/"&gt;http://iamlegend.warn...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Running time: ~2hrs | PG-13 Animal and zombie violence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cast: Will Smith, Alice Braga, Salli Richardson-Whitfield&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director: Francis Lawrence&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Genre: Sci-Fi Disaster Film, Monster Film, Science Fiction, Sci-Fi Horror&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert Neville (Will Smith) is a brilliant scientist, but even he could not contain the terrible virus that was unstoppable, incurable and manmade. Somehow immune, Neville is now the last human survivor in what is left of New York City, and maybe the world. But he is not alone. He is surrounded by ''the Infected''?victims of the plague who have mutated into carnivorous beings who can only exist in the dark and who will devour or infect anyone or anything in their path. For three years, Neville has spent his days scavenging for food and sending out radio messages to find any other survivors. All the while, the Infected lurk in the shadows, watching Neville?s every move, waiting for him to make a fatal mistake. Perhaps mankind?s last, best hope, Neville is driven by only one remaining mission: to find a way to reverse the effects of the virus using his own immune blood. But his blood is also what The Infected hunt, and Neville knows he is outnumbered and quickly running out of time.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my red meetup hat.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198592814000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>check this link out:
http://www.darkhorizons.com/news07/071204h.php
^apparently, the first 6minute of the Batman sequel: The Dark Knight will accompany these screenings. ANOTHER REASON TO GO!-JF</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196766557000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I AM LEGEND IMAX+ first 6min. of Batman The Dark Knight!</name><id>6852993</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198281600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6852993/</event_url></item>