<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Washington St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822075</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>For tickets visit MERI site</phone><name>Trinity Repertory Company</name><city>Providence</city><id>825670</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.416074</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's our first Meetup of the season, and we are kicking off with &lt;a href="http://www.trinityrep.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Trinity Rep's&lt;/a&gt; Cabaret, a vibrant musical that takes place in a nightclub in pre-war Germany. If you've seen the Liza Minnelli version on TV, forget everything you saw. This musical has been revamped -- it's a little racy, a lot of fun and the music is phenomenal. Here's a better &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5RF-AFJ5VFs" target="_blank"&gt;clip &lt;/a&gt;with Alan Cumming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We saw this last year at Brown University, and it is worth seeing again, or for the first time. For those of you who couldn't get tickets through Brown, here's another chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $20 + $5 surcharge by the theatre = $25/ticket. For this one, I will purchase a group of tickets so we can sit together in small groups or in one big group. &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;You need to prepay online using Amazon payments&lt;/span&gt;. There are a few seats left, so I'll take whatever seats I can get. If they run out of seats, I will issue refunds. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;The deadline to pay for tickets is Thursday, Sept. 3 at 5 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're having a Meet &amp;amp; Greet for all members -- new and current -- beforehand at &lt;a href="http://www.trinitybrewhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Trinity Brewhouse&lt;/a&gt; around the corner, starting at 5 p.m. You pay for your own dinner, drinks, apps. You're welcome to come to both if you'd like, or just the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will &lt;b&gt;meet in the lobby of Trinity Rep at 7 p.m.&lt;/b&gt; for the show, so please be on time. I will be holding a small (think sheet of paper) red &amp;amp; white Meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to our first show of the season, and hope to see a lot of new and current members!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me holding small Meetup sign in the lobby of Trinity Rep</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254612859000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251647900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cabaret -- Trinity Rep</name><id>11237925</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252796400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/11237925/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/e/3/global_6574579.jpeg</photo_url></item>