<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>439 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.346640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 338-8884</phone><name>Masa </name><city>Boston</city><id>668968</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069084</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come and join me in The South End at Masa for Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome to Masa, where the Southwest meets the South End. For five years we've been spicing up the palates of Boston's most sophisticated diners and serving up libations to the hip bar crowds from the South End, Back Bay, and Theater District. Our menu pairs the flavors and cooking styles of a Southwestern kitchen with fresh New England ingredients. Combine this with our carefully selected wine list or our original award-winning cocktails and Margaritas to put the finishing touches on a memorable evening that feels like a short trip to Santa Fe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Chef:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A consummate professional with award winning credentials, Executive Chef Philip Aviles comes to Masa with an incomparable resume. Before Masa he came from The Waldorf Astoria in New York City. He also was Executive  Chef at Stingy Lulu's, the popular East Village eatery. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at Masa brunch! Afterward, I'll be heading over to Nick's to watch some baseball (it's in the calendar)! :]&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Need to RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255734572000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254933964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch in The South End at Masa </name><id>11572223</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255276800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11572223/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/c/global_6726124.jpeg</photo_url></item>