<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>671 Adams Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02122</zip><lat>42.286967</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-297-5611</phone><name>Heiress Boutique</name><city>Boston</city><id>1425768</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054545</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://sphotos.ak.fbcdn.net/hphotos-ak-snc4/hs955.snc4/74837_118498688212744_100001578395847_140575_2638914_n.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring out the edge!&lt;br /&gt;Boston based designer Blond Di, has thrust into the fashion sphere with one of a kind, custom designed clothing. Each piece hand-designed every stud, pearl, spike, &amp;amp; zipper handpicked to reference her dazzling unique style. Blond Di’s unconventional designs pair well with everyday chic items from the trendy fashionista’s closet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heiress Boutique is a chic, glamour-inspired clothing boutique in the heart of Do...rchester. Opening their door early this fall Heiress Boutique showcases a combination of timeless pieces and new emerging fashion forward garments. Their carefully selected collections include interesting accessory, playful tops, sophisticated pants, sexy cocktail dresses, and stunning outerwear for the trendy fashionista’s closet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blond Di is scheduled to unveil the Bondij Royalty collection to the public November 19, 2010 at Heiress Boutique 671 Adams Street Dorchester Ma 02124.&lt;/b&gt; Blond Di’s has created the Bondij Royalty collection exclusive for Heiress Boutique. The collection features vintage couture and edgy punk rock designs evocative of the rebel in every fashionista.&lt;br /&gt;Being a slave to fashion never looked so good Bondij by Blond Di keeps you chained to the pulse of fashion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Heiress client is a smart Fashionista that revel in finding beautiful, unique and original designer items at fabulous prices. Impressively put together, it is hard to believe how little she spent.&lt;br /&gt;The Bondij Royalty collection will be available for retail sale exclusively at Heiress Boutique. Come meet Blond Di and receive a complimentary styling from Heiress Boutique. The world of high fashion right next door. &lt;br /&gt;See More&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aishah Abdul</member_name><member_id>9619622</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290219263000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289408607000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>(Mixer) The Unveiling of The Bondij Royalty Collection at Heiress Boutique!</name><id>15404546</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290214800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/15404546/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/4/global_10197972.jpeg</photo_url></item>