<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Water St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.326004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Common Man</name><city>Concord</city><id>671401</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.645100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sorry for the short notice, but I'd like to call a planning and strategy meeting for this Thursday evening. This will be a time to discuss as a group how we want to work. Do we want to host more events? Street actions? Literature drops? Infiltrating other groups with common interests? Raise issues online with internet forums? You have a say!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet at the Common Man, in Concord, at around 6:30pm. If you can't make it right on time, feel free to join us later as we'll probably be there for a while. Bring some ideas about how you would like to see this group move forward. Let's plan to meet in the bar upstairs; we can move to a table downstairs if we need to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make this meeting, fret not--there will be others in the near future. In the meantime, send me any suggestions or feel free to use the messages feature on this site to communicate with the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the calendar on this site, too as there are some events coming up which may interest you. If you haven't looked at the members list, in a while check that out as we have had some recent joiners. Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Common Man Concord&lt;br /&gt;www.thecman.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;25 Water St&lt;br /&gt;Concord, NH 03301&lt;br /&gt;(603) 228-3463&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3581956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189290874000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1188953903000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Planning and Strategy Meeting</name><id>6298648</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189117800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/6298648/</event_url></item>