<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I already know its Easter Weekend and its far and its early... blah blah blah.......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this single day event, I am going to hike a 7.5 to 8 mile portion of the Appalachian Trail in Salisbury.  The start point will be Undermountain Trail on Rt. 41 in Salisbury.  We will hike UP to meet the trail and then take a right to go to the top of Bear Mt. at 2316 ft.  After enjoying the views, we will turn around and head south.  Our finish point will be on Rt. 44 near Lower Coble Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a mostly downhill adventure (well we are heading south right ?).  The next point of interest will be Lion's Head before finishing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like to meet at the finish point on Rt. 44 at 9:30 a.m.  From there we will take a second car up the start point at the Undermountain Trail on Rt. 41.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its spring so count on wearing water proof hiking boots.  Dress in layers and bring at least a liter of water and snacks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do not care to hike with dogs so I prefer they are not brought.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am coming from the Hartford area so we can car pool, but there needs to be two cars out there that day.  Email me for car pool interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to end spot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Salisbury&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=91-106+Canaan+Rd.&amp;amp;zipcode=06068" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to hike start&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Salisbury&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=10+Foot+Hills+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06068-1108&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=42.029778&amp;amp;longitude=-73.428983&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239744175000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238519240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AT Hike Bear MT Salisbury CT to Lower Coble Rd/Rt. 44 </name><id>10079601</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239456600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10079601/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/e/global_2859934.jpeg</photo_url></item>