<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Centers of Light will be showing Budrus for August&amp;rsquo;s Conscious Cinema. This documentary follows a Palestinian man and his daughter as they organize non-violent resistance to the building of a barrier wall that would destroy their village. The power of their organizing is that it brought together Fatah and Hamas, Israelis and Palestinians, men and women. This movement has gained international attention and is still growing. It is a beautiful testament to the influence that non-violent action can have on the consciousness of all beings.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; This month, the organization we will raise funds for is the Palestine Children&amp;rsquo;s Relief Fund, a non-political, non-profit organization dedicated to fighting the medical and humanitarian crisis facing children in the Middle East. To learn more visit &lt;a href="http://www.pcrf.net/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.pcrf.net/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; The Centers of Light are mystical Christian centers and communities dedicated to consciousness, spiritual growth, and empowerment.&amp;nbsp; Each of the 14 Centers of Light across the country offer daily meditation, sacraments, seminars, and spiritual classes. Christian Mysticism is the inner, esoteric path of Christianity, comparable to Kabbalah in Judaism, Zen Buddhism, or Sufism in Islam. All Centers of Light work to bring peace to the planet by helping people gain real, deep connection with God and become dynamic forces for positive change.&amp;nbsp; For more information, please visit www.CentersOfLight.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314491062000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313193495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie - Budrus</name><id>29298151</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314486000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/29298151/</event_url></item>