<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;This is another film from Turkish director, Reha Erdem. Last weekend a few of us saw his most recent work, Times and Winds. Upon surfing the net to find out more information about this director I noticed that an earlier film of his is screening this weekend at the MFA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set in contemporary Istanbul, this intriguing comedy-drama centers around Ali, a taxi driver who has lost his memory in an accident and reverted to a childlike innocence. His dysfunctional family and friends are either vexed by his amnesia or suspicious about its authenticity, but it?s soon clear that everyone in this multi-character farce has something to learn about being human.  MFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film begins with Ali?s accident. Ali has lost his memory. With Ali?s confusion, all the characters of the story find themselves in a state of chaos. This chaos being the chaos of daily life, of life itself. The mystery of a precious ring passing  from one to another with each claiming to be the owner, the distant story of a robbery, and a mock police investigation add even more flavor to the story. But there is a parallel story within ?Mommy, I?m scared?. This is the story of the human body. This story, which in real life exists in every human body regardless of revolutions, incidents, or intrigues, comes to the forefront in the film. It outshines intrigue. It shadows the eyes and ears of the human bodies observing the incidents in the film. What?s human anyway. A memory woven by fears, weaknesses and desires and a fragile body made up of flesh, blood and bones.   A Week of Turkish Cinema&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ali?s father and the neighbors try to help him&lt;br /&gt;remember ? Neriman, the tailor who lives downstairs with her son Keten; Ipek, the young pregnant woman whose&lt;br /&gt;boyfriend wants his mother?s ring back; Selvi, the doorman?s wife, who spends her time on the balcony among the&lt;br /&gt;seagulls swooping and sailing above the stunning harbor of Istanbul.&lt;br /&gt;Meanwhile, Neriman might be allergic to her dog, and the butcher says the only answer is to send the dog away.&lt;br /&gt;Selvi?s little boy, Cetin, has not been circumcised, and the parade is leaving soon. Aytekin has avoided military service&lt;br /&gt;as long as he dares, but maybe his trembling hand will be enough to spare him. Umit, the pretty gymnast who shares&lt;br /&gt;the apartment with Ipek, is preparing for admission to the Academy, which will allow her to stay in Istanbul. Keten&lt;br /&gt;has a crush on Ipek, and wants to help her raise her baby, but first he will need the courage to stand up to his mother.&lt;br /&gt;Against the backdrop of the beautiful city of Istanbul, with their lives intertwined by the mystery of Ipek?s ring, these&lt;br /&gt;characters learn how much more it is to be human than bones and muscles and beating hearts.  The Global Film Initiative&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Festivals and Awards:&lt;br /&gt;Best Actor (Ali Dusenkalkar), 10th Nurnberg Turkey-Germany Film Festival (9-20 March 2005) &lt;br /&gt;Best Director, Best Screenplay (Reha Erdem, Nilufer Gungormus), Best Actor (Ali Dusenkalkar), Best Supporting Actress (Isil Yucesoy), Best Supporting Actor (Koksal Engur), Best New Actor (Ozan Colak), 16th International Ankara Film Festival (3-13 March 2005) &lt;br /&gt;23rd International Istanbul Film Festival (National Competition) &lt;br /&gt;FIPRESCI (International Critics' Association) Award &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then again, it might not be as good as Times and Winds. There's very little information about Turkish films on the web.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom,  Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film's conclusion and then its off to a local eatery to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the director: REHA ERDEM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to study cinema he quit his History study at Bo&amp;#287;aziçi University and went to Paris in 1983. He completed the Department of Cinema at Paris University. He did his graduate study in the Department of Modern Art. He made his first feature film ?Oh, Moon? in 1989. The film won an award at Nantes Film Festival. It was shown in several festivals abroad. It was chosen the Best Film of the Year by the Writers Association. The second film he made ?Run For Money? (1999) represented Turkey at the Oscar Awards in the category of Best Foreign &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197397977000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196824932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What's a Human Anyway?- A 2nd Film from Turkey</name><id>6858366</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197225000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6858366/</event_url></item>