<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/1/4/event_199824852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;There are times when you feel you are driven by a force you can’t resist: suddenly you can’t be a good daughter, an understanding wife, caring mother or reliable co-worker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are times when you ask yourself why you can’t be like your sister, or your best girl-friend, or your mother, and times when you can’t stand them at all and are glad for who you are.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We can fall in-love, get into fights or become withdrawn and distant with the same people we’ve known for years. Who is standing behind the scenes and making us change our attitude toward seemingly the same situations?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Men always find women impossible to understand. Scientists blame hormones for our inner conflicts and ups and downs, and prescribe medicine to get us back in control of our moods and our lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why are we, women, so complicated?  Can we explain things to ourselves at least?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wouldn’t it be wonderful to have some clarity on why we can get along easily with some other women and openly hate some other “types” of them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this workshop we will discuss “archetypes” of women’s personalities. In the ancient world, main archetypes of women’s behavior were described through stories and myths of Gods and Goddesses. Some of the Goddesses support men, and some motherhood. Some of them protect you from harm, some drives you into chaos.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These Goddesses all live in us. In order to understand yourself, you should meet them, get to know them better and learn how to handle their power within you to use it for your own growth instead of destruction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this workshop you will&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;explore your artistic side through drawing an image of your beautiful Goddess and to awaken and embrace your feminine spirit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;learn about the major seven Goddesses and their positive and negative traits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;go through a simple test to find out which Goddess takes rule over you now and how to create inner peace with other conflicting voices inside&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;nourish &amp;amp; celebrate your beautiful feminine spirit&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;through a sequence of eight movements that awakens the Goddess within and claims her power back&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Workshop details:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When: &lt;strong&gt;Friday, March 1st&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Time: &lt;strong&gt;6pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to bring: any snack to share with other during a tea break&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Price: &lt;strong&gt;$15&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>9452646</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362244425000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360426807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting to Know My Goddess (Goddesses) Within</name><id>103814342</id><headcount>4</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362178800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/103814342/</event_url></item>