<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>403 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363571</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-576-3400</phone><name>Cafe Luna</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669119</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ciao!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who want to enjoy a walk outdoors with good friends then this is a meetup for you. We will start our walk at Central Square and head towards Harvard Square. We can rest and buy drinks or ice cream. Then head back to Central Square. Those who want to go their own way to a restaurant or cafe can do so at any time. The size of this meetup is without limit. There are no fees and no commitments. What a great opportunity to meet many members of our Euro meetup! There is no time limitation to this meetup ... it can last all day if you want!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer is a great time to enjoy the scenery along Massachusetts Ave; and, Harvard Square is animated and fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it rains that day, 06/08th,  then the event will be rescheduled for the next Sunday 06/15th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who do not want to walk, they can sit down at the La Luna Cafe or any nearby place and wait for the walking group to return. Although going on the walk would be more fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us!! I would really like to see a great turnout! Many members are waiting to meet you!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is easy to find in Central square and inexpensive. The Green Street Garage is located at the corner of Green St. and Pearl St. Enter the garage by going down Pearl St. for one block (Pearl St. is parallel to Prospect St., one block east of Prospect St.) and then taking a right onto Green St. The entrance to the garage is on your left. This garage is only $1 per hour to a maximum of $5. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 3 municipal lots along Bishop Allen Drive that are free after 6:00 pm on weekdays and they are free on Sundays. There is also a very large private lot on Prospect Street that is free and open to the public after 5:00 pm. There is an open-air city parking lot across Mass Ave behind Blockbuster Video (Bishop Allen Drive and Norfolk Street), and another open-air lot across Mass Ave behind Quest Diagnostics/McDonalds (Bishop Allen Drive and Douglass Street). In both of these lots, the meters go off at 6pm so parking is FREE in the weekday evenings. Public parking is free at the meters and Public parking lots all day Sundays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS - If we get a good turnout we can schedule more of these events with greater frequency during the summer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting in front of La Luna Cafe. My cell number is 508-498-1651 .  The cafe is one block after Blockbuster, half a block after McDonalds, around the corner across the fire station. Massachusetts Ave corner before Main St.  Free parking!!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213125124000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Summer is here so let's enjoy the great outdoors. This is an easier format to mix with other members and to meet more members than the typical restaurant setting.  Also this is a healthy and inexpensive meetup alternative.</why><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211829680000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Walk - Central Square to Harvard Square</name><id>8014044</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212951600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/8014044/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>