<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The philosophical argument between proponents of free will and determinism is, in my view, an argument between two false positions IF each side of the argument is formulated as an absolute position that excludes the other.&amp;nbsp; My reasoning is simple.&amp;nbsp; Is gold adulterated with copper pure gold?&amp;nbsp; Obviously not.&amp;nbsp; If determinism is adulterated with even a particle of freedom then determinism is false, because one "free" action disrupts the entire deterministic process. Likewise, if free will is adulterated with even a particle of causal determination then free will is false because we are not absolutely free if the ground of "free" decision is shaped by a determined or even partially determined chain of events.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To be or not to be, that is the question." Hamlet's soliloquy is as much about freedom as it is about being. What is human existence without at least the sense of freedom? And is not the acceptance that death "comes when it will come" (&lt;em&gt;Julius Caesar&lt;/em&gt;)&amp;nbsp; also an acceptance that all freedom of being--or the applicability of&amp;nbsp; its conception--expires? This discussion involves the perennial philosophical debate of freedom v. determinism, but it also concerns what it means to be be free, especially if freedom is&amp;nbsp; not an absolute but, rather, a concept with many qualifications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adulterated freedom is not pure freedom, and adulterated determinism is not pure determinism.&amp;nbsp; "Freedom's just another word for nothin' left to lose...La-da-da da-la-da la-da, Bobby McGee, yeah." -- &lt;span&gt;by Kris Kristofferson and Fred Foster for&lt;/span&gt; Janis Joplin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people). &amp;nbsp; After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.&amp;nbsp; It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!&amp;nbsp; While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; expenditure of $12 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill for food and/or drink plus tax and tip is under $12 the balance will be added to the gratuity).&amp;nbsp; Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks. To simplify, many folks just round off to $20 and add and adjust if they order drinks. &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.&amp;nbsp; However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the little mall area closes for the night. &lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333289683000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330907644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Relative Freedom</name><id>54976872</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333148400000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/54976872/</event_url></item>