<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 Daniel Webster Hwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.792336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>891-1717</phone><name>Takumi</name><city>Nashua</city><id>279621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470276</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Note:  This event requires a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason.  Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The April Restaurant of the month is the Takumi Sushi &amp;amp; Habachi Japanese Restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Takumi, modeled after the award-winning Oga's Japanese Cuisine restaurant in Natick, Mass., serves up the freshest sushi and “real” Japanese food north of Boston, according to restaurant manager Motoi Nakanishi.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When he says “real” Japanese food, Nakanishi is referring to food they make themselves, and fish that comes fresh, not frozen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“We're not just going to buy it from somebody else, we're going to make it,” Nakanishi said. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon entering the 197 Daniel Webster Highway eatery, guests encounter a soothing, in-ground water fountain filled with swimming fish and surrounded by a fancy stone floor. Various Japanese decorations abound, and tall bamboos give an authentic Japanese feel while jazz music fills the air. Transparent, custom-made copper curtains hang from the ceilings, complementing the handsome cherry wood floor and pine countertops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I tried to make it a New York style restaurant,” said Nakanishi, pointing to the handmade glass and wood partitions. “The customers always come in here and say, ‘wow, this is different.'”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 183-seat Takumi has a bar area/lounge that seats 52, and the restaurant gives diners a choice of sitting at Teppan tables, the sushi bar or the dining room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teppanyaki is stir-fried food eaten off a large table-top grill. The word comes from the Japanese words for iron and stir-fry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trained Teppan masters cook steak, lobster, chicken or vegetables right in front of the guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Our menu is for everyone, whether you eat raw fish or don't eat raw fish,” said Executive Sushi Chef Michael Wang, holding up a whole eel imported from Japan. “We buy everything whole,” he said. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Takumi imports fish from Japan twice a week, and gets deliveries from Boston three times a week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.takumijapanese.com/Reviews/The%20Telegraph%20Online.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.takumijapa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.takumijapanese.com/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.takumijapa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271718278000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269995574000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Restaurant of the Month</name><id>jdcjnyngbwb</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271545200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/13042897/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/2/global_14036882.jpeg</photo_url></item>