<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover fees and goodies</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sorry-this meetup is auto generated. Since it's Easter we will meet on Saturday instead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So you don't get spammed any further-the meetup on this Saturday, March 28th will be at Peter's Park instead of Doggie Day-please take note as it will only change on the meetup site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join for our first Sunday outdoor meetup of the season! Just a reminder that we will have a Sunday meetup on the second weekend of the month, and a Saturday meetup on the fourth weekend of the month.  More fun for the dogs!  Please be aware that these rarely last 2 hours with the dogs so heated up!  If for some unknown reason it's below freezing or raining then we will move to Doggie Day on Tremont Street-I'll update accordingly the day before based on weather predictions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Terri &amp;amp; Simon &amp;amp; Louie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: Unless there is a snowstorm we are on! I'll email around 8AM if the weather we cancel.  Please use your discretion driving in foul weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a month meetup fee. This is a GROUP fee and if not paid, our Boston French Bulldog meetups, would not exist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the small fenced in area of the park</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240671335000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236524846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Bulldog April Meetup</name><id>9907978</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239458400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/9907978/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/1/global_381217.jpeg</photo_url></item>