<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>TBA</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.228695</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Colleen's Place</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>11642042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.522568</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Ladies!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I met many of you at the dating discussions meetup. Some of the stories I heard made me shake my head in awe and dismay. Others, made me laugh hysterically! That all being said, I need to document your stories for the play/musical I am writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been wanting to write this play for many years and 2013 is the year I am going to do it! It is a play about dating from the woman's perspective and it is all going to be based on true happenings!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want you to come prepared to share your most outrageous stories! They can be about anything! The more insane, the better! I'll be bringing a tape recorder and notebook with me to make sure I don't miss a thing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if you have no plans for Valentine's weekend and you want to hang out with a bunch of ladies to share food, drink and laughs, please join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet in Worcester, Shrewbury or Westborough. I need to see how many ladies are interested before I choose the location. If anyone knows of a restaurant that has a small room we can use, please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you on the 17th!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361146116000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359917697000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies!  Spend an afternoon eating, drinking and exchanging dating horrors!</name><id>102819972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361127600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/102819972/</event_url></item>