<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>(Norway, 2009) Written &amp;amp; Directed by Bent Hamer. Cast: Bard Owe, Espen Skjonberg, Ghita Norby. Celebrate Norwegian pride with Norway's upcoming entry for Best Foreign Film at the next Academy Awards! And if you're not Norwegian or even slightly Scandinavian, you'll still enjoy this whimsical-in-a-good-way movie that might best be described as &amp;quot;Ingmar Bergman's Wild Strawberries done as a comedy&amp;quot;! The film opens as the about to retire engineer Odd Horten (Bard Owe) takes his last train through the gorgeous snowy expanses of the North. What lies ahead is the big question. Does he dare to eat a peach, fly in a plane, survive a nighttime drive with a blindfolded driver, or even wear red high heels? A tender look at the possibilities waiting to be explored as we age, or as one character challenges Horten, &amp;quot;It is never too late for driving blind!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Three and a half stars a precise, deadpan drama of slapstick existentialism.&amp;quot; Ty Burr, Boston &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;90 min&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be sitting out front asking if you are in meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255730145000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250961173000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>O'Horten</name><id>11172755</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254266100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11172755/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/a/global_10318666.jpeg</photo_url></item>