<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wednesday, November 11, 2009 @ noon. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once again the Smedley Butler Brigade, Veteran’s For Peace, Chapter 9, is relegated to the end of Boston?s Veterans Day Parade simply be cause the parade organizers don’t care for our messages of peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We gladly march behind the street sweepers in a show of opposition to war or the glorification of war. We believe that the best way to honor veterans is to abolish all war and bring all veterans home, out of harms way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please show your support by joining us this Nov 11th . Our presence has made a difference. We will meet at 1200 at the corner of Charles and Beacon streets. This is the northwest corner of Boston Commons, just across the street from the Boston Public Garden. The City of Boston has issued us a permit to have speakers at Government Center (parade end) so please plan to join us for that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would also like to invite everyone to the Veterans For Peace fundraiser at Johnny Ds after the parade. Please come and bring your friends. The cover charge will go directly to Veterans For Peace. Good music and good friends. Please come and enjoy while supporting peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30-10:00PM&lt;br /&gt;Johnny Ds 17 Holland St. Davis Square&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to make earlier dinner reservations (recommended) please call 617-776-7450. The food is good! For more information, call 617-776-7450.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258132450000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257014556000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Veteran’s For Peace/ IVAW marching @ Bostons Veterans Day Parade</name><id>11756699</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257958800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/11756699/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/2/global_7665970.jpeg</photo_url></item>