<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348507</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-778-0089</phone><name>LIR</name><city>Boston</city><id>234803</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084251</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join me for Happy Hour at LIR.  It is an Irish Pub only very nice inside!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lir&lt;br /&gt;903 Boylston St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02115-3104&lt;br /&gt;Phone: (617) 778-0089&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scene&lt;br /&gt;Imagine a sports bar opening inside the neighborhood library. Lir's 21 televisions are nestled inside dense, largely decorative bookshelves, ensuring that the game is always on. An enormous spiral staircase leads to a similar bar upstairs, and of course, more TVs. A hidden &amp;quot;chill-out room&amp;quot; in the basement promises loungey digs with clubby music, popular for the younger late-night crowd. The largely Irish staff is polite and prompt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Draw&lt;br /&gt;The best feature is its location: a minor detour from Newbury Street and a stone's throw from the Prudential Mall. In other words, it's perfect for taking a break from shopping. Local suit-and-tie types enjoy hearty pub fare (Dublin sirloin served with homemade brown bread) for lunch and after work, when the happy-hour mingling game begins. Sixteen beers on tap counter a lengthy list of signature cocktails like the mint-chocolate-chip martini, a concoction of Kahlua, vodka and creme de menthe. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189375354000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187625955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Happy Hour- September Meetup</name><id>6212114</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189202400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/6212114/</event_url></item>