<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bare Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.866578</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MSSF @ Rocky Pond</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>1285063</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.694725</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;My dog, Buffett, and I will be exploring new parts of MSSF or enjoying more familiar trails on the only days when Massachusetts doesn't allow hunting. Hikes will generally be 2-3 hours but check the posting weekly for any changes in starting time, length, or meeting place.  Inclement weather cancels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggestions about areas or trails to hike are welcome as there are a lot of Sundays and I may run out of ideas.  Post a comment or e-mail your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear layers appropriate to the weather and bring water and snacks for yourself and your dog (s) if your bringing any along.  Most hiking will be on trails or dirt roads but bring a leash for road crossings or short distances near traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All ages are welcome but if you have concerns about new, young, or older hikers, feel free to contact me to check or request specific hike conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's always good to check the hike status before heading to the forest in case of last minute cancellations or changes.  If you find you cannot attend, please try to change your RSVP several hours prior to hike time so we do not wait for you.  Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laura Troll</member_name><member_id>11017991</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351454587000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350741262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Sundays during Hunting Season</name><id>dvmxqdyqnblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351443600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/87802912/</event_url></item>