<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Jamal Malik, an 18 year-old orphan from the slums of Mumbai, is just one question away from winning a staggering 20 million rupees on India’s “Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?” But when the show breaks for the night, police arrest him on suspicion of cheating; how could a street kid know so much? Desperate to prove his innocence, Jamal tells the story of his life in the slum where he and his brother grew up, of their adventures together on the road, of vicious encounters with local gangs, and of Latika, the girl he loved and lost. Each chapter of his story reveals the key to the answer to one of the game show’s questions. Intrigued by Jamal’s story, the jaded Police Inspector begins to wonder what a young man with no apparent desire for riches is really doing on this game show? When the new day dawns and Jamal returns to answer the final question, the Inspector and sixty million viewers are about to find out. &lt;br /&gt;Cast: Dev Patel, Freida Pinto, Madhur Mittal, Anil Kapoor, Irfan Khan &lt;br /&gt;Director: Danny Boyle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Who would believe that the best old-fashioned audience picture of the year, a Hollywood-style romantic melodrama that delivers major studio satisfactions in an ultra-modern way, was made on the streets of India with largely unknown stars by a British dire&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Kenneth Turan&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With dazzling, magical realism and vigorous storytelling, the film has an enchanting power, fusing a fairy tale quality with gritty realism.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;USA Today&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Claudia Puig&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;...a story of social mobility that is positively Dickensian in its attention to detail and the extremes of poverty and wealth within a culture.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Variety&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- Todd McCarthy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell phone number is 203-812-0705 in case anyone needs to reach me.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby.  The movie starts at 6:45.  Let's meet no later than 6:30.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231198439000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230211317000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slumdog Millionaire</name><id>9386735</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231025400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/9386735/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/4/b/global_6802939.jpeg</photo_url></item>