<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.981155</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Town Hall Gallery</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1625121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.947128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff"&gt;We're meeting in a new Location this month. This month's challenge is "spring"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffffff"&gt;Read on for more details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Location:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We've grown quite a bit in the last year. Now, while this is a fantastic and friendly group of photographers, we needn't put up with others sitting in our laps for want of space. So starting this month, we'll be meeting in the much larger and more artsy Town Hall Gallery building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Town Hall Gallery is the large beautiful brick building smack dab in the middle of downtown Exeter, across from the bandstand and the Town Hall offices (which is the small ugly brick building where you pay for your car registration).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park on the street or in the nearby&amp;nbsp;municipal&amp;nbsp;lot and walk on over. Walk around the left side of the Town Hall Gallery building (on the side facing the Citizens Bank drive-up windows), and enter the door on the left hand side. Take the elevator to the second floor. Make a left out of the elevator, and enter the room on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brown Bag Bingo Slideshow:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A good chunk of this month's meeting will be taken up by the Brown Bag Bingo slideshow - 100 photos of 20 objects. Whether you were part of BBB or not, you will no doubt enjoy this slideshow and learn something from it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Challenge: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;We have a challenge for this month's meeting - &lt;strong&gt;Spring&lt;/strong&gt;. Between now and the the meeting, take and bring 1-3 photographs which somehow speak to your interpretation of the subject - please feel free to take great liberty with your interpretation of the subject. We'll pass around the photos and see how creative, technical, fun, and skilled we can all be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't be shy, we have a very encouraging group of critics and we'll all learn something from the experience. Most of all, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;have fun shooting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring other photos if you'd like feedback or critique, and be prepared to [helpfully] critique others'.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything photography- or photographer-related is fair game.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk around the left side of the Town Hall Gallery and enter the door on the left. Take the elevator to the second floor. We'll be in a room off the same wall as the elevator.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305913449000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280350438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPA Monthly Meeting and Brown Bag Bingo Slideshow!</name><id>zkddpyphbzb</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305844200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/16611779/</event_url></item>