<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Curzon Mill Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.822050</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-7223</phone><name>Maudslay State Park</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>848934</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.926670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets do this beautiful state park again.  A former millionaire's estate, it is located along the Merrimack River in Newburyport, MA. The ground should be clear of snow and ice so we will, in all likelihood, be hiking.  I'd like to do a little longer hike this time, focusing on the outer perimeter trails, probably about three miles.  It is easy to moderate hiking.  We will meet at the main entrance on Curzon Street at 10:00am.  There is a $2.00 parking fee, the rest of the park is free.  Dogs are allowed in the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI - although these are fairly easy trails, I suggest wearing light hiking boots/shoes.  I've seen, in the past, people with street sneakers having a difficult time.  Bring water and a snack if you like.  I always carry a poncho in case of an unexpected shower.  It makes it a lot more enjoyable if you are prepared.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click this link to check out the trail map - &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/maudslay.gif" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click to view Maudslay State Park -          &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/maud.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From North and South: Take Rte. 95, exit 57 to Rte. 113 east. Follow 113 east for half a mile and turn left on Noble St. At stop sign turn left onto Ferry Rd., bear left at fork and follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From West: Take I-495 exit 55 to Rte. 110 east. Continue 1 mile to Merrill St., turn right at second light. Continue on Merrill St./Spofford St. for 1.5 miles. Turn right before stop sign onto Ferry Rd., follow signs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be next to my green Toyota 4Runner in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238252363000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236867492000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maudslay State Park</name><id>9939118</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237644000000</time><rsvp_limit>31</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/9939118/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/1/global_7643441.jpeg</photo_url></item>