<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>117 Ridge Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03049</zip><lat>42.722033</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 465-7787</phone><name>Beaver Brook Association</name><city>Hollis</city><id>986510</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.607524</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Welcome to the Second Annual Beaver Brook Winter Hike - Saturday December 5th -  Hollis,  NH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plunk and I have not been to Beaver Brook in quite a while and we remember it as a lovely area with numerous trails and beautiful scenery.  And the smells there are pretty good too  (this coming from a Beagle of course).    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In fact,  it was exactly a year ago that we had a meetup at Beaver Brook....so let's make this an annual event. &lt;br /&gt;We hope you will join us for what promises to be a lovely afternoon in a truly scenic area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hunting is not allowed on the property,  however it is still advisable to wear orange in case any hunters disregard the posted signs.   It never hurts to be on the cautious side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress in layers,  wear hat and gloves,  bring water for you and your dog (snacks couldn't hurt either) and don't forget your pooper bags.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should also bring a leash .....just in case.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/9/f/highres_11655775.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Beaver Brook Association,  at Maple Hill Farm&lt;br /&gt;When:   Saturday  December 5,  2009  at  High Noon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to the Beaver Brook Association if you would like to learn more about them.  You can also print out trail maps on their site:    &lt;a href="http://www2.beaverbrook.org/bbwarewe.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Beaver Brook Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Carpooling:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone wants to carpool,  we will meet at 11:15 am, in the Hannafords Parking Lot on Bicentennial Drive in Manchester (on the Hooksett/Manchester Town Line).     Go to the very front of the parking lot closest to Bicentennial Drive (furthest from the building).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Here are driving directions from the files section of our meetup site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beaver Brook&lt;br /&gt;117 Ridge Road&lt;br /&gt;Hollis, NH 03049&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 6 (off of Rte 3), then turn right onto Broad Street/Route 130. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drive approximately 6 miles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;[Once you get in to the &amp;quot;main town&amp;quot; of Hollis, but while you are still on Route 130,  you will pass Lull Farms on your left, then Brookdale Farm also on your left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the fork in the road just past Brookdale Farm, bear right and travel approx one block, &lt;br /&gt;passing the Harvest Market shopping center on your right,  to the set of lights. &lt;br /&gt;There's a bank building with a Dunkin Donuts on that corner, and a little café across the street with a chicken on the sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue with the directions from the Beaver Brook web site below.]&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travel to the set of lights in Hollis (there is only one set of lights in Hollis). &lt;br /&gt;Turn left at the lights; you will be on Route 122 South. &lt;br /&gt;Drive approximately 1 mile and turn right onto Ridge Road. &lt;br /&gt;Drive approximately 1 more mile. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maple Hill Farm will be on your right (117 Ridge Road). &lt;br /&gt;You will see a large gray farmhouse with a barn attached to it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Beaver Brook office is in this building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, including those caused by negligence and or other reasons. You also agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Plunk will be the cute beagle screaming......Over Here......Over Here.......Over Heeeeeere !!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judi-Judi-Judi</member_name><member_id>7477606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260291410000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257441701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beaver  Brook in December</name><id>11803536</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260032400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/11803536/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/global_6390313.jpeg</photo_url></item>