<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's meet for&amp;nbsp;a Monday Evening Walk&amp;nbsp;@ Pond Meadow Park (PMP) as we welcome Spring tomorrow! &amp;nbsp;Tonight's walk is on the earlier side as the sunsets @ 6:55pm and at least one other meetup group will be joining us this evening. &amp;nbsp;This is one of our favorite walking locations.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We will be meeting on the Braintree side of PMP at the top of the path where the Bike Path Rules are posted immediately next to the parking lot next to the map and ranger station. &amp;nbsp;Let's meet and get to know each other while walking around the pond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The loop is 1.6 miles, with the walk to and from the parking lot it is 1.9 miles.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It takes about 35-40 minutes to walk the loop.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If we walk the loop twice it's a total of 3.5 miles and takes between 1 hr and 1 hr and 15 minutes, depending on pace.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If we walk to the street of the Weymouth entrance it adds .4 miles and takes about 5-10 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[Please Note: There are only two entrances to PMP - in Braintree and Weymouth.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There is only one place to meet on the path and that's where the Braintree and Weymouth paths converge.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If we walk against the flow of traffic and you will be more than 10 minutes late you could potentially meet us at the merge as we will wait 5-10 minutes for late (Yes RSVP) arrivals, and within 5-10 minutes of our departure we will pass the convergence of the paths.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;However, if we walk the right away we won't pass that point until almost 1/2 hour into our walk.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this time is too early/late for you and you would like to walk PMP please note it in your RSVP so we may note your feedback for scheduling future walks and events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Note: As this is in conjunction with at least one other meetup group, please do not double or triple RSVP. &amp;nbsp;Please RSVP Yes to one meetup group and No to the others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following meetup groups have been confirmed for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South of Boston/South Shore Fit Clubs: www.meetup.com/southshorefitclubs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Shore Walkabouts: www.meetup.com/walkabouts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pond Meadow Park Monday Evening Walk w/ At Least One Other Meetup Group&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monday, March 19th @ 5pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pond Meadow Park&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;470 Liberty Street, Braintree&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-843-7663&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.pondmeadowpark.org/"&gt;www.pondmeadowpark.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Flagpole in front of Ranger Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela &amp;amp; ??? (Would love to have a co-organizer, especially if you are interested in hosting future walks!)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: At&amp;nbsp;least 4 Yes RSVPs by 4pm on Saturday, March 17th.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Attendance is currently unlimited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: Welcome, 1 adult per member!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: Please finalize your RSVP by&amp;nbsp;NOON on Monday, March 19th.&amp;nbsp; Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our No-Show policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(We will do&amp;nbsp;our best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by&amp;nbsp;3pm on the day of the walk.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Follow Union Street to the first set of lights.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PMP is 500 feet up on the Right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We recommend you park outside of the gate, as the gates are locked at approximately 6:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet at the Flagpole in front of the Ranger Station.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332201050000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329926501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pond Meadow Park Monday Night Walk w/ At Least One Other Meetup Group</name><id>53337222</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332190800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/53337222/</event_url></item>