<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's use this great hike to Leaterman's Cave as an opportunity to walk off the turkey coma.  This hike is near Black Rock State Park but not in it.  The Leatherman hiked a loop 365 mile long from the Connecticut River to the Hudson River between 1858 and 1889.  His clothing was made entirely from leather scraps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike takes you up to a picturesque plateau overlooking the valley and Rt. 8.  There are ups but it is worth the challenge to see the views and the rockfall cave.  The trail should be no more than 5 miles and we should be done by 2:00, at the very latest.  That's no more than four hours for you all doing the math.  Bring water and a snack for a break on top of the cave.  I strongly recommend wearing a backpack so you are hands free for this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The directions lead you to Black Rock State Park.  DO NOT GO INTO THE PARK.  When you reach the park entrance, continue west on route 6.  As you head up the big hill, the trail head will be on your left.  We will be parking on the road.  General maps for this section of the trail are in the walk book.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear hiking boots and appropriate clothing for the temperature that day.  Layers are the best way to go and a pack large enough to keep any clothing you must shed.  Trust this is not a naked hike event :).  Rain will cancel the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Mapquest link:  &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?name=Black+Rock+State+Park&amp;amp;city=Watertown%2C+Town+Of&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=Thomaston+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06795&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.65199&amp;amp;longitude=-73.09592&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS&amp;amp;id=1032505886" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(old link don't think works right &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/mq/9-2eNN9Tt_Ipn4ngz8" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260028791000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258291951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Leatherman's Cave near Blackrock State Park, Watertown Ct</name><id>11877977</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259420400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11877977/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/f/global_705503.jpeg</photo_url></item>