<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1670 Maple Valley Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02827</zip><lat>41.716686</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Solving For X</name><city>Coventry</city><id>13373352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.698929</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;X = the ideal Rhode Island forest hike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;L x (D squared) + T over W + Y = X&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given this formula where L = location and the two Ds are Distance of the hike and Difficulty respectively, and the T = time to completion, divided by the variable W which is weather plus the Y (that would be you), we should be able to find X, the ideal hike in the category, Rhode Island forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this problem we'll use Parker Woodland at 1670 Maple Valley Rd. Coventry RI for the L. Given the relative central location it provides, it is one of the more optimal areas in terms of accessibility to the most members. It also includes all the elements that make a woodland hike enjoyable, such as interesting sights, streams, boulders, rocky outcroppings and all around natural beauty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first D, distance, we'll do a 5.25 mile loop designed to see all the attractions in the woodland without the added non interesting extra mileage. Some would consider 5.25 miles to be too short but for some it may be too long, so it kind of puts us into an ideal range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the second D, difficulty, we'll make it moderately strenuous which will appeal to those that want to push themselves beyond a pleasant walk in the woods but not to over exert to the point of non enjoyability. The many assents add to the physicality of the hike to compensate for the relatively shorter distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The T in this example will be 2.5 hours, enough to make it worth while and fulfilling but to leave time for socializing and whatnot afterwards. If hanging out after a hike is not your thing, there's always the chores that need to get done at home to consider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be divided by the one truly uncontrollable variable W which is weather and the one truly controllable one Y which is You and we should have all the variables in place for a great group hike. As for Y bring plenty of extra water and wear good hiking boots and understand the liability waiver for the group applies to this and all events with the group.&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/2/event_234603522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>michael</member_name><member_id>8899394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368906867000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368301581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solving For X</name><id>118914202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368883800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/118914202/</event_url></item>