<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Walk Hill Street</address_2><address_1>Wachusett Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.293244</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethel AME Church</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>974655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The &lt;a href="http://www.jphs.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Jamaica Plain Historical Society&lt;/a&gt; gives &lt;a href="http://www.jphs.org/2010-historic-walking-tours/" target="_blank"&gt;free walking tours&lt;/a&gt; every Saturday.  This one on July 31st is about the Woodbourne neighborhood:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&amp;quot;This neighborhood developed from nineteenth-century summer estates into a model suburban enclave. It contains examples of representative New England architecture with designs by local architects and builders. It also contains an unusual garden city model housing development by the Boston Dwelling House Company.&amp;quot;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;The tour starts at 11am sharp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, so be there or be prepared to take on the challenge of finding us.  I haven't gone on these walks before and they don't have a map of the walk online, so I have no idea where this walk will lead us.  I will send out my cell phone number to the RSVPs. Please remember to keep your  RSVP updated.  They cancel in case of rain, but if it's a light rain and they cancel, we'll walk around anyway.  Really bad rain will cancel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This walk starts at the Bethel AME church steps, at the corner of Walk Hill and Wachusett Streets, as noted on the website.  This is about a 10 minute walk from the Forest Hills Orange Line station.  I'm not sure about parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm limiting this to 10 people so we don't overwhelm the tour guide.  I'm not sure how popular these tours are with the rest of the world.  Please remember this is a free public tour, so there will be other non-meetup people there, and I'm not sure how many people show up to these.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug</member_name><member_id>4908818</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282698344000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279684942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jamaica Plain Historical Walking Tour (Woodbourne)</name><id>14165845</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280588400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/14165845/</event_url></item>