<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fitchburg, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.662548</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Willard Brook State Forest</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>10355382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.792110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us in this 2.5 hour (3 mile) extremely picturesque hike alongside the babbling Williard Brook, which will continue with a loop thru the park.  Willard Brook State Forest contains 2,597 acres and is located in the towns of Ashby and Townsend, 50 miles from Boston. Here you can find the character and feeling of forests usually found much farther west in the state with a tumbling brook and quick water amid groves of classic New England woods.  Hike leader: Richard F. Home phone 978-400-5564. Plan to arrive 10 minutes early unless you are familiar with the meeting location.  Bring water and something to eat as we will stop for a 10 minute snack.  We will be back to the car by 12:15.  You must be able to carry a moderate pace thru this entire hike.  Total elevation gain is about 400 feet.  I presume dogs are allowed as I see nothing to the contrary.  Does anyone know?  Is anyone opposed to dogs?  I'm not bringing one but many have asked in the past.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park in the parking lot along side 119 at the gated entrance to the park where we wil meet. The gate is currently closed and does not allow you to drive into the park itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the west: Follow Rte. 2 East to Rte. 31 North in Fitchburg. Follow 31 North through Fitchburg to the Town of Ashby and the intersection with Rte. 119 East. Follow Rte. 119 East approx. .5 miles to the campground entrance on the right.  Allow 15 min extra if you are using a GPS for this route as they are doing construction on 31 and have detours.  Many have got lost. &lt;br /&gt;

From the east: Rte 2 West to Fitchburg and Rte.13 North. Follow Rte. 13 North to Rte.119 West in West Townsend. Turn left onto Rte. 119. Follow Rte. 119 approximately 4 miles to the park entrance on the left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Richard Fallon</member_name><member_id>10897888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353288547000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353088920000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Williard Brook State Forest</name><id>91687312</id><headcount>10</headcount><duration>9900000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353249000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/91687312/</event_url></item>