<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Weisner Bldg (E15) Lower Level</address_2><address_1>20 Ames Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.360748</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5229</phone><name>MIT Bartos Theater</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1396923</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;This year's School of Architecture and Planning theme for the Fall 2010 MIT Program in art, culture and technology is &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Give Me Shelter: Second Skin for Extreme Environments?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt; All lectures are free, open to the public, and held in the MIT Bartos Theater from 7:00 pm to 9:00 pm. &lt;i&gt;Flyer&lt;/i&gt;: &lt;a href="http://visualarts.mit.edu/downloads/Lecture_Series_F10/Lecture_Series_Fall_2010.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://visualarts.mit...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;October 18, 2010&lt;/b&gt;: Dava Newman&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Second Skin Bio-Suit&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT Bartos Theater&lt;br /&gt;Weisner Bldg (E15) Lower Level&lt;br /&gt;20 Ames Street&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://visualarts.mit.edu/about/lecture.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://visualarts.mit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;With support from the NASA Institute for Advanced Concepts and Trotti &amp;amp; Assoc. Inc., Cambridge, Mass., the BioSuit was developed to provide a ‘second skin’ capability for astronaut performance. Processes such as electrospinning and melt-blowing have been used to develop fibers for the suit. A current mockup uses nylon, spandex and urethane layers with varied properties and electronics incorporated into the suit and helmet materials that can have 'smart textile' functions relating to physiology (thermal comfort), communications and spatial orientation. Space suit research can lead to improvements in the quality of life here on earth, too, through advances in orthotics that can help children with cerebral palsy and 'smart orthoses' for stroke patients&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be grabbing a bite to eat at the Food Court right next to the Kendall / MIT Red Line Stop and the Mariott Hotel at 24 Cambridge Center in Cambridge starting at 5:30 pm. Feel free to drop by! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a seven minute walk to the MIT Visual Arts Center, walking down Main Street, and taking a left at Legal Seafood onto Ames Street. The MIT Bartos Theater is in the lower level of the MIT Visual Arts Center. We should probably leave the Food Court at 6:25 pm and grab seats at 6:40 pm so we can sit together as a group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About this year's theme, Give Me Shelter&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://visualarts.mit.edu/about/lecture.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://visualarts.mit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Give Me Shelter lecture series draws together speakers from different disciplines to discuss questions such as: How can bodywear function as body extension or to support the human body under unusual conditions such as hot and cold climates? How can we expand the notion of the boundary between the body and environment? What kind of second skin would be required to survive walking through a volcano, living under water, or visiting outer space? How does clothing contribute to the question of the protection of endangered peoples and environments?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Dava Newman, according to her MIT Faculty Page:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://esd.mit.edu/Faculty_Pages/newman/newman.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://esd.mit.edu/Fa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Margaret MacVicar Faculty Fellow&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Professor of Aeronautics and Astronautics and Engineering Systems &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Director, Technology and Policy Program&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Harvard-MIT Health, Sciences and Technology &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Lead, Bio-Engineering Systems Focus Area, MIT Portugal Program &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dr. Newman received her Ph.D. in Aerospace Biomedical Engineering from MIT. Her expertise is in multidisciplinary research that combines aerospace biomedical engineering, human-in-the-loop modeling, biomechanics, human interface technology, life sciences, systems analysis, design and policy. Dr. Newman's research studies are carried out through space flight experiments, ground-based simulations, and mathematical modeling. Current research efforts include: advanced space suit design, dynamics and control of astronaut motion, mission analysis, and engineering systems design and policy analysis. She also has ongoing efforts in assistive techologies to augment human locomotion here on Earth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dr. Newman is the author of &lt;i&gt;Interactive Aerospace Engineering and Design&lt;/i&gt;, an introductory engineering textbook with accompanying CD-ROM, published by McGraw-Hill, Inc. in 2002. She has also published more than 100 papers in journals and refereed conferences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Dr. Newman received her BS degree from the University of Notre Dame and SM degrees in 1989 from MIT's Technology and Policy Program and department of Aeronautics and Astronautics&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://visualarts.mit.edu/about/lecture.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://visualarts.mit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Located in Kendall Square, Cambridge. Take the MBTA red line to the Kendall/MIT stop. Follow Main Street west to Ames Street, turn left, and walk one block. Ames Street has limited on-street parking. Visitors may park in MIT campus lots after 5 PM. (The Hayward Lot is on Hayward Street, off of Amherst Street&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287519927000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286480074000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dava Newman presents her Second Skin Bio Suit @ MIT</name><id>15037016</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287442800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15037016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/4/global_18554692.jpeg</photo_url></item>