<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Downtown</address_1><state>NY</state><lat>40.714352</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>online at Occupy Sandy website</name><city>New York</city><id>10143392</id><country>us</country><lon>-74.005974</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Cross-posting in solidarity with our friends in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, Boston was spared the worst of the damage caused by Hurricane Sandy. All donations collected at our &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/events/88924452/"&gt;Election Night Viewing party&lt;/a&gt; will be donated to Occupy Sandy relief efforts. If you're not able to join us, please donate &lt;a href="https://www.wepay.com/donations/occupy-sandy-cleanup-volunteers"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occupy Sandy is a coordinated relief effort to help distribute resources &amp;amp; volunteers to help neighborhoods and people hardest hit by Hurricane Sandy. They are a coalition of people &amp;amp; organizations who are dedicated to implementing aid and establishing hubs for neighborhood resource distribution. Members of this coalition are from Occupy Wall Street, &lt;a href="http://www.350.org"&gt;350.org&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.recovers.org"&gt;recovers.org&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.interoccupy.net"&gt;interoccupy.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DONATE &lt;br /&gt;

 Gifts of any amount appreciated, seriously $5, $10, $20, $50 or more. Donations of over $250 will be provided a tax receipt. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="https://www.wepay.com/donations/occupy-sandy-cleanup-volunteers"&gt;https://www.wepay.com/donations/occupy-sandy-cleanup-volunteers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;READ &lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/11/02/occupy-wall-street-helps-sandy-victims-_n_2060275.html"&gt;Huffington Post article about Occupy Sandy. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/11/02/occupy-wall-street-helps-sandy-victims-_n_2060275.html"&gt;From their website:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our economic system is set up to look for quick money rather than long-term options, and many of the situations we are seeing are symptoms of that problem. With Sandy, you saw that Goldman Sachs had all of its lights on while NYU medical center was performing an emergency evacuation because they ran out of power. We want to build an alternative economic structure that is based on longevity rather than profit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not only bringing in relief to areas that are not experiencing government aid, but also working with existing organizations to build strong community centers. We are building a relief effort that will still give communities access to necessary resources 5 years from now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who's homes were lost and businesses destroyed may not have the resources to rebuild their lives. These are the people who are forgotten by short-term shelters and Red Cross tents, because they require a sustainable, local, long-term approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, to donate or volunteer: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://interoccupy.net/occupysandy/"&gt;http://interoccupy.net/occupysandy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352517107000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351996309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DONATE: Occupy Sandy Relief NYC</name><id>89854492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352505600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/89854492/</event_url></item>