<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Friday Film Night &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Benefit for The Growing Green Wellness Center!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD, Inc. film showing @ 7pm!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organic potluck dinner &amp;amp; discussion with Chef Mark Shadle of It's Only Natural Restaurant in Middletown. Mark will be speaking about the importance of local foods. And then, following the film, Karl Weber, the editor of the companion book, FOOD Inc, will be speaking about food policy in the US. There will be a Q&amp;amp;A session and a book signing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are asking for a $10-20 donation for this event as a way to support this community wellness center. However, no one will be turned away for lack of funds! If a $20 donation is made toward the event, it will be applied toward a complimentary monthly membership at the wellness center. For a description of member benefits, please see &lt;a href="http://www.growinggreenevents.com/join-our-community.php." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.growinggreenevents.com&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Growing Green Wellness Center&lt;br /&gt;197 New Britain Ave &lt;br /&gt;Hartford, CT 06106&lt;br /&gt;860.983.5276&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Film will start promptly at 7 pm.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food, Inc. exposes America's industrialized food system and its effect on our environment, health, economy and workers' rights. Filmmaker Robert Kenner lifts the veil on our nation's food industry, exposing the highly mechanized underbelly that has been hidden from the American consumer with the consent of our government's regulatory agencies, USDA and FDA. Our nation's food supply is now controlled by a handful of corporations that often put profit ahead of consumer health, the livelihood of the American farmer, the safety of workers and our own environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring interviews with such experts as Eric Schlosser (Fast Food Nation), Michael Pollan (The Omnivore's Dilemma, In Defense of Food: An Eater's Manifesto) along with forward thinking social entrepreneurs like Stonyfield's Gary Hirshberg and Polyface Farms' Joel Salatin, Food, Inc. reveals surprising—and often shocking truths—about what we eat, how it's produced, who we have become as a nation and where we are going from here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodincmovie.com/about-the-issues.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Issues - FOOD Inc Website&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to join us after the film for a community discussion with author Karl Weber!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264378072000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262019643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FOOD Inc.</name><id>12159768</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264204800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12159768/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/9/global_12517769.jpeg</photo_url></item>