<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Union Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.379343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Union Square Plaza </name><city>Somerville</city><id>696121</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This was a crowd favorite last year, so we do not want to mess with success !!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plan is to hi tail it to Rockport and then it will be all about the ride.  Rt127 to Rt 133 to Rt 1A  Along the way we will stop for lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cape Ann, Massachusetts: The Other Cape&lt;br /&gt;30 miles north of Boston. You round a corner or crest a hill and wham! -- suddenly you've driven into a painting. It's something about the way the light refracts off the ocean on all sides, making ship masts and fish shacks seem to glow from within. It's something about the natural beauty of the water crashing onto the granite. But most of all, it's about the power of suggestion -- since artists have painted Cape Ann so often, there's barely an inch of it that hasn't been memorialized in oil or watercolor, making a visit seem a kind of perpetual scenic déjà vu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artists &amp;quot;discovered&amp;quot; the cape's natural beauty in the early 19th century, when they founded the country's first artists' colony on Rocky Neck in Gloucester as well as a smaller colony in the seaside village of Rockport. Setting up their canvases in the open air, they painted the brawny backs of fishermen unloading cod from their catch on the nearby rich fishing grounds of Stellwagen Bank, or weathered schooners that had been setting out for generations to hunt for swordfish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Cape Ann unique is that both artists and fishermen are still here. Unlike some Cape Cod enclaves that see legions of cocoa butter-toting tourists descend every Memorial Day only to seemingly close shutters in October, Cape Ann's towns are year-round communities, with trawlers steaming out of the harbor before dawn and artisans painting and sculpting in the coves. Along the streets of Gloucester today, the briny smell of fish mingles with the smell of fried seafood, and shrieking gulls wheel over a harbor crowded with fishing boats.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wearing scooter gear hanging around scooters :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Ricca </member_name><member_id>6927550</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255355673000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235086097000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beautiful North of Boston Scenic Tour </name><id>9779156</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255177800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/9779156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/9/global_7380745.jpeg</photo_url></item>