<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Redstone Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06042</zip><lat>41.801041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rave Motion Pictures Buckland Hills</name><city>Manchester</city><id>664343</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.547752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It looks like everyone is as excited to see this movie as I am.  Here are the final plans.  Please update your RSVP's as necessary.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:30  Dinner at John Harvards. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;They have agreed to take a reservation prime time on Friday night so PLEASE show up early so we can be ready to be seated at 7:30.  No one will be seated after 7:40.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Harvard's is at:  &lt;br /&gt;1487 Pleasant Valley Road&lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06040&lt;br /&gt;tel 860-644-2739&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;10:00 The Dark Knight (IMAX version) at Showcase Buckland Hills.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I am purchasing 30 tickets in advance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; so we can get the discount and all sit together.  You'll need to pay me in cash for them.  If you have to make last minute changes to your RSVP it's important that you call me.  (Cell phone listed below).  &lt;i&gt;By the way, if you need to drop out, don't worry.  I can sell back as many as 10 of them.   I'm covered as long as we have 20 or more. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a long movie so we won't be out until 12:45 or so.  After the movie we can grab a drink at Chatters (right in the theater) to save some drive time or go to Shea's if you prefer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the IMAX version: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dark Knight: The IMAX Experience will feature four sequences filmed with IMAX® cameras. This marks the first time ever that a major feature film has been even partially shot using IMAX cameras, marking a revolutionary integration of the two film formats. The follow-up to the action hit Batman Begins, The Dark Knight reunites director Christopher Nolan and star Christian Bale, who reprises the role of Batman/Bruce Wayne. In the new film, Batman raises the stakes in his war on crime. With the help of Lieutenant Jim Gordon and District Attorney Harvey Dent, Batman sets out to dismantle the remaining criminal organizations that plague the city streets. The partnership proves to be effective, but they soon find themselves prey to a reign of chaos unleashed by a rising criminal mastermind known to the terrified citizens of Gotham as The Joker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the RSVP's are full and you're still interested you can call me to see if there are any last minute drop outs.  Also if you need to change your RSVP at the last minute, my cell phone is 203-812-0705.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See details below</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217201209000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214680502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dark Knight - Dinner and a Movie</name><id>8235288</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217027700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/8235288/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/1/global_4608321.jpeg</photo_url></item>