<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Darmouth st and Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350094</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston's Copley Square Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>6798412</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077332</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;http://www.japanfestivalboston.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; To commemorate the Centennial of the original gift of cherry trees from Japan to Washington, D.C. in 1912, a number of events will take place in various cities across the U.S. this spring. In Boston, “Haru Matsuri Boston 2012” will be held on Sunday, April 29th as a part of “The Greater Boston-Japan Cherry Blossom Festival.” &lt;br /&gt;

 “Haru Matsuri (or “Spring Festival”) Boston 2012” – a daylong event in historic Copley Square – has been prepared by volunteers from numerous Japan-related organizations in Boston and is supported by the Consulate General of Japan and a number of Japanese and American corporations. It will be the first Japanese-style festival in Boston and will be the largest event ever organized by the local Japanese community. Haru Matsuri will present a unique opportunity for Boston families and visitors to enjoy Japanese food and entertainment and to learn about Japanese culture in an entertaining environment. Featuring 80 booths offering delicious foods and goods, games and activities typical to traditional Japanese festivals, as well as music and performances by local artists, Haru Matsuri will be a day full of fun and festivity for participants of all ages. There will also be organizations which have been providing support for those affected by the great earthquake and tsunami that devastated the eastern region of Japan last March. &lt;br /&gt;

 We hope that families of all backgrounds will join us in celebrating spring with us and enjoying a Japanese festival firsthand on April 29th at Copley Square!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carlton SooHoo</member_name><member_id>2174911</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335769731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335356412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Japan Spring Festival in Boston</name><id>62049362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335711600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/62049362/</event_url></item>