<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;THIS MEETUP HAS BEEN RESCHEDULED.   I  received an email from ETTB stating that this event was being held on Thursday, Aug. 12th, instead of the previously scheduled Saturday Aug. 14th.  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(From the ETTB website: PLEASE NOTE: DATES AND TIMES CAN CHANGE DUE TO CIRCUMSTANCES&lt;br /&gt;BEYOND OUR CONTROL. PLEASE BE SURE TO CALL THE CLUB FIRST!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Since this event is now happening during the week, please adjust your RSVP's if necessary.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fantastic band Eight to the Bar will be returning to the 1149 for the third time! ETTB will be playing Motown songs tonight, so everyone will be up and dancing. Their last Motown show was great - everyone from our group was on the dance floor! Although ETTB is usually a swing band, I am beginning to really enjoy their Motown shows...with all our favorite songs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There was no cover charge last time ETTB played there - however, the dance area (back room) is quite small, so I would advise you to arrive early, if possible.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Would anyone be interested in dinner before the show? This way, we can be sure to get a table in the dance area. &lt;u&gt; No Maybe's for dinner - I cannot reserve a table without a definite count!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup sign on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>9267328</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282658618000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Exciting People Having Some Fun!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mingle-with-singles</urlname><id>1452082</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Mingle with singles 45+ Socializing and dancing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278985337000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Music &amp; dancing (Eight to the Bar) and possibly Dinner at 1149 Restaurant</name><id>14084390</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281657600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mingle-with-singles/events/14084390/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/0/global_10652416.jpeg</photo_url></item>