<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2450 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.333930</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Metroplitan Waterworks Museum</name><city>Chestnut Hill</city><id>2313361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.154120</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The waterworks museum is a new comer on the extensive list of Boston Museums. I recently noticed  a talk they're having on the Quabbin and was interested in checking out their beautiful building as well as what the speaker has to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the website - &lt;a href="http://www.waterworksmuseum.org/"&gt;http://www.waterworksmuseum.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;J.R. Greene has devoted his life to researching and writing the stories related to the construction of the Quabbin Reservoir. A member of the MWRA Advisory Board since 1991, Greene will speak about the engineering and construction of the Quabbin.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cost: $5&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin reservoir is the drinking water supply for most of the towns in the Metro Boston area (excluding Cambridge, Winchester, and a few others) but few people on this side of the state know the story of its creation. I grew up in Western Massachusetts so Quabbin is a topic near to my heart! Years ago I read a fascinating history on the story which in a nutshell goes something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the great depression area Boston was a growing city and saw a clear need for expanded drinking water but couldn't find any in the immediate area. A state official who enjoyed fishing on the swift river of central / western Massachusetts suggested damming the river to create a reservoir. Clearly not a popular idea with the town residents! Well 4 towns (Enfield, Dana, Greenwich, and Prescott) had their charter's revoked by the state and were literally erased from the map to make the reservoir. The residents were paid to tear down their own town, dig up the dead, dismantle the church, etc along with James Micheal Curly's infamous work crews from Boston. The towns were then flooded with some of the infrastructure left intact. The roads that formally went to these towns are now the various gates around Quabbin. Clearly having 4 towns destroyed so a distant capital could enjoy a resource few Western Mass residents needed did not go over well in that part of the state. To me this brings up some fundamental questions about the right of a town to exist and the nature of democracy. I'm not sure if these topics will come up in the talk but I'm interested in hearing the point of view from someone in the Massachusetts Water Resource Authority (MWRA).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: this talk cost money! I don't know if anyone will think its worth it but I'm going anyway. I will likely take a walk around Chestnut hill reservoir beforehand with a strong possibility of a burrito in Cleveland circle as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wait outside until 6:45.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>2367399</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1336093663000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335409721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Reservoir Talk at Chesnut Hill's Waterworks Museum</name><id>62183782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335998700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/62183782/</event_url></item>