<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1167 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02190</zip><lat>42.164208</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-335-5600</phone><name>Ecco Trattoria</name><city>Weymouth</city><id>838268</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.955251</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A very brief lesson in Italian:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Trattoria&lt;/i&gt; is a word for a smaller, relatively informal restaurant. Outside of Italy, as might be expected, the term denotes a restaurant that is specifically Italian.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ecco&lt;/i&gt; essentially means &amp;quot;there it is&amp;quot;. Like the French &lt;i&gt;voila&lt;/i&gt;, it is often used as an interjection when one produces something with a flourish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The above is offered by way of introducing you to &lt;a href="http://www.eccotrattoria.com/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ecco Trattoria&lt;/a&gt; in Weymouth, where the food is Italian, and the flourishes implied by the name appear happily on patrons' plates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Situated in a strip mall on Route 18, Ecco does not look especially promising from the outside. Inside, the floor plan is open and the decor is modern and tasteful, but the real aesthetic statements are made by the food, which is good enough to stand out in an area where Italian restaurants are par for the course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be heading there for an early-ish dinner at 6:30 on Tuesday, January 6th. The choice of date will allow our members to take advantage of the last day of SSDOMG's event fee-free period, as well as Ecco's &lt;a href="http://www.eccotrattoria.com/pastanight.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pasta Night specials&lt;/a&gt;, which are only served on Tuesdays and Wednesdays, and give diners a choice of ten different entrees with salad for just $10.95.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike encourages you to have a look around Ecco's very comprehensive website, which includes links to reviews by both TV Diner and The Patriot Ledger, then plan to join him at a restaurant that he considers a dependable favorite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ecco Trattoria&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1167 Main Street, Weymouth&lt;br /&gt;781-335-5600&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eccotrattoria.com/main.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eccotratto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, January 6 @ 6:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up to two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; None! As a holiday gift to our members, we are not charging our normal $2.00 event fee! Members and their Guests will only pay for what they order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; Pasta Night entrees cost $10.95 and include a choice of Ceasar or house salad. Dinner choices on the regular menu range from $12.99 (Angel Hair Pasta) to $24.99 (Filet Mignon or Sirloin Steak).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over two years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps us to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Monday, January 5 @ 6:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; Ecco Trattoria is located on Main Street (Route 18) in Weymouth. Please watch this space for more detailed directions to be posted prior to the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232586320000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230348933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ecco!</name><id>9391378</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231284600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9391378/</event_url></item>