<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 Merrimac Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.365092</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 624-0202</phone><name>Bulfinch Hotel</name><city>Boston</city><id>1451002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.063261</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;My name is Kathy Benharris and I am thrilled to have been asked by Jamall Oluokun, Ron Ranere, and Shirley Willet to assume the helm as the new organizer of our meetup group.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I am a fashion consultant and event planner, model, and designer liaison that loves the business of fashion.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;In my role as organizer, my goal is to provide members with information and contacts&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;which can assist you with realizing your business goals regardless of what part of the fashion industry you work in, or wish to work in.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I am a huge believer in the power of networking and the results that can be achieved by attending our meetups. At my first Boston Fashion Meetup, I met many of the fashion industry players here in Boston that I had previously only read about. It was also at this meeting that I met John Bilotti, who I have asked to be an assistant organizer. John is an incredibly talented professional that I have had the pleasure of working with on several successful projects. John and I have provided brief summaries on our professional experiences below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The entire leadership team is excited to announce our first Boston Fashion Meetup event this year. We hope you can join us at the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Flat Iron Tapas Bar and Lounge at the Bulfinch Hotel &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;on Wednesday, March 2rd from 5:30 - 8:00 pm for a member mixer and fashion swap.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;This informal "open house" style gathering will allow you to drop by at your convenience and is an excellent way to network with other members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Attendance for members will be free and the Flat Iron Tapas Bar at the Bulfinch Hotel has generously offered to provide appetizers. There will be a cash bar. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Please use this link to access additional information and directions: &lt;a href="http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;To participate in the voluntary fashion swap, bring a new / gently used / or even a well enjoyed but still wonderful item from your closet that you no longer want. Members will have the chance to swap their item with other member&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our entire leadership team is committed to offering you meetups that will provide you with timely data regarding industry trends and opportunities, both here in Boston and beyond. Upcoming meetups are being scheduled that will be more formal in nature with a seated panel of experts answering your questions and sharing their take on the topic at hand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone on March 2nd&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;- don&amp;rsquo;t forget to bring your enthusiasm and business cards. Please RSVP so we have a general idea of how many members are planning to attend. Thanks and please let me know if you have any questions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Kathy Benharris&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Kathy Benharris&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &amp;ndash; I have had the privilege of working with many of the talented designers,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;fashion stylists, event promoters, models, make up artists, hair stylists, music / DJ&amp;rsquo;s, photographers, and public relations professionals here in Boston. As a fashion event planner and show production consultant, I have run fashion events during Boston Fashion Week, as well as contributed to many other shows and fundraisers.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I recently co-produced the Boston Symphony Orchestra&amp;rsquo;s fashion competiton:&lt;em&gt; Project Beethoven&lt;/em&gt; as well as last year&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Project Tchaikovsky&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I am very proud of my excellent relationship with our area&amp;rsquo;s incredible fashion and design schools&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;As a Dynasty Model, I understand also what it is like to work on the other side of the camera. I thoroughly enjoy promoting the designers and boutiques that I work with as a liaison and am passionate in my pursuit of opportunities for my clients. My past experiences as a retail executive in TJX&amp;rsquo;s home office and as a store systems sales professional have given me excellent insight into other components of the fashion industry.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Kathy Benharris &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;kbenharris@aol.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;John Bilotti&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;, - Graduated 1991 w/degrees in Computer Science &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;and Photography from UMass. While developing my technical career over 20 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;years working for companies such as Stratus Computers, BB&amp;amp;N, Archivas, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hitachi Data Systems, and Demandware; I continued to pursue my love for art &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;and photography.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I have worked as a commercial product photographer, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;photography teacher, event photographer, nightclub photographer, portrait &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;photographer, and most recently a fashion photographer. I have also &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;produced and coordinated many public events over the years, including &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;corporate events, fashion shows and charity fundraisers. For 2011 I am &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;growing my own event management and media company (Perfect Events &amp;amp; Media), and I have signed on as a charter member of the new Worcester Photography Studios scheduled to open in spring 2011, and will have access to a new world class studio in central MA.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;John Bilotti&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:john.bilotti@perfectboston.com"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;john.bilotti@perfectboston.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;978-340-5853&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://www.bulfinchhotel.com/index.php</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathy Benharris</member_name><member_id>9272727</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Bilotti</member_name><member_id>9519600</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305241016000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Flat Iron Tapas Bar and Lounge at the Bulfinch Hotel on Wednesday, March 2rd from 5:30 - 8:00 pm for a member mixer and fashion swap. This informal style gathering is an excellent way to network with other members and share your ideas and feedback.</why><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297883045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BOSTON FASHION MEETUP NETWORKING MIXER &amp; FASHION SWAP</name><id>16589573</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299105000000</time><rsvp_limit>120</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/16589573/</event_url></item>