<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Lansdowne St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347389</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 693-2583</phone><name>House of Blues</name><city>Boston</city><id>924938</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>*&lt;b&gt;EDIT: Because the only other person who RSVPed is going to be there at 8, I'm going to stand outside at 8 instead of 7.  Look for me then!&lt;/b&gt;*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Jenny Lewis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenny Lewis is an indie folk singer/songwriter/guitarist, who is best known for being the lead singer and guitarist for the indie rock band Rilo Kiley. She has released two solo albums, 2006's &lt;i&gt;Rabbit Fur Coat&lt;/i&gt; (with The Watson Twins) and 2008's &lt;i&gt;Acid Tongue&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1995, she formed the indie rock band Rilo Kiley along with her friends Pierre De Reeder, Blake Sennett and Dave Rock (later replaced by Jason Boesel). Beginning with a country sound, Rilo Kiley gravitated toward a downbeat indie rock sound, and with their 2004 album More Adventurous found widespread success. Critics such as Pitchforkmedia attributed this to the &amp;quot;wise&amp;quot; decision to front Lewis on most of the songs (on earlier albums, Sennett contributed about half the vocals). The song &amp;quot;Portions for Foxes&amp;quot; was a hit, and in 2005 the band was picked up by Warner Bros., putting them on a major label for the first time. They opened for Coldplay on their U.S. tour in 2005.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2002, Lewis was asked to contribute some female vocals for The Postal Service, whose album Give Up was an international success. Lewis performed in the video for the hit &amp;quot;We Will Become Silhouettes,&amp;quot; and toured with the band in 2003. Lewis also contributed vocals to several tracks on the 2004 Cursive album The Ugly Organ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2004, Conor Oberst invited Lewis to record a solo record for record label Team Love. Described by Lewis as &amp;quot;a kind of soul record,&amp;quot; &lt;i&gt;Rabbit Fur Coat&lt;/i&gt;, released in January 2006, features contributions from musicians Conor Oberst of Bright Eyes, M. Ward, Maroon 5 guitarist James Valentine, and Ben Gibbard of Death Cab for Cutie on a cover of The Traveling Wilburys song &amp;quot;Handle With Care.&amp;quot; The Watson Twins provide accompaniment and the album is billed as Jenny Lewis with The Watson Twins. Lewis toured with the Watson Twins in support of the album in early 2006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 2008 sees the relase of a second solo album, titled &lt;i&gt;Acid Tongue&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She has also provided vocals on tracks for The Elected and Johnathan Rice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Infamous for her quirky clothing and ever constant red hairstyle, Lewis has become a fashion icon in the indie music world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lewis was given an &amp;quot;Esky&amp;quot; for Best Temperature Raiser in Esquire’s 2006 Esky Music Awards in the April issue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Excerpted from &lt;a href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jenny+Lewis/" target="_blank"&gt;last.fm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The opening acts for this concert are Deer Tick and Farmer Dave Scher.  Tickets are $20, and doors are at 7.&lt;br /&gt;I will be driving into the Fenway area for this event.  There is a Red Sox-Yankees game scheduled at the same time, so there is a chance that I may be tied up looking for parking.  If this is the case, feel free to line up to get in before I get there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet outside the venue. Look for the Meetup sign!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wing</member_name><member_id>3393735</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248566410000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244315334000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jenny Lewis at the House of Blue</name><id>10591948</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244674800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/10591948/</event_url></item>