<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce and John O’Leary are going to be leading a fun night with group members analyzing the Enneagram types of famous people.  For Enneagram fans this is a great opportunity to have a good time and further your knowledge.  Here is a description of the event from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“This event will be co-led by John O'Leary who is a consultant, musician and humorous political campaigner.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to this fun and informative evening of typing some of the most famous people in the world. Herb and John have been teaching this constantly updated workshop and studying famous personalities and their types for years. Ask all the questions you want to ask about famous people and their type!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring or share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it. Herb always has great snacks. Great food, company and a fun topic - an awesome way to spend a Friday night!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282980819000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280472465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enneagram Types of Politicians, Sports Figures, Celebrities &amp; People in History</name><id>14261282</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282950000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/14261282/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/8/global_7203288.jpeg</photo_url></item>