<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Witches of Eastwick by John Updike&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.borders.com/ProductImages/products/00/02/80/a/2801919_a.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt; BEFORE THEY WERE THE WIDOWS OF EASTWICK, OUR HEROINES WERE A TRIO OF DELIGHTFULLY WICKED WITCHES. In a small New England town in that hectic era when the sixties turned into the seventies, there lived three witches. Alexandra Spoffard, a sculptress, could create thunderstorms. Jane Smart, a cellist, could fly. The local gossip columnist, Sukie Rougemont, could turn milk into cream. Divorced but hardly celibate, the wonderful witches one day found themselves quite under the spell of the new man in town, Darryl Van Horne, whose strobe-lit hot tub room became the scene of satanic pleasures. To tell you any more, dear reader, would be to spoil the joy of reading this hexy, sexy novel by the incomparable John Updike. Praise for New York Times BestsellerThe Witches of Eastwick: “A dazzling book . . . Updike is devilishly clever.” –Los Angeles Times “New England’s past and present are brilliantly interwoven in this narrative . . . [Updike] has brought [this] culture wittily and radiantly to life.” –The New York Times “A great deal of fun to read . . . fresh, constantly entertaining . . . John Updike [is] a wizard of language and observation.” –The Philadelphia Inquirer “A wicked entertainment . . . In book after book, Updike’s fine, funny impressionistic art strips the full casings of everydayness from objects we have known all our lives and makes them shine with fresh new connections.” –The New Republic “Witty, ironic, engrossing, punctuated by transports of spectacular prose.” –Time “Vintage Updike, which is to say among the best fiction we have.” –Newsday Selected byTimeas one of the Five Best Works of Fiction of the Year&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please bring your a book or 2 or 3 to swap! Thanks!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the table closest to the cafe door. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269796871000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256827254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Book Club &amp; Book Swap - The Witches of Eastwick</name><id>11741299</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269471600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/11741299/</event_url></item>