<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I think last month's potluck was a big success i say we should do something this month. Something personal, and go out after like we did last month. Or we can go a bit more exciting and go out to a fun place. My fun spots i have thought of is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An overnighter in NYC...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah i know the Party Bus was wild when we got off. But its NYC and we were drunk off our asses. But if we can stick together and hit some spots in a group, this could be a really fun night. We can do Rockafeller Center, Times Squares, Eat dinner at a decent food spot and dance our asses off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for where to stay for the night... NYC is pricey now it being the holidays doesn't help. If we split up each room by 6 &amp;nbsp;or probably 8, a $450 room is about $60- $75 a person which is more or less the total of an "ok" hotel stay.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to get there... I think we have a couple of options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*We can meet up and car pool (for those who need to) all the way down to New Haven. If i understand right, the tickets are $14 the most but if we get a group package then it's cheaper. THIS IS ONE WAY... For Round trip its $28 or less pending on the group discount rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**We can get a one way limo trip over there and then come back on train the next day.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***And those who feel they do not want to stay we can find ways by train or limo that same night.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think this trip is to easier to plan than what it sounds like. Especially if we have a group of 14+. That would be awesome! We will have the group discount for the train or the split of a 16 passenger limo wouldn't be that bad. The split of the hotel rate would be less than $75 if we go for a hotel no more than $450. So hopefully we'll have a good turn out. Based on the expenses, I'm not going to make this official until i have 10 people. This will be a huge way to start saying our goodbyes &amp;nbsp;to 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christian&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll set up a meet up spot</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324166870000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323110263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate The Holidays</name><id>43458372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324162800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/43458372/</event_url></item>