<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Somerset Pkwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.786247</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603 886-1200</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Nashua</name><city>Nashua</city><id>671445</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.509540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Campaign to Launch Doorknocking Effort
 &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 23 &amp;middot; 9:00am - 5:00pm
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Location
 &lt;br /&gt;Crown Plaza Hotel
 &lt;br /&gt;2 Somerset Parkway
 &lt;br /&gt;Nashua, NH 03063
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Doors will open at 9:00am. We will distribute walking lists for the Nashua area. Then there will be a brief seminar on basic door to door etiquette and strategy, as well as how to manage the data you will be collecting. For those that have volunteered on campaigns before it shouldn't be anything terribly new.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Ron Paul will lead the charge as he gives a speech to rally supporters before we head out. Ron is scheduled to speak at 9:30 so be here early to get a chance to hear him speak and meet with him afterwords.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Those who are planning on attending please RSVP to 
&lt;a href="mailto:shaunb@ronpaul2012.com"&gt;shaunb@ronpaul2012.com&lt;/a&gt; as soon as possible. We would like to have an estimate as to attendance so we can better break out the regions.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;As you know New Hampshire is a bell weather state and a win here can lead snowball support to win the GOP nomination. For example 4 of the last 6 GOP nominations all won New Hampshire.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;That is why it is so important to turn out for this event. The better we are early on the better chance we have of winning. So tell friends, family, and even complete strangers to get their butts down to Nashua on the 23rd.&amp;nbsp; We will be having people coming from from all over New England to help with this first push. At least two buses of volunteers, paid for entirely by grassroots, are coming up from NYC, so what's your excuse?
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;We will be the first campaign to have boots on the ground; lets start rewriting the course of history right now!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=126990870722441" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=126990870722441&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311431179000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310416363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Official NH Campaign Kickoff!</name><id>25364401</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311426000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/25364401/</event_url></item>