<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Former ballet dancer Kate Beckinsale dons the vinyl catsuit and ice blue contact lenses yet again for the latest Underworld film. OMG I love these movies! The secret war between vampires and werwolves is no longer secret, the humans know, and are out to exterminate the freaks of nature. Or something. Whatever, there will be vampires and werewolves and lots of shooting. Special thanks to alert member Shannon who made sure we didn't miss this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scheduled a week after opening because I had some conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group before the movie, we gather outside the theater showing the film after the film ends. And then we go out for a discussion 'n' food 'n' beer. Or wine, or cocktails, according to your preference. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/c/4/event_84995012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will see the &lt;strong&gt;7:00 IMAX show&lt;/strong&gt;. I will be at the lobby at 6 and&amp;nbsp;I will be wearing my red trucker hat with the meetup logo. If the movie is upstairs, I will be waiting at the tables near the front windows. If the movie is downstairs, I will be across from the refreshment stand. We'll head into the theater 20 minutes before showtime. Yes I know that's awfully early when you add it to the 10 to 20 minutes of previews, but hey, it'll give you a chance to talk to your neighbor!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I strongly advise buying tickets ahead of time on fandango.com.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Underworld Awakening" brings a stunning new dimension to the epic battle between Vampires and Lycans, as the first film in the franchise to shoot in 3D.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kate Beckinsale, star of the first two films, returns in her lead role as the vampire warrioress Selene, who escapes imprisonment to find herself in a world where humans have discovered the existence of both Vampire and Lycan clans, and are conducting an all-out war to eradicate both immortal species.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailers 'n' Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=57859"&gt;http://www.comingsoon.net/films.php?id=57859&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meetup description for how to find the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328033749000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326162593000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Underworld Awakening</name><id>47436502</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327793400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/47436502/</event_url></item>