<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213814</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;** The Center of Light is moving to Framingham March 15, 2010 **&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Way, The Truth and The Life&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, March 18 • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $25, bring a friend for free!&lt;br /&gt;85 Edgell Road, Framingham, MA 01701&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jesus said he was the Way, the Truth, and the Light. This means following him takes you right to God, to the light. Throughout the last two millennia, people have misconstrued this statement, building it up to be limiting or restricting. Instead, it is a call to freedom, a call to real life, a call to love. Allowing the Master of love to show you the way brings a freshness to your life that is unimaginable; but you have to see for yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this enlightening seminar with Mother Clare Watts, you will have a real experience of this Way, this Truth, and this Light. You will have ample opportunity to ask questions and engage in discussion with like-minded and like-hearted seekers. Welcome to a new reality that will set you free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the Sophia Peace Center. She is the author of Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is a white house on Framingham Common in Framingham Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269828058000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268244319000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar:  The Way, The Truth and The Life</name><id>12839862</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268955000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/12839862/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/2/global_7927570.jpeg</photo_url></item>