<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>166 Ave. A</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01376</zip><lat>42.607123</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-863-4441 </phone><name>Ristorante DiPaolo</name><city>Turners Falls</city><id>997152</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.557930</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Laugh, connect, meet, hang out, enjoy the food, meet that 'special someone' (you never know...) or a business connection or a kayaking buddy or just have a great and interesting conversation with someone you may never have met otherwise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We love to support our local farmers and chefs and artists so we are purposely choosing restaurants that have made a name for themselves by using fresh, healthy local ingredients and who are doing innovative things with food. If you have any suggestions, we are open!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;here's the restaurant's description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ristorante DiPaolo, serving fine Italian cuisine from many regions, opened its doors in March of 2006 in the quaint turn-of-the-century mill village of Turners Falls, MA. It's a short drive from Northampton, Amherst, and Brattleboro, VT. and the over-all experience is well worth the journey. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Denise DiPaolo has created an elegant décor and a warm, sexy ambiance that features a full bar, a well rounded wine list, and outside dining in season. Her partner Chef Hilton Dottin blends his 25 years of traditional Italian cooking with the Caribbean flair of his native Dominican Republic. Chef Dottin's mouth-watering Italian seafood dishes, risottos, and pastas are all prepared with the freshest locally grown and produced products available. You will be greeted with warmth and friendliness and treated to the most comforting food and great service.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will be the largest table! Ask for the EatUp! Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>9683028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251066135000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>food lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Western-Mass-Eat-Up</urlname><id>1464899</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4700012207</group_lon><name>Western Mass Eat-Up!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245974916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[Western Mass] Eat-Up! July Meetup at Ristorante DiPaolo in Turners Falls</name><id>10737645</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248991200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Western-Mass-Eat-Up/events/10737645/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/3/global_9352659.jpeg</photo_url></item>