<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi, Everybody: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all the tourists gone, this is the time of year we can reclaim our beach area&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a nice quiet walk on Long Sands and Short Sands Beach in York followed by a great lunch or brunch at the popular York Harbor Inn!  Here is their website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yorkharborinn.com/dining/dininghome.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yorkharborinn.com/dining/dininghome.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yorkharbor...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The walk will be about 3 miles and last about an hour to an hour and a half.  From there we will head up the road a ways to lunch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the directions to York Beach coming from the north down the Maine Turnpike: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through the toll booth; exit is next immediate right (Exit 7).  Bear left where the ramp splits.  Stop Sign.  Take left to lights.  Right at lights to next set of lights.  Left at these second set of lights.  This will take you towards York Village.  In the Village, the road (York Street) splits at a fork.  Bear right at this fork.  The road will wind and turn - just follow the road (in fact you will pass York Harbor Inn on the way to the beach!) until you come to the beach.  We will meet in the general vicinity of Anchorage Inn or Sea and Surf.  Just look for a Silver Subaru Forester.  We will meet there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!  Write if you have any questions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy &lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a silver Subaru around the Anchorage Inn / Sea and Surf vicinity</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344779568000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287741078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk on York Beach followed by lunch at The York Harbor Inn!</name><id>15192222</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289746800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/15192222/</event_url></item>