<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1307 Seabright Ave</address_1><state>CA</state><zip>95062</zip><lat>36.975482</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(831) 426-8893</phone><name>Pacific Cultural Center</name><city>Santa Cruz</city><id>734615</id><country>us</country><lon>-122.008907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;We have a special guest to sing you to new levels of awakening your heart and throat chakras, award winning new age vocalist Sophia Songhealer, will be offering her gift at our Puja this Saturday!!!  You don’t want to miss it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Normally $25, this event is now FREE; we welcome your love offering donations! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrate Charles’ Birthday with us and Sophia to begin your New Year with a Tantric ritual of great power to manifest your heart’s desire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This special Puja is designed to heal, awaken, and open your entire energy system, especially the heart chakra of your body. This ritual is profound, educational and great deal of fun. In a Puja you will stand in a circle with other people and practice many different meditations with those in the group. Through these exercises you will gain a deep understanding of Tantric principles and practices in a safe atmosphere to assist you in going deeper in your private relationships.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles is giving away your choice of one of two of his awesome CD’s, “Intro to Tantra Practices and Principles” or “Beyond Beginner’s Tantra”, a Tantra Birthday gift to everyone who attends!  Plus, you can enter our drawing to win one of many educational Tantra products.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Kerry Churchill for more information about this Puja and our Beginners Weekend Seminars in the Santa Cruz Mountains of California ~ please invite your friends, and family!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Phone: 831.566.2113 &amp;#9829; Email: santacruz@sourcetantra.com &amp;#9829; Website: &lt;a href="http://www.sourcetantra.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.sourcetantra.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah Alchin, ACTE</member_name><member_id>7260814</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232422766000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Tantric Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tantrausa</urlname><id>1157501</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Tantra USA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231967946000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Famous New Age Vocalist, Sophia, will be singing at the Puja this Saturday!!</name><id>9524101</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-28800000</utc_offset><time>1232249400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tantrausa/events/9524101/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/c/1/global_4199313.jpeg</photo_url></item>