<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425R Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.484785</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-231-1111</phone><name>Roller World</name><city>Saugus</city><id>843513</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.019189</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;There's an indoor roller skating rink in Saugus called Roller World. Admission is $7.50 which includes a roller skate rental. If you want to rent inline skates it's $3.00 extra. You can also bring your own roller or inline skates.&amp;nbsp; Usually they are only open until 4:00 p.m. on Sundays, but since Monday is the holiday they are open later.&amp;nbsp; It's usually not crowded at this time and there will be less children.&amp;nbsp; Afterward if people are interested we can get Sunday dinner at Kowloon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always try to organized T-accessible events and even though this is in Saugus there is a bus route that travels nearby. You can log onto www.mbta.com and use the address above for details. It's Sunday so the bus may not run often so if people want to try to carpool&amp;nbsp;put it in your comment when you RSVP. For those of you driving, it's on the south bound side of Route 1 behind Honey Baked Hams. If you miss that entrance from Route 1 you can also reach the parking lot from the KFC or Taco Bell parking lots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm only allowing one guest.&amp;nbsp; If you need to bring more, have them sign up for the group.&amp;nbsp; This is also a joint event with Social Fun.&amp;nbsp; If your plans change, please update your RSVP.&amp;nbsp; Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dee&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside front entry way on the left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dee</member_name><member_id>4101956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330281590000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Inline / Roller / Ice Skaters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-inline-roller-ice-skating</urlname><id>569309</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Skating</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328121327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indoor Roller Skating &amp; Dinner at Kowloon</name><id>50582512</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329691500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-inline-roller-ice-skating/events/50582512/</event_url></item>