<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Title: THE 2ND HALF, 2007: MARKETS AND TOP TEN PICKS, ARTHUR R HOGAN III, DIRECTOR OF GLOBAL EQUITY PRODUCTS, JEFFERIES &amp;amp; CO&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: As we move forward into the second half of 2007 markets continue to move up, despite higher crude prices, interest rates, the specter of subprime mortgage defaults and a saturated real estate market. Art Hogan will give us his comprehensive global markets overview as well as his Top Ten Picks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio, Arthur R Hogan III&lt;br /&gt;Art Hogan has been Director of Global Equity Products since 2004. He joined Jefferies in 1998 as an account executive on the institutional equity desk, and served as Chief Market Analyst and Regional Manager for Jefferies? Boston Office. Prior to joining Jefferies, Mr. Hogan spent several years on the institutional equity trading desk at Morgan Stanley and served as Head of Institutional Equity Sales at Dean Witter. From 1984 to 1993, Mr. Hogan was Vice President of Fidelity?s Capital Markets Division during which time he spearheaded Fidelity?s floor brokerage operation at the Boston Stock Exchange.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Hogan appears regularly on business news programs including CNN, MSNBC, Bloomberg-TV, Reuters TV, and CNBC, frequently serving as guest host on ?Squawk Box?, and is regularly quoted in The Wall Street Journal, The New York Times and Financial Times. Mr. Hogan provides objective, informative analysis on the general economy, market volatility and corporate data in a candid, straightforward manner. On average Mr. Hogan appears in the media approximately every business day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Hogan received a Bachelor?s Degree from the University of Vermont in 1983, where he majored in Economics and Political Science.  Mr. Hogan serves on the Boston Stock Exchange Board of Governors, Boston Option Exchange Board, and Boston Security Traders Association Board, as well as a number of community-related organizations, and has been selected several times as one of Irish America Magazine?s ?Wall Street 50? honorees. Mr. Hogan is married with two children and currently resides in Duxbury, Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PREMEETING EVENT STARTING AT 6:00&lt;br /&gt;Bob Podd's Tom OBrien Trading Methodologies&lt;br /&gt;Starting at 6:00, Bob Podd will lead a session of Tom OBrien trading methodologies. The topics will include: Fibonacci retracements and expansions, individual stock and market trends by benchmarking volume, target prices and proper entry points, plus other topics included in the book Timing the Trade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The agenda for the meetup will be:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 6:50 Bob Podd's premeeting session (see above)&lt;br /&gt;7:00 - 8:00 Meeting Starts with Fred Sears's Q&amp;amp;A, Stockpicks&lt;br /&gt;8:00            Feature Presentation by Art Hogan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186324396000</updated><rating><average>4.78999996185</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>51</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182989095000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Investor's Business Daily July Meetup</name><id>5945303</id><headcount>62</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185404400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/5945303/</event_url></item>