<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Announcing an opportunity to work with Socializing for Justice as an Organizer Intern! This is an amazing learning experience and we're hoping to find the right person who shares our passion for social change and has a willingness to learn more about organizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The description is below, anyone interested should send their resume and a brief statement of interest (cover letter) to SoJust's co-organizer &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/suggestion/"&gt;Robbie Samuels&lt;/a&gt; - robbie@robbiesamuels.com. Position starts in late January or early February and ends in June. Interviews scheduled on a rolling basis until position filled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please share this with your friends. &lt;em&gt;You do not have to be a student to apply.&lt;/em&gt; If you are a student, we'll work with you if you're able to receive credit. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE ORGANIZER INTERN - WINTER/SPRING 2013 Jan-June &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Socializing for Justice (SoJust) is a grassroots Boston-based group that hosts fun social events twice a month to bring together like-minded individuals working for justice as a means of building a stronger, cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community, network and movement. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. Co-organizers are looking for an intern to assist in all facets of their work to implement the vision of SoJust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity for someone who wants to learn about organizing and movement building in a very tangible way. Join us and learn more about using in person and online social networking to create social change. &lt;strong&gt;You'll also be introduced to great connectors in Boston's progressive community - great resources for when you're looking for your next internship or job!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The responsibilities and opportunities of the organizer intern would include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Co-hosting SoJust events; set up, greeting, networking, and break down &lt;br /&gt;

 2) Posting events on the web and around town to ensure visibility of SoJust in a wide range of communities &lt;br /&gt;

 3) Assisting with maintaining and growing SoJust's online web calendars and venue databases &lt;br /&gt;

 4) Manage @SoJust's twitter account, including scheduling tweets and responding to @replies &lt;br /&gt;

 5) Representing SoJust at outreach events throughout Boston &lt;br /&gt;

 6) Monitoring media coverage of SoJust and maintaining SoJust's press contacts database &lt;br /&gt;

 7) Cultivating skills to live the SoJust vision and becoming a great social networker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The ideal candidate has a strong desire to learn the fundamentals of organizing for social change and preferably some knowledge of identity and oppression issues, the ability to take direction, show &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;initiative and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; follow through in a dynamic environment is a must.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Excellent attention to detail and a willingness to ask questions are also critical.  Strong communication skills are required, as are demonstrated proficiency with email and web research.  Ongoing training, supervision and mentorship will be provided; dress code and work environment are casual.**Work hours and location are determined by intern with the exception of scheduled events and meetings.**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours: position is part time and unpaid 20 hours a week.  Occasional evenings, flexible schedule, and dependability are a must. $20 monthly stipend provided to cover cost of meals at outreach events and meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Justice, &lt;br /&gt;

 Robbie&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robbie Samuels &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust Co-Founder &amp;amp; Co-Organizer&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Send your resume and cover letter to robbie@robbiesamuels.com</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessica Critcher</member_name><member_id>46812122</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362039235000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358860665000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Apply to be our next Organizer Intern!</name><id>100805442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362027600000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/100805442/</event_url></item>