<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This time, we're going to try a TV series, appropriate for the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come visit the 360 State Street Screening Room for a showing of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coupling: Season 1&lt;/strong&gt; (British Comedy Show, 2000-2004)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starring: Jack Davenport, Gina Bellman, Sarah Alexander, Kate Isitt, Ben Miles, and Richard Coyle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could Visit the &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0237123/"&gt;IMDB Page Here&lt;/a&gt;, and notice it's rated 9.1/10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AJ's Description: Coupling is a British Comedy who's prime targets are Relationships and Sex.&amp;nbsp; (No, it does not contain explicit&amp;nbsp;material that I recall.)&amp;nbsp; It is by far one of the most hilarious Television series I have ever seen.&amp;nbsp; It is actually pretty even sided, so guys and girls alike should enjoy.&amp;nbsp; You might even get a little insight into how the opposite sex thinks by watching this.&amp;nbsp; (Or some very silly ideas as well.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each episode is about 30 minutes long (includes no commercials) so if it's not your cup o' tea it will be easy to make an early exit in between episodes.&amp;nbsp; Also do not get it confused with the US version.&amp;nbsp; Much like with other well done UK comedies (i.e. "The Office") the US tried to make it's own version but failed miserably in this case, this British version is Excellent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I set the time for 7pm, but we will not start showing the DVD until shortly after 7:30. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Notes: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I have to limit RSVP's to 18 for theater size. There are NO Maybes allowed for this event, please only respond Yes if you're sure you can make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will need your full names&lt;/em&gt; if I don't already have (or remember) them &lt;em&gt;for the Concierge to let you in&lt;/em&gt;, and you may be asked for ID. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please either put your name in your RSVP or e-mail it to me.&lt;/span&gt; (If you live in the building just let me know that instead.)&amp;nbsp; If it's less than 24 hours before and we have a waiting list of people whom did send me the required info, well I'll just say I do not want to have to be mean here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list.&amp;nbsp; As the date aproaches you may automatically be added if someone backs out.&amp;nbsp; Just pleast still send me your name for the Concierge as a contingency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Notes:&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are instructions near the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7 pm.&amp;nbsp; If you don't mind a longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evenings (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street Starting at 4:30 or 5). 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only at $5 Daily Max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday, the entrance is on State street just to the right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297713697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>British Comedy can be Funny...</why><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296180803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Screening: "Coupling" Season 1</name><id>16337850</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297468800000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/16337850/</event_url></item>