<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>between Devens St &amp; Harvard St</address_2><address_1>83 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.373922</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 242-6009</phone><name>Tangierino</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>761029</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062762</lon></venue><fee><label>reservation fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Of all the gin joints, in all the towns in all the world, she had to walk into. . . Tangierinos?! &amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey, it's a lot quicker than a plane trip to Casablanca and you don't have to worry about terrorists along the way! And while Boston Restaurant Week is a great time to explore new restaurants, it can also be a wonderful way to return to a place you love but can't necessarily afford to go to frequently. Tangierino's, in Charlestown, is one of the latter as far as I'm concerned. It's got spicy, flavorful Morroccan cuisine and one of the more exotic atmospheres I've encountered in the greater Boston area. (Perhaps the occasional appearance of a belly dancer has something to do with that.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston restaurant week menu at Tangierino's is available only on week nights, and includes classic dishes like b'stila, harira soup, and tagines. But the regular menu will also be available for those who are feeling more adventurous. Perhaps we can compromise between the two and order a couple of additional dishes for group tasting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking at Tangierino's is a major stumbling block -- the narrow Charlestown streets that surround it are permit parking only, there's no parking lot, and the valet parking is pricey. However, I have an easy fix. . . we can meet at my office building, I will validate everyone's parking, and then we can head over there in one or two cars and share the valet fee. If it's a nice evening, we may even choose to walk. . . it's about 10 minutes or so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us. . . it could be the beginning of a beautiful friendship :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. As usual, your $2 reservation fee is intended to show you are serious about coming and will be added to the tip for our table.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Either meet at my officek 2 Constitution Plaza, Charlestown, or go to the restaurant -- reservation will be in my name.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1251045465000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248530394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Restaurant Week dinner at Tangierino's</name><id>10954378</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250200800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/10954378/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/2/0/global_9843872.jpeg</photo_url></item>