<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,
Rob Suggested this Dance for an alternate to those who dont like the Chowderpot or want to try something new.

But some can go here and to the Pot, go to both, be a doppelganger, a 2 timer and play two partners at once at two locations, play the increased Blondie odds,or the hot guys odds, or is it odd guys,whatever,its another option for you..

Ladies if your dateless, you might have a better chance of getting guys numbers here without even asking, they are really HOT for you. But they are of good quality compared to some of Chowder Pot men.

Guys, your are on your own, Good Luck.

The Chowder Pot its not a date getting event.(per se),its us as a safe small group dancing with each other, you can if you are interested invite anyone standing with their hands deep in their pocket to the group. Im not shaking hands with them if it looks like their pockes were cut out.
AL-r 

Ok From Rob:
FYI: This rare "Single Event" dance is the same evening as the Chowder Pot ConnTacts dance you've posted.  It's less expensive, likely the drinks will be less expensive as it's not a high-priced bar (I'd guess he's bringing in his own wine, beer, etc. to sell at a nominal price), SINGLES oriented, and, I'd suspect, less crowded and noisy.  The Chowder Pot dances are going on all the time and ConnTacts have frequent dances in the area, too.  As such, you may want to consider this dance instead.

Dancing is not my strong suit, and I may or may not go to either one, but just making you aware of it for you to decide which is best for you and your group.  It's open to all, not just Single Event paid members, for the same price, but only advertised to singles, I assume, as such, far fewer "couples" than at the Chowder Pot...

more "available"  "blondies" for you to hunt down!  

I heard they had a very good turn out  afew months ago when they had their first dance there and he typically puts out a pretty good buffet.
- Rob

 AL-r ; OH NO, I dont want to hunt them..just tease them and kiss them....Hmm i better be more attracted to Dark Hair and/or Dark eyes Ladies more in the future..

==
From: 
To: "The Single Event" 
Subject: DANCE &amp; MIXER!! Friday September 28th - The Officers' Club of CT - State Armory Hartford - 6:30 to Midnight - A Very Special Event!!
Date: Thu, 13 Sep 2007 10:03:23 -0400

A Singles Dance and Mixer... hosted by The Single Event
Come and enjoy a very special evening at The Officers' Club of CT
Friday ~ September 28th ~ 6:30 to Midnight
Meet &amp; Mingle/Buffet 6:30 to 8:00 PM ~ Cash Bar
Dancing 8:00 to Midnight ~ DJ
Admission 14. ~ By Reservation ~ Casual Attire

The Officers' Club of CT
State Armory ~ 360 Broad Street ~ Hartford
Corner of Broad Street and Capitol Avenue
The entrance is the door located to the right of the Armory's main entrance.
It is not unusual to hear the Officers' Club described as "The best kept secret in Hartford."
The building has most recently been named to the distinctive National Register of Historic Places.
Mogen light granite was used to form the exterior walls; the same stone used for the Cathedral of St. John the Divine in New York City. The building is an outstanding example of Classical Revival architecture.
&lt;a href="http://www.ctofficersclub.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.ctofficersclub.com&lt;/a&gt;

Singles Dance &amp; Mixer - The Officers Club of CT
360 Broad Street - State Armory
Hartford CT 06103
9/28/2007- Friday- 6:30 to Midnight
Event Cost: $14.00

PARKING: Parking is available in front of the Armory after 4:30 PM (barrier arm must be up). Parking is also available on the driveway leading to the parking garage entrance... And behind the Armory. Parking is also available in the parking lot on Capitol Avenue, across from the Armory.

DIRECTIONS:
Coming from the West on I-84: Take the Capitol Avenue Exit # 48 (bear right- Asylum Avenue exit is to the left). At the end of the ramp (light) turn right onto Capitol Avenue. The Legislative Office Building (LOB) will be on your right. Take first right into driveway. Armory is on your left just past the stop sign.

Coming from the East on I-84: Take the Asylum Street Exit # 48. At the end of the ramp (light) turn right and then bear left onto Farmington Avenue (sharp right will be Asylum Avenue). At the first light turn left onto Broad Street (YWCA is on the corner). Continue straight through next set of lights (highway entrance). The Armory is down the hill on left - turn left into driveway just before the next traffic light. The Armory is on your left and the Legislative Office Building (LOB) is in front of you.

Coming North on I-91: Follow signs for the I-84 West Exit to Waterbury (will be a left exit off I-91). At end of exit, there will be two sets of lights. Continue straight through the lights, but stay to your left - entrance to I-84 West. Follow I-84 from the East direction above.

Coming South on I-91: Follow signs for the I-84 West Exit to Waterbury. Follow I-84 from the East directions above</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191191445000</updated><rating><average>3.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189706433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Alternate Dance Choice from the Chowder Pot Dances</name><id>6352636</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191018600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6352636/</event_url></item>