<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 tremont st</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.347540</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6174267387</phone><name>doggie day</name><city>Boston</city><id>200308</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068560</lon></venue><fee><label>Suggested Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>or what you feel is right</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The December Meet-Up will be held at Doggie Day in the South End.  Due to other meet-ups, we will be meeting from 10 am until noon.  Because this is an indoor location, it is very important that you RSVP correctly - number of people and dogs, whether or not you will make it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, even though the venue is free, Doggie Day is requesting that members of all Meet-ups being hosted at their facility bring donations from the Boston MSPCA Wishlist.  The group that supplies the most donations will win a party at Doggie Day!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The link to the wishlist is:  &lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/site/PageServer?pagename=ACAC_BostonHomepage" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope everyone can make it!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancellation procedure: If it is raining, too hot, too cold, etc. a cancellation notice will be sent via email and posted on the meetup website 2 hours prior to the meetup time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: Meetup.com charges each group a $15 a month meetup fee. This is a GROUP fee and if not paid, our Boston French Bulldog meetups, would not exist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The organizer is in charge of paying this fee every month. It would be greatly appreciated if at each meetup, each member can submit a donation that goes towards the monthly $15 fee. Give $1, give $10. If at the end of the meetup, the organizer has not collected enough to meet the $15, she will pay the difference. If she receives more than $15, the extra would go towards the next meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing everyone there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to allow payment by PayPal, I had to put a minimum &amp;quot;Suggested Donation.&amp;quot;  This is just to cover the meetup.com fee.  You can give whatever you feel is appropriate.  The cost is $15 per month, so you don't have to give every month either.  Whatever works for you.  And you can do it through PayPal or at the MeetUp.  Hope this helps!! &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166468642000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1163876753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston French Bulldog December Meetup</name><id>5276970</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1166281200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/5276970/</event_url></item>