<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Leslee mentioned this place to me and I agree with her that this a great place to take the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Train map and description at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newtonconservators.org/14hemlock.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newtoncons...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A National Historic Landmark, the handsome stone bridge contains the Sudbury Aqueduct, with a pedestrian walk on top. Visitors standing under the arch can make a fine echo and view the deep river gorge, waterfall, and steep hemlock-covered banks. Spectacular views atop the bridge.  We are meeting at the Newton parking lot rote 9/Ellis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HISTORY:&lt;br /&gt;1600s  English settlers knew the Ponkapoag Indians built a fish weir here to trap fish in the weir's branches, catch fish from canoes, and smoke the fish on the river banks.&lt;br /&gt;1700s  Grist mill, saw mill, fulling mill, snuff mills, and wire mill were built nearby.&lt;br /&gt;1877  Echo Bridge built by Boston Water Works as the second largest masonry arch in the U. S.&lt;br /&gt;1895  Acquired by Metropolitan District Commission (MDC) for Metropolitan Park System, one of its first purchases.&lt;br /&gt;1984  MDC water system, including Echo Bridge, taken over by newly created Massachusetts Water Resources Authority (MWRA). MDC still manages Hemlock Gorge.&lt;br /&gt;2003  MDC becomes part of Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR).&lt;br /&gt;2006  Echo Bridge was briefly closed to pedestrians due to concern about safety of the railings. The bridge was soon reopened after temporary fencing was installed. The MWRA and city officials are seeking funding for permanent repairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fresh City&lt;br /&gt;241 Needham St&lt;br /&gt;Newton, MA 02464&lt;br /&gt;(617) 244-7071&lt;br /&gt;www.freshcity.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My cell phone number is 617 3190789</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Luba</member_name><member_id>3354277</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208871682000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>we are awesome</why><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207524144000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hemlock Gorge Reservation</name><id>7687372</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208615400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7687372/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/1/1/global_3715041.jpeg</photo_url></item>