<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's back! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a pot luck for those that enjoy Bollywood movies.  Please bring something to munch on and share.  This is not Indian food themed, so don't feel like you have to bring Indian food (although it is yummy and I won't say no!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those that have been to my house:  We have redone somethings and will be hanging out in the basement now.  Sometimes it gets cold.  If you are one of those that gets cold easily, bring an extra sweater.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've tended to notice that we have gone off the beaten path of a bollywood movie.  I would like to try and get back to it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is what we have watched so far.  There is one movie missing that we had watched in October.  I don't remember the name.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movies:&lt;br /&gt;Saawariya &lt;br /&gt;Bhoot &lt;br /&gt;Hum Tum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please explore the &amp;quot;view instantly&amp;quot; version of netflix to get some ideas on what you may want to watch!!  I can watch items on my tv from the internet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;There will not be a car in the driveway.. please use the driveway!  Let yourself in.  You do not have to take your shoes off cause there are a bunch of shoes by the door!  I will make signs to tell you how to get to my basement.  Its really easy, but there are stairs!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>i live here. (duh)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267574853000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263048536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bollywood Potluck</name><id>12268875</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267401600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/12268875/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/global_9344168.jpeg</photo_url></item>