<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>2010 French American Innovation Day&lt;br /&gt;When:              Monday, December 6, from 8:30 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Broad Institute            &lt;br /&gt;                        7 Cambridge Center&lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;Website:           &lt;a href="http://2010faid.france-science.org//objectives.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://2010faid.franc...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FAID 2010 is a high-level seminar whose primary objective is to take stock of recent scientific and translational developments concerning Alzheimer's disease. The event is intended for French and American practitioners, researchers, doctoral candidates, and fellows with a common purpose: to learn about the work of their colleagues, and to strike up a conversation or even a collaboration designed to accelerate the progress of knowledge and therapeutic solutions. During each session, two experts on the topic, one French and one American, will describe their research and the status of their work, starting with the first session dedicated to genetics and finishing with session six on biopharmaceutical perspectives. Organized annually for the past 8 years by the Office for Science and Technology of the French Embassy in the United States (Boston office), this French-American seminar introduces an innovative way of addressing a topic. The Massachusetts Life Sciences Center is an organizational partner of this event. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291646748000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287448902000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 French American Innovation Day</name><id>15153295</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291642200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15153295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>