<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>FREE video night in Nashua!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to forward this announcement around to friends who are interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join our &lt;b&gt;Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/home.php?#/group.php?gid=159949076301" target="_blank"&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;follow us on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mv911truth" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter: mv911truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This month in Nashua:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://collapsemovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Collapse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'd be hard-pressed to find a movie that channels the anxieties of our time with the power and terror of the documentary Collapse. For 82 riveting minutes, Michael Ruppert, a former Los Angeles cop who became a rogue investigative reporter and author, sits in what looks like a brick bunker and talks about where he thinks the United States is now headed. It's not a pretty picture, but it is not a naive one either. The grippingly articulate Ruppert is like Noam Chomsky as a wry pundit of doom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2006, he predicted the current economic crisis, and his startlingly detailed foresight seizes your attention. So you'd better believe that you're sitting up and listening when he starts to talk about ''peak oil'' — i.e., the likelihood that most of the planet's oil reserves have already been eaten up. According to Ruppert, the ''economic crisis'' is more than a bad patch; it's the finally visible symptom of a greater underlying instability. And what's coming? A society, he says, that will have to reimagine how it lives if it wants to survive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Collapse was directed by Chris Smith (The Yes Men), who interviewed Ruppert for 14 hours and does a superb job of editing his words into a dramatic cautionary monologue. You may want to dispute Ruppert, but more than that you'll want to hear him, because what he says — right or wrong, prophecy or paranoia — takes up residence in your mind. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Entertainment Weekly&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also at this meeting:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Announcements to follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring your blank DVDs&lt;/b&gt; to the meeting and be sure to get a copy of each video we screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We may have time for other short videos, so bring your favorites to suggest to others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord. The 4th Tuesday is open for a more northern meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetings are free, but we appreciate donations to continue building our video library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 7:00&lt;/b&gt; if you can, in order to help set up the healthy snacks and beverages (that you bring to share with others - a gift of a box of tea for Gene's inventory would be appreciated) and enjoy the pre-meeting networking. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7:15 and then on to the video screening right after that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.com" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Forward this invitation to everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Write us&lt;/b&gt; at MerrimackValley911Truth@gmail.com with suggestions for next month.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288798978000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270557926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Collapse</name><id>jmbknynpbdb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288738800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/15161319/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/8/global_18943800.jpeg</photo_url></item>