<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Essex Marian off Rte 133</address_2><address_1>35 Dodge St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01929</zip><lat>42.634550</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(800) 748 -</phone><name>Essex River Cruises &amp; Charters</name><city>Essex</city><id>403346</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.779100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE - Essex River Cruise is sending a boat to pick us up. We will depart from Periwinkle's - UPDATE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's your chance to take the last riverboat cruise of the year.&lt;br /&gt;The Periwinkle's lunch may be full but there is room for you on the 3:30 PM Essex River Cruise.&lt;br /&gt;Pack your own lunch or pick something up in town to munch on while we cruise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Essex River Cruise Cost: $23 for adults $10 for children&lt;br /&gt;Experience up close the Choate Island film site of &amp;quot;The Crucible&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Witches of Eastwick&amp;quot; on a nearly two hour narrated cruise. Enjoy the spectacular beauty of New England's famous fall foliage at its peak. &lt;a href="http://www.essexcruises.com/narrated.html" target="_blank"&gt;Essex River Cruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Stroll along the streets of Essex from 5:30 PM until 6:00 PM visiting antique shops, and historical sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.essexshipbuildingmuseum.org/collections&amp;amp;research.html" target="_blank"&gt;Essex History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings.&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of everyone's time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay your way.  &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO after 11:30am Saturday October 20th, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.  &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the venue's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me (Tonya) at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                   If do not contact me it will be counted as if you NO-SHOWED 3 times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194491459000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192594145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Essex River Cruise - ONLY</name><id>6564355</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192995000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6564355/</event_url></item>