<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>256 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.371742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 647-4000</phone><name>Watch City Brewery</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669403</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236840</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Yep, you read that right - bacon rauchbier*, a/k/a bacon beer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch City Brewery is at it again with another envelope pushing, interesting beer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They are actually brewing two versions - one in a cask, which will be available for a limited time only, beginning 6 PM on January 5, 2010, and the other, which will be available on tap starting on January 14, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Aaron and Dave, the brewers at Watch City&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cask version&lt;/b&gt; is &amp;quot;a smoked Brown ale with the real essence of Benton's Bacon from Tennessee! We carefully and cleanly extracted all the flavor of this cooked bacon and put it into our cask version of this brew!  And &lt;b&gt;the tap version&lt;/b&gt; will have &amp;quot;a sweeter, smokier flavor with 3 times the essence of the bacon from the first one.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Either way, they say the aftertaste of the Rauchbier reminds them of &amp;quot;a campfire breakfast... the slight smokiness of the malt, a hint of vanilla with the essence of the hickory flavored bacon all meld in your mouth in a subtle, full breakfast fashion ... who can say no to bacon at breakfast so why not in a beer???&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, I will email my cell number to all yes and maybe RSVPs the afternoon of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*what is rauchbier?  It's an old German beer style, usually dark and not unlike Oktoberfestbier. According to Beer Advocate, the traditional method of brewing involves drying green malts over an open fire of beech wood, giving a &amp;quot;unique smokiness&amp;quot; flavor that tastes of &amp;quot;spiced, smoked meat&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263686893000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262651655000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bacon Rauchbier Night</name><id>12222463</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263513600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/12222463/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/5/global_12506405.jpeg</photo_url></item>