<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>212 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.402157</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-776-7890</phone><name>Sabur Restaurant</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.126686</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  So I know everyone is crazy (or at least going crazy) with the upcoming holiday season, so I thought we could take a moment out to breath and enjoy some great food and fabulous company. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Join me at Sabur - a Mediteranean restaurant that I have heard fabulous things about! The menu looks great! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Look forward to seeing you there.  ----  Marie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These MEMBER GUIDELINES added  by Tonya, were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly so we can be seated together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with comment about your circumstances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If brunch is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. *If there is an overwhelming response, there is a possibility our reservation is increased or another seating arranged.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I must change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, without an explanation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's which are staffed based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call the organizer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please, rate the event and venue by completing the post event survey.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a reservation under my name.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1230491139000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229014668000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at Sabur</name><id>9321598</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229875200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/9321598/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/d/global_6535197.jpeg</photo_url></item>