<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone,&lt;br /&gt;   We have a change of plan for the Conscious Movie Night. Since &amp;quot;Padre Pio&amp;quot; seems to be unavailable for us at the moment, we are going to view another film instead: &amp;quot;What Dreams May Come&amp;quot;. It is a visually amazing movie (delightful to watch just for that), but more than that, it gives us some good food for consideration regarding how we are the creators of our own state of heaven or hell.  See below an excerpt from a review on Amazon, from someone who liked this movie very much. I welcome you all to join us!&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stellar film and visual effects!, February 12, 2001 &lt;br /&gt;By  D. Litton &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is such a profound sense of drama, magic and emotion behind the story in &amp;quot;What Dreams May Come,&amp;quot; a film based on the novel by Richard Matheson.  Matheson's visions of heaven and hell are magnificently realized here, in an austentatious and elegant scope of visual and auditory imagery that jumps right for your eyes onscreen.&lt;br /&gt;The movie begins with the chance meeting of two American tourists traveling in Switzerland. Soon after, Chris and Annie become inseperable, and after their wedding, they bear two children. Many years later, Ian and Marie are killed in a car collision, leaving their parents distraught yet overcoming. Another couple of years later, Chris dies in a car accident as well, on his way to celebrate the &amp;quot;Double D&amp;quot; anniversary of his wife's emotional recovery from their childrens' deaths. This begins his trip into heaven, which is rocky at first during his attempts to console his living wife, then graduating into his acceptance of his immortality and ascemding into heaven, which turns out to be the creation of his own thoughts and settings. When he realizes that he is not completely happy without Annie, he becomes depressed, so it is no surprise that when Annie commits suicide and is sent to hell, he readies himself to rescue his wife from her emotional confines that keep her in her prison of eternal darkness.   ...&lt;br /&gt;This film is one of those movies that showcases the possibilities for filmmaking in the future. Really, when you think about it, there is no way that the movie could have been made thirty years ago and still have the same impact as it does now. The settings and scenery play the most important role of the movie, for they provide the reason for the emotion and action that affects our characters. ...&lt;br /&gt;Heaven is elegantly portrayed in this film, and is done so with a new twist: that each person has their own private heaven created in the image of their own personal desires and thoughts. Chris's heaven is based on the paintings of his wife... This is one of the most incredible film achievements ever, taking us to a special place that is warm, inviting, and personifies every thought we, as an audience, have ever had for beauty and vision. &lt;br /&gt;Hell is given a truly horrifying and intense treatment, displaying visions of suffering as well as the personal and emotional pain of life that haunts us all. Somewhat like the way in which Heaven is created, Hell is seen as a persons's &amp;quot;life gone wrong,&amp;quot; which allows for the creation of their pain-driven eternity. &lt;br /&gt;There is a unique chemistry between the two leads that carries on the film's emotion and power. Robin Williams is charming, humorous and bold as Chris Nielsen, and through his acting and talent, he is able to make us believe in the love that Chris holds for Annie. Annabella Sciorra is moving as Annie, embodying all of the emotions and grief that set the stage for the second half of the story. When the two are together onscreen, they are happy and in love, and we buy it because they make it appear very authentic. Cuba Gooding, Jr. plays the angel that brings Chris to heaven, doing well in his performance of helping Chris through his struggle to realize his death. Max von Sydow, whose part is not as big as others he has had, is the tracker who takes them all to hell, and his words of wisdom keep the film's informative angle moving. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What Dreams May Come&amp;quot; will go down in history as one of the most innovative and spectacular films ever made, full of ambition and inspiration. In its story, we are taken on a journey of the human heart, as well as a striking vision of what may lie in store for everyone under God's eye.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347529000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232637362000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Night:   What Dreams May Come</name><id>9577797</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233360000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9577797/</event_url></item>