<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>124 Temple Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.305347</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 562-2327</phone><name>Black Bear Saloon</name><city>New Haven</city><id>270466</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.927917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>My birthday this year falls on a Friday, so I figured I'd celebrate in true NHC style: with a bar/pub-crawl!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at Black Bear Saloon at 7pm SHARP and drink for an hour. The first five people get wristbands to drink FREE for an hour (some Black Bear restrictions apply, don't forget to tip the barkeep!) so be sure to find me fast!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bar list is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Black Bear Saloon, 7-8p (first 5 people to find me get FREE drinks for an hour)&lt;br /&gt;Richter's, 8-9p&lt;br /&gt;Pacifico, 9-10p&lt;br /&gt;BAR, 10-11p ($1 well drinks and domestic beers, 10-11p, with $6 cover after 10pm)&lt;br /&gt;Miya's Sake Bar, 11p-12a (I'm in negotiations with Bun for drink specials!)&lt;br /&gt;Rudy's, 12a-? (for Frites and last call)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;After 7pm (officially), you may park at the Yale parking lot on Howe St, just past the intersection with Elm &amp;amp; Howe. The pizza place on the corner of Elm and Howe (Pizza at the Brick Oven) is right next to the Yale lot, and diagonally across the street from Rudy's. Park there if you plan to sober up at Rudy's! But don't be late to Black Bear. Street parking is a safe bet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pub crawls are a great time, and you DON'T HAVE TO DRINK to come and have fun! Load up at Black Bear, then coast through the rest of the night! Come celebrate with me, and I promise you'll have fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who come to the bar crawl (to at least 2 bars) will receive a private invitation to a special beach bonfire party (location is off the beaten path, and the neighbors are cool) ...and I guarantee you won't want to miss that! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friendly FYI: those who chronically RSVP to NHC events with a &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; will be shot. Just come to an event already! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're the 6th person who arrives at Black Bear Saloon, and you want to drink free there, you can compete with the 7th person to arrive for a wristband, which I will save for this purpose :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Present-giving is optional. Having fun (or buying me drinks) is not.&lt;br /&gt;Eric is the contact for this event: 860-214-9361&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190308239000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189129873000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eric's Birthday Bar Crawl 7pm Black Bear Saloon</name><id>6312108</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189810800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6312108/</event_url></item>