<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy (est. 4+ miles...whatever the whole group is okay with)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shoreline Hike @ North Quabbin!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/6/4/event_54936452.jpeg" width="360" height="270" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The road from Gate 35 follows the shoreline for 2 miles before heading inland.  How far we hike depends on the group that attends...I just need a good walk after the last 2 weeks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is easy for the first part. It's an old dirt road, and completely flat along the shore. If we continue into the woods, it will be hilly. It's up to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a lunch or some snacks, and enough to drink...Cheryl and I haven't decided how long we want to hike, just that we want to get the heck out there! There will be rain off and on, so please dress for the weather with a raincoat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Regulations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* No swimming or wading. (Public drinking water supply.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* No animals. (Same reason.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* "Carry in, carry out." (Take your trash with you when you leave; no trash cans.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Do not remove items from the reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Do not block gates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East, take 122 North, or from the South, take 37 or 37A North onto 122 North. "Old N Dana Rd" is several miles further on the left. (You can see "S Athol Rd" further on, on the right.) If you pass between North and South Spectacle ponds (water on both sides of the road, some marsh grasses on the south side), you have gone too far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the West or North, take 202 to 122 South. After you pass between North and South Spectacle ponds, look for "S Athol Rd" on your left. Slow down, because "Old N Dana Rd" is coming up on the right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gate 35 is at the end of Old Dana Rd. Do not block the gate. Whoever gets there first, back a car length or two.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a white Dodge Stratus. Park on either side at the end of the road. Don't block the gate.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337137987000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336969683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rain? So what! Let's hike Quabbin Reservoir from Gate 35!</name><id>64690102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337094000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/64690102/</event_url></item>