<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 1 1 Bolyston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>7 1 1 </name><city>Boston</city><id>450422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi guys, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope this event will be even better than the last one.  For this event 7 one 1 is not charging any cover, if you guys come in from 10.30 - 11:00 pm.  The event will take take place on December 28, 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first meetup had about 3 members attend (Thanks to those of you who came!), the place was a little dead until about 11.45 pm.  The crowd was pretty decent after 11.45 pm, considering it was very close to xmas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However for the next meetup we hope even more members will rsvp.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So for 2008, we hope to have events regularly once a week at 7 one 1 (or some other venue if that changes) .  Has our membership for this meetup grows, we will have more events per week.  For example, we might have a pool &amp;amp; bowling night at Jillians, or an thursday night happy hour mixer.  We hope to be consistent at least will the number of events.  We have seen meetups where they meetup every one or two months, while that maybe good for a book club, but for social events, they need to be more frequent, because everyone has a different schedule of when they can attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That be said, we hope you guys will come out this friday, for a after xmas mixer.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you guys have a happy holiday! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venue: 7 one 1&lt;br /&gt;Venue fee: none , from 10.30pm -11:00pm, please rvsp, so we can put you on the guess list.&lt;br /&gt;Venue meeting place: &amp;quot;This meetup will take place near the sushi bar area of 7 one 1.  When you walk down the stairs it is the bar to your left.  Its obviously the smaller bar of the 2 bars that are in 7 one 1.  Also there is a huge fish tank right near the bar. &amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Venue Park: Parking always available on newbury street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T: Green Line to Copley Square&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This meetup will take place near the sushi bar area of 7 1 1.  When you walk down the stairs it is the bar to your left.  Its obviously the smaller bar of the 2 bars that are in 7 1 1.  Also there is a huge fish tank right near the bar.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>highrollerbostongroup</member_name><member_id>5803712</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199231900000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Our real goal of this meetup, is just meet like minded young professionals in fun, relaxed atmosphere.  A way to extend your current network of people.</why><group><who>Night Lifers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonnights</urlname><id>860845</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Nights</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198515855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AFTER XMAS MEETUP YOUNG PROFESSIONALS</name><id>6963169</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198899000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonnights/events/6963169/</event_url></item>