<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>32 Vassar Street</address_2><address_1>Ray and Maria Stata Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building 32 Room 155</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1119883</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us to hear from three thought leaders in the Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing field.   Note room change to Stata Center 32-155 (across the hall).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This panel discussion will explore contrarian views about Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing solutions. There has been much hype about the technologies and recently some questions regarding the pace of adoption. Ten years ago there were only a few vendors offering Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing technologies -- today there are thousands of hardware, software and service providers. Which ones deliver value? What is the reality of RFID deployments? Who is getting traction? What are the benefits of improved visibility without the need for human intervention? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many other questions will be addressed during this event including:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is the current state of the Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing market? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What are the primary impediments to mass adoption?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is RFID such a significant competitive advantage causing some groups to hide their successes?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What's missing today?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How should adopters of RFID solutions best organize?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How should the RFID and associated industries get organized?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What role should industry and government groups play?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What are groups like GS1 and AIM Global doing effectively? Where are they falling short?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Where's the best place for end users to SEE a comprehensive array of real world Auto-ID &amp;amp; Sensing solutions in an unbiased setting?   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come ask your own questions to our panel of experts.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PANELISTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ann Grackin, CEO, ChainLink Research&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more than two decades, Ann Grackin has been on the frontlines of the research and technology frontier, leading global strategies for Fortune 500 firms, with assignments in Asia, Europe and the North America. Ms. Grackin has been an innovator in Supply Chain and RFID with recent work on Supply Chain Risk, Global Trade and RFID strategies. Ms Grackin was an advisor to the Under Secretary of Defense for Logistics for over six years. She has a leadership position on the IEEE Critical Infrastructure Protection Committee, which advises the U.S. Congress on technology issues.  &lt;br /&gt;Ms. Grackin created Supply Chain Risk Management practice at Marsh &amp;amp; McLennan, where she consulted for Fortune 500 firms on supply chain risk issues. She was a Foundation Partner at Benchmarking Partners and led the Supply Chain practice. Subsequently, she served as Vice President of Supply Chain Strategy at AMR Research. At Digital Equipment Corporation, Ms. Grackin led the Supply Chain Management architecture program, and was Director of IT in Logistics and Manufacturing, including the implementation of  leading packages in use today. She is a popular speaker and writer on supply chain management best practices and technology. She is the Editor-in-Chief of Parallax View, an online supply chain management magazine read by over 300,000 executives. She volunteers her time to support professional development, teaching university executive-level programs at Penn State, University of Texas at their Center for Supply Chain Intelligence, Stanford and Wharton, as well as for supply chain industry organizations such as APICS, the Ontario Institute/Purchasing Managers of Canada (PMAC), the Council of Supply Chain Management Professionals (CSCMP) and other associations.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Russ Klein, Vice President, Aberdeen Technology Research Group&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Russ Klein is a Vice President and Director of Aberdeen's Technology Research Group. He has been covering emerging technologies at Aberdeen since 2006 including a focus on RFID and item serialization. Prior to Aberdeen, Klein founded several successful software companies developing global trade, e-commerce, knowledge discovery, and other systems. Recently, he served as senior engineer for Delfigo Corporation, a Boston-based startup that was selected to present at MIT's Entrepreneur Showcase in 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michael Liard, RFID Practice Director, ABI Research&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Liard provides ABI Research clients with strategic insight and analysis on the RFID market, based on a deep understanding of industry dynamics, market players, end-user applications, and enabling technologies. His research focuses on RFID equipment/hardware, RFID  software and services, and key vertical and application markets as well as biometrics and anti-counterfeiting. Mr. Liard has covered the RFID industry since 2000. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before joining ABI Research, Liard was practice director for AIDC/RFID at VDC Research (VDC), where he pioneered the company's RFID market research over a period of six years. He has authored more than 50 reports on RFID and AIDC-related topics, is a regular commentator for the industry press, and has been a speaker at dozens of conferences including RFID Journal Live!, RF Edge (formerly RFID World), CTST, AIM Global Summit, and UK Networking Forum. Prior to VDC, Liard worked at Accenture, where he was a Change Management Analyst in the firm’s Organization and Human Performance practices. He holds a BA in political science from Providence College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moderator: Tom Coyle&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom’s career focus has been to deliver wireless technology solutions for the supply chain, transportation. government and retail customers. As Vice President at Mark IV Industries Tom led business development efforts for new initiatives. Mark IV is a leading provider of RFID systems and is the largest toll tag manufacturer today, the maker of EZ-Pass transponders and readers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom led Sales &amp;amp; Marketing efforts for Matrics, Inc., a leading RFID hardware provider which was acquired by Symbol (now Motorola) in 2004. At Savi Technology (now Lockheed Martin), Tom was the Director of Strategic Alliances. Savi is a leading provider of active RFID hardware and software solutions. As director of business development at Texas Instruments, Tom led efforts for RFID and GPS-based tracking solutions. Tom held consulting and management positions at EG&amp;amp;G (Cambridge, MA) supporting efforts at the Volpe National Transportation Systems Center. He was a supply chain analyst for General Electric. He is a graduate of the U.S. Military Academy at West Point. He began his career as a test pilot and maintenance manager with an air cavalry unit in the U.S. Army. Tom was a founder and past President of the Kendall Square Learning Project, an adult literacy program based in Cambridge, MA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For registration, please visit &lt;a href="https://alum.mit.edu/smarTrans/public/Register.dyn?eventID=38584&amp;amp;groupID=298" target="_blank"&gt;https://alum.mit.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Coyle</member_name><member_id>10894197</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268863968000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MITRFID</urlname><id>1547070</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>MITEF of Cambridge RFID Circle (Auto-ID &amp; Sensing Solutions)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258687026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Research Analyst Panel for the Wireless World</name><id>11917225</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268690400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MITRFID/events/11917225/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/4/global_13059348.jpeg</photo_url></item>