<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>103 Terrace Hall Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.495970</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781)270-4800</phone><name>Guard Up! Family Swordsmanship</name><city>Burlington</city><id>1035029</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.224542</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/8/f/4/event_23023252.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Attack the Zombies! Kathy Sherman, from the New England Horror Meetup is planning on running an event at "Guard Up! Family Swordsmanship" in Burlington on Saturday, June 4th at 6:45 pm. It's twenty-five bucks each for "Humans vs Zombies". Humans -- that would be you, at least at first -- are armed with the provided nerf blasters. You are attempting to defend yourself from the oncoming zombie attack. If the zombies "vomit" on you, you get to choose if you wish to remain play as a Human, or if you want to join the Zombies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All who are interested must call up "Guard Up! Family Swordmanship" and pre-pay the twenty-five dollars before the event. Visa and Mastercard are accepted. There are only spots for 40 people. Please call Guard Up to make arrangements, then place *PAID* in your RSVP so Kathy can see how many Nerd Fun members have paid.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the New England Horror Meetup event page:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Horror-Group/events/17437469/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Horror-Group/events/17437469/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The New England Horror Meetup has done this once. Let's do it again. The Group had a blast!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;WHEN&lt;/strong&gt;: Saturday, JUNE 4TH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;TIME&lt;/strong&gt;: meet: 6:45 Shooting brains: 7:00 P.M.-8:30 DO NOT BE LATE!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Guard Up Fencing and Swordsmanship, 103 Terrace Hall Ave., Burlington, MA 01803&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;PHONE&lt;/strong&gt;: 781-270-4800&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;COST&lt;/strong&gt;: $25.00 YOU MUST PRE-PAY!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to reserve your spot&lt;/strong&gt;: Call Guard Up at 781-270-4800, and mention you want to reserve a spot for the Saturday June 4th Zombie Adventure, and pre-pay. After, go to the RSVP section of this page and mark down "*PAID*". &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. Maher will be at Guard Up Fencing and Swordsmanship at 6:30 pm early, and will be taping up red MEETUP signs pointing people in the room we will be gathering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the Guard Up site, taken from their Halloween Adventure site:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://guardup.com/birthday-parties-events/halloween-adventure/"&gt;http://guardup.com/birthday-parties-events/halloween-adventure/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;ZEE Corp Blog Entry 2034: While doing some repairs around the facility we stumbled upon an old trunk full of strange, grotesque relics. We&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to figure out exactly what these are. We decided to call in a few experts&amp;hellip; and that&amp;rsquo;s when people started disappearing. Now the trunk has been ransacked, and guests have reported seeing sickly-looking, stumbling figures around. We&amp;rsquo;re not completely sure what&amp;rsquo;s happening, but just to be on the safe side, we&amp;rsquo;re putting out the call for reinforcements. Join us! Help battle the brain eating undead; figure out why they are rising; and help put them down once and for all. The future of human kind depends on it!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Guard Up! Family Swordsmanship will be running two 1 hour highly interactive Zombie events designed for teens and adults. Participants will battle zombies with Nerf&amp;reg; Blasters (provided) and try to outwit the undead using special tools and information. Story line changes each week&amp;hellip; picking up where it left off".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video&lt;/strong&gt;: Zombie Invasion Promo for Guard Up! in Burlington, MA  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9a8Y09TYn0"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W9a8Y09TYn0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://guardup.com/directions/"&gt;http://guardup.com/directions/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Directions from I-95 North or Southbound:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take exit 32B. Bear right at the end of the exit ramp. Drive past the Burlington Mall then down a short incline to the intersection of Burlington Mall Road and Middlesex Turnpike. Proceed through traffic lights for just over a half mile and look for the intersection with Terrace Hall Ave on the right (where the Fire Department is). Take this right and drive past the Fire Department.&amp;nbsp; We are building #103 on the left.&amp;nbsp; Park in lot behind Guard Up and walk to the front entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>T.J. will be placing signs up leading from the main door to the room we are meeting in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307373887000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Where else can you attempt to defend yourself vs the Zombie Invasion?</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304088245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Human vs Zombies: Repel Zombie Horde with Nerf Blasters @ Guard Up in Burlington</name><id>17479462</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307227500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/17479462/</event_url></item>