<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>pp or $80 per couple</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please join Meetup member Winter Robinson for the second retreat in the Returning to Our Roots series.  For those of you new to permaculture design, Zone 00 is the &amp;quot;self.&amp;quot;  Sessions are designed to challenge your belief systems, &amp;quot;tweak&amp;quot; your connection to nature and, of course...listen to your inner guidance for health and clarity, and make something that is &amp;quot;practical.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This session will cover &amp;quot;things my grandmother would have taught:&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stop being squeamish and start being &amp;quot;practical&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Hear&amp;quot; what your physical body is telling you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Listen&amp;quot; everything is alive: plants, animal, mineral&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medicine and health&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making simple herbal remedies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is more information from Winter about these events....&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The process:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This highly experiential process is not about a new way of thinking, but a new way of being. Rather than thinking out of the box, participants are coached in being out of the box...the difference being one of experience. From being outside of the box, we gain a whole new perspective on the nature of reality. This requires complete relaxation of the body. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With soft music in the background, wearing your own headset, I gently lead you through a series of guided imagery exercises designed to help facilitate a state of deep relaxation. (Once relaxed, we can be observe our thoughts without following them or letting them take over. We can become aware of how our thoughts feed our fear, deny reality, and/or inhibit our creativity and inner wisdom.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The sheet mulch is laid, the garden is planted, the greenhouse opened up for the warm months.  Our new chicks are rapidly outgrowing their pen and our new turkey has made himself at home. It would seem I barely have time to think of an online class, or reflect on intuition, spirituality, or the state of the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But that is exactly what I have been doing. I've been pondering &amp;quot;just what is this time we've been waiting for, and what...if anything, do I do?&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I ask the questions: &lt;br /&gt;Just what does it mean to live sustainably?  Is it even possible? &lt;br /&gt;What do I need to be doing in order to live &amp;quot;comfortably&amp;quot; over the coming years? &lt;br /&gt;What is my intuition telling me about these times in which we are living? Could I be wrong? What if I'm right? &lt;br /&gt;Am I a victim or creator of my circumstances? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My time in the garden has brought me back to things I sense I have done before (perhaps in some other time, place or dimension): growing herbs, seeing devas, hearing plants, feeling at one with nature, having a sense of &amp;quot;place&amp;quot; in the scheme of it all. And I wonder, &amp;quot;What if we, as humans, develop a strong sense of reverence for where we live, not just our home, and the land we inhabit, but the planet?&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many, if not most of us, have developed a habit of avoiding things that need addressing. I certainly know that I have. I have developed defense mechanisms to help me avoid seeing the truth.  Until last summer, I ignored facts that were upsetting, and I colored the truth to myself (&amp;quot;It can't really be that bad,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;It won't happen in my lifetime). We all do this.  We do everything that we can to make things seem better than they are. In our mind we tell ourselves, &amp;quot;This is just a passing thing.  It will get better.&amp;quot; Or,&amp;quot;When X wins the election, my life will change for the better.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do this because we are human.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I believe that only as a collective will humanity  survive.  I also believe that, collectively, we share a creative genius that we can tap. I further believe that it is time we stop talking about intuition, spirit, the earth...and start doing.  By listening to and hearing our deepest truth, by having a desire to achieve something that matters to us, we are guided to roll up our sleeves, feel whatever we feel, face the truth directly and honestly, and get to work.    &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This summer and fall I will be holding two, one-half day retreats. I see these retreats as the beginning of a support network in which we will be there for one another in the coming times.  It is a way of building &amp;quot;community.&amp;quot;   If I need an onion and you need a cup of honey, we will exchange...just as our mothers and grandmothers did.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Winter Robinson is internationally recognized as an author, teacher, consultant and medical intuitive adept at facilitating the intuitive process, multi-sensory development and exploring human consciousness.     &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;A licensed therapist, she is the author of A Hidden Order: Uncover Your Life's Design,Intuitions: Seeing With Your Heart, and Remembering: A Gentle Reminder of Who You Are. Winter has also created a series of guided imagery CDs to help the listener with the reduction of stress and deepen the alliance with the source of inner wisdom. Visit Winter online at www.winterrobinson.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225112804000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214934548000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Returning to Our Roots Part 2, with Winter Robinson</name><id>8255092</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224939600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/8255092/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/global_4650293.jpeg</photo_url></item>