<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Evan, the organizer of Fashion 2010, planned the Designers Group on Tuesday, Aug. 3rd. to continue our theme of “selling”. I am making the SAME meetup, Aug. 3rd. for this group as well. Please, please remember that the Designers Group meetup is ONLY for DESIGNERS, because we do not have the space for all kinds of members, especially for both meetup groups to be involved. Thank you for respecting that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I thought it would spark some great discussion and learning for designers to have more specific details and decisions they must make  ahead of selling in order to be properly prepared. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Designers Susan Hurst and Lucy Chen, two meetup members and protégés from my Boston Design Lab, are just at the beginning of planning a business that will include selling their clothing designs. They will talk about the discussions we’ve had about the pros and cons of the present fashion market; the many design considerations for their target consumers (that they are collaborating on); fabric sourcing problems; the possibilities in production of “one-offs” versus mass production; and the all important costing versus market prices. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to a very exciting meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;Shirley, Assistant Organizer&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will greet them</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley Willett</member_name><member_id>1480973</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280927906000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279213850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Designers Group: “Preparing to Sell” , Aug, 3rd.</name><id>14112163</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280872800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/14112163/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/f/global_9836927.jpeg</photo_url></item>