<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Perseids is one of the best meteor showers to observe, producing up to 60 meteors per hour at their peak. This year's peak occurs on August 13 &amp;amp; 14, but you may be able to see some meteors any time from July 23 - August 22. The waxing gibbous moon will provide some interference in the evening, but after it sets, the morning hours should provide some spectacular viewing opportunities. The radiant point for this shower will be in the constellation Perseus. &lt;b&gt;Look to the northeast after midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign up and join the group at a camp out! This is what we call car camping, so you don't need to worry about backpacking your gear in for this one.  Its a casual affair, hike before or the morning after, I'll let you guys chose, but Mt Hale and Mt Zealand are across the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The US Forest Service has some developed campsites that we can use. There is a large open area and room for 15 campers/3 cars.  Your annual parking pass or $3 is your fee for this &amp;quot;no frills&amp;quot;: campsite. You guys are welcome to suggest a different one but these are nice and usually vacant. First come first serve,so if you can come early and secure the spot, it would be great. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must RSVP to see this location.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP and set up arrangments to meet</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250543763000</updated><rating><average>1.66999995708</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248382306000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Perseids  Meteor Shower Campout:: White Mountains</name><id>10943882</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250370000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10943882/</event_url></item>