<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>259 County Farm Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03820</zip><lat>43.218910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Strafford County Superior Court House</name><city>Dover</city><id>848630</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.936470</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The proposed increase of 2.85% for the 2009 Strafford County budget  &lt;br /&gt;will likely go challenged by some county delegates and those  &lt;br /&gt;organizations that lost their funding.  We will be communicating with  &lt;br /&gt;the delegation and urging them to adopt the proposed budget put forth  &lt;br /&gt;by the Strafford County Commission.  Yes, there are going to be staff  &lt;br /&gt;reductions and vacant positions that will go unfilled, but as we know,  &lt;br /&gt;this is happening to taxpayers being asked to pay this bill too.   &lt;br /&gt;There will also be some non-profit groups that will no longer receive  &lt;br /&gt;taxpayer money, but in these difficult times, these concessions simply  &lt;br /&gt;needed to be made to lesson the burden on the taxpayer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, we urge everyone to review this information and contact the NH  &lt;br /&gt;State Representatives that make up the Strafford County delegation to  &lt;br /&gt;let them know that you support the 2009 Strafford County budget as  &lt;br /&gt;proposed.  We also urge you to attend the the public hearing on this  &lt;br /&gt;budget to express your support of this budget to the County  &lt;br /&gt;Commissioners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday January 15, 2009 at 7 PM&lt;br /&gt;Strafford County Superior Court House&lt;br /&gt;259 County Farm Road&lt;br /&gt;Superior Court Room #1, 2nd floor&lt;br /&gt;Dover, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also please visit &lt;a href="http://www.rochestertaxpayers.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.rochestertaxpayers.org&lt;/a&gt; to view new county  &lt;br /&gt;information.  Feel free to view and make comments in our blog area and  &lt;br /&gt;please participate in our current survey.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your continued support is what makes the differnce!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best Regards,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RCTA&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232410673000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231598223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Strafford County Budget:  Public Hearing</name><id>9491041</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232064000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/9491041/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/f/global_6800399.jpeg</photo_url></item>