<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Aborn St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>331-8829</phone><name>Cuban Revolution</name><city>Providence</city><id>493494</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415690</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As a not-so-recent newcomer to town, I find the holiday times the most important to connect to fellow transplants. Thanksgiving tends to be my favorite of them all. Family is too far away to traverse the insanity of holiday air travel for me, your host Val. I hosted a great T-day potluck at my place a few years ago but my kitchen this year may be disassembled that weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I invite any of you who will be around, back in town by Saturday night of that weekend to come out for dinner. We'll keep the head count low, but if there is a wait list can add more. Should be prepared to bring cash and pay for your portion of the meal. This will not be a split the check equally situation. If we get 12 instead of 8, we may ask for two 6-tops for a little bit quicker service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who may be interested in just grabbing drinks and hitting the dance floor at Local 121 later on that night is welcome. Send your phone or email and we'll post where we end up - Local 121 probably final destination as the DJ starts at 11pm and spins 90s-esque danceable tunes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;gobble gobble!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353812449000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351900055000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>T-day (wknd) Saturday Outing</name><id>89714182</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353801600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/89714182/</event_url></item>