<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Watertown, MA</address_2><address_1>65 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.362003</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>617-926-2562</phone><name>Contemporary Art Gallery at ALMA, the Armenian Library &amp; Museum of America</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>505137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.080890</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey there my fellow improv incubators,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;       I hope you are all doing something random and fun and that your lives are fantastic.  I am contacting you all to announce a photography exhibition I will be part of all this month with five other photographers.  The flyer below should provide all the details but if you have any questions about the exhibit, my project, or directions, don't hesitate to e-mail me back.  As stated below the Opening Reception and Gallery Talk will take place Sunday February 10th from 2-4pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And yes, just to clarify admission is FREE.  So please pass this on to your friends and/or invite them to come along.  Just hit up mbta.com for some public transit directions.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Thanks and I hope to see all of you soon!   And by all means if I haven't been in touch lately, shoot me a message back and lets catch up.  I'll do my best to be there for a little bit tomorrow and do something silly.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jason  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The Ballad of Life &lt;br /&gt;February 1 - 29 2008  |  Group Exhibit  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reception &amp;amp; Talk: Sunday February 10, 2-4pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artists: Jeffrey Engel, Jason Jedrusiak, Kate Russell Jones, George Libbares, Marcus Stern, Melanie Thornton&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gallery: Contemporary Art Gallery at ALMA, the Armenian Library &amp;amp; Museum of America&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ballad of Life is an exhibit featuring six bodies of work, a story by each artist that collectively looks at various aspects of existence. Dreams, surrealism, nostalgia, reality and religion are among the themes of stories narrated by photographers, who with their vision will take you to different grounds. Each collection hums its own melody, but together they chant the Ballad of Life. Visit www.photoemerge.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Naveed Nour, &amp;quot;The Balad of Life&amp;quot; Curator describes the collection: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Engel is exploring the meaning of his childhood dreams and has found a way to depict some of the images which he has been treasuring in his memories all these years. Jedrusiak is combining his strong poetic side with his photographic skills to show us the darker sides of metropolitan backstreet alleys that we usually won't explore on our own. Libbares is using the life of a musician friend as a mirror to reflect on himself. Russell-Jones has gone back to document a place that she once used to call home, when still living under the protective wings of her parents, but which has now turned into nostalgia. Stern is looking at life as if there are no boundaries, and with his surrealistic sense of curiosity he is shedding new light on reality, or perhaps the lack of it. Thornton is touching on the subject of faith and with her unique and respectful approach has started to document stories that are public but yet very personal to those depicted in her narrations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Armenian Library &amp;amp; Museum of America, Contemporary Art Gallery (3rd Floor)&lt;br /&gt;65 Main Street, Watertown, MA 02472 | 617-926-ALMA |  www.almainc.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours: Thur. 6-9PM, Fri. 1-5PM, Sat. 10 AM-2PM, Sun. 1-5PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Car - From the West: Take Mass Pike (Rt. 90) east to exit 17 (Watertown). Move to left lane and take left over Mass Pike and proceed straight onto Galen St. to Watertown Sq. Take a left onto Rt. 20. - Main Street. Library is on right at the corner of Main St. and Church St. From the East: Take Rt. 16 West Mt. Auburn Street to Watertown Square. Take a right onto Rt. 20 Main Street. Library is on right at the corner of Main St. and Church St. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By Public Transportation - Watertown Square is served by many MBTA bus routes. MBTA information is (617) 222-3200, or online at www.mbta.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Seriously i usually stand out in any venue.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202843328000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Um, its free, you get to hang out with me more, get creeped out by my photography and poetry, and there's free snacks and such.</why><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202357406000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jason's Photography Exhibition Opening and Reception!!!</name><id>7281353</id><headcount>80</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202670000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/7281353/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/f/7/global_3160855.jpeg</photo_url></item>