<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>80 Carby St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02090</zip><lat>42.235863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hale Reservation</name><city>Westwood</city><id>669427</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.231890</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's get together again at Hale Reservation and enjoy a vigorous walk.  After the walk   &lt;br /&gt;those interested can get together for lunch at a local restaurant.   We will be having lunch at Chipotles Restaurant on Route 1 in Dedham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hale Reservation (HR) comprises 1,100 acres of woodland, meadows, wetland, four ponds, 20 miles of hiking trails, and Native American archaeological sites. In summers, it is the nation?s largest complex of day-camps, receiving 4,400 children daily (1,800 are subsidized) from over 70 Greater Boston communities. Year-round, over 1,000 children from 200 schools and organizations enjoy outdoor educational experiences ? how to swim, paddle a canoe, study environmental science, and experience the beauty of nature. The physically challenged are encouraged by accessible facilities, including a wheelchair-accessible fishing pier. The Health Center is pro-active, not only giving first aid but collecting public health data on the children, providing wellness education and significant primary health care for those at risk. All this is owing to the philanthropy of Robert Sever Hale, who in 1918 began purchasing land for use by Boy Scout troops. When he died in 1941 over 900 acres were set aside (the rest has been donated or acquired) ??for camping, etc. ?with a feeling that it belongs to all?so long as such activity is charitable and benevolent in nature.? HR is an institution with tremendous potential even beyond what they have already achieved ?an ideal philanthropic investment opportunity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194894283000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192558973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HALE RESERVATION WALK  </name><id>6560443</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194721200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/6560443/</event_url></item>