<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Locust St #1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.774986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-912-7136</phone><name>Nichiren Buddhist Sangha</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>753460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jukai (joining the Sangha, taking precepts) -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jukai is performed at this Temple several times a year in the spring and in the fall. Following the standard which was set by Nichiren Order of North America, we wait a minimum of six months before performing Jukai. There is no rush to become a member. It is only performed when the person is ready and has enough time to make a informed decision. During the introductory period the new person will learn basic Buddhist concepts, history or Buddhism, Lotus Sutra, Nichiren doctrine and practice. They will work with the minister to develop a strong practice and faith.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the Jukai, Omandala Gohonzon (object of veneration) is given to the practitioner for their home altar. The new member takes vows to uphold the Lotus Sutra and follow the directions of Nichiren Shonin. The Sangha then welcomes the new members. Everyone is always welcome to participate and or watch the ceremony. If you feel you would like to become a member please talk to the minister. If you would just simply like to see the ceremony please join us. The ceremony is conducted at our home Temple for New England in Haverhill MA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.newenglandbuddhist.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryuoh Faulconer Shonin</member_name><member_id>7835520</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318256585000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-616</urlname><id>1275091</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Haverhill Buddhist Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317737753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jukai Ceremony</name><id>36085452</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318168800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-616/events/36085452/</event_url></item>