<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Sunset Ln</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01612</zip><lat>42.327626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Maria College</name><city>Paxton</city><id>725813</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.918336</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I'd like to invite the members of the Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group to a special presentation about Quasars by Dr. David Wexler at 7:30 PM in the Science Building at Anna Maria College in Paxton, MA. For those members who would like to know a little more about Quasars ( Quasi-Stellar Objects ), please check out this website link : &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://imagine.gsfc.nasa.gov/docs/science/know_l1/active_galaxies.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://imagine.gsfc.n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basically they represent the cores of very active galaxies that are almost at the very observable limits of space - 12 billion light years away! Scientists study them across all wavelengths in order to learn more about that and Dr. Wexler has given this general talk to many astronomical clubs across Massachusetts to great acclaim. Please join the members of the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc, for this great talk starting at 7:30 PM with doors open early at 7PM - Dr. Wexler's talk will be about 40 minutes with plenty of time for questions and answers. Aldrich Society members will also host an observing session after the event and will have plenty of munchies and warm beverages for all who attend along with some great door prizes! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your telescopes and binoculars if you have them but Aldrich members always share their night sky views through their personal telescopes with all who attend this event!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The talk will be upstairs in the Science Building toward the back of the campus - a sign will be posted outside the Science Building and there is plenty of nearby parking for all who attend!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297612291000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295411951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Special Presentation about Quasars by Dr. David Wexler</name><id>16102774</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297555200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/16102774/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>