<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The trip will be a Lowell-Anderson bushwhack. We access the bushwhack via the Carrigian Notch Trail. Lowell first, then Anderson. We will leave a car at the nancy Pond TH in case we exercise the option for heading north to Mt Nancy, but I have heard that the area north of Anderson is wicked, wicked bad and want it to be optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not forget that if it is cold and raining, we will not be bushwhacking - an alternate trip will be proposed. In wet/cold conditions, it is absolutely impossible to stay dry. Add the s-l-o-w pace of bushwhacking and hypothermia is a real concern.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up and/ or email me if you are interested. If you have any questions, email me first. If you are not absolutely certain what a bushwhack entails please email me before signing as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8:00 AM is the hike start time. Carpooling will need to be earlier and that time is TBD. I encourage carpooling if possible. If an alternate carpool location is desired, just let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By participating in this outing, you agree to follow the hikesafe responsibility code, stay with the group for the duration, and abide by leadership's safety-related changes of plan that may need to be made while in the field).&amp;nbsp;Also note that bad weather may change the hike plan and wicked bad weather will cancel. Weather related decisions will be made Friday morning and an email will go out if needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my tan corolla</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew B</member_name><member_id>4803051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320000615000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318818028000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH100: Lowell and  Anderson</name><id>37631992</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319889600000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/37631992/</event_url></item>