<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>There are plenty of sites available at this campround. Just 90 minutes from Boston, call and make your reservation today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can have 2 tents and 2 cars in each campsite. Please bring your own food. We can improvise a shared meal Saturday night around a campfire. I would like to do a little hiking and rent canoes on Saturday, and go swimming in between!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear Brook, with over 10,000 acres, is the largest developed state park in New Hampshire. Located in the southeast region of the state, there is plenty to do and see for everyone. Hiking, biking, swimming and fishing are a few of the favorites. Forty miles of trails through the heavily forested park, leading to seldom visited marshes, bogs, summits and ponds, offer a variety of options for hikers, mountain bikers and equestrians. Canoe rentals are available at both Beaver and Catamount Ponds, while rowboat rentals are also available at Beaver Pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear Brook State Park Campground is remotely located in the park on the shore of Beaver Pond, five miles from the day-use area. Canoe and rowboat rentals, as well as showers and laundry facilities, are available. A camp store offers a selection of camping supplies, ice, wood, and snacks. Located adjacent to the campground is a small beach and swimming area reserved for campers only. Pets are permitted at this campground, but must be leashed and attended at all times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear Brook is a popular group destination with many ponds, streams and trails for exploration. Enjoy the museum complex, swimming, canoeing and fishing. The 97-site campground offers a camp store, canoe and rowboat rentals, showers, laundry facilities, a dump station, ice and firewood. Reservations for organized youth group camping may be made by calling 603/271-3628, Monday through Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/ParksPages/BearBrook/BearBrkCmp.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186451291000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184104504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping weekend</name><id>6003543</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186182000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6003543/</event_url></item>