<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers, we will be having a fun filled night playing the &amp;quot;Dating Game&amp;quot; ! We will be discussing proper ways to meet others and techniques on how start up a conversations with someone new. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a professional there who will discuss and provide proper techniques on the art of kissing! Free demonstrations will be given to any willing participant! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After this we will go to a local restaurant / nightclub for dancing and socializing at which point we will practice our newly learned techniques. We will also play the dating game at the restaurant / nightclub! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come prepared for an evening of fun and remember, dating is a game. It is an important game , but it is a game. All games are frustrating when you are first learning the rules, and dating is no different. But, like other games, dating becomes fun as you master it. We will be having other &amp;quot;Dating Game&amp;quot; night's in the future where we will have group discussions as well as practice sessions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come out and do something different tonight! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be having a potluck dinner, so bring some thing to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And remember; Dress to impress! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions don't hesitate to contact me at: 603-509-2907. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296179920000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216285273000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trailblazers Event: The Dating Game </name><id>8357205</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219530600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8357205/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/2/global_4820402.jpeg</photo_url></item>