<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Carpool gas donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person (no PayPal)</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mt. Holyoke Range State Park is a little North of Springfield with 3,000 acres! We'll hike 5.5 miles and encounter a couple ponds with visible signs of beaver activity. At the midpoint we will be atop Mt. Norwattuck (1,106 ft.) with great views if weather permits (See photos from the 1/28/06 version of the hike). We will then decend via a safe path down and around some short cliffs on the southwestern side of the mountain. The exertion going up the mountain and back down again is moderate for about a mile total but well worth it. Most of the hike would be light to low moderate in difficulty. Streams, forest, and quiet solitude dominate the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is a clone of the hike done on 1/28/06 and hopefully more of the membership will choose to enjoy the beauty of the park in the winter. Hiking shoes are advised as there can be snow and wet muddy conditions in places. Please bring some water for yourself too. A daypack or bookbag would be advised to carry your water and to stow a jacket as you warm up on the ascent of the mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetup will be at 10 AM at the parking area off of Bachelor St. at the south end of the park (see the park map at the park link). directions are below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike about 3 hr. and get back to the vehicles at about 1 PM. Then the plan is to head out to eat lunch together back down MA-116 in S. Hadley. There are plenty of good places to eat in one place there near Holyoke College. We would finish up eating at about 2 PM and head home.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to trailhead parking:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take I-91 N toward SPRINGFIELD&lt;br /&gt;2. Merge onto I-391 N via EXIT 12 toward CHICOPEE / HOLYOKE CTR. (4.2 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;3. Take the MAIN STREET exit- EXIT 5 (0.2 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;4. Turn RIGHT onto MAIN ST (1.0 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;5. MAIN ST becomes CANAL ST / MA-116 (0.3 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;6. Turn LEFT onto N BRIDGE ST / MA-116. Continue to follow MA-116 (3.9 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;7. Turn SLIGHT LEFT onto WOODBRIDGE ST / MA-116. Continue to follow MA-116 (3.5 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;8. Turn RIGHT onto AMHERST RD (0.5 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;9. Turn LEFT onto BACHELOR ST (1.1 mi.)&lt;br /&gt;10. Trailhead with parking will be on LEFT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S will provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor at a 9 AM for those interested. There will be a blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. Drive is a hour. Return at about 2 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Take I-91 N to EXIT 45 (CT-140, E. WINDSOR)&lt;br /&gt;2. Turn RIGHT onto CT-140 E&lt;br /&gt;3. At stop light, turn RIGHT onto CT-5 S&lt;br /&gt;4. Less than a mile on RIGHT you will see Wal-Mart&lt;br /&gt;5. Go down the drive to Wal-Mart and meet near entrance &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/hksp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/hksp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1166577834000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1140686498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Mt. Holyoke Range SP in Amherst MA</name><id>4861011</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1141484400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/4861011/</event_url></item>