<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;"Eric and Katie create a magical acoustic blend of sound that soars sweetly above the listener, swirls to new heights, and then drifts softly back down to earth. You're left with the inescapable desire to press repeat!" &lt;br /&gt;

-- Fiddler and notloB alumna Lissa Schneckenburger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome back Katie (Newton Celtic seisiún, 5/16/09) and Eric (8/11/07 &amp;amp; 8/13/08, Dave Carter tributes and 11/2/07, in support of the Rowan Brothers) and together 3/2/12!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie McNally and Eric McDonald found each other in high school as like-minded musicians in the Boston traditional music scene. Both sought to functionally push the envelope of traditional music, using original music and modern sensibility to add new color to the familiar style of tunes that have been passed down for generations. Over the years and many impromptu musical moments, this musical relationship congealed into a cohesive unit. Now the music, while based heavily in the Scottish tradition, is infused with influences from two diverse and educated musical backgrounds, where carefully arranged traditional pieces seamlessly give way to original compositions. Every set provides an enthralling dynamic intensity, jerking the listener's emotional chain back and forth with an ultimately satisfying blend of feeling. Having always been two of the busiest players around, these two have amassed a reputable list of experience, currently including the scottish powerhouse Cantrip (McDonald) and the fiddle supergroup Childsplay (McNally). This practiced musicianship shines in the melodic texture and murky tones that linger long after a McNally/McDonald performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KATIE MCNALLY has grown up steeped in fiddle music. She is a former New England Scottish Fiddle Champion and a two time runner up for the National title. She recently graduated Tufts University, where she studied traditional music from many cultures (including a semester abroad in Glasgow, Scotland). Katie is quickly becoming a renowned instructor. You may often find her leading workshops for the Boston Scottish Fiddle Club or teaching at Boston Harbor Scottish Fiddle School. She also performs with the fiddle Supergroup, Childsplay, alongside many of the nation's finest acoustic musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ERIC MCDONALD is known for his tasteful playing on both the mandolin and the guitar. A former student at Berklee College of Music, he cut his teeth touring with acts such as Matching Orange and The Dave Rowe Trio. He has studied with some of the best mandolinists in the world, including John McGann, Joe Walsh and Sean Staples. As a guitarist, Eric is an in demand accompanist, performing with acts such as Brendan Carey Block and Kyle Carey. He is on staff at Passim School of Music and Maine Fiddle Camp, and tours with acts such as Rebecca Wudarski, Cantrip and Pesky J. Nixon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katie McNally &amp;amp; Eric McDonald's website: &lt;a href="http://www.katieandericmusic.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.katieandericmusic.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donation $10-15 plus $1 preservation fee. &lt;br /&gt;

20% discount for Loring-Greenough museum members. &lt;br /&gt;

Reservations suggested and strongly recommended, email notlobreservations at gmail dot com &lt;br /&gt;

More info at the notloB website - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please sign up for our concert announcements - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee from JP Licks &lt;br /&gt;

Pastries from Fiores&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;===&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;notloB Folk Concerts has produced not-for-profit concerts in the greater Boston area since 2007. The series is volunteer-run; 100% of the donations go to the musicians and production expenses. Admission is by suggested minimum donation. A suggested minimum donation (varies by concert) is requested. If you cannot support the artists with dollars, please consider volunteering your time and energy. Your donations cover venue rental, sound system rental, sound engineer, publicity and other production expenses. 100% of the balance goes to the artists (many of whom travel many miles). Sometimes there are shortfalls, so extra donations are gladly accepted. If you cannot afford the suggested donation amount, consider volunteering! And please, no credit cards or checks, cash is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography, video recording, &amp;amp; sound recording. No still, video or sound recording is permitted without permission of the artist and the house. If you would like to share photos of past concerts, email the pictures and/or web link to notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In this era of pop-driven acoustic music, notloB is keeping the folk tradition alive." ~ Jack Hardy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upcoming: &lt;br /&gt;

February 18 - tba &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/179348295541321/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/179348295541321/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

February 23 - Fellswater &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/437938576260887/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/437938576260887/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

March 9 - Bronwyn Keith-Hynes and Catherine Bowness &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/302018473243058/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/302018473243058/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358568534000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1356471812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Katie McNally and Eric McDonald (Celtic)</name><id>96491332</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358557200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/96491332/</event_url></item>