<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>It's that time of year again!  Time for drinking like a lephrechaun! Don't forget to wear green or something St. Patrick's Day-ish (or whatever the heck you want!).   By now, most people know what I look like, but I will be wearing my shamrock headband and a green Sox shirt.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's all the info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Kick off the St. Patrick's Day Holiday season in Harpoon style! &lt;br /&gt;-What better place to begin the season than inside the largest brewery in Boston?!?!?! &lt;br /&gt;-Food vendors selling Corned beef &amp;amp; cabbage along with other delicious food &lt;br /&gt;-Cash bars offering a selection of fresh Harpoon and UFO beer featuring Celtic Ale &lt;br /&gt;Featuring live Irish and Rock and Roll bands from the Boston area &lt;br /&gt;-Come dance the jig, enjoy Harpoon beer, and celebrate St. Patrick! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When will it be?&lt;br /&gt;-Friday: 5:30 PM to 11:00 PM (Doors close at 9:30 pm)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where is it?&lt;br /&gt;-At the Harpoon Brewery, 306 Northern Ave., Downtown Boston. &lt;br /&gt;-Inside The Brewery amongst the tanks and outside under huge circus tents &lt;br /&gt;-Free shuttles from the South Station area. Departs from behind the Federal Reserve along the -Fort Point Channel off Summer Street.  Look for the Shuttle Sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details:&lt;br /&gt;-Cover charge $15.00 and includes a souvenir Pint Cup (does not include food or beer) &lt;br /&gt;-Cash bars serving a selection of fresh Harpoon beer for $5.00 per 16 oz. cup &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check the website for the upcoming band schedule.  Usually, Joshua Tree plays there and they're really good.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's usually a coat check (a few $$) so you don't have to lug your coat, etc. around all night.  Bathrooms are porta-potty's, so be prepared!  Also, the food isn't THAT good, so eat something before hand or take a snack with you.   There are a few food vendors inside south station if you want to grab something there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**I recommend taking the T and leaving your car at home, especially if you're going to drink.  The beer is stronger than normal, since it comes fresh from the brewery.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting between 5 and 5:30 outside Clarke's.  Then we'll head over using the shuttle.  Please RSVP by 4pm on March 6th so we know who to look for at Clarke's.  Maybe's will be considered a &amp;quot;No&amp;quot; at that point.  Thanks! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet outside of Clarke's at SOUTH STATION-NOT Faneuil Hall!!!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>6283119</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236734055000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232377880000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harpoon St. Patrick's Festival</name><id>9555229</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236376800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/9555229/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/8/global_7387032.jpeg</photo_url></item>