<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7A Bartlett Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03878</zip><lat>43.250000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Andy's House</name><city>Somersworth</city><id>582725</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.870000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This time I'd like to share the movie &amp;quot;The Secret&amp;quot; and discuss. I've noticed in our email discussions that there are different versions which people did or didn't like, but I'm not sure which I have -- I'll have to get back to you about that. I decided to make the time earlier since I learned at this past meeting that it takes more time to eat dinner, watch the movie and discuss, than the usual meeting does...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry about the change in location -- I was unclear where Andy lived. It's Somersworth!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meeting will be at Andy's house in NH. I'm sorry for choosing a private residence again for our location, but I simply don't know where to gather for a movie showing! The libraries I've checked out require me to bring my own TV and DVD player and their hours don't fit well. I've been told churches often have meeting rooms, but I think they still require me to bring my own equipment -- and I really don't want to lug my TV and DVD player around. If anyone has any ideas PLEASE PLEASE tell me!!! Also PLEASE PLEASE don't be afraid to come to meetings at individual's homes! I want to meet new people in this group and I'd love more people to attend these discussions -- they will be much better with you! PS&amp;gt; Portland area people, I promise I will do something near you soon! :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's a block towards Maine from the corner of Rt 9 (High Street) and Indigo Hill Rd (Rite Aid &amp; a traffic light are at the corner). It's an apartment building. The doorbells don't work, but it's the door to your immediate left as you enter foyer.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raina</member_name><member_id>4359513</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209830180000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Metaphysics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metaphysics-387</urlname><id>682186</id><group_lat>43.4399986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7600021362</group_lon><name>The New England Metaphysical Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207257440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Meeting</name><id>7667778</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209330000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metaphysics-387/events/7667778/</event_url></item>