<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Batterymarch Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.357452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Battery Park Bar and Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>2350361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054070</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE: THE PARTY IS ON! Oscars and PRIZES, PRIZES, PRIZES! Absolut will be sponsoring tastings of their new champagne-vodka product, and we'll have iTunes gift card prizes and chances for free beer. We've got about 30 RSVPs across the four meetups. We hope to see you there!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Put on your BEST party clothes and join us at Battery Park for a special RED CARPET viewing of the 85th Annual Academy Awards on Sunday, February 24th! The Oscars starts at 7:00pm but get there early to walk the red carpet and pick your prime seat for the show! There will be lots of activities and PRIZES, PRIZES, PRIZES! We'll be offering a voting ballot, Oscars bingo, and a prize for BEST DRESSED.  Special guest sponsors will also be on hand!  We want to do this party up! So pull out your best party dress/suit/tux and COME ON DOWN!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no fee to attend this event.  Battery Park is located in the Financial District in Boston.  Conveniently located near State Street (Orange and Blue Lines), Aquarium (Blue Line, Government Center (Blue and Green Lines), and Downtown Crossing (Orange and Red Lines).  If you plan to drive in, street metered parking is free on Sundays.  There are also a couple of pay garages nearby.  Everyone is responsible for their own food and drink. SO PLEASE PAY AS YOU GO OR MAINTAIN A SEPARATE TAB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the RED CARPET!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beverly Doughty</member_name><member_id>29050952</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361761710000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360597121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Academy Awards RED CARPET Viewing Party</name><id>104080142</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361750400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/104080142/</event_url></item>