<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>room 4-231</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.378963</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT)</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9932142</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119621</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn and practice Python basics with this project-driven workshop!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audience&lt;/strong&gt;: Women and their friends who have no or limited programming experience. This event is welcoming and respectful of trans women. Men are welcome as guests of women who are attending (please RSVP as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Friday evening you'll set up your development environment and start learning Python through a self-directed tutorial and online practice problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday we'll spend the morning on a lecture-based introduction to the language, taking breaks to practice concepts on bite-sized exercises. In the afternoon we'll break out into groups to practice Python through short projects on a variety of fun and practical topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://meetup.bostonpython.com/events/56754812/"&gt;photos and feedback&lt;/a&gt; from our previous workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You must be able to attend both days of the workshop to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to provide an environment in which women can develop their programming skills with confidence. Our staff are predominantly women from the Boston programming and open source communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href="https://openhatch.org/wiki/Boston_Python_Workshop_7"&gt;Workshop wiki&lt;/a&gt; for more information on laptop setup, lecture material, and the projects, as well as workshop logistics including parking and childcare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Venue details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT is hosting this event. We'll be in room 4-231 on the main campus for the first day of the event. See the &lt;a href="https://openhatch.org/wiki/Boston_Python_Workshop_7#Venue_and_Logistics"&gt;venue section of the wiki&lt;/a&gt; for directions and a map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday evening (11/2): laptop setup and first steps with Python&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6pm to 9pm: set up your development environment and start learning Python.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Things to bring: a wireless-enabled laptop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday (11/3): lecture and projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9:30am - 10am: settle in and review Friday's material.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10am - Noon: welcome and lecture-based introduction to Python with hands-on practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Noon - 1pm: lunch, provided by us! If you have dietary restrictions, please e-mail us as you RSVP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1pm - 4pm: projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4pm - 4:30pm: wrap-up and next steps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Things to bring: the same wireless-enabled laptop from Friday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using the Twitter API to write parts of a Twitter client.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wordplay and how to cheat at Words with Friends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming graphical effects for a ColorWall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessica McKellar</member_name><member_id>14046470</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352153694000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>60</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350915048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A project-driven introduction to Python for women and their friends</name><id>88039732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351893600000</time><rsvp_limit>65</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/88039732/</event_url></item>