<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;February 4, 2012 - 8:30 am to 5:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Crowne Plaza Hotel. 100 Berlin Road. Cromwell, CT &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=403"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=403&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=403"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Fortune Magazine is dedicated to teaching people how to make money. Come and find out why Fortune Magazine recommended Andy Heller's Buy Low, Rent Smart, Sell High Strategy as being one of the top five strategies for building wealth through real estate. Andy will explain why his proven and diversified program for real estate investing offers investors an unprecedented opportunity for building wealth and taking control of their financial futures in today's real estate market. Give us just 2-3 hours per week, and we will show you how easy it is to make hundreds of thousands of dollars in real estate investing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Bonus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; All those who pre-register for this full day workshop at the end of the workshop receive a free copy of Andy Heller's best selling book, "Buy Even Lower".&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At this full-day workshop, you will learn:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

- How to consistently purchase real estate below market. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to identify the right type of property for your preferred investment model. &lt;br /&gt;

- About the best ways to buy discount properties today. Take a deep dive into the Buy Low, Rent Smart, Sell High preferred method of buying low: bank-owned foreclosures (aka post-foreclosures and REO Properties). &lt;br /&gt;

- What most investors do when calling banks without success... and learn the Regular Riches way to successfully approach banks. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to buy from banks that do not allow wholesaler assignment, and why banks are the absolute best source for discount properties when wholesaling! &lt;br /&gt;

- About financing your purchases. &lt;br /&gt;

- Our formula for establishing the Maximum Purchase Price for all types of properties, regardless of type, condition, or your investment strategy. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to negotiate to a successful purchase. &lt;br /&gt;

- About Lease/Purchasing. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to establish the right lease/purchase terms. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to minimize Repairs and maintenance headaches... let other landlords deal with them... not you! &lt;br /&gt;

- How to reach out and advertise to find the best tenants. &lt;br /&gt;

- The ten point checklist for selecting the best tenants. &lt;br /&gt;

- How buy and flip investors and buy and hold investors can benefit from lease/purchasing in today's real estate market. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to sell properties without paying real estate commissions. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to sell properties for fair market value without discounting. &lt;br /&gt;

- How to quickly get your property under contract.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328366688000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327588866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bank-Owned Foreclosures And Rent-Smart Lease Options All-Day Workshop</name><id>49710742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328362200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/49710742/</event_url></item>