<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In Italy, esca means “to lure,” which is exactly the task that this newly opened restaurant and wine bar intends to achieve with its impeccable cuisine, extensive wine list, and distinctive décor. Esca serves as a testimony to the unparalleled elegance and savory fulfillment offered only by a true Italian dining experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Upon immediate entry, one may take note of the atmosphere that emanates of style, comfort, and elegance. Richly colored wood, marble, and granite adorn the interior while murals depicting the Italian countryside accent the walls. Unique to Esca is the wall behind the bar that was meticulously constructed to resemble the inside of an Italian wine cave. Within this carving is a sample of the finest wines served at the restaurant. An anterior seating area offers the option of al fresco dining, or dining with an open view of the veranda. An elevated mezzanine provides an overlooking panaroma of the dining area. A rearward banquet area capable of seating 150 people adds a final charm to the intimate setting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After being seated at a table most appropriate for your dining occasion, you can expect to be welcomed by a vast selection of dishes suited to meet any appetite. Each dish is an ensemble of strong, distinctive flavors and made only from the freshest ingredients including local fruits and vegetables, Hereford certified beef, George's Bank seafood, pasta fresca, and aged cheeses. The great diversity of food offered by Esca demonstrates that Italian dining is one of life's true pleasures. A second menu encloses a listing of the hundreds of global, esoteric wines offered at one's fingertips. Esca is the only area restaurant capable of bringing such variety, value, and sophistication to a single cellar. Without a doubt, Esca has brought leisurely dining to an exalted level through its cuisine that combines the best of Sicily and Northern Italy and its thoughtful array of international wines. &lt;br /&gt;Esca restaurant and wine bar, located on Main Street , corner of Washington Street in Middletown, Connecticut, and disguised by unpretentious facades on the city's street, is a first rate Italian restaurant offering stunning cuisine and service. Owners Carmelo and Marisa Bramato and daughter, Elisa Bramato, invite you to experience the best of Italy as presented by Esca Restaurant and Wine Bar in the culmination of traditional Italian cuisine and contemporary fine dining ambiance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will spend an evening at this elegant establishment and celebrate good food and great friends. Please join us for this very special affair at which we will toast our dear friend and assistant organizer (Debonair) Deb Heller as she rounds the corner of a new year. HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DEB!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign on the table/ask for Terri Bruno's table...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259023376000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256364543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening of Elegant Dining: Esca Restaurant and Wine Bar..</name><id>11699102</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258849800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/11699102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/0/global_11376304.jpeg</photo_url></item>