<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 North Moodus Rd.,</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06469 </zip><lat>41.530704</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 668-7885 </phone><name>HEARTSTONE LABYRINTHS</name><city>Moodus</city><id>1166345</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.456648</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>HeartStone Labyrinths Open House &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us at the Fall Open House and the walk the Forest Labyrinth and Peace Labyrinth. Labyrinths have been around for over 4000 years and are found in just about every major religious tradition in the world. They have been an integral part of many cultures such as Native American, Greek, Celtic and Mayan. The Hopi called the labyrinth the symbol for &amp;quot;mother earth&amp;quot; and equated it with the Kiva. Like Stonehenge and the pyramids, they are magical geometric forms that define sacred space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you walk a labyrinth, you meander back and forth, turning 180 degrees each time you enter a different circuit. As you shift your direction you also shift your awareness from right brain to left brain. This is one of the reasons the labyrinth can induce receptive states of consciousness. It can also help to balance the chakras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope others will want to attend this event and that we can go together as a group for healing purposes. Labyrinths are truly sacred places. The design itself is inherently powerful. The space and the experience of walking it are also very sacred and powerful and help us feel a greater sense of Oneness. It is a tool for people of all beliefs to come together for a common spiritual experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heartstone Labyrinths&lt;br /&gt;Moodus, CT&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1 to 5 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;Cost: FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://bookseedstudio.files.wordpress.com/2008/11/lichgate-labyrinth-green-idea-20081.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286855032000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285448914000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Labyrinth Walk</name><id>14894635</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286730000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/14894635/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/7/0/global_17122976.jpeg</photo_url></item>