<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a hike that our single members might enjoy. Charlie's Active Singles hikes are for active single people in their 30's through 50's and average up to 100 people per event! These events have been found to be fun and well planned!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet-up is at 9:00 AM at location of the hike. Hikers are usually split up into 3 different hiking skill levels (something like advanced, novice, and social) and the difficulty of the hike corresponds. The hike starts at 9:30 AM and usually lasts about 2 hours. Afterwards, dinner facilities are arranged for refueling and socializing. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS (a bit sketchy but best I have -Contact Charlie for clearer directions): &lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 8 south get off at exit 24.&lt;br /&gt;* End of ramp go right (for a short distance) &amp;amp; turn right over the metal bridge.&lt;br /&gt;** First intersection turn right onto Cold Spring Rd.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow this road for 1.3 of a mile.&lt;br /&gt;* First left turn at fork. strait to parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*North on route 8 get off at exit 23.&lt;br /&gt;* Right turn end of ramp onto 42 East.&lt;br /&gt;* Follow road to center of town (Beacon Falls) &amp;amp; turn left before first traffic light.&lt;br /&gt;* Go over metal bridge. &lt;br /&gt;* Follow above directions rest of the way (**).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very rough location/directions for the meetup location via MapQuest (no sure of the parking area location):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Beacon+Falls&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=299+Cold+Springs+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topographical map of the area via Google Maps:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;q=299%2BCold%2BSprings%2BRd,+beacon+falls,+ct&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.445493,-73.069468&amp;amp;spn=0.018561,0.031929&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=addr" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles is a 10 year old, non-profit Connecticut organization that brings together singles who enjoy participating in a variety of outdoor activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT: Charlie (organizer of Active Singles) 860-489-9611&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No official Hartford Area Hiking leadership is planned to be at this hike. Just mingle with the other Active Singles (you're one!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO Children or Dogs, Singles only (this doesn't mean you can't have a boyfriend or girlfriend). Wear Hiking Boots. Bring water. Optional Brunch follows each hike. Non hikers can join us at the restaurant. Call Charlie early to reserve a spot for Brunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Singles&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.activesingles.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.activesing...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>May not be any hiking group leadership at the event... event is run by Active Singles organization.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230389256000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228503271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Active Singles Hike to Beacon Falls in Beacon Falls CT</name><id>9287295</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229868000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/9287295/</event_url></item>