<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>NORWELL</address_2><address_1>DOVER ST.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.160000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>NORRIS RESERVATION</name><city>Norwell</city><id>276099</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.820000</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SUNDAY, MAY 20, 2007 , 11:00 am - Norris Reservation Dover St., Norwell, MA.  A walk through Norris Reservation's two-mile trail system takes in a cathedral of pines, groves of beech and scattered American holly.  A granite outcrop, set too deep for early farmers to remove, emerges from the forest floor.  Stone walls mark former property boundaries, pastures and croplands, and a rustic boathouse serves as an observation deck over the North River.  Visitors can also enjoy bird watching, cross country skiing and fishing.  For those interested in lunch after the walk we will meet at Strawberry Fair Restaurant in Norwell.  Directions from the reservation to the restaurant - head est on Dover St. toward Main St/Rte 123.  Take a sharp left at Rte 123 and travel for 3.4 miles.  Turn right onto Rte 53/Washington St. for 2.2 miles.  Turn lefft at Pond St/Rte228 for 79 feet. Turn left to stay on Pond st./Rte228 for 154 ft. The restaurant is located at 14 Pond St. Norwell.MA 02061.  It serves delightful sandwiches of all kinds as well as brunch.  See you there.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541384000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178301288000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUNDAY MAY 20, 2007 NORRIS RESERVATION</name><id>5742121</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1179673200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/5742121/</event_url></item>