<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>159 Pelham Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.728558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Days Hotel And Conference Center Methuen</name><city>Methuen</city><id>8168652</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.205849</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;World Renowned – Dr Joel Wallach is coming to Nashua NH!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://traftonbernadette.wordpress.com/dead-doctors-dont-lie/"&gt;Listen to Dead Doctors Don't Lie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHEN:&lt;/strong&gt; Oct 2, 2012 6am – 10pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt; Days Hotel, 159 Pelham St, Methuen, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP:&lt;/strong&gt; An RSVP is required as seating is very limited. You are encouraged to bring friends with you. However, please RSVP with Bernadette Trafton at dette101@gmail.com as soon as possible with subject line – “I would like to RSVP for Dr. Wallach on Oct 2, 2012″.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to expect:&lt;/strong&gt; Registration and Networking will begin at 6pm. We will begin the business overview at 7pm and Dr. Wallach will begin his revolutionary health lecture at 7:30pm. At the end of the lecture, there will be ample time for you to get your personal health questions answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Dr. Wallach:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A biomedical research pioneer, Dr. Joel D. Wallach, DVM, ND spent more than 40 years in the field of Veterinary Medicine, observing and researching the effects of individual nutrients on animal health, before becoming a Naturopathic Physician in 1982. Today, Dr. Wallach is renowned for his groundbreaking research on the health benefits of selenium and other minerals. He currently dedicates his time to lecturing throughout the world on the therapeutic benefits of vitamins and minerals, and on lobbying the U.S. Food and Drug Administration on behalf of the dietary supplement industry. &lt;br /&gt;

He is a recipient of 2012 Klaus Schwarz Award recognizing the work of pioneers in the field of trace element research –&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Wallach obtained a Bachelor of Science in Agriculture from the University of Missouri in 1962, with a major in Animal Husbandry (Nutrition) and a minor in Field Crops and Soils. In 1964, he was awarded a Doctorate in Veterinary Medicine (DVM), also from the University of Missouri. Thereafter, Dr. Wallach completed a three year (1965-68) post-doctoral fellowship at The Center for the Biology of Natural Systems at Washington University in St. Louis, Missouri. In 1982, he obtained a Doctorate in Naturopathic Medicine (ND) from the National College of Naturopathic Medicine in Portland, Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early Work&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Wallach has held key positions with leading zoos and universities in the United States and Africa, including Director of the Jacksonville Zoological Park in Jacksonville, Florida; Research Veterinarian for the South Africa National Parks Department (where he was a member of the famous “Operation Rhino” team); and Director of Research at the St. Louis Zoological Park in St. Louis, Missouri. At the request of Africa’s National Parks and Wildlife Management Department, Dr. Wallach led an expedition to capture and mark elephants in the Wankie Game Preserve in Rhodesia as part of a migration study. He is one of the founders and a former editor of the Journal of Zoo Animal Medicine. A prolific author, he has published more than 70 scientific papers and six books including the famous textbook, Diseases of Exotic Animals, still used today by leading veterinary schools, and on the Smithsonian Institute’s recommended reading list for Zoological Garden and Aquarium libraries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Groundbreaking Research on Trace Minerals&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

As a researcher at the Emory University Yerkes National Primate Center in Atlanta, Georgia in 1977, Dr. Wallach discovered the world’s first known case of non-human cystic fibrosis in a selenium-deficient Rhesus monkey. At the time, cystic fibrosis was believed to the result of a human genetic disorder. Dr. Wallach’s monumental discovery set him on a 20-year path of research on the health benefits of selenium and other minerals. As a result of this work, he became known as The Mineral Doctor and the Father of Liquid Mineral Supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Founding of Youngevity&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

In 1997, Dr. Wallach and Dr. Ma Lan, MD, MS, founded American Longevity, now known today as Youngevity. Within five years the company has enjoyed global growth and currently has offices in offices in Canada, Australia, New Zealand, Singapore, South Africa, and Japan. Today Youngevity enjoys an esteemed, premier presence in the field providing high quality, innovative, and unique products to health conscious consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Amendment Advocate&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Wallach currently dedicates his time to lecturing throughout the world on the therapeutic benefits of vitamins and minerals, and on lobbying the U.S. Food and Drug Administration on behalf of the dietary supplement industry. His tireless efforts and dedication to the public’s First Amendment rights to complete information on the therapeutic benefits of nutrition prompted the FDA to establish Qualified Health Claims for Selenium (“may reduce the risk of certain cancers”) and Omega-3 Essential Fatty Acids (“may reduce the risk of coronary heart disease”). Only a few Qualified Health Claims exist, placing Youngevity in a unique position among Dietary Supplement and Direct Marketing companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publications&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Wallach is the author/co-author of more than 70 articles published in peer-reviewed journals covering nutritional and pharmaceutical research. As well he is a major contributor to eight books, including the famous textbook, Diseases of Exotic Animals, still used today by leading veterinary schools, and on the Smithsonian Institute’s recommended reading list for Zoological Garden and Aquarium libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349230052000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>92</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346501802000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Business Overview, Health Seminar and Networking</name><id>80364522</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349215200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/80364522/</event_url></item>