<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>128 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01527</zip><lat>42.189972</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-865-1181</phone><name>Millbury Public library</name><city>Millbury</city><id>900576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.763163</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I have booked the Public Meeting Room at the Millbury Public Library in Millbury, Massachusetts for our next Meetup on November 03, 2009 at 6:30 PM. The topic will be a great PowerPoint slide show called Galileo's Vision which covers the major impact that Galileo had on our Cosmic Vision by his improvements in telescope design! His amazing observations will be tied to the revolutionary changes that have happened in amateur astronomy today and the radical advances made by the Hubble Space Telescope which has further advanced our view into the Universe!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My talks are very dynamic and will appeal to general audiences - please attend and get to meet some of your fellow amateur astronomers from the Oxford Astronomy Group and the Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc.!  I am not sure if there is any place close by to observe but I will take a trip to the Library to check the site out on Wednesday ( Oct 28 ) and will update members in the near future.  I will update people on our group's future and see how we can best manage the costs of maintaining this site in the future.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see a lot of faces at this event - bring your imagination and plenty of questions and prepare to have a great evening! By the way, NASA's  Ares 1X - another attempt at the maiden voyage of this new rocket will be attempted on Wednesday morning - I hope all goes well for this next generation rocket that will be replacing the Space Shuttle which is retiring in 2010. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Jim J. Zebrowski &lt;br /&gt;    Oxford Astronomy Group Organizer &lt;br /&gt;    President Aldrich Astronomical Society, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the dude wearing the Einstein shirt that glows in the dark! ( Now, that alone is worth the price of admission! )</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim J. Zebrowski</member_name><member_id>8778693</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257523835000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Astronomy buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1352763</id><group_lat>42.1100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Oxford Astronomy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256702167000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oxford Astronomy Group Meetup at the Millbury Public Library</name><id>11730132</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257291000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Oxford-Astronomy-Meetup-Group/events/11730132/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/4/global_7975572.jpeg</photo_url></item>