<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352478</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-482-7799</phone><name>Gypsy Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>669047</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Want to meet Boston’s most eligible singles and help a great cause? Then join 500 guests for one of Boston’s best singles events: the 3rd Annual Project Smile Date Auction, proudly presented by Table for Eight. During this exciting fundraising event, Project Smile will be auctioning off dates with traffic stopping police officers, smoldering fire fighters and other terrific single men and women. Their event has even resulted in a marriage for one lucky couple! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention ladies: Not only will you win a date with a great guy, you will also receive a pair of sexy high heels, courtesy of Sofft Shoes! Great shoes and a hot date, what can be better than that?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guys, don’t miss out! Boston’s beauties are waiting for you to win a date with them! And they each have a necktie just for you. Event will also feature a silent auction with Spirit Airline tickets, Red Sox, Patriots and Celtics items, tickets and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each “couple” will receive a gift certificate to use on their date to some of Boston’s best spots including The Capital Grille, Fleming’s Steakhouse, Ruth Chris, Toro, Turner Fisheries, harbor cruises, comedy shows and more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So bring your friends or come solo and have a terrific evening and support a great cause. All proceeds go directly to supporting Project Smile, the non profit organization dedicated to helping children involved in traumatic situations. Project Smile was founded by your Meet Up organizer, Catherine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are only $16 and include a gift bag for the first 350 guests. Gift bag includes product from Axe Hair, Sofft Shoes, Yelp, Cholive truffles and other great items!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Tickets can be purchased at www.projectsmile.org/events.htm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tix are also available at the door, however advanced purchase is recommended.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253656862000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>metrowestyoungprofessionals</urlname><id>951974</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>Metro West Young Professionals Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251682047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Awesome Charity Event! 3rd Annual Project Smile Charity Date Auction</name><id>11242471</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253313000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/metrowestyoungprofessionals/events/11242471/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/global_9282182.jpeg</photo_url></item>