<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>84 Mass. Ave</address_2><address_1>Lobdell Dining Hall, 2nd floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Stratton Student Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>460571</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.130000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for an evening of International Folk Dancing including line, circle, and couple dancing from eastern Europe and the world, hosted by the International Folk Dancing Club at MIT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In their own words, this is what its all about:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We dance mostly village dances and some dances choreographed in folk style to the complex and fascinating rhythms and music of Eastern Europe: Bulgaria, Romania, Serbia, Croatia, Greece, and others.  We round out the repetoire with a few dances from other parts of Europe and the world (such as Israel, France, Russia, even England and the US).  Most of the dances move in the traditional lines or circles; the repetoire also includes some couple dances (but you don't need to bring a partner).&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dances will be taught between 8:00 and 9:30 pm, and then music and dancing will continue until about 11 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also from their web site: &amp;quot;For your comfort &amp;amp; safety, please wear sturdy low-heeled shoes that you're comfortable running &amp;amp; jumping in.&amp;quot;  (I don't expect to be running and jumping there, but who knows??)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is their web site, if you would like more information: &lt;a href="http://mit.edu/fdc/www/international.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://mit.edu/fdc/ww...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximately half-way through the evening, there is usually a pause to take a donation.  Suggested donation is $1.00 for anyone who isn't an MIT or Wellesley student.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking is available in the N10 Lot (off Albany Street east of Massachusetts Avenue) or West Annex Lot (on Vassar Street west of Massachusetts Avenue, next to the West Garage), or on the street.  No parking permit is required at these lots after 5:30 pm or on weekends. Metered street parking is free after 6 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Final note:  If you are intimidated by dancing, don't be.  Its a lot of fun and a great way to get to know people.  If your afraid of feeling and looking ackward and clumsy, we'll all be there feeling ackward and clumsy together.  Come out for a great time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of the Lobdell Dining Hall at 7:45.  The Dining Hall is located on the second floor of the Stratton Student Center (Building W20, located at 84 Mass. Ave., directly across the street from the main entrance to MIT).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201050368000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198706487000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>International Folk Dancing</name><id>6972396</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200877200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/6972396/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/8/3/global_1218899.jpeg</photo_url></item>