<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***Note: For parking you may park at the Salem Commuter Rail lot, the Church St. Parking lot, the Musuem Place Parking Garage, or you can park on or around Cross St., if it is at least one block north/east of Lemon St. (where there are no parking restrictions for October).***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at 21 Lemon St. (the pumpkin house) in Salem.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To change this up this Meetup from the other ones that we will have had, we'll incorporate dinner into this one.  David and I will provide a main entree dish (one containing meat and one vegan), and if other people could bring either a side dish or salad.  I haven't been to a potluck in quite some time, but they always wind up being fun.  Those who want to get together for dinner, please come at 7:00, and the board gaming will begin at 8:00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In your RSVP, please indicate if you will be coming at 7:00 or 8:00.  Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Again, just to note, there are cats in the house who will be kept in another room.  Sorry for any problems this causes.  Hopefully, we'll soon get more people willing to host in their pet-free homes.  Any suggestions for other meeting places would certainly be appreciated.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, from now on, the week of events, people can no longer RSVP maybe.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200116485000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189129109000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Board Games in October</name><id>6312040</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192230000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/6312040/</event_url></item>