<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>220 College St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.306095</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203) 772-4002</phone><name>Pacifico</name><city>New Haven</city><id>664396</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.929570</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's the link: &lt;a href="http://www.pacificorestaurants.com/home_nh.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pacificore...&lt;/a&gt; . I think that after our outing at &amp;quot;THE PLACE&amp;quot; in Guilford, this will be a nice contrast. I hear the food is wonderful and MOST importantly they have Key Lime Tarts for desert!! I have set the limit at 8 people but the restaurant tells me that if the response is strong I can increase that a bit, so please RSVP early so I can get a sense of the interest. I've set the time early at 6PM since it is a Sunday. Here are some typical reviews: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“There is a deliciously lively air to the place — due in no small measure to the excellent mojitos — and the people are having too good a time to be restrained by convention…In short, Pacifico is a find. It is just a millimeter short of excellence, and that will not be long in coming.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;– The New York Times, June 25, 2005  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Chef Rafael Palomino is an exciting talent, riding the curling edge of a Nuevo Latino wave.”  &lt;br /&gt;– Westchester Weekly, May 31, 2001 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The warm, human buzz in the two-floor-high space plays off the colors and the open kitchen to create an emulsion of atmosphere that is more than the sum of its parts.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;– The New Haven Advocate, March 2004  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There’s nothing passive about Pacifico. The place is as vibrant as a samba, slinky as a tango, sexy as a cha-cha in double time.The all-important corner of College and Crown is alive again — hooray!&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;—EntertainmentCTCentral.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the New Haven Dining Out Group</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244844104000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>dining companions</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-590</urlname><id>719640</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>The New Haven Area Dining Out Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243469053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pacifico - Cervezas, Mojitos, Tapa's --- and so much more.</name><id>10508622</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244412000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-590/events/10508622/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/7/global_3095463.jpeg</photo_url></item>