<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft New England Research and Development Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1534447</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This month's meetup is sponsored by WP Engine:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/0/4/event_213491012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;WP Engine is the one of the most mature premium managed hosting platform for websites and apps built with WordPress. WPEngine powers tens of thousands of websites, delivering the fastest, most reliable, and most secure web experience.  Businesses large and small have come to rely on WP Engine’s exceptional customer service team that specializes in solving problems ranging from troubleshooting plugins, making themes scalable, and mitigating site migration headaches.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:30-7:00 Networking/Food&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00-7:10 Opening Remarks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:15-7:55 Talk 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:55-8:30 Talk 2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk 1 (Advanced beginner/Intermediate): Live-Staging &amp;amp; Migrating Sites for Clients by Collin Matthews (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/collinjmatthews"&gt;@&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/collinjmatthews"&gt;collinjmatthews&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A live, online staging site can be a great service to offer your clients as you build their new WordPress theme, plugin, or entire site. We will discuss the benefits of offering a staging site to clients, show you how to launch one quickly and easily, and describe how to migrate from staging to production with just a few clicks. We will also migrate a real site together step by step while answering any questions you may have along the way! This also applies to anyone looking to change hosting providers, or move WordPress in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Bio:&lt;/strong&gt; Collin Matthews is the founder and CEO of SierraPulse, a WordPress development and design shop based in Boston. He also offers WordPress and Shopify consultancy services at &lt;a href="http://collinmatthews.me/" target="_blank"&gt;collinmatthews.me&lt;/a&gt;, and is the creator of &lt;a href="http://thinkorporate.com/" target="_blank"&gt;thinkorporate.com&lt;/a&gt;, a forthcoming networking site that connects high school and college students who have a passion for web design and development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk 2:  (dev): Git Going: Version Your Code Like It's 2013 by K.Adam White (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kadamwhite"&gt;@kadamwhite&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Version control. Losing your work stinks, so if you don't use a version control system, you should! Git is a distributed system developed by the creator of the Linux operating system to help manage code contributions from a world-wide team of contributors.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Github, a code hosting site built on top of Git, launched five years ago this month and has since become the largest code hosting service in the world. Knowing how to use Git isn't just a powerful tool to help your team collaborate—it's become an essential skill required for contributing to many open source projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll go over the basics of managing your code with Git, both from the command-line and using a graphical interface, then we'll talk about how to get the most out of using Github's powerful toolset to organize your team's WordPress projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bio:&lt;/strong&gt; K.Adam White is an engineer at &lt;a href="http://bocoup.com/"&gt;Bocoup&lt;/a&gt;, the Open Web company of &lt;a href="http://community.bocoup.com/bob/"&gt;rooster sticker&lt;/a&gt; fame, where he writes awesome JavaScript web applications. He is a co-organizer of the Boston WordPress meetup group. &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Eng</member_name><member_id>9694496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366748853000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>WordPress fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-wordpress-meetup</urlname><id>1340213</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston WordPress</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>106</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359334997000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BWPM Apr2013: Live-Staging &amp; Migrating Sites (beg/int) &amp; Git Going (dev)</name><id>101692882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366669800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-wordpress-meetup/events/101692882/</event_url></item>