<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come meet Marie Bankuti, experience Life Coach!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is Life/Success Coaching?&lt;br /&gt;Imagine an athlete with unfocused, natural ability, or a singer with lots of raw, undeveloped talent.  Coaches assist them to develop what they already possess naturally.  That?s the idea behind Life Coaching!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Life Coaching is a thought provoking, creative partnership.  In a safe and supportive atmosphere,  the client is inspired to reach her maximum potential, both personally and professionally. &lt;br /&gt;Join us for a taste of what Life Coaching is like. Participate in group activities and witness a coaching demonstration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio:&lt;br /&gt;Marie Bankuti, PMP, is a Life / Success Coach and independent consultant.  Marie is trained by the internationally known Coaches Training Institute and remains a member in good standing of the International Coach Federation (ICF), the Project Management Institute (PMI), and the International Institute of Business Analysis (IIBA).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please bring your business cards for a raffle!&lt;/u&gt;  (Of course, bring extra cards to give to each other!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By popular request, this meeting will be potluck.  Please bring a snack or beverage to share.  (No alcohol.)  I will provide tablecloths, cups, plates and napkins.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my picture on the site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen K.</member_name><member_id>3407018</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214839963000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>You'll have the opportunity to meet career women like you who want to support each other.  Every month, we'll have a different speaker who will present a topic of interest.  Plus, there will be lots of time for socializing!</why><group><who>Professional Women</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Women-in-Business-Network</urlname><id>997886</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Women in Business Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211501075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Women in Business Network - Newton Meeting</name><id>7994826</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214521200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-in-Business-Network/events/7994826/</event_url></item>