<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will be starting this hike on Jericho Rd and ending at the davis path trailhead parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt;The Jericho (south) trailhead is reached by following Jericho Rd.—called Rocky Branch Rd. (FR 27) by the USFS—which leaves US 302 just east of the bridge over the Rocky Branch, 1 mi. west of the junction of US 302 and NH 16 in Glen; it is paved for about 1 mi., then a good gravel road up to the beginning of the trail about 4.4 mi. from US 302.north of Jackson, just north of the highway bridge over the Ellis River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's hike  Davis path from Mt Stairs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The path leaves US 302 on the west side of the Saco River at a paved parking lot near the Notchland Inn, 5.6 mi. south of the Willey House site in Crawford Notch State Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Davis Path, completed by Nathaniel T. P. Davis in 1845, was the third (and longest) bridle path constructed to the summit of Mt. Washington. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sections leading up the dauntingly steep southern slopes of Mt. Crawford and Stairs Mountain give some idea of the magnitude of the task Davis performed in building a trail passable to horses along this ridge. The resolution that enabled Davis to push forward with this apparently hopeless task was the inspiration for the naming of Mt. Resolution. This trail is almost entirely within the Presidential Range–Dry River Wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will pass Mt Crawford, Mt Resolution and shelter on our way to the Giant Stair Spur which offers unlimited views of the wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description&lt;br /&gt; The Davis Path is the easiest route to descend from Giant Stairs. There is very little water on the Davis path. All hikers should plan on having enough water.&lt;br /&gt; We will not be able to filter water until after we get below treeline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;trail plan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  starting at Rocky Branch Trailhead - south               hike 2.00 mi/1 hr 3 min/+324 ft on the Rocky Branch Trail&lt;br /&gt; The Rocky Branch Trail begins at Jericho Rd. and immediately crosses Otis Brook and the river on logging-road bridges. It utilizes a new gravel logging &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;road, crosses another brook and joins a railroad grade. The trail bypasses the grade on the uphill side of a boggy section of the grade and then crosses Lower Stairs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brook. It continues north along the river.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Rocky Branch Shelter #1 access  hike 0.01 mi/1 min/+4 ft on the Rocky Branch Trail&lt;br /&gt; A spur path on the right leads 60 yd. to WMNF Rocky Branch Shelter #1 and tentsite. The trail then reaches a junction with the Stairs Col Trail on the left.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Stairs Col Trail&lt;br /&gt; entering wilderness area&lt;br /&gt; hike 1.80 mi/1 hr 44 min/+1604 ft on the Stairs Col Trail  It leaves the Rocky Branch Trail opposite the side path to the Rocky Branch Shelter #1 area and &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;follows an old railroad siding for 50 yd. It then turns sharp left, crosses a swampy area, and climbs briefly to a logging road, where it enters the Presidential &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Range–Dry River Wilderness. From here nearly to Stairs Col, the trail follows old logging roads along the ravine of Lower Stairs Brook, becoming quite steep and &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;crossing the headwaters of the brook, where it enters a birch glade. The trail becomes gradual as it approaches Stairs Col, with an impressive view up to the cliffs of &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stairs Mountain, then it crosses this small, ferny pass and continues down the west slope a short distance to meet the Davis Path. For the Giant Stairs, turn right.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Davis Pathhike 0.40 mi/25 min/+408 ft on the Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; The Davis Path now veers northwest, passing west of the precipitous Giant Stairs, ascending gradually along a steep mountainside, then zigzagging boldly &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;northeast—with occasional steep scrambles on ledges—toward the flat top of Stairs Mountain.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Giant Stairs spur  hike 0.20 mi/7 min/+1 ft on the Giant Stairs spur&lt;br /&gt; to Stairs Mtn&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  4.41 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  3 hr 20 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +2528 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -187 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  +2341 ft   hike 0.20 mi/7 min/-1 ft on the Giant Stairs spur&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/25 min/-408 ft on the Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; The Davis Path then zigzags up the ledges toward the flat top of Stairs Mountain with occasional steep scrambles. The trail then passes the precipitous &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Giant Stairs to the east and bears southeast.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Stairs Col Trail  hike 0.30 mi/11 min/-6 ft on the Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; Here the Stairs Col Trail to the Rocky Branch diverges left. The path passes just west of Stairs Col, the small, wild pass between Mt. Resolution and Stairs &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountain. At the junction with the Mt. Parker Trail, a spur path diverges left to Resolution Shelter.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Parker Trail and Resolution Shelter access&lt;br /&gt; hike 1.50 mi/58 min/-128 ft on the Davis Path  The Davis Path continues through the col and the Parker Trail diverges left (east) and leads to open ledges &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;near the summit of Mt. Resolution, then continues to the Mt. Langdon Trail and Bartlett village. Fine views can be obtained from open ledges by ascending this trail &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;only a little ways from the Davis Path junction. Leaving this col, the path runs south, descends slightly, and keeps close to the same level along the steep west side of &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt. Resolution. It then passes over a ledgy shoulder of Crawford Dome, with good views to the impressively precipitous face of the small peak of Mt. Crawford. The &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;trail descends to the col between the peak of Mt. Crawford and its ledgy, domelike east knob (sometimes called Crawford Dome) then climbs over the knob. At the foot &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of a large, sloping ledge, a side trail diverges right and climbs to the bare, peaked summit of Mt. Crawford, from which there is a magnificent view of Crawford &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Notch, the Dry River valley, and the surrounding ridges and peaks.&lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Crawford spur   hike 2.20 mi/2 hr 4 min/-1915 ft on the Davis Path&lt;br /&gt; The Davis Path follows this ridge south, descending over bare ledges with good outlooks, particularly to Mt. Carrigain and the Tripyramids. It then leaves &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the crest and soon enters the old, carefully graded bridle path and begins to descend the steep ridge between Mt. Crawford and Mt. Hope by zigzags. It then leaves the &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presidential Range–Dry River Wilderness. It climbs toward the main brook, crosses a tributary and then crosses the brook bed at a point where there may be running &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;water upstream. It then follows a logging road along the bed of a small brook (normally dry in summer). It swings left and leaves the WMNF and the woods. It crosses a &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;small brook and then turns onto a path along a power line. It continues straight west across an overgrown field near a camp and into private land. It crosses the new &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;suspension footbridge (Bemis Bridge) and follows the west side of the Saco River about 200 yd. downstream to the paved parking lot near the Notchland Inn on US &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;302.&lt;br /&gt; to Davis Path Trailhead&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  9.01 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  7 hr 5 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +2968 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -3086 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  -118 ft&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248784927000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242422295000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stairs Mountain via Davis Path</name><id>10421256</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248611400000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10421256/</event_url></item>