<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I am excited to invite you to a one day workshop to explore your energetic boundaries, by being initiated into the powerful fundamental principles of energy ownership taught in the Energetic Boundaries: Healing Without Effort, Level I class. The workshop will take place on Saturday, November 7, 10:00 am -5:00:30 pm at the Energy Restructuring Institute at 57 University Rd, Brookline.  Please register as soon as possible, since space is limited.  This workshop is a prerequisite for the Energetic Displacement Reintegration certification. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Using the power of the universal alignment participants will experience how to heal their past without reliving pain and how to reclaim energy lost to people or situations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the process of reclaiming, they will&lt;br /&gt;learn skills to become less affected by their own negative moods and those of others&lt;br /&gt;feel safe and retain confidence when faced with judgment and critics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each of us is a soul, an individualized aspect of creation, which incarnates over and over again.  In this way the evolution of our consciousness takes place.   The energy field is a container, a permanent home given to the soul since that moment, when the initial spark of creation was seeded in the space dedicated exclusively for our soul.  The energy field is the souls permanent abode that shelters it through successful incarnations in the physical body.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a soul &amp;quot;lowers&amp;quot; itself into the physical body during a reincarnation, its energetic container expands. It stretches out its boundary to encompass the body as it grows, to the span of our outstretched arms, with the precision of the laws of sacred geometry.  The circle in Leonardo DaVinci's 'The Vitruvian Man' holds a hidden key to our understanding of the physicality of our Energetic Boundary formed by the Human Energy Field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your energetic boundary is a spherical region of space with the body in the center -- smaller when you are a child and growing bigger as you become an adult. Most people think of the notion of personal boundaries as merely representational, rather then a physical reality. Most of us do not occupy our energy space fully because we do not even know that it exists or how large the energetic space is that we own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we strive for the spiritual evolution of our planet, we must first achieve unification of our physical body, our soul and its energetic container. The fundamental purpose behind every incarnation is to work through challenges of human relationships.The Energetic Boundary course will assist you in exploring the the path for your soul's journey and the energetic nature of your relationships by studying the principles of energy field interactions and the universal laws that govern them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;There is a big gap exists between what we know to be true and the ability to live from that place.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Energetic Boundary course will help you bridge this gap for you.  &lt;br /&gt;If you feel you are living but not fully alive, being but not being truly yourself, join us in this course and being your friends to discover the purpose for your soul in this life .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price: $135,  $150 day of workshop.&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: 10:30 am to 5:30pm supervised individual and group practice;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279135615000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256953563000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Energetic Boundaries - Your Healing WIthout Effort.</name><id>11753294</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257606000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/11753294/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/b/6/global_11525046.jpeg</photo_url></item>