<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 West 2nd Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.342758</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Artists For Humanity</name><city>Boston</city><id>11249662</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053642</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TICKET **SALE** TOMORROW: FEBRUARY 21. ONE DAY ONLY. TICKETS ARE $50 INSTEAD OF $75.&lt;/strong&gt; (Includes three drink tickets, appetizers, music, food, and is a chartiable donation)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bostonglow.nationbuilder.com/ignite_the_nite_2013_tickets"&gt;https://bostonglow.nationbuilder.com/ignite_the_nite_2013_tickets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT'S FOR A GREAT CAUSE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a fun night out with Boston's hippest crowd- young professionals up to senior donors. Drinks, food, dancing, live music, special guests and a silent auction to support Boston GLOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you familiar with Boston GLOW? We're a 100% volunteer run organization that raises money to provide scholarships for young woman in Boston's most under-resourced schools in our most at-risk communities. Last years Ignite the Nite event raised $30,000 in scholarship funds, and this year our goal is a minimum of $35,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the third year of the gala, so we're excited for great success. The last two years have resulted in 8 of our scholarship winners going to college, some of them first exiting the shelter system, procuring safe housing and earning their GED, others finally leaving behind a neighborhood riddled with gang violence to start a brighter future for themselves and their families.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy tickets here: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.bostonglow.org/ignite_the_nite_2013_calendar2"&gt;http://www.bostonglow.org/ignite_the_nite_2013_calendar2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;** I am volunteering at the event, so if someone else could step up as "Organizer," that would be appreciate as I just can't do both! **&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362107029000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359046877000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston GLOW Ignite the Nite</name><id>101183502</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362096000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/101183502/</event_url></item>