<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;NOTE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: The protest starts at Noon. I will post further details from Sherry as they become available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me to help &lt;a href="http://activedogs.meetup.com/310/members/7980720/"&gt;Sherry &lt;/a&gt; raise awareness about Puppy Mills by joining her group in a peaceful protest in front of Debbie's Pet Land store in Nashua.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a perfect time of year to enlighten lots of people as they prepare to purchase a pet for a Christmas present. Many are NOT aware of the conditions and the cruelty inflicted on these puppies' mothers.  Let's point people to the Animal Rescue League and the Humane Society for their new pet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Won't you help raise awareness and make a difference. The less demand for Puppy Mill puppies the less they will breed and hopefully go out of business.&lt;br /&gt;See our group's message board for more information on Puppy Mills - &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/messages/boards/thread/5859306/0/#23317498"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are more details from Sherry:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SATURDAY 12-2&lt;br /&gt;DECEMBER 6TH  &lt;br /&gt;DEBBY'S PET LAND  &lt;br /&gt;The Pheasant Lane Mall &lt;br /&gt;Daniel Webster Highway&lt;br /&gt;Nashua, NH&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We assemble at the entrance of the Pheasant Lane Mall by Barmakian Jewelers and Uno's Pizza.&lt;br /&gt;Parking in the Petco or Home Depot Lot....   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Our Peaceful Protests &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WE ARE THE VOICE FOR ANIMALS.&lt;br /&gt;Help us give them a chance to be heard.......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every weekend through Christmas, rain or shine we'll hold a Peaceful Protest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our goal is to raise awareness of the Pet Store/Internet Breeder, Puppy Mill Connection. Our country euthanizes, (even more heartbreaking, some states still painfully gas animals), minimally 5-7 million animals a year at a cost to taxpayers of more than a billion dollars. So, Why are we adding to the overpopulation problem?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is our responsiblity to our faithful companions to Encourage Adoption from shelters or breed specific recue groups and NOT to buy. Education is key. When people stop buying puppies in pet stores or thru online internet ads, the puppy mills will go out of business and the misery will end. Please join us in this fight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Together we can make a difference for dogs suffering in puppy mills being used as breeding machines for profit sake and shelter dogs longing for loving homes!  We need YOUR HELP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We supply all the protest signage, literature, and brochures to hand out but feel free to get creative and bring your own....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Life Of A Puppy Mill Dog = &lt;a href="http://puppymilldogsvoice.org/images/stories/PuppyMillCrueltyFlyer.pdf"&gt;PuppyMillCrueltyFlyer.pdf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine</member_name><member_id>4894798</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228756102000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228087727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Protest against Puppy Mills</name><id>9253090</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228582800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/9253090/</event_url></item>