<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Central Sq.)</address_2><address_1>492 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.363860</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 864-3278</phone><name>The Middle East Restaurant and Nightclub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>257177</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101670</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thu 10/15 @ Middle East (downstairs)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/thedodos" target="_blank"&gt;The Dodos&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/therubysuns" target="_blank"&gt;The Ruby Suns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;doors 8pm, 18+, &lt;a href="http://www.ticketmaster.com/venue/8547" target="_blank"&gt;tickets&lt;/a&gt; $14&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll plan on meeting at or around the Middle East at 8:30 or so.  Any suggestions for pre-show drinks are welcomed.  Details will follow closer to the day of the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Dodos (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Originally formed in 2006 as Dodobird by multi-instrumentalist Meric Long, unpredictable San Francisco indie rock duo the Dodos acquired their new moniker with the arrival of Logan Kroeber, a fellow West Coast artist whose penchant for experimental drumming and progressive metal melded perfectly with Long's interest in West African Ewe drumming and country blues fingerpicking. The Dodos released their debut album, Beware of the Maniacs, that same year independently, followed by Visiter in 2008. Long and Kroeber added electric vibraphonist Keaton Snyder to the fold and collaborated with producer Phil Ek on 2009's Time to Die, which found the trio exploring a more fleshed-out sound. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ruby Suns (from allmusic):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ruby Suns combine psychedelic indie pop with world music influences, drawing inspiration from the travels of the group's only permanent member, Ryan McPhun. Although born and raised in California, McPhun's thirst for adventure eventually drew him halfway across the globe, where he ventured into Africa and Thailand before settling in New Zealand. Auckland's music scene was rich, and the multi-instrumentalist spent time in various pop groups (the Tokey Tones, the Reduction Agents, and the Brunettes) while fronting his own act, Ryan McPhun &amp;amp; the Ruby Suns. After releasing a self-titled debut under that moniker, the band shortened its name to the Ruby Suns and signed with Lil' Chief Records, securing distribution deals in Europe and Australia along the way. The Ruby Suns toured the U.S. in 2006, and McPhun returned home to write and record the band's sophomore effort in his Auckland basement. Inspired by the indigenous music of Africa and Kenya, the diverse Sea Lion -- named after a sea lion colony that lies adjacent to California's Hwy 1 -- was released in 2008 on several labels, including the Seattle-based Sub Pop.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll email my cell number closer to the day of the show.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew</member_name><member_id>8828135</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255827936000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music Shows</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indierockboston</urlname><id>679091</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Indie Rock Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253540632000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dodos &amp; The Ruby Suns @ The Middle East (Downstairs)</name><id>11425771</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255654800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indierockboston/events/11425771/</event_url></item>