<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Richmond Square</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.827108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-521-9229</phone><name>Waterman Grille</name><city>Providence</city><id>699167</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.380879</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Its been awhile, so its time to go again! If you've never been to or heard about this event, this is your chance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PechaKucha is a world wide phenomena with its roots in Japan, but our Providence PechaKucha has been the the only one world-wide to run consecutively without missing a month! For those that don't know, PechaKucha is a series of short presentations by anyone on any subject. Put simply: 6 minutes and 40 seconds of adult-style ...show &amp;amp; tell. (20 slides every 20 seconds). So for those with short attention spans - its great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We haven't been in a while as a group, so I'm posting it as an event for the uninitiated. Its a great monthly event that brings out lots of people and who knows, maybe you'll be inspired to make your own presentation sometime. I was skeptical when I first heard about it 3 years ago, but it only takes one time and you'll be hooked and back for more each month!&amp;nbsp; For more info on the PechaKucha and the list of presenters this Wednesday click here:&lt;a href="http://pecha-kucha.org/night/providence/newsletters/2375"&gt;http://pecha-kucha.org/night/providence/newsletters/2375&lt;/a&gt;. So, let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the silver scarf! I believe the venue will be downstairs - just ask the Hostess where to go.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327542421000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327098760000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PechaKucha at Waterman Grille!!!</name><id>48951312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327537800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/48951312/</event_url></item>