<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trinity College</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.748314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio</name><city>Hartford</city><id>291370</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.690384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come see a French film (with subtitiles) with your French friends and, if you'd like, meet for pizza beforehand!&lt;br /&gt;The 2008 French Film &amp;quot;The Duchess of Langeais&amp;quot;set in 1820's France will be shown at Trinity College's Cinestudio. The French title is &amp;quot;Ne touchez pas la hache&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;For those who would like to dine -in French- before it, we will meet at 5:30 at First &amp;amp; Last Tavern at 939 Maple Avenue Hartford.  They have delicious pizza and it is some of the best food in Hartford. I chose the 5:30 time so that we don't have to rush.If it's a nice evening perhaps we can sit outside.&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP please say whether you will join us for the film only, or for both film and pizza.The restaurant appreciates a &amp;quot;head count&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;The film is at 7:30 and costs $8; $7 for students, seniors,teachers. The theater can be tricky to find if you've never been there before. Parking is free anywhere on campus.Meet in lobby at 7:25.  &lt;br /&gt;Merci,&lt;br /&gt;Dianne &lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;br /&gt;Guillaume Depardieu, Jeanne Balibar, and Michel Piccoli star in director Jacques Rivette's adaptation of the Balzac novella The Duchesse de Langeais, which tells the tale of a Parisian socialite who is romantically pursued by a Napoleonic war hero. The story begins as grieving French general Armand de Montriveau (Depardieu) arrives at a Majorcan church to speak with French nun Antionette le Langeais (Balibar). General de Montriveau believes le Langeais to be a woman he once loved dearly, but eventually lost. As the pair is reunited under the watchful eyes of the presiding priest and mother superior, their romantic past gradually comes into focus. It was five years ago that bored socialite Antoinette first became enamored with the wounded soldier whose rousing tales of adventure offered exciting contrast to her highly refined lifestyle. Though she was married at the time, the coquettish cosmopolitan quickly fell under the spell of the commanding military man -- who vowed that very night that Antoinette would be his lover. As their romance grows more complicated, the passionate pair finds it increasingly difficult to deny the powerful connection that binds them. ~ Jason Buchanan, All Movie &lt;br /&gt;For further detail try www.ifcfilms.com/viewFilm.htm?filmId=516&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217540184000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French</urlname><id>459167</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Groupe de French</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214752957000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French film and pizza!</name><id>8239219</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217367000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-West-Hartford-Groupe-de-French/events/8239219/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/8/7/global_1365207.jpeg</photo_url></item>