<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From Watson Adventures:&lt;br /&gt;Someone, or something, has been bumping off Museum of Science staffers involved in the recent discovery of a long-lost invention by Benjamin Franklin. This “infernal machine” has a murky past: Freemasons supposedly used it as part of a secret ritual. Are the deaths caused by the invention, or part of the fabled “Curse of the Freemasons”? Or is a serial killer on the loose? Your team of sleuths will have to crack a secret code and uncover the museum’s secrets to solve the mystery and stop the killings. This hunt is for adults only. Warning: this is one of our most challenging hunts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, visit the Watson Adventures website at &lt;a href="http://www.watsonadventures.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.watsonadve...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT: You must purchase tickets for this Meetup from Watson Adventures; RSVPing for this Meetup will not automatically give you a spot in the hunt.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To buy tickets, visit Watson Adventures' online ticket site here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ovationtix.com/trs/pe/8013895" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.ovationti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During checkout, you'll be asked &amp;quot;Are you joining friends who signed up separately? If so, tell us who&amp;quot;.  Write “Nerd Fun”.  Use the discount code &lt;b&gt;NERDFUN&lt;/b&gt; to get a $2 discount.  It is suggested that you get your tickets early as they can sell out.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign in the lobby</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wing</member_name><member_id>3393735</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280169457000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277353103000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watson Adventures' Murder At The Science Museum</name><id>13895362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279993500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13895362/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/6/global_6710214.jpeg</photo_url></item>