<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 N State St </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.206638</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Legislative Office Building (the building in back of the State House)</name><city>Concord</city><id>7703092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.539322</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The NHGOP will hold an informational training session for candidates for State Representative this coming Saturday, June 16th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presenters will include experienced, veteran legislators, campaign professionals, policy experts and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you know other Republicans running, please forward this invitation along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHEN: &lt;br /&gt;

Saturday June 16th, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

9:30am Registration / Coffee &lt;br /&gt;

10:00am Program Begins &lt;br /&gt;

Program will last from 10a-2p, with a break for lunch. Lunch will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHERE: &lt;br /&gt;

Legislative Office Building(the building in back of the State House) &lt;br /&gt;

Room 210 (Second Floor) &lt;br /&gt;

33 N State St – Concord, NH 03301&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information or to RSVP, please contact: hrvpac@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: &lt;br /&gt;

Street parking is available at no charge on any street adjacent to the State House and Legislative Office Building. Due to the Farmer’s Market taking place on Capitol Street, next to the State House, we will open the Legislative Office Building’s parking garage, upper level. To access the upper level, you must enter from Capitol St. Capitol St. is a one way street. You must access Capitol St. via Green St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From I-93, take exit 14. From the North, take a right after you exit – from the South, take a left, heading towards downtown. This is Centre Street. Follow Centre St. through its intersection with N. Main and N. State Streets. At the next set of lights, take a left onto Green St. The second street on your left is Capitol. Click here for a visual look at the area.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340555160000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339621163000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GOP State Rep Candidate Training</name><id>69045472</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339853400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/69045472/</event_url></item>