<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Titcomb Street, Newburyport, MA</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.811325</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Central Congregational Church</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>1669321</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.874229</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What does it take to move from knowledge, concern and inertia about the criticalissues of our time to creativity, engagement, action and a sense of empowerment?For a number of people in the Newburyport area, the answer is the learning,discussion and support that comes from joining with others to form a Community Resilience Circle. These circles are designed to study, discuss and vet ideas forchange in an environment that encourages and supports social action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To date two resilience circles have formed in the Greater Newburyport area and anotherwill be starting this fall. Join us as Transition Newburyport leader Conrad Willeman and other local citizens discuss the empowerment and connectednessthey found in taking part in a Community Resilience Circle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program will be followed by a Local Flavor Community Potluck at 5pm. Local Flavor Community Potlucks are monthly, zero-waste gatherings focused on celebrating local food, engaging discussions and building new friendships in the community. Bring a potluck dish, using a many locally-sourced ingredients as possible, and a “mess kit” (non-disposable plate, cup, utensils and napkin). All ages are welcome..&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Conrad</member_name><member_id>5639588</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369005049000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permaculture Advocates</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1360397</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Northshore Permaculture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366575870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Voices: The Power of Community Resilience Circles</name><id>115464842</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368993600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northshore-Permaculture-Meetup-Group/events/115464842/</event_url></item>