<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list.  A yes list will be provided as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Criteria:  All hikers must be able to maintain a minimum pace of two miles an hour for a minimum of two hours.  All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to trailhead:  This trail climbs to the Kinsman Ridge Trail 0.4 mi. north of North Kinsman from a recently relocated trailhead on the east side of NH 116, 0.3 mi. south of the old trailhead (which was adjacent to the Franconia/Easton town line). The new trailhead, with a short road leading into a large parking area, is 4.7 mi. south of NH 18 in Franconia village, just beyond the Tamarack Tennis Camp, and 1.7 mi. north of the Easton town hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;starting at Mount Kinsman Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 2.00 mi/1 hr 46 min/+1350 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; The trail leaves the southeast corner of the parking area and in 20 yd. it turns sharp left and ascends moderately through a partly logged area. It enters an attractive hemlock forest, soon dips to cross a small brook, and ascends generally eastward. It swings left and levels off, passing an unmarked path diverging sharp left, and in another 30 yd. turns right onto a logging road, joining the older route. (In the reverse direction, turn left off the road onto a footpath at a sign.) The road soon swings left, passes an old sugarhouse that stands on the left, and swings right again. It makes a short bypass to the left of a wet section of road, enters the WMNF and turns right off the road (cairn and arrow), then in 30 yd., turns left onto another road. This road, distinctly older and steeper, crosses a substantial brook near the site of the former Kinsman Cabin. Farther up the trail crosses a small brook that falls over a mossy ledge to the left of the trail, then crosses Flume Brook. Just over Flume Brook, a side path on the right descends close to the brook bank for 150 yd. to small, steep-walled Kinsman Flume, a classic eroded dike with an overhanging boulder at the top that presents a reasonable facsimile of a profile. The main trail continues on the road for another 70 yd., then turns sharp left at the point where another spur path diverges sharp right, descends briefly, then makes an easy ascent to Bald Peak, a bare ledgy dome with fine views that crowns a western spur of Kinsman Mountain. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Bald Peak spur &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 31 min/+1441 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; The blue-blazed trail now winds up the mountainside at easy to moderate grades, with good footing except for short, scattered steep pitches with rough footing. It crosses several small brooks and follows a short relocation to the right. Higher up it swings right and angles upward, then swings left and climbs straight up to the ridge top, where it meets the Kinsman Ridge Trail. For North and South Kinsman, turn right; for Kinsman Pond and Kinsman Junction, turn left.&lt;br /&gt;The ax-blazed trail now joins and follows Flume Brook, winding up the mountainside at easy to moderate grades, with good footing except for short, scattered steep pitches with rough footing. It crosses several small brooks and it swings right and angles upward, then swings left and climbs straight up to the ridge top, where it meets the Kinsman Ridge Trail. For North and South Kinsman, turn right; for Kinsman Pond and Kinsman Junction, turn left. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/12 min/+420 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; From Kinsman Junction, the Kinsman Ridge Trail (now part of the AT for the rest of its length) turns right and climbs up ledges to the junction where the Mt. Kinsman Trail enters on the right, then continues to climb steeply to the summit of North Kinsman. &lt;br /&gt; to North Kinsman &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.90 mi/35 min/+54 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; Here a side path (sign) leads to the left 25 yd. to a fine outlook to the Franconias and continues, descending steeply, another 70 yd. to a ledge that looks directly down on Kinsman Pond. The true summit of North Kinsman is a pointed boulder on the left (east) side of the main trail, 30 yd. north of the outlook spur. The main trail descends steadily to the col between North and South Kinsman, then ascends relatively easily and passes 15 yd. to the west of the north knob of South Kinsman’s summit. The Kinsman Ridge Trail then crosses a scrub-filled sag to the bare south knob of South Kinsman, which is very exposed to the weather. (Note: The section of the trail between South Kinsman and Harrington Pond may require much extra time, particularly for those with heavy packs, and is also somewhat exposed to weather.) &lt;br /&gt; to South Kinsman &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 4.90 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 4 hr 4 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3571 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -306 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +3265 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.90 mi/35 min/-54 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; From here the Kinsman Ridge Trail crosses a scrub-filled sag, passes 15 yd. to the west of the north knob of South Kinsman, and descends relatively easily to the col between South and North Kinsman. The trail then climbs steadily to a side path (sign) that leads to the right; this side path runs 25 yd. to a fine outlook to the Franconias and continues, descending steeply, another 70 yd. to a ledge that looks directly down on Kinsman Pond. The true summit of North Kinsman is a pointed boulder on the right (east) side of the main trail, 30 yd. north of the outlook spur. &lt;br /&gt; to North Kinsman &lt;br /&gt; hike 0.40 mi/12 min/-420 ft on the Kinsman Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt; The Kinsman Ridge Trail now descends steeply to the junction with the Mt. Kinsman Trail on the left. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; hike 1.60 mi/1 hr 31 min/-1441 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; From the Kinsman Ridge Trail, the Mt. Kinsman trial descends straight down from the ridge top. It levels out a bit, crosses several brooks and then continues winding down the mountainside at easy to moderate grades, with good footing except for short, scattered steep pitches with rough footing. In this section, it follows Flume Brook through an ax-blazed trail. &lt;br /&gt;It passes a spur path on the left which descends briefly, then makes an easy ascent to Bald Peak, a bare ledgy dome with fine views that crowns a western spur of Kinsman Mountain. The main trail continues on a road, reaching another side path on the left. This spur descends close to the brook bank for 150 yd. to small, steep-walled Kinsman Flume, a classic eroded dike with an overhanging boulder at the top that presents a reasonable facsimile of a profile. The main trail crosses Flume Brook then crosses a small brook that falls over a mossy ledge to the right of the trail. &lt;br /&gt; to the junction of Bald Peak spur &lt;br /&gt; hike 2.00 mi/1 hr 46 min/-1350 ft on the Mt Kinsman Trail &lt;br /&gt; It crosses a substantial brook near the site of the former Kinsman Cabin. It leaves the road then, in 30 yd., it turns onto another road (cairn and arrow), and leaves the WMNF. It makes a short bypass to the right of a wet section of road, passes an old sugarhouse that stands on the left, then follows alongside the edge of a grass-grown log yard. Many roads enter from the right. The trail always takes a left at these forks. The trail follows a sandy logging road that descends moderately under tall pines to the gate. &lt;br /&gt; to Mount Kinsman Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 9.80 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 8 hr 8 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3878 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3878 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth&lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a black four door Toyota Echo</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1285424280000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284986729000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NORTH &amp; SOUTH KINSMANS</name><id>14830156</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285419600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14830156/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/a/global_17612186.jpeg</photo_url></item>