<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon &amp; Charles Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.356281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>262855</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069084</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>for group expenses</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This event is rain or shine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've been to the Common for demonstrations, rallies, festivals, but have you ever been just to socialize en mass? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us as SoJust kicks off our Summer events with Socializing for Justice on Boston Common for good ole' outdoor fun!  Blankets, food, frisbees, kids, dogs, musical instruments, games...If you can do it outside and you can share it with others, we'll be doing it.  All of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(The photo is of brave SoJusters at last year's event.  We are there, &lt;i&gt;rain or shine!&lt;/i&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PACKING LIST:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;__Blankets&lt;br /&gt;__Camping chairs&lt;br /&gt;__Snacks&lt;br /&gt;__Water&lt;br /&gt;__Games (frisbees, balls, travel board games, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;__Dogs&lt;br /&gt;__Info about events or groups you want to share with SoJusters&lt;br /&gt;__anything else you'd want to do outside and share with others!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you looking for like-minded progressives to hang out in the Common with?  Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns on a blanket? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions while snacking and playing frisbee?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Help us take over a grassy patch at the corner of Beacon and Charles Streets for outdoor family-friendly togetherness.  We're testing out the radical concept of assembling in public, on blankets, with frisbees, for justice.  No loud speakers necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be on the Boston Common near Beacon and Charles Street.  Look for folks in the new SoJust t-shirts and SoJust signs.  We'll be the friendly ones wearing name tags - join us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hilary</member_name><member_id>3092728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>36</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211341916000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1206928868000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Socializing for Justice on Boston Common</name><id>7636915</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211133600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/7636915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/b/global_3694107.jpeg</photo_url></item>