<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>190 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.405361</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Flora Restaurant</name><city>Arlington</city><id>2951791</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.142273</lon></venue><fee><label>Reservation Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/9/7/event_47023671.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The typical Restaurant Week dinner is a limited selection of less-expensive options from the restaurant's regular menu, intended to whet your appetite for a return visit to further explore that menu. But Flora has a different approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They let you choose either a traditional three-course dinner or select two of their "medium" plates with your choice of either an appetizer or a dessert. And what a wonderful range of "medium" plates they have to choose from! Gnocchi with pistachio pesto, steak with chimichurri sauce, an Indian vegetarian plate, grilled bluefish. . . well, it sure sounded like a taster's dream to me! Where else can you get so many options for $33.11?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's more, they are serving this menu throughout the month of August, so if you can't join us on the 14th, check it out on your own beforehand or afterwards and let the group know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must pay a reservation fee of $3 in order to R.S.V.P. -- which will be added to the tip for our table. I will calculate everyone's bill with any add-ons like drinks and let you know what you owe. (Feel free to order entirely from the regular menu if you wish, but note that in this case, I'll request a separate check for you. It's too complicated otherwise!)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a Meetup tent card on the table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315072450000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312917485000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Restaurant Week Dinner at Flora, Arlington</name><id>28865501</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313361000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/28865501/</event_url></item>