<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>People often tell me they don't dream at all or they don't remember their dreams. The truth is that everyone dreams every night during sleep. We usually don't remember our dreams because as soon as we wake up we start thinking about the day ahead and we get up. If we would take a moment to record our dream memories in the morning before we get up, we would find that soon we would be remembering more and more dreams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keeping a dream journal is a great way to remember your dreams. What is a dream journal? A dream journal is a permanent record of your dreams. The most common type of dream journal is a blank book that you write your dreams into. Journals can include drawings as well as written words. You can also interpret your dreams in your journal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this Meetup, we will be doing some show and tell. So, if you have a dream journal, please bring it. If you don't have a dream journal, that's ok, just bring yourself. Deerheart will show the various types of dream journals and explain how to start journaling. We will also be doing dream sharing. If there is time, we may do some journal writing and/or drawing. There will be pens and paper available for people to write with. Anything you write on plain paper can later be transfered to a journal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is an exercise you can do to develop your dream muscles. When you go to bed say the following words to yourself, &amp;quot;When I sleep tonight I will have a dream, I will remember my dream, I will know the meaning of my dream, and I will write my dream down when I wake up.&amp;quot; You can also write these words on a small slip of paper and put into your pillow case. Your unconscious mind will provide you with a dream. Be sure to have paper and pen by your bed before you go to sleep. When you wake up, write down any dream memories or dream fragments you remember. If you don't get anything the first night, do the exercise again the next night. Eventually, you will get something. Then bring your results to our Meetup to share with the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deerheart has been keeping various types of dream journals off and on for twenty-five years. Deerheart is an artist, a spiritual advisor, and dream guide. An experienced explorer of the dream realms, he has had many teachers of art, creativity, yoga, meditation, dreamwork, shamanism, psychology, empowerment, and healing. He has an online dream journal (a dream blog) called &lt;a href="http://deerheartdreams.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Deerheart Dreams&lt;/a&gt; ( &lt;a href="http://deerheartdreams.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://deerheartdreams.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://deerheartdream...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ). In addition to starting Boston Dreamers Meetup Group, he also started the Facebook group called &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=36258693723" target="_blank"&gt;Dream Blog Network&lt;/a&gt; ( &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=36258693723" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=36258693723" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, August 11, 2009&lt;br /&gt;7 pm - 9:00 pm (Two hours)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is a sliding scale - $10-$20. Anyone who cannot afford to pay should contact the group organizer Deerheart, to arrange alternatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. Blessings, Deerheart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by car: Very limited parking at chapel, otherwise nearby streets such as Broadway and Mass Ave. There is a free small parking lot on Kirkland Street side of chapel, up to 8 cars. Coming from either direction on Massachusetts Ave into Harvard Square, turn onto Cambridge Street, then onto Quincy Street and around the corner onto the parking lot on Kirkland Street. The chapel is right on the corner of Quincy Street and Kirkland Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions by T: The Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel is a lovely Gothic-revival stone chapel located at 50 Quincy Street in Cambridge, Mass. Please note that the official and historical name as may be found on maps and church directories is The Cambridge Society of the Church of the New Jerusalem (Swedenborgian). We are located at the corner of Quincy and Kirkland Streets, across from Harvard's monumental Memorial Hall/Sander's Theatre, which is behind Harvard Yard in Harvard Square. Access is an easy 5 minute walk from the Harvard Station MBTA stop on the Red Line and buses - just walk through Harvard Yard and ask anyone for Memorial Hall if you don't readily see the large fancy tower, then walk around the Hall to the chapel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and directions for the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel&lt;/a&gt;, check out their website ( &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252454496000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247792256000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dream Journals and Journaling</name><id>10894083</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250031600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/10894083/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/6/global_9701254.jpeg</photo_url></item>