<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>237 North Quinsigamond Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01545</zip><lat>42.291504</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Donahue Rowing Center</name><city>Shrewsbury</city><id>1617965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.753685</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please arrive in time to be in your kayak and ready to leave the launch, with military precision ;-) at 5:45 PM.  I'd like to keep a good pace so we can do the length of the lake and back (a little over 6 miles round-trip). We'll paddle toward the southern end and turn around after we have gone for about an hour. If we make good time we may be able to explore the southern end a bit before turning around.  Let's see how fast we can go! We'll try to be back at the launch site around sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like to dilly-dally or are a slow paddler, this would not be a good trip for you.  The shoreline is varied with homes, condos and some woods.  It's not so scenic that you would really want to take your time, but it is a nice paddle.  We'll probably see some rowing shells out practicing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find us, look for the entrance to a huge parking lot just north of the driveway for Donahue Rowing Center at 237 North Quinsigamond Ave in Shrewsbury.  The launch site is managed by the town of Shrewsbury and there is a concrete ramp at the bottom. Please launch to the side of the ramp to allow trailered boats access to the ramp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***PLEASE NOTE***&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;: PFD (worn), whistle, Headlamp/flashlight if out near/after sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional/recommended&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: pump/bailer, insect repellent, sunscreen, water, snack, change of clothes in drybag, hat with brim/visor and sunglasses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The following is copied from the Quinsigamond Rowing Assoc. website, and I found it interesting:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Competitive rowing teams first came to Lake Quinsigamond in 1857. Finding the lake ideal for such crew meets, avid rowers established boating clubs on the lake's shores, the first being the Quinsigamond Boating Club. More boating clubs and races followed, and soon many colleges (both local and abroad) held meets on the lake. Beginning in 1895, local high schools held crew races on the lake. In 1952, the lake played host to the National Olympic rowing trials. Lake Quinsigamond is currently considered the fourth best natural body of water for rowing in the world. The lake has played host other national regattas such as the US Nationals in 1979 and the US Masters Nationals in 2005.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367946863000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367598839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Fitness" Paddle Lake Quinsigamond</name><id>117552972</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367876700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/117552972/</event_url></item>