<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>995.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;2 Day Multi-Day Program - Lodging Included&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our program offers more than recipes.  We care about your health and healing. Learn skills easily used at home when the training and cleanse is done.  Follow-up support after the program is available and recommended for all participants. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Goals of the 2 Day Multi-Day Program:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Healing - Through this opportunity, you learn abundant delicious healthy food choices - Additional &lt;li&gt; Healing Techniques and Sessions are also given &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Cleansing - Detox gently and replenish the body with vibrant foods - out with the old, in with the new &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Education - Know the reasons and the science behind this food and lifestyle choice - be an educated eater &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Immersion - Total immersion is extremely helpful to get positive healing momentum in this team supported environment - program includes lodging &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Support and Community - Our team, as well as other participants, offer great support and a community experience to help everyone adopt these simple and effective techniques &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Live Energy and Live Food - Vegan Nutrition and Foods together with Tong Ren energy healing, breathwork, informative talks, meditation, relaxation, sunshine, exercise and community offer an excellent environment for healing &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organic Healing Food&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Daily Nourishing Green Juices - Efficient power packed nutrition for maximum benefit, healing and absorption - 3 times a day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Daily Immune-building wheatgrass juice - every morning &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Nutritious and Delicious Green Smoothies - everyday - Vitamins, minerals and your favorite fruits and greens in a glass &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Easy Kitchen sprouting for mung beans, lentils and others &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Quick &amp;amp; Easy Sandwiches &amp;amp; Wraps - Purple &amp;amp; green cabbage wraps, nori rolls, collard rolls, romaine sandwiches, stuffed bell peppers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Salads and Dressings - Enjoy making and tasting a variety of salads and dressings &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Non-dairy milk - Using ingredients like almonds or sunflower seeds, learn a better alternative to dairy milk for better nutrition and more calcium &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Pasta techniques including Pasta Marinara meal &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Daily Activities and Training&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Easy to learn daily exercises including Master Gao simple warm-up and stretching, Dao Yin Qi Gong, yoga, The 5 Tibetan Rites &amp;amp; Daily Meditation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Basic kitchen knife skills &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Pasta tools and other kitchen utensils &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Tong Ren Group Healing Treatments and Education&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vegan Nutrition Lectures; Healing, detox, food combining, ph balance, colon health, digestion and absorption &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Healthy alternatives to processed sugars &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Including 2 Nights Lodging - 10 hours lectures, demos and presentations - All Meals, Juices - Shared Room&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class Begins Friday Evening for Orientation and Introduction- Friday and Saturday Night Lodging Included&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$895 if Booked 30 Days in advance - Otherwise $995&lt;br /&gt;$800 Each For Couples - Otherwise Shared Room&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information go to: &lt;a href="http://www.livefoodcuisine.com/larchesinn/larchesprograms.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.livefoodcu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>7932349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275223556000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269218664000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2 Day Multi-Day Program - Organic Healing Food</name><id>12950708</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274475600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/12950708/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>