<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join the NBMAA from 5:30-8 p.m. Friday, March 6, 2009 for First Friday  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mar. 6&lt;br /&gt;King Porter Jazz Band&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen Porter is one of the most prominent Bassists of our time. Born and raised in Hartford, CT he began playing the bass at an early age in church becoming very accomplished in the gospel music scene. Seeking for a more challenging form of musical expression he began to apply to the most noted colleges of music. After being turned down by most of them, he was given the chance to audition for the great Jackie Mclean, who gave him the opportunity to attend the Hartt school of music. Jackie Mclean who was known for discovering new talent, knew exactly what type of direction Stephen needed placing him under the tutelage of the great Nat Reeves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through his given talents teamed with the guidance of these great men, Stephen has become a solid bassist who is known for his creativity and ability to set the direction of the music from behind the scenes while maintaining musicianship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen has accompanied very well known musicians such as Mulgrew Miller, Cyrus Chestnut, Jimmy Greene, Wayne Escofree, Warren Byrd, and also played at the legendary jazz club the Blue Note with his mentor Jackie Mclean, who gave him the nickname King Porter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;King Porter is dedicated to performing creative soul searching music and becoming the best bassist he can be. He will be performing with Warren Byrd on piano and David Davis on alto sax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Friday features live jazz music performed by local and nationally-known musicians, an opportunity to view the Museum's premier permanent collection of 300 years of American art, gallery talks, art activities, a chance to mix and mingle with other art and jazz lovers, a selection of light hors d'oeuvres, wine, beer and soda. The cost is $5 for Museum members and $10 for non-members, $3 for beer and wine, soda is free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is so hard to find people here some times plan to come and have a good time and if we connect then great.  If not enjoy the music and the Art.  anybody else want to be the point person???? maybe we need two or three...&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It is so dificult to meet at a certain spot.  On Feb 5 I will e-mail yeses My #</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236631463000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230963432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Friday at New Britain Museum of Art</name><id>9432028</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236378600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/9432028/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/0/global_2892656.jpeg</photo_url></item>