<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Hi, Everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this middle day of the holiday weekend (when traffic will be at its low point!) join us for a hike and picnic here in York.  Most of you are familiar with this hike by now, located in the western end of York away from the beach and crowds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The combined hike and picnic will last about 3 hours.  Total hiking mileage about 4.  From 10:00 - 11:30 we will do the Mount A portion of the hike and from 11:30 - 1:00 we will do the picnic portion of the hike in a super nice wooded area across the street from Mount A.  Footwear appropriate for pebbles, rock slabs, and wet areas are recommended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is OK to leave your picnic lunch in a cooler in your car for the first half of the hike since we will come back again to the car for the second portion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who have more time after 1:00 and wish to go on a longer hike or head out for coffee, we can do so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there! For those hoping to enjoy the foliage enroute - it is about 30% or so in this area - still beautiful though.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Randy&lt;br /&gt;RandyS@maine.rr.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;The directions are easy: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Route 95 north over the big bridge to Exit 7 just before the toll booths. (NOTE: There are two Exit 7s -one in Portsmouth, NH before the bridge and the one in Maine before the toll booths. It‘s that &lt;u&gt;second&lt;/u&gt; Exit 7 - the one in Maine - that we're looking for). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit 7 - Go to the end of the ramp - stop sign - take left - and then the next immediate available right (the road ends at that point, so you have to turn right), and go approximately 6.3 miles (the name of this road is Chases Pond Road which becomes Mountain Road - same road; just keep going straight). You will come to a small parking lot at the base of Mount Agamenticus (the paved road ends at this point). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the lot is full (and it’s small so it usually is), you can park on either side of the road. I’ll be waiting in a silver Subaru Forester across the street for the first couple of hikers, then after that we will gather at the back edge of this parking lot, towards the large boulders under the trees.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>For the first few hikers, we will meet near a silver Subaru Forester on the right side of the road. After that, we will gather at the edge of the parking lot near the boulders. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Randy</member_name><member_id>10613717</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286809807000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286446830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike and Picnic Lunch in York!</name><id>15032053</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286719200000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15032053/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/6/a/global_18158666.jpeg</photo_url></item>