<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 124</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>42.760536</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kidder Mountain</name><city>New Ipswich</city><id>7918052</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.872932</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/d/e/event_140497342.jpeg" width="292" height="231" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;About Kidder Mountain &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Kidder Mountain (1814 ft) is an easy hike located in New Ipswich, NH, in southern NH. &lt;br /&gt;

Distance: 3 miles &lt;br /&gt;

Time: About 2 hours &lt;br /&gt;

Trail: a section of the Wapack Trail (hiking north), plus Kidder Mountain Trail &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.wapack.org/kidder.html"&gt;http://www.wapack.org/kidder.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please note there are some sections of the trail with roots, rocks, and overgrown areas, but it's a relatively easy climb. Plan to wear long pants and bring bug spray, water, snacks, sunscreen, and camera. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The trail head and parking is right off Turnpike Road (Rt. 124) in New Ipswich NH on Old Rindge Road. About 200 ft down the road from Windblown X-C Ski area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/8/a/event_140495722.jpeg" width="295" height="204" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

(Here's the optional part)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the hike we’ll take a short drive over to Pickity Place in Mason NH for a 5-course gourmet lunch! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

About Pickity Place&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Since 1786 our quaint little red cottage has graced the hills of southern New Hampshire, seemingly untouched by time. The enchanting cottage was chosen by Elizabeth Orton Jones as the model for her illustrations in Little Red Riding Hood (Little Golden Books, 1948). Today it is a mecca for gardeners, foodies and anyone looking for inspiration and relaxation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/0/2/event_133376322.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Dining at Pickity Place&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our 5-course gourmet luncheon draws guests back to Pickity Place time after time. From appetizers to dessert, the delightfully different luncheon dishes are accented with herbs and edible flowers grown and harvested from our very own culinary garden, served in a quaint, comfortable atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our menu changes each month and we serve at three private seatings each day: 11:30, 12:45 and 2:00. The dining room is open seven days a week and reservations are advised to assure a table. Be sure to plan some time to enjoy our gardens and uniquely New England gift shop! &lt;br /&gt;

________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pickity Place requires an advance reservation, and their luncheon timeslots fill up quickly so reservations will be made soon. I'll make a 12:45pm reservation. The luncheon is $21.95 per person plus tax and gratuity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pickity Place does not have wine and beer on the menu but we can bring our own which they will serve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More Information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pickityplace.com/"&gt;http://www.pickityplace.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menu:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pickityplace.com/menu.html"&gt;http://www.pickityplace.com/menu.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pickityplace.com/finding.html"&gt;http://www.pickityplace.com/finding.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note, the attendee list must be limited to 10 for the luncheon, but anyone can attend the hike. Reservations for over 10 people require a deposit so instead of trying to collect $ for the deposit I decided to keep the group a small number. There is a wait list available so if more people are interested I will add another date for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike is weather-permitting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you can join us!   &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1344870634000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340740306000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Kidder Mountain and (optional) 5-Course Lunch at Pickity Place</name><id>70845262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344778200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/70845262/</event_url></item>