<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Lexington Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06052</zip><lat>41.664328</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.229.0257</phone><name>New Britain Museum Of American Art</name><city>New Britain</city><id>853476</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.792121</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>**This event is hosted by the AIGA - please direct any questions and/or your RSVP to secretary@connecticut.aiga.org **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Patrick Coyne&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patrick Coyne will discuss the history and philosophy of the magazine, how CA's competitions work and how creatives are chosen for profiles in the magazine. He will also present a selection of award-winning design and advertising projects produced on limited budgets and discuss the future of creativity in the post-information age.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, April 29, 2009, 6:00–9:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Britain Museum of American Art&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Hart Benton Gallery&lt;br /&gt;56 Lexington Street, New Britain CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AIGA Members: $15&lt;br /&gt;Non-members: $20&lt;br /&gt;AIGA Student Members with ID: $5&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash or check accepted at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP to&lt;/b&gt; secretary@connecticut.aiga.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Patrick Coyne&lt;/b&gt; · Patrick Coyne is editor and designer of Communication Arts. In addition to determining the layout and content of the magazine, Coyne writes feature stories and the editor's column. He has also guest lectured at numerous creative clubs and universities. The recipient of numerous awards for his design and art direction (including a silver medal from the Society of Illustrators), Coyne received the 2004 Design Leadership Award from the American Institute of Graphic Arts. Prior to joining CA in 1986, Coyne studied at the California College of the Arts, worked for Michael Mabry Design and SBG Partners and established the multi-discipline, San Francisco-based design firm of Patrick Coyne Stephanie Steyer Design Office.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Communication Arts&lt;/b&gt; · Communication Arts is the leading professional journal for designers, art directors, design firms, agencies and corporate communications departments. Current circulation is 60,000 paid. Through editorials, feature articles and annual competitions it sponsors, CA provides new ideas and information, while promoting the highest professional standards for the field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sponsors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lebonpress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lebon Press&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nbmaa.org/" target="_blank"&gt;New Britain Museum of American Art&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241215780000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239656615000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AIGA - Patrick Coyne</name><id>10177312</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241042400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/10177312/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/e/c/global_701868.jpeg</photo_url></item>