<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>144 Green Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316454</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sweeney Concert Hall in Sage Hall </name><city>Northampton</city><id>1420666</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.638301</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Impulse Ensemble is performing a free concert in Northampton. &lt;br /&gt;Sounds like a great gig thisu Sunday at Sweeney Concert Hall in Sage Hall at Smith College&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fusion Nomads - 4pm-7pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Smith College Music Department presents Fusion Nomads, a free concert of music spanning genres and continents, featuring artists including Hassan Hakmoun, The Impulse Ensemble, and Senegalese hip-hop group Gokh-Bi System. Starts at 4 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Morocco-born performer Hassan Hakmoun, is a staple of New York’s rock, jazz, and fusion scenes for his “spiritually charged voice and playing.” His driving, rhythmic music and his instrument, the sintir (a long-necked African bass lute) are rooted in Gnawa, a Moroccan ceremony of spiritual release. Hakmoun’s trance-like music is deeply felt, and he brings a tradition of healing to renderings of jazz, pop, and classical Arabic music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Impulse Ensemble features Jim Matus (electric laoutar and vocals), Derrik Jordan (electric violin, vocals, and percussion), and Tony Vacca (balafon, gongs, percussion and Spoken Word). They describe their work as a “red-hot way-cool free-flow fusion of World Music, Jazz and Spoken Word” and “share a special interest in the converging traditions and innovations that are constantly redefining what it is to be an American musician at this point in time.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of Gokh-Bi System, a Senegalese hip-hop group, are childhood friends from the Dakar, Senegal hood of Pikine Guinaw Rail–literally “the other side of the tracks.” Gokh-Bi System reunites rap with its ancient West African ancestors in a style dubbed “ancient meets urban.” A distinctive component of GBS’s authentic sound is the ekonting, an ancient instrument once used to calm social unrest played by Sana. Gokh-Bi’s positive message, inspired by rap greats from The Last Poets to Chuck D, transform the group's sound into an uplifting yet hard-hitting African homecoming for hip hop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.impulseensemble.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.impulseens...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289233625000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288890630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fusion Nomads </name><id>15339095</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289163600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/15339095/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/9/global_19384137.jpeg</photo_url></item>