<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Oxford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.378357</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Museum of Natural History</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692976</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Support the local music scene at a Nerd-tastic Cocktail Party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TICKETS are available at the door tonight.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.paypalobjects.com/en_US/i/scr/pixel.gif" width="1" height="1" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Cambridge Symphony Orchestra cordially invites you to our fourth annual benefit gala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSO Night at the Museum II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;An evening exploring the wonders of live music and natural history&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hors d’oeuvres, Cash Bar – Music, Door Prizes, Raffle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sunday, April 7, 2013 6:30PM – 9:30PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Adults: $25&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Children 12 and Under: $10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please visit the Will Call desk in the Museum Lobby to identify yourself as having pre-paid for your tickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring additional friends and family. We will be able to accept cash, checks, or credit card payment there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Silent Auction Items will be on display in the Dinosaur Hall matched with a descriptive page and a bid sheets for each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Minerals Exhibit the CASH BAR will again be cash-only so remember to bring the necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kleznics will provide lively music as you mount the staircase to the Museum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Five ensembles from the Cambridge Symphony Chamber Players will entertain in Colors or Dinosaurs Again, check your program for who will be performing were, when during the Gala.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Con Brio, a favorite last year, will perform in Dinosaurs just before the awarding of the Raffle and Auction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raffle and Silent Auction wrap-up begins at 8:45. We aim to award the last Raffle prize at about 9:15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have arranged for &lt;strong&gt;FREE PARKING at the 52 Oxford Street&lt;/strong&gt; garage. &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/images/stories/hmnh_map.pdf"&gt;http://www.hmnh.harvard.edu/images/stories/hmnh_map.pdf&lt;/a&gt; Please tell the attendant 'We're going to the Cambridge Symphony Gala at the Harvard Museum of Natural History&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking the MBTA Subway:&lt;/strong&gt;Take the Red Line to the Harvard Square stop. Walk through Harvard Yard and down Oxford Street one block. The Harvard Museum of Natural History is the large brick building on your right, just a six minute walk from Harvard Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking the MBTA Commuter Rail:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the Fitchburg Line to Porter Square. Walk 50 yards on Somerville Avenue, cross the tracks on the bridge, and bear right onto Oxford Street and continue to #26. The museum is less than a mile from Porter Square.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving directions&lt;/strong&gt; use the address:Harvard Museum of Natural History, 26 Oxford Street, Cambridge, MA in online maps and GPS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off-campus parking On-Street metered parking: There are a limited number of 2-hour metered spaces located on Oxford and Kirkland Streets. &lt;strong&gt;Parking is free on Sundays and resident permits are not required.&lt;/strong&gt; Please read the street signs carefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commercial garages: There are commercial parking garages in Harvard Square; however, the museum cannot validate parking for those businesses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a meetup sign, and meetup stickers.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365648439000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363101821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CSO Night at the Museum II – Fourth Annual Benefit Gala</name><id>108888562</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365373800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/108888562/</event_url></item>