<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meeting will be full of decisions, information, updates, ideas and of course, photo's of Oshkosh 09.&lt;br /&gt;Have a say in our future and be here and get involved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matt Scales, our webmaster (and cook) was awarded the Web Editor's 1st Place for our own website! Nationally recognized now out of over 1,000 chapters! We'll congratulate Matt tonight also... Good going Matt. Watch for the next issue of EAA Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;An idea I discussed with Matt was to see if we could erect a small monument, sort of, near the picnic tables at FIT, on that grass strip area to the right of the gate. On it have the airfield diagram and how traffic patterns are flown etc. So people can &amp;quot;see&amp;quot; and understand.. Along with a couple more outside speakers for unicom. The kind you see at a state park or something on that order...&lt;br /&gt;Just another idea for the communitty stuff....  :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regular articles in papers regarding GA and benefits. A column monthly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Local aerial shots for papers submitted regularly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chamber membership and participation from fca and fpa.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NE leaders forum created to refresh and share ideas&lt;br /&gt;To local airports and communitties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scholarship or other funds redirected towards local GA ads.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open House at KFIT as outlined in AOPA's site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fields trips from local schools organised and publicised on a larger scale. One whole school at a time coordinated with teachers classroom work. Math, science, history...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Videos taken and put on you tube and FPA site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Offer free Communitty Leader flights in fall/spring. Fuel discounts and help from FIT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raise our monies (for these events) with local Plane Wash days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Offer to pay fuel or subsidise for participating pilots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Compile list of Who's Who of FPA members and what they do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Include members of Gale associates for everything. They know the details about FIT's future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Promote GA and FIT on a larger blitz scale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wings and Wheels media blitz.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And anything else??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe, &lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250370944000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247612561000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 August Meetup</name><id>10877382</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250028000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/10877382/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/c/1/global_4198801.jpeg</photo_url></item>