<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Typical coffee tab</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The first Bay State Underground reading of the 2009-2010 season. After the reading, we may retire to a local cafe or pub to discuss our own writing and larger literary issues. Accordingly, bring copies and be prepared for conversation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The readers: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saskya Iris Jain began collecting stories at an early age in New Delhi, where she was raised by a German mother and Indian father. She studied at Berlin’s Freie Universität and Columbia University. She holds an MA in Theatre Studies and English Language and Literature. Her translation of Erika Fischer-Lichte’s “The Transformative Power of Performance: A New Aesthetics” was published by Routledge in 2008, and she is currently an MFA candidate studying fiction at Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rebecca van Laer grew up in Georgia. She has work published or forthcoming in The Cimarron Review, Monkeybicycle, Pemmican, and others. She is currently an MFA candidate at Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Yuill's work has appeared in A Public Space, Newsday, Salamander, Literary Imagination and Coelecanth, among others. His first book of poetry, Medicine Show, is forthcoming from the University of Chicago Press next spring. Advance copies may be obtained on Amazon.com. He teaches at the New England Institute of Art, the Massachusetts College of Art and Boston University. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michelle Sterling is in the MFA program at Boston University.   She's primarily been published by small presses that have the names of superheroes, such as Pistol Press, Cyclops Press, Matrix magazine, and Invisible Publishing.  A non-fiction article about a psychology study she conducted in a hospice in Bangalore will be published in The Believer in 2010.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260144380000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257556397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reading: Bay State Underground</name><id>jnhtymqbgb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259971200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/11815983/</event_url></item>