<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fearing Pond Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.824314</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 508-866-2526</phone><name>Fearing Pond, Myles Standish State Forest</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>987634</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.670242</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Fish without a license this day only at Fearing Pond during the Myles Standish State Forest 4th Annual Fishing and Nature Appreciation Event, “Take Me Fishin'!” Bring your own poles or use ours.  We provide the worms and we’ll even bait your hook for you. Fishing demonstrations will get you started and there’ll be someone nearby to assist if needed. The pond is freshly stocked with trout and prizes are awarded for the biggest fish (last year we had 18 winners thanks to local donors!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But there’s more than fishing! Fun and informative nature activities will highlight the wonders of the Myles Standish State Forest pine barrens. Activities include: find-that-bird, build-a-fairy-house, gyotaku printing, Lubadrums drum-circles and more. Winners of the 2010 Friends of Myles Standish State Forest 2nd Annual photo contest will be announced at 2:45 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel like working to help the forest before playing? Join either the Girl Scouts Wareham Service Unit or Den 7 Carver Cub Scouts for forest work parties in recognition of National Public Lands Day from 10 AM to Noon and then come to fish.  Contact Sharl Heller to sign up for a work party or to volunteer: email slheller@comcast.net, phone (508) 591-7533.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Take Me Fishin’!”  is sponsored by The Friends of Myles Standish State Forest (FMSSF), the Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR), and MassWildlife. Spend the day with us at Fearing Pond, where you can fish, BBQ, picnic, swim, enjoy learning about nature or just hang out with people who love the forest. The event is free, accessible and open to the public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information contact DCR in MSSF at (508) 866-2526 or email friends@friendsmssf.com, or visit &lt;a href="http://www.friendsmssf.com" target="_blank"&gt;Friends of Myles Standish State Forest on the web at www.friendsmssf.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/thomgiff#100082" target="_blank"&gt; Photos from the 2009 fishing event are available here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melissa </member_name><member_id>9473646</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Vickstrom</member_name><member_id>11406046</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285536606000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284726690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Myles Standish State Forest Free Family Fishing Event</name><id>14802036</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/14802036/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/4/global_18013812.jpeg</photo_url></item>