<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Inman Square</address_2><address_1>212 Hampshire St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-9330</phone><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>696974</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.100572</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rylesjazz.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ryles Jazz Club &lt;/a&gt;Saturday March 6 at 9:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;b&gt;ATLAS SOUL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  world music for world peace!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are back at Ryles for a great show! We 'll play new tunes and have many special guests...&lt;br /&gt;Bring your dancing shoes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4pPJWl31Ats" target="_blank"&gt; A short video from our show at Ryles back in Oct.09&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=282520735697&amp;amp;ref=mf" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Event Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlas-soul.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Get a free download of ATLAS SOUL's newest CD when you sign-up to the mailing list!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price $12 at the door&lt;br /&gt;$10 if you say that you are from this meet-up group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Atlas Soul's blend of jazz, funk and Middle-Eastern/Arabic grooves is a facinating sonic stew that will catch any listener's ear. This is their second appearence on our CD- We like'em, and you will too.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;- Global Rhythm Magazine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“What hits hardest about Atlas Soul’s sound is the natural funk of North African music and also powerful vocals, which span fluid, passionate Gnawa melodies and husky Raï hooks. There is great wisdom in a world-music outfit that embraces divergent genres (but not so many that the sound loses its identity)&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Banning Eyre - The Phoenix &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feedback we got from our last shows..(Thanks, it means a lot to us!)&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sheila&lt;br /&gt;October 13, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ On a scale of 1-10, Atlas Soul is way beyond a 10! The musicians are extremely talented, spirited, professional. The music is a nice blend of musical funk, world, jazz...even a hint of hip hop beats. Great energy &amp;amp; an engaging interaction with the audience, it was easy for the band to rouse the crowd to dance, clap and sing along throughout the show for an incredibly fun time! Sets were long &amp;amp; satisfying, the one break very brief. I loved the band, all of the music, danced all night and place them among on the best bands I've seen in a long time! It was a great time for all! A must see for folks who love this style of music and who love to dance. ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;L.N. (Cambridge)&lt;br /&gt;January 5, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Wow. Three thumbs up! What a great evening, even though Atlas Soul only played one set. Excellent band - the best I've seen in a Boston club - If what I saw last night was typical, these guys are NYC-quality, no problem. More specifically - 1) the mix of genres (funk, North African, soul, jazz, world) really was as described and it all worked really well together, each element coming out distinctly at different times, but all of it blending together smoothly and unbelievably well; 2) their music is great to dance to; and 3) even though the music itself has a really nice raw energy, they're the most professional-sounding band I've seen in a club in Boston - each member by himself could probably make any lesser band worth seeing just bc that member is so good; all together, they have a nicely polished sound, and are really &amp;quot;together&amp;quot; as a band.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have a table reserved</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheila </member_name><member_id>6189105</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268142006000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265908499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ATLAS SOUL  (jazz world)</name><id>12580721</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267927200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/12580721/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/f/global_13047263.jpeg</photo_url></item>