<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;I will post more trail descriptions later. &amp;nbsp;We will be starting from the trailhead on Route 302, unless someone can confirm that the parking lot at the head of the connector is clear during the winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a traverse, so there will be no need to carpool to another location. &amp;nbsp; We'll ascend to the summit of Eisenhower via the Crawford Path (Starting at the Crawford Path on Route 302), then double back to hit Mt. Pierce and descend via the Webster Cliff Trail and the Mizpah Cutoff which will take us back to the Crawford Path. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for winter cold and potentially poor weather conditions. DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is dangerous in cold weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance. Come prepared to stay dry!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Traction (crampons) and head lamps will be required. &amp;nbsp;Microspikes will not be sufficient.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunrise is at 6:44 am.  Sunset will be at 5:35 pm. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike is *VERY EXPOSED*. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are no huts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a full winter hike. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER.  If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around.  The mountain will be there another day. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My hikes area always dog friendly, but please know the limits and abilities of your dog in cold weather and snow.  I will not have my dogs with me on this hike. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike.  I rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form of great views &amp;amp; enjoying the outdoors, SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable, I will reschedule. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - If you do not provide us with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book time is about 7 hrs, 20 minutes and 10.1 miles&lt;/strong&gt;.  Plan on it taking ** hours, possibly more with the winter conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit   &lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------   &lt;br /&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crawford Path from Route 302 to Southern End of the Eisenhower Loop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.3 mi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.5 hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Crawford path begins on US 302 opposite the AMC Crawford Notch Hostel.&amp;nbsp; After .2 miles, it merges with the Crawford Connector (on the left).&amp;nbsp; Continue straight up the Crawford Path.&amp;nbsp; The Crawford Path follows the south bank of Gibbs Brook and at .6 miles a side path leads 40 yards to the left to Gibbs Falls.&amp;nbsp; Soon the trail passes an information sign for the Gibbs Brook Scenic Area, then climbs moderately but steadily.&amp;nbsp; At about 1.2 miles from Mt. Clinton Rd, the trail begins to cimb away from the brook, angling up the side of the valley.&amp;nbsp; At 1.0 miles, the Mizpah Cutoff diverges east for Mizpah Spring hut.&amp;nbsp; The Crawford Path continues to ascend at easy to moderate grades, crossing several small brooks, then reaches its hight point on the shoulder of Mt. Pierce and runs almost level, breaking into the open with fine views.&amp;nbsp; At 3.1 miles it reaches the junictio with the Webster Cliff Trail.&amp;nbsp; From Mt. Pierce to Mt. Eisenhower, the path runs through patches of scrub and woods with many open ledges that give magnificient views in all diretions.&amp;nbsp; Cairns marks the way.&amp;nbsp; The path winds about heading generally in a northeasterly direction, staying fairly near the poorly defined crest of the braod ridge, which is composed of several rounded humps.&amp;nbsp; At 3.8 miles, the trail crosses a small stream in the col, then ascents mostly on ledges to the junction with the Mount Eisenhower Loop, which diverges left at 4.3 m&lt;/span&gt;iles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eisenhower Loop to the summit of Eisenhower and back&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;.8 mi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;50 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eisenhower Loop to Webster Cliff Trail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;1.2 mi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;50 minutes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webster Cliff Trail to the Mizpah Cutoff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;1.2 mi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;30 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mizpah Cutoff to the Crawford Path&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;.7 miles&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;35 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crawford Path to Route 302&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;1.9 mi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;1 hr 5 minutes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Totals  &lt;br /&gt;--------  &lt;br /&gt;10.1 miles  &lt;br /&gt;7 hours, 20 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;DISCLAIMER (SHAMELESSLY PLAGERIZED FROM ANOTHER MEETUP HIKER): MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY OR WINTER HIKING. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN  (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS IN WINTER BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic, usually a Meetup Sign in the window</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298308720000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>They are there! I need the exercise! Time is running out to get in your winter peaks!</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297804299000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter 48:  Eisenhower and Pierce</name><id>16577022</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298208600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/16577022/</event_url></item>