<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>352 Hooksett Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>43.011730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Livingston Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>671425</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.453660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>join us for a weekly walk around the pond when  you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;update 2/3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I just wanted to add a few comments.  I was very encouraged by our HUGE group last week... but it was also a bit overwhelming!  in a good way!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know its a bit corny, but since we are still getting to know one another i will do an attendance for all that reply yes for the meet up.  that being said, as a general note, if you know you can't make it, please make every effort to change your response.  I do look at the website right before i leave the house.  I would hate to wait for some one who isn't coming, and leave someone who is late. and please forgive me, i'm really bad at names!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, with such a variety of dogs, some of us walk faster/slower than others.  I would like to maintain a consistant pace, but don't want anyone to have a hard time keeping up.  If you know you will be slower, please let us know and we can match you with a buddy. I don't want anyone walking alone, it defeats the purpose of having such a great big group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, we will try to keep the loop going, walking around twice, straight through.  this comes back to slower/faster walkers.  maybe we can find a happy medium that everyone is comfortable with?  as always if you have time constraints, just let us know and  we'll see you off! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know some folks wanted to take advantage of some of the off the trail trails. for the most part, izzy and i will be walking the regular loop, but feel free to take advantage of the parks offerings.  I just don't want anyone off on their own!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if anyone has any questions or comments, please feel free to comment!  this is designed to be a &amp;quot;group effort&amp;quot; and if you have an idea just put it out there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;we'll see everyone sunday, and i know we didn't get to it, but there is a coffe shop close by so speak up and let me know if you want to head that way.  I'm pretty easy going, i just want iz to have her friends!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>people with dogs will find each other, scent, sight or sound</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>melissa </member_name><member_id>7279035</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234290120000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232677537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Livingston Park/ Dorrs Pond</name><id>9582545</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234116000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/9582545/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/3/4/global_4216148.jpeg</photo_url></item>