<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Certified Hypnotherapist Glenn Bigonet is going to be introducing us to hypnotism.  Here is a description of this fascinating event from Glenn:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Ever wonder what hypnosis/hypnotherapy really is?  If you could be hypnotized?  Does it really work?  What is it good for?  How it can help you in your life?   Join Glenn Bigonet, Certified Hypnotherapist, for this 2 hour discussion and demonstration of hypnotherapy and get all your questions answered and more.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The truth about hypnosis: what it is, and what it isn’t. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How you can use hypnosis to help you in your life without extensive training. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;What waking hypnosis is and how it is used to control you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The different levels of hypnosis and the benefits of each. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The different modalities of hypnotherapy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The secrets of how to use a pendulum. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A simple yet powerful technique for reducing anxiety. &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glenn Bigonet is a Mental Health Counselor in private practice in Needham.  He regularly uses hypnosis and teaches self-hypnosis to help his clients free themselves of their emotional blocks so that they can feel freer and more in control of their lives.  For more information about Glenn and his work, check out his website at &lt;a href="http://www.glennbigonet.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.glennbigonet.com&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost of attending the hypnotism lesson is $10.00.  The event will be held at Glenn’s office in Needham.  There is plenty of free parking.  In addition, one can get there by taking the Commuter Rail to Needham Heights or by bus.  I can also give a few people a ride to Riverside (Green Line) after the event.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Glenn Bigonet</member_name><member_id>9409368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269262610000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264987827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hypnotherapy:  What is it Really? - A Fascinating Event Led By Glenn Bigonet</name><id>12478635</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269039600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/12478635/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/e/0/global_3173088.jpeg</photo_url></item>