<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Understand jQuery's vast impact to become more productive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Earlier last year we had the pleasure of hearing from &lt;a href="http://www.bostonphp.org/component/option,com_gigcal/task,details/gigcal_gigs_id,59/Itemid,42/" target="_blank"&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt; founder, John Resig as he introduced us to his open source JavaScript Library.  This month, please join BostonPHP and Ken Downs (founder of Andromeda; see our &lt;a href="http://www.bostonphp.org/component/option,com_gigcal/task,details/gigcal_gigs_id,27/Itemid,42/" target="_blank"&gt;PHP Framework discussions&lt;/a&gt;) as he shows how jQuery was crucial to completing the &amp;quot;last mile&amp;quot; of the Andromeda user interface.  There will be many code examples, ranging from the simple to the not-so-simple, leading to an overall conclusion that jQuery is best thought of not as a collection of cool tricks, but as a comprehensive foundation for a very productive approach to browser programming. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an additional bonus, we will be giving away two copies of Learning jQuery 1.3 and jQuery UI 1.6 courtesy of our friends at Packt Publishing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ken Downs has been programming business software since 1992.  In 2004 he started &lt;a href="http://www.secdat.com" target="_blank"&gt;Secure Data Software&lt;/a&gt; to develop and promote &lt;a href="http://www.andromeda-project.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Andromeda&lt;/a&gt;, an open source, PHP programmer productivity tool with the motto &amp;quot;the fastest easiest way to get it done, get it right.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239152451000</updated><rating><average>4.44999980927</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233838177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March User Group:: jQuery and the Last Mile</name><id>9678782</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236810600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/9678782/</event_url></item>