<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>559 Washington Street Boston, MA 02111</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353710</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Paramount Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>7356002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062431</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;How do you imagine your downtown? During the last decade Boston’s downtown has been notably recognized as an area that is only active during the workday hours, however, in the past few years, many individuals and organizations have been working to widen the appeal of the area and increase its activity. Boston’s downtown neighborhood is currently being transformed into one of the most vibrant areas of the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Downtown Boston bridges together the Theatre District, Downtown Crossing, the Ladder District and The Financial District. Each neighborhood is dynamic in their own right and provides Boston with invaluable assets. With a renewed perspective on downtown Boston and its potential we will craft a conversation about its current state and the possibilities for its future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panelists include Joe Larkin, principal, Millennium Partners; Rosemarie E. Sansome, president, Downtown Boston Business Improvement District Corp.; Ed Kane, principal, Big Night Entertainment Group and downtown resident; Amy Grier, a downtown resident; and, Craig Davis, Macy’s store manager. The moderator is Nancy Ludwig FAIA, Icon Architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reception: 6:30 – 7 pm &lt;br /&gt;

Forum: 7 – 8:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://commonboston.org/cb12-forum/</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jen Sutherby</member_name><member_id>47375052</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340239802000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337818839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>COMMON BOSTON - Forum: Downtown Boston: Past, present and future</name><id>66081512</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340231400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/66081512/</event_url></item>