<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>330 Pequot Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06890</zip><lat>41.136570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 292-6124</phone><name>Southport Galleries</name><city>Southport</city><id>1211138</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.283801</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/a/event_95640682.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;You are invited to a very special event on Sunday, March 11, 2012, from 4:30 to 6:30 PM! We are hosting an artists' reception to honor the youth who participated in this year's Discovered Spirit Project. This is a rare opportunity for you to meet youth representative of those whom we serve through our programs at Covenant to Care for Children. The participants created masks guided by professional Connecticut artists, who volunteered their time and talents to the project, Dorothy Hall, Heather Wilson, Julie Nearing and Marta Cunha, and Rachel Correll. The masks are part of a juried show displayed at Southport Galleries in Fairfield County. Sarah Biggers, Gallery Manager, has again generously allowed use of this beautiful Southport gallery located in the renovation of the village's historic hardware store. Our Discovered Spirit Exhibit will share gallery space with acclaimed professional artists of the region! Celebrity judges include: Diann Cook, artist and author, and Representative Tony Hwang of Fairfield who will present awards for the masks showing the greatest originality, presentation, and representation. Beverages and hors d'ourves by Artisan at The Delamar Hotel will guarantee this to be an afternoon to remember. This is a free event. Southport Galleries is located at 330 Pequot Ave, Southport, southportgalleries.com. For more information, please contact Covenant to Care for Children. We hope to see you there, and please invite your friends and neighbors! In Our Third Year Covenant to Care for Children (CCC) is pleased to announce our Discovered Spirit Project. This project is for children and youth with any experience in Connecticut's Department of Children and Families, the Foster Care system or the CCC Mentoring Program. The project is intended to give them a voice by encouraging self-expression through art. Words alone are not enough to express what children feel. This is especially true when they are faced with the complex issues of divorce, grief, violence, abuse, neglect or coping with poverty. We are giving a voice to these children to express a wide range of emotions and help them work through conflicts and traumas. We expect to see an array of outcomes with our masks from the whimsical to the evocative. While expressing themselves in this visual way, the children gain a sense of empowerment that can help them develop a positive self-image and improve their self-esteem. After the gallery opening event, the masks will be available for viewing and purchase at the gallery through March 16, 2012. After this period, the masks will travel to faith-based, public, and gallery sites throughout Connecticut as a traveling display during the following ten months. Our goal is to bring broader awareness of Covenant to Care for Children and the children we serve, offer an opportunity at recognition and accomplishment to the children participating, and build support of our programs. To ask questions about upcoming Discovered Spirit events near you, please visit our website. Share and help promote our advocacy work by shopping for art gifts, apparel and merchandise in our Zazzle store. To visit the store, click the link CCC's Store at Zazzle or use the shopping screen found on our CCC home page. www.covenanttocare.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We have the entire gallery for this event.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331520563000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329872568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discovered Spirit Project</name><id>53263232</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331497800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/53263232/</event_url></item>