<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Under the Hood: Open Source Business Models in Context - given by Stephen Walli, Vice-president of Open Source Development Strategy for Optaros. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People debate regularly about whether or not open source software is “good for business,” and how one makes money on something given away “for free.” They raise concerns over the commoditization effects and portray a gloomy future where open source software will “eat its way” up a stack of functionality until software is valueless. This talk looks at historical open source companies, then steps back to look under the hood at a broader business context for the dynamics at work to provide a business model for open source software. Part of the story behind Microsoft´s community projects will be told along the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, after any healthy technical discussion food &amp;amp; drink must follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optaros is located next to TD Banknorth Garden, so there's plenty of nearby parking and access via the Green and Orange Line. There is a Garden events scheduled for the 3rd so please plan accordingly if you're driving in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.BostonPHP.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.BostonPHP....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1128641612000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston PHP Meetup November Meetup</name><id>4777873</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1131060600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/4777873/</event_url></item>