<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>HOLIDAY INN SELECT WOBURN</address_2><address_1>15 Middlesex Canal Park </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.497452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-897-4000</phone><name>Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grill </name><city>Woburn</city><id>1173954</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.158722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;***Please Update your RSVPs fot his event***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join my Red Sox Natives Meetup for our First Annual Spring Training Kick-Off Happy Hour and Party at 6 pm on Saturday, March 12 at Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grille in Woburn. as we prepare for the 2011 Red Sox season and Kiss Winter Goodbye with live music from the Herland Brothers at 9pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have never been to Scoreboard, it is located at 15 Middlesex Canal Park Lane next to the Holiday Inn and Showcase Cinema off Route 128 in Woburn. Scoreboard has 18 High Definition and Plasma TVs ranging in size from 50 to 92 inches. More info at http;//www.tpsscoreboard.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join the Red Sox Natives at Scoreboard if you are a Red Sox fan or Baseball fan. Join us if you are a Boston Happy Hour Drinking Buddy looking for a different suburban venue. Join us if you have something Baseball to promote. Join us if you are sick of winter and like the Herland Brothers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information on the redsoxnatives and the event can be found on meetup or on redsoxnatives.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It promises to be a busy night&amp;nbsp;starting at 6 pm with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Complimentary popcorn, wings and treats provided by Scoreboard. There is a Cash Bar.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet &amp;amp; Greet with Red Sox Natives and Organizers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet&amp;nbsp;Native and Boston Happy Hour Drinking Buddy Mindy Finkelstien who is representing the Natives on May 22 in The Run To Home Base 9k at Fenway Park. Complete Details are on the Natives calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any optional donations to Mindy's&amp;nbsp;$1,000.00 Mandatory Fundraising Goal&amp;nbsp;will get yoy raffle tickets for wine, Yankees tickets...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participate in fun trivia and the Natives 2011 Fantasy Forecast Contest (Details to be announced)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 9pm stick around for optional dinner, drinks and dancing with live music provided by the&amp;nbsp;Herland Brothers at Scoreboard's Annual Kiss Winter Goodbye Bash. &lt;a href="http://www.herlandbrothers.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.herlandbrothers.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.herlandbrothers.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scoreboard will be packed after 8:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to tip your servers and maintain your own food and bar tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us early or later. Wear your Sox gear. Bring cool guests and fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover, however please RSVP here and update so Scoreboard can handle us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you on Saturday, March 12.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frank&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the Scoreboard hostess to direct you to the Red Sox Natives section. All are encouraged to wear Red Sox gear.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>3178870</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299987802000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It has been a long winter. Spring Training is under way. Saturday night is the night we turn the clocks forward and the days get longer. A bunch of Tonya's Happy Hour Drinking Buddies who are Red Sox Natives are attending.</why><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298926566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Sox Natives 2011 Spring Training KickOff Happy Hour&amp; Kiss Winter GoodbyeBash</name><id>16739664</id><headcount>51</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299970800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/16739664/</event_url></item>