<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>225 Water Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.981853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 778-8856</phone><name>Seacoast Artists Gallery</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1073167</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.949883</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>200.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We're excited to bring Sid Ceasar's extraordinarily well-received Portable Portrait workshop back to the Seacoast. Whether you're interested in lighting or not, you'll find this workshop extremely worthwhile, and take away lots of information you'll use for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/3/a/event_21877946.jpeg" style="max-height : 200px ; max-width : 200px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;I can honestly say Sid's has been the best workshop I've ever taken,&amp;nbsp;and last year's participants will back this up. I enjoyed using and applying simple techniques and I use what I learned whenever I'm out with my gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Portable Portrait Workshop is a portable lighting workshop with Sid Ceaser (see &lt;a href="http://www.sidceaserfineart.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Sid's websites&lt;/a&gt;). This workshop will give attendees a chance to learn location portraiture with affordable, small, battery powered speedlights, using a selection of light modifiers. Get your flash off the camera axis and up on a lightstand, and start learning the simple, effective ways to create compelling portraiture outside on location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Schedule&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start at the Gallery where Sid will spend about an hour introducing lighting concepts and showing you the inexpensive equipment you need (or may already have) in order to light like the pros. Then we'll head outside and practice what we learned until the last photographer drops (usually between 7 and 8PM).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Cost&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The cost is $200, which includes equipment, model fees, location fees, and everything else. Refunds will be given if the workshop is canceled, rescheduled, or if you cancel at least 10 days prior to the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to meet base costs, we'll need a minimum if five in order to go forward. We will cap the amount of photographers at eight in order to give everyone a fair shot at plenty of practice. If we get a lot of folks on a waiting list, we'll schedule another Workshop soon thereafter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;What to Bring&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Bring yourself, your SLR camera with plenty of room on a memory card, and small notepad and pen for taking notes. Your camera should have a hot shoe to which we'll connect a remote trigger for the light. Any lens will do, but a wide angle lens will work best. Most importantly, bring a positive attitude! Everything else will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should be familiar with the basic cameras operation, how to adjust aperture and shutter speed, and should shoot in RAW if possible so you can work on images when you get home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since it's April and we'll be shooting outside (weather permitting), be sure to bring a jacket or sweater you can layer on as the temps drop in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;More Info...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;If you've been to recent monthly meetings, you've heard last year's participants rave about it. If you haven't, more information on past Portable Portrait Workshops is &lt;a href="http://www.portableportrait.com" target="_blank"&gt;available on this website&lt;/a&gt;. And a few hundred photos of participants is &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/portableportrait/" target="_blank"&gt;available on this Flickr Group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;a href="http://astore.amazon.com/ceaserphotog-20?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;node=7"&gt;here is a list&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;of some of the equipment we'll be using.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come into the gallery, you cannot miss us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sid Ceaser</member_name><member_id>12740201</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305506744000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It's amazing, and you'll learn something regardless of whether you intend to work with strobes or not.</why><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299519603000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portable Portrait Workshop with Sid Ceaser</name><id>16831115</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305392400000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/16831115/</event_url></item>