<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(North end of Commercial)</address_2><address_1>155 Dow Street </address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.997409</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 624-2022</phone><name>Fratello's Ristorante Italiano</name><city>Manchester</city><id>964854</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.465958</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A powerful, blazingly honest memoir: the story of an eleven-hundred-mile solo hike that broke down a young woman reeling from catastrophe—and built her back up again. At twenty-two, Cheryl Strayed thought she'd lost everything when her mother died young of cancer. Her family scattered in their grief, her marriage was soon destroyed, and slowly her life spun out of control. Four years after her mother's death, with nothing more to lose, Strayed made the most impulsive decision of her life: to hike the Pacific Crest Trail from the Mojave Desert through California and Oregon to Washington State—and to do it alone. She had no experience as a long-distance hiker--indeed, she'd never gone backpacking before her first night on the trail. Her trek was little more than “an idea, vague and outlandish and full of promise.” But it was a promise of piecing back together a life that had come undone. Strayed faces down rattlesnakes and black bears, intense heat and record snowfalls, and both the beauty and intense loneliness of the trail. Told with great suspense and style, sparkling with warmth and humor, Wild vividly captures the terrors and pleasures of one young woman forging ahead against all odds on a journey that maddened, strengthened, and ultimately healed her.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>RobC13</member_name><member_id>13707536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363391581000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club</urlname><id>1332912</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>The Southern NH Books and Brew Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360811513000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Discuss Wild by Cheryl Strayed</name><id>104539102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363215600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Southern-NH-Books-and-Brew-Club/events/104539102/</event_url></item>