<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A looping hike of roughly 6.25 miles and roughly 4 hrs. at Hubbard Park in Meriden, CT. &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;This is an experimental hike as about half of it will be on trail we have not done before (South Mountain).&lt;/span&gt; We'll stop at Merrimere Resevoir and follow the road to the back, ascend South Mountain to the cliffs, return to the back end of the reservoir, loop around the back end of the reservoir, return via East Peak along the cliffs above the reservoir, decend the steep trail from Castle Craig, and back to the start. There will be many beautiful Fall views on the various cliffs with water views aplenty. About half of the hike will be on a portion of the Metacomet Trail. (There is an easy out for those who cannnot do the larger milage and additional time so they do 5.1 mi. and 3 hrs., half would be easy roadwalking.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet at the parking lot on the east side of Mirror Lake and we'll hike from there.&lt;/b&gt; (There is a pool on the south side of the parking lot and a playground on the east)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to some steep sections and a fair amount of up/down I would rate this hike moderate. You must bring a quart of water and trail appropriate shoes. A small backpack would be advised to carry water and maybe a snack so hands are free for the steep trail section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; (Notch Rd., Meriden, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=95+Notch+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;[Lat.=41.5499, Long.=-72.8321]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trail map&lt;/b&gt; (1st page) &amp;amp; general information:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meridenlandtrust.com/Hubbard_quad.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meridenlan...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information&lt;/b&gt; about Hubbard Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cityofmeriden.org/CMS/default.asp?CMS_PageID=426" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cityofmeri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1286966496000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286407066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Hubbard Park (South Mtn.) &amp; Castle Craig in Meriden CT</name><id>15027522</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286733600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15027522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/f/global_705503.jpeg</photo_url></item>