<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Use The BallRoom Entrance</address_2><address_1>156 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.735825</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chowda Pot Dance, Hartford</name><city>Hartford</city><id>412745</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.659599</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a REPLICATe posting of the event from my other group, so a bunch of you already know of this..
BUT THERE MIGHT BE SOME OF YOU THAT MIGHT BE INTERESTED..so i invite you to some activity outside of kayaking..

Ok Tired of that lazy fat turkey you are with who wont dance with you.?
Too much stuffing got you stuffed ? 
Dont be a vegetable and just sit there.. 
can you Forget paddling till the better weather..?

Here is your time to do the turkey strut, shake your gobbler, strut your stuff, and dance like you were in a turkey shoot..make like there are hungry ants in the pants.

I loved the last Halloween dance, the people i met and the laughs were just great.

This dance is in a place for you to let go in a decent environment..
Dont bring any paddles..or life jackets...

There is a mix of music..from (some) line dance stuff, 60's, and the rest all over the time up to the present dance stuff..

Well those who have been here in the past with us know all about what this place is and how it is.. its a place that seems safe for us..never have had any problems or ligitimate complaints...some couldnt find the signs.. 
they are there..please look..

LOOK FOR 2 MEETUP SIGNS ON THE TABLE..yes look on the tables individually first..this place has a lot of people....so its easy to get "Visually Distracted"... no im not gonna give the abbreviation of those 2 words..

For those of you that have not been here..Chowder Pot is a pretty good place to dance...and eat some food Buffet style.. and dance with who you feel sfe with..US.. 
we do that in the BALL ROOM..not the restaurant part.. enter at the Ball Room.. its the first entrance you see after you pull in the drive way..the restaurant is on the back side of the building.

i will get there earlier and grab a table..but other groups do the same thing...one person sitting at a large table is not good..a few of us can do a better job at reserving..unless someones BIRTHDAY is about then..then i call in to reserve a table... fess up now... tell me you are just turning 40.. ok ...chicken i see..well they give you some cheap champain.. to boot..., 

dinner starts at 8 goes to 9 or so, coffie and cookies stuff later.. closer to 12 or so. 
Dinner: usually bred, salid, zities in spag sause, chicken, and my favourite..muscels cooked in butter garlick spicy stuff..(keeps away the ladies which want to bite me)..why would anyone want to BITE ME ??.... 
This time there might be a different menue, dont know for sure yet.....but hey, i think the food is only one tasty part of the night...i love the other things better..so there..

Connecticut ConTacts, Inc. 
SPONSORING DANCE PARTIES FOR SINGLES NOVEMBER 30 @7:45 pm 

&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; LOOK FOR THE 2 MEETUP signs on the table&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;, (near the DJ if i can get a table there)


its now 20 bucks to get in... no jeans..too bad..jeans on Ladies look fine to me..maybe they dont want them to bust on the dance floor while all that HOT activity is going on...might need the fire hoses...makes the floor wet..wow a reason to wear the life jacket

Ok getting there: 
Directions to the U.S.S. CHOWDER POT IV

165 Brainard Rd., Hartford, CT


From New Haven: I-91 N to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd.). 1st right off exit. Immediate right into Chowder Pot parking lot.


From Springfield &amp; Points North: I-91 S to Exit 27(Brainard Rd.). Left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road &amp; turn right at light onto Brainard Rd. Go through one traffic light. Chowder Pot is on right. 


From Danbury &amp; Points West: I-84 E to I-91 S to Exit 27 (Brainard Rd.). Turn left off exit onto Airport Rd. Go to end of road &amp; turn right at light onto Brainard Rd. Go through one traffic light. Chowder Pot is on right. 


From Manchester: I-84 W to Charter Oak Bridge Exit. Go over bridge and take 2nd exit (Exit 87, Brainard Rd.). Go right off exit. Chowder Pot is on right.

i dont like maybe rsvp's for events that i have to save table space for..its not fair to those that want a place...right &gt;?? good i knew you would understand...

Last Note: 
I Choose Tables that are AWAY FROM THE SPEAKERS Main direction for conversation and for safety..(reason below LOL) 
either you go or not..if you are a maybe in reality..things depend i know..then say "maybe" in the NO area..then change later to yes.. 


There is usually another Meetup Group or other Related Group going in conjunction to make it a combined event or side by side event depending on seating available. 
Some of you are in the other groups going also so familliarty will be much higher. 
Our other groups attending is: Friendship &amp; Fun- For Professional Single Women 45+ , Activities and Friendship Group Hartford County, etc...

Even though the title is a singles dance..no one is going to ask you if you are or not..and i dont care either, its a dance event i thought you might find of interest...</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196643032000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195226413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dance With Your Kayak.  Or a Sexy Real Person.AT The HFD Chowder Pot Dance Event</name><id>6753138</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196469900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6753138/</event_url></item>