<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Dyer Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821461</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brown Continuing Education</name><city>Providence</city><id>7193882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.407707</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn about the evolution of the downtown park design, and what we can learn from other cities as Providence shifts from planning to implementation of our community's newest green space.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I missed the last lecture in this series due to my cold, but there's one more, and I'm hoping to make this one! The lecture will run from 5:30-7:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location map - please scroll to the bottom of this link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.brown.edu/ce/events/event.php?id=10"&gt;http://www.brown.edu/ce/events/event.php?id=10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presented by Naomi Darling, Urban Studies, Brown University; and Bonnie Nickerson, Department of Planning and Development, City of Providence; Mike McCormick, Planning, Design &amp;amp; Construction, Brown University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://www.brown.edu/ce/events/images/Naomi_Darling.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naomi Darling, AIA, LEED AP BD+C, is a principal at Darling Loeffler-Puurunen Architecture, a full service architectural practice based in New Haven, CT. The firm aims to produce socially responsible and environmentally conscious projects at all scales in terms of size, time, and permanence with a special consideration of site and place. Darling was one of 20 participants recently showcased in EP:2011, the second annual exhibition of work, art, and designs of emerging architects across North America sponsored by The American Institute of Architects (AIA) Center for Emerging Professionals. Prior to cofounding her practice, Ms. Darling worked at Olson Sundberg Kundig Allen Architects, Studio ABK, and Kengo Kuma and Associates. Ms. Darling’s early experiences working as a researcher studying climate change in Antarctica and as a scientist about the SSV Westward, were formative experiences that have helped shape both her teaching and practice today. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Darling teaches “Green Cities” in the Urban Studies Department at Brown University. The seminar looks at parks and open space within our cities through a series of international case studies, both historical and contemporary. In addition, Darling teaches courses in sustainability at the Yale School of Architecture. Darling received a BSE in civil engineering and architecture from Princeton University and a M.Arch from the Yale School of Architecture. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://www.brown.edu/ce/events/images/Bonnie_Nickerson.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonnie Nickerson, AICP, is the Director of the Long-Range Planning Division of the city of Providence’s Department of Planning and Development, a position she’s held since 2007. As Division Director Bonnie oversees the City’s comprehensive and neighborhood planning efforts as well redevelopment and special area plans. The Long-Range Planning staff leads initiatives in urban design, GIS, waterfront planning, environmental planning and transportation and transit planning. The division also oversees large grant projects such as the current HUD Community Challenge project, and coordinates efforts with local, state and regional planning partners. Prior to her current position, Bonnie joined the City Department as a principal planner after working in the non-profit sector and as a VISTA volunteer. Bonnie has a Bachelor of Arts Degree from Mount Holoyoke College and a Master of Community Planning from the University of Rhode Island and lives in Providence with her husband and two boys. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;img src="http://www.brown.edu/ce/events/images/Mike_McCormick.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike McCormick, AIA,is a licensed architect responsible for the planning and execution of the recent capital plan of approx. $1 billion undertaken by Brown over the last 8 years, adding over 1 million square feet and renovating another 2 million square feet. He is a frequent speaker at the Society of College and University Planners and the Association of University Architects. He holds degrees from Ball State University and M.I.T. and has 25 years of experience in planning, architectural design, and project management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing the brown and pink scarf in my picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337343549000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337015874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lecture - Out Our Front Door: Shaping Providence’s New Signature Public Space</name><id>64748262</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337203800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/64748262/</event_url></item>