<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Reservations made already.  If you RSVP yes please show up &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;The Third Annual Melting Pot Wine Dinner&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;First Course.     A cheese blend of Grand Queso and Guda cheese. Blended with fresh garlic and Peppa Dew peppers, topped with scallions and a fresh zest of lime. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First Course: Frescobaldi Pomino Bianco &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Second Course.    A wonderful mix of spinach, baby Portobello mushrooms, Red Onion, Chopped bacon and Roma Tomatoes with a tangy burgundy shallot vinaigrette. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Second Course: Castello di Querceto Chianti Classico Riserva &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Third Course.    A delightful Entrée consisting of   the freshest of ingredients. Including Ahi Tuna, Teriyaki marinated sirloin, Filet mignon, Shrimp, and Chicken. All served with an array of fresh vegetables, and a hand made assortment of sauces &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Third Course: Castello di Nippozano Chianti Rufina Riserva &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Fourth Course.    Silky White chocolate swirled with bananas, brown sugar and a dash of cinnamon, Flambéed table side . This decadent dessert is served with a plate of fresh fruits and pastries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fourth Course: Frescabaldi Vin Santo dessert wine &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;b&gt;$60 dollars per person (includes tax and gratuity)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;20% of all proceeds go to the St. Jude Children's Research Hospital&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;b&gt;COURTESY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a friendly reminder we would like people to be considerate towards the organizers knowing that some of these events take more time and effort than others by RSVPing accodingly. We know things can change suddenly but a nice one liner email/text/call explaining why you can't make an event or if you're running really late to event you said yes to would be ideal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rules for Engagement:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow meet up members participating in the event by arriving promptly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first serve basis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please do not show up unexpectedly - if you do not make it to the YES list please do not show up anyway &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. MAYBE'S will be changed to a NO the day of the event if the organizer sees fit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for THREE (3) events you will be removed from the group - all of us organizers talk so it may be a combo of missing more than one organizer's events or just one organizer's events - it doesn't take long to change your RSVP&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's/event locations who's staff is based on our reservation - no one wants to be inconvenienced&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal/event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must call or text the appropriate organizer so they know what is going on&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email the appropriate organizer about rejoining - if the event was run by X organizer do NOT email or complain to Y organizer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is always appreciated, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward - if you have complaints please make a recommendation on how to improve the event OR better yet offer to organize an event with us and add your improvements to your own event &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leaving a nasty comment does nothing for anyone except offend people&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you for your cooperation and hope to see you all at our events very soon! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Beantown and Beyond 20-40 Something Singles&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the bar / hostess stand area</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209683168000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207151211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Melting Pot Wine Dinner - Proceeds go to St Jude's</name><id>7657811</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209510000000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/7657811/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/2/global_2186386.jpeg</photo_url></item>