<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>179 Great Rd  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01460</zip><lat>42.539207</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 692-3033 </phone><name>Nashoba Valley  -Tubing Park</name><city>Littleton</city><id>877409</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.458084</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;[Update 1/9/10:  After alot of attempting manipulation I was unable to get a group rate.  The group rate has set times for tubing and our planned time does not fit into that category.  The price for this event will be $25.00 for a two hour ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because of the amount of people we will be waiting for and the elements I have changed the meeting place from the ticket booth to the Lodge.  The lodge houses the refreshment center and the restrooms so we could get a nice cup of coffee/Tea or cocoa as a prewarmup while we wait for others to arrive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As of today 15 out of the 16 lanes of tubing are open....can't wait to fly down one of them tomorrow....we may even be able to get a group slide in...wouldn't that be a blast....see you all at Nashoba tomorrow &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/love.gif' border='0' alt='love struck' /&gt;/color]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Update 1.3.10:  Now that we have plenty of snow and Nashoba is fully open with 16 lanes of tubing this event will not have an alternate...we will definitely be going Tubing.  For those of you wanting to do the Lazer Craze keep checking the schedule we will be scheduling that in the coming months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be calling Nashoba this week to see if we can get a group rate for this event and to find out if we need a reservation for dinner.  Please update your rsvp and let me know if you will be going to just tubing, just dinner or if you will be attending both&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok so we don't know if there will be snow or if Nashoba will have made snow so we are posting this event with an alternate in case there is no snow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan A:&lt;br /&gt;We will go snow tubing at Nashoba Valley and then proceed to the Outlook Restaurant at the Ski area for nice dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tubing:  Come on down and grab a snow tube, let the lift take you up the mountain and WEEEEE slide right down one of the 16 lanes of tubing down the mountain.  The Tubing price is $25.00 per 2 hour pass, a group rate is available but we need 15 ppl and we have to call in advance.  If we do get 15 interested members I will call Nashoba to get the group rate.&lt;br /&gt;Tubing is located in a different location than the ski area so please be aware of the different locations.  The tubing area is located at 179 Great Road Littleton MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dinner:  After 2 hours of fun filled snow tubing we will proceed to the ski resort at 79 Powers Road in Westford Ma (approx 5 min car ride from the Tubing area).  Where we will have a nice dinner relaxing in front of the fireplace at the ski lodge while watching the skiers come down the mountain.  The Outlook Restaurant is reasonably priced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For further details about Tubing or the Outlook Restaurant check out Nashoba's website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan B:  If there is no snow availabe for Snow tubing we will go to Lazer Craze in North Andover for a game of Lazer Tag and we then catch some dinner at a local restaurant (TBD).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come on down to Nashoba or if no snow come on down to North Andover....hope to see you on the slopes&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lodge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263328802000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259629872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snow Tubing w/Alternate Event</name><id>11985108</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263155400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/11985108/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/7/global_12048263.jpeg</photo_url></item>