<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>65 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.366306</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-926-2562 </phone><name>Contemporary Art Gallery at ALMA, the Armenian Library &amp; Museum of America</name><city>Watertown</city><id>669407</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.185850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Admission to ALMA is $7/person for non-members. If we get eight or more confirmed reservations, I will try to arrange a guided tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Correct address is 65 Main Street, Watertown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;About the museum&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Museum’s collections constitute the largest and most diverse holding of Armenian cultural artifacts outside of the Republic of Armenia. They comprise over 20,000 artifacts, including: 5,000 ancient and medieval Armenian coins, over 3,000 textiles and 180 Armenian inscribed rugs, and an extensive collection of Urartian and religious artifacts, ceramics, medieval illuminations and various other items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Museum maintains an active program of changing exhibits, averaging 14 exhibits annually, which celebrate the Armenian heritage, past and present, and provide new experiences for returning visitors and display the wide range of materials in the collection. While most of ALMA's holdings are kept in storage for inspection by researchers, less than 5% of the artifacts, are on exhibit at any given time. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ALMA's artifacts include prehistoric, Urartian, religious, ceramic, medieval and various other objects&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/img/museum1.jpg" width="158" height="152" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/img/museum2.jpg" width="166" height="152" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/img/museum3.jpg" width="166" height="152" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff"&gt;In the Gallery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Life and Works of Arshag Fetvadjian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/Arshak_Fetvadjian.jpg" alt="Fetvadjian" width="107" height="159" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through December 30, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 Free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fetvadjian Arshag Fetvadjian in New York, around 1920&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Homage exhibit to the Armenian painter and art historian Arshag Fetvadjian (1866-1947). Born in Trebizond and trained in Rome, Fetvadjian became one of the most prominent Armenian painter of the late 19th century. He is known for his watercolor paintings of the architectural monuments of the medieval Armenian city of Ani as well as portraits of Armenians at the turn of the 20th century. He is also the designer of the currency and postage stamps of the first Republic of Armenia (1918–1920).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the creation of the Republic of Armenia in 1918, the members of the country's Finance Ministry commissioned Fetvadjian to design the new currency (to replace the Russian ruble) and stamps for the nascent state. Fetvadjian's attractive designs featured animal motifs that were found on the decorations in Ani. The printing was conducted in Europe but just as the banknotes were being printed in Paris, Soviet Russia was completing its conquest of the republic. By December 1920, the Armenian state was finally absorbed by the Soviets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The banknotes were never put into circulation and thus have become a curious icon of an unfulfilled dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stamps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stamps and 100 rubles banknote created by Fetvadjian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/Stamps_Armenia_1919-1921.jpg" alt="Stamps" width="233" height="129" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.almainc.org/100Rubles.jpg" width="251" height="126" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354413890000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351576244000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>visit the Armenian Library and Museum of America</name><id>89147082</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354316400000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/89147082/</event_url></item>