<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Ashes of Time Redux&lt;/b&gt; Hong Kong 1994/2008 93 minutes &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Screens at 2:05&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is one of the most celebrated examples of 1990s Hong Kong cinema: it won multiple awards in its native Hong Kong, along with a Golden Osella for Best Cinematography at the 1994 Venice Film Festival.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to the film's trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.sonyclassics.com/ashesoftimeredux/trailer.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sonyclassi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Director Wong Kar-Wai's (In The Mood For Love, Chungking Express, 2046)  was not  satisfied with the original release of &lt;b&gt;Ashes of Time&lt;/b&gt; and has now produced a re-edited version:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Asked to deliver a sword-fighting extravaganza, Wong perversely blurs, fractures and pixilates the choreography while having his all-star cast lounge around in overlapping reveries, soaking in the director's themes of memory, being and love. (The &amp;quot;tumult of the heart&amp;quot; referenced in the opening Buddhist crawl is the focus.) No less than the romantics of his later films, Wong's ancient warriors are obsessed with time and passion; icons out of old Shaw Brothers movies, they find the rigidity of their archetypal roles gradually eroded by the transience of their emotions. Radically (almost maddeningly) disjointed but never less than intoxicating, Wong's most obscure film is a trance worth falling into.  Slant Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And here's the plot:  It nominally centers on Ouyang Feng who ekes out a lonely existence as an itinerant hired sword. Getting on in years and tormented by memories of a lost love, he also works an agent for other mercenary assassins from his remote desert abode. Ouyang's old friend and fellow swordsman, Huang Yaoshi drowns his lovelorn misery in a magical wine that makes him forget. Later, a mysterious young man named Murong Yang  hires Ouyang to kill his sister's unfaithful suitor, Huang Yaoshi. The following day, that spurned sister, Murong Yin , hires Ouyang to protect her dearly beloved. Meanwhile, Hong Qi  finds some redemption for a life of killing by accepting a poor girl's offer to avenge her brother's death — a task that Ouyang brusquely shunned. In another subplot, a master swordsman  is slowly going blind. He agrees to defend a village from horse thieves so that he can afford to go home and see his wife before his eyesight fails completely.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll be going to a nearby restaurant for our group discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Tom near the front row at the end of the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223941369000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ashes of Time Redux </name><id>8956073</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224957600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8956073/</event_url></item>