<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you were not able see The Fighter with the group back in Dec, here is your second chance. I am the second chance man!!!     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet for a pre-movie dinner about 5:30 pm (see RSVP question for more info). If you don't join us for dinner, look for us in the lobby of the theater about 7:10. I'll be wearing a Harvard hat, a red coat, and looking down at my smartphone trying to identify you as you walk in.  I'll be going into the movie at 7:20. If we miss you, look for us after the movie. We will most likely go for tea or Moroccan mint espresso or...after the movie.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To help me understand better who's coming, please RSVP &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; if you really mean &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot;. There is no limit on the event and you can RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; right up until show time. So no worries, right?     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showtime may change. I'll update you if it does.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;++++++++++++++++++++++     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Fighter&amp;quot; is the life story of boxer &amp;quot;Irish&amp;quot; Mickey Ward and his trainer brother Dick Eklund, chronicling the brothers' early days on the rough streets of Lowell, Mass., through Eklund's&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Eklund's battle with drugs and Ward's eventual world championship in London. It is more the inspirational tale of these two brothers who, against all the odds, come together to train for the historic title bout that will unite their fractured family, redeem their pasts and, at last, give their hard-luck town what it's been waiting for: pride.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://trailers.apple.com/trailers/paramount/thefighter/" target="_blank"&gt;Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Harvard baseball hat, red coat, looking down at smartphone.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ShaneO</member_name><member_id>8134848</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296315492000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295319839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fighter (Second Chance)</name><id>16087466</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295828100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/16087466/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/6/global_20079478.jpeg</photo_url></item>