<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>342 Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.339832</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northeastern University</name><city>Boston</city><id>7387782</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088196</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The highlight of each year’s BUILD program is the Annual Youth Business Plan Competition, or “BPC” which represents the culmination of a year of hard work by our 9th- graders and their mentors. Teams present their innovative business ideas and prototypes&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;during two rounds of competition. Winners receive start-up funds to launch their business.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;The BPC celebrates our students’ creativity and energy, on a day of competition where one team will emerge victorious, and everybody wins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BUILD is an exciting 4-year college success program that uses entrepreneurship to motivate disengaged students to excel academically, graduate from high school, and attend college. Our students develop their own business ideas, write business plans, pitch to funders, and launch real businesses.This real-world business experience makes school relevant and motivates them to succeed. Over the past thirteen years, 95% of BUILD seniors have been accepted to college,with over 80% accepted to 4 year colleges and universities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Rotaract Club will need volunteers to help with setting up the rooms, serving food, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ray W</member_name><member_id>2975533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370193421000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrotaract</urlname><id>1501340</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Rotaract - A Service/Social Club for 18-30 Yr Olds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366410112000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Volunteer at BUILD Business Plan Competition</name><id>115212772</id><headcount>50</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370102400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrotaract/events/115212772/</event_url></item>