<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>July 17-19 7PM&lt;br /&gt;Ski Wheelers Ski Lodge&lt;br /&gt;North Conway,NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Janet M will be car pooling from Norwich, VT; Redscarlet56@gmail.com; 802-295-5109&lt;br /&gt;Leaving early on Friday AM to bike in North Conway on Friday. Trip is about 2 1/2 hrs&lt;br /&gt;I am not the HOST;  Please send the check to Cheryl:  address listed below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year had 18 people from meetup out of 65 who went down the river.   So please join me and my friends for a weekend you will not forget.  This is a fun filled weekend of meeting new people and discovering new ways to enjoy the great outdoors on the cheap side. &lt;br /&gt;Cost:  $128 which includes meal and lodging (Friday and Saturday nights), includes canoe or kayak, $25 off if you bring your own boat.  The lodging is clean but like camping indoors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday night Happy hours/a canoe, or kayak with a day on the river/ 2 breakfast/picnic lunch/ lobster, steak or chicken dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:&lt;br /&gt;Friday night 7:30-11:  Check in, get settled and join us for a welcoming get together; snacks, beer and wine.&lt;br /&gt;Saturday 7 AM:  Meet in the dining room for a make your own breakfast ( breakfast items furnished)&lt;br /&gt;Pack your lunch in your own coolers, lunch foods and drinks provided to make your picnic lunch.&lt;br /&gt;8:40 AM:  Leave lodge for Northern Extremes ( formerly Saco Canoe) Route 16 Conway&lt;br /&gt;9:00 AM:  Must be at Northern Extremes for 9:00 AM shuttle LIMITED SPACE on the shuttle.  Those with their own canoe/kayak should car pool to put in and arrange for a ride back to take-out.  Lunch on the river, sun laughs, water battles, swimming!!&lt;br /&gt;3:00-6 PM:  Volleyball, pool, ping-pong, darts, socializing or relaxing after having a hard day on the river.&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM: Feast of lobster, steak, and BBQ Chicken at the Ski Wheelers Lodge&lt;br /&gt;9:00 PM-1 AM:  Informal party at the Ski Wheelers Lodge, music, dance and pool and ping pong, (BYOB)&lt;br /&gt;SUNDAY:  Wake up fresh coffee, and have breakfast at your leisure, enjoy the day bike, hike or shop&lt;br /&gt;Take a river swim, or hang out to get to know your new friends.&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: smaller cooler, sweatshirt, or fleece ( it can get cool on the river) allow for the possiblity of rain, and bring foul weather gear ( we go if it rains), a dry bag or large zip lock bag to keep things dry ( such as your camera), an arsenal of water-ejecting weaponry ( please no water balloons), Insect repellent and SUNSCREEN SPF 30, beach towel, bathing suit, watershoesd, sandals, or old sneakers, SLEPING BAG, or linens &amp;amp; blankets, pillow and bath towel ( members remind your guests). &lt;br /&gt;YOUR SENSE OF ADVENTURE, A WILLINGESS TO HELP OUT, AND YOUR SENSE OF HUMOR&lt;br /&gt;Please send your check to:   ( we only accept checks from members of meetup, only)&lt;br /&gt;Ski Wheelers Ski Club by JUNE 29, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheryl Slowik&lt;br /&gt;11 Sparhawk Street #2F&lt;br /&gt;Brighton, Mass 02135&lt;br /&gt;Choice:  Lobster, chicken or steak&lt;br /&gt;Please order only what you can eat&lt;br /&gt;We need accurate kayak/ canoe count&lt;br /&gt;Deduct $25 from the package cost of $80 if you are bringing your won canoe/ kayak&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be already there.  / Will have meetup sign with Janet M</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janet   M56</member_name><member_id>9081920</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249404842000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244479679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NORTH CONWAY Canoe/Kayak Weekend</name><id>10604043</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247871600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/10604043/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/3/global_9048915.jpeg</photo_url></item>