<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>301 US Route 1</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>03904</zip><lat>43.111882</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kittery Trading Post</name><city>Kittery</city><id>949132</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.734279</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Greetings, I hope you will attend this lecture, The Kittery Energy Committee is pleased to announce that one of the Founding Partners of GridSolar, LLC will be presenting the GridSolar Project to the Committee.  This presentation is open to the general public.  The Committee encourages you to attend this to learn more about this innovative project. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Central Maine Power Company has proposed a major $1.5 billion upgrade of its transmission grid to accommodate what it projects to be growth in peak load over the next decade.  This project will impact hundreds of private landowners across south and central Maine as CMP exercises its right of eminent domain to take land for new transmission corridors and to expand existing ones. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Silkman who runs GridSolar is also a principle in Maine Renewable Energy -- the green electricity provider for the state of Maine.  I understand that NH is also going thru the same upgrade process and renewable activists in NH will be looking to Maine to see how it plays out here and possibly emulating the approach in NH. &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A new Maine company, GridSolar, has proposed a Smart Grid alternative - the GridSolar Project.  The GridSolar Project will meet peak load growth by developing distributed solar generation in those regions of Maine where such load growth occurs.  It represents a lower cost option, one that is environmentally less impactful, does not require the use of eminent domain and creates the potential for thousands of new “green” jobs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See everyone there!  &lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244975549000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241400290000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Grid Solar Project</name><id>10329723</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241562600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/10329723/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/e/e/global_1941310.jpeg</photo_url></item>