<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>114 Whitney Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.314545</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(203) 562- 4183</phone><name>New Haven Museum &amp; Historical Society</name><city>New Haven</city><id>501007</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.921260</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From the Historical Society's webpage, www.newhavenmuseum.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of the:  Saving Our Cities/Saving the Land: New Urbanism Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&amp;quot;Come in from the cold this winter and explore some of the critical issues facing our communities.  For six weeks in January and February we will feature films, commentary and lively discussion as we ?travel? across the country in search of answers to the challenge of urban sprawl, community alienation, clogged transportation, the loss of independent commerce and the corresponding threats to precious historical resources.  Find communities looking for new ways to come together, define their neighborhoods and fight the Big Box.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connecticut has been facing the problem of city versus town since colonial days, resulting in 169 governmental entities with great independent spirit but little interconnectedness.  How do we come together?  How do our communities maintain a sense of identity in an increasingly homogenized world?  What about our cities?  A century ago they were the engines of the industrial age.  But what is their role now and in the future?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The issues facing us here are being addressed by communities across the nation.  At each of our evening programs commentators will lead discussions that will bring the challenges home and help us rethink the &amp;quot;American Dream.&amp;quot;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Thursday's Film &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Independent America&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Follow the filmmakers on a transcontinental journey through 32 states in search of ?Independent America.?  Hear from hardy souls fighting for the right to remain independent in a land smothered by Big Box stores and fast-food chains.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film screening is free, open to public with refreshments available for purchase&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact:  Jeanie (203) 804-2199&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203806350000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202063294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Independent America: Film Screening    </name><id>7254763</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203633000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7254763/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/c/global_351724.jpeg</photo_url></item>