<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is not a MeetUp event! So please - To Register go here!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.asmpnewengland.org/events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.asmpneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Putting Your Business in Focus&lt;br /&gt;A Strategic Approach to Marketing Photographers &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is the best way to advertise? &lt;br /&gt;How do I set myself apart from all the competition?&lt;br /&gt;How much time and money should I expend to market my business? &lt;br /&gt;What do I need to do to grow my business in a down economy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like many professionals, photographers are often expert at what they do, but find the prospect of marketing their business daunting. Taught by Beth Darman Stone of ClairStone Communications, Putting Your Business in Focus: A Strategic Approach to Marketing Photographers will help answer these questions. We’ll examine your business and industry, your clients and their experience of your business, your competitive environment, and the tools available to your industry. The seminar is designed to help you develop a strategic approach to creating a marketing and communications plan that works for your business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marketing is everything a company is and does, a phrase commonly cited by Beth and her partner Lisa Clair. Want to learn more?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About our company:&lt;br /&gt;ClairStone Communications is a strategic marketing and communications partnership offering small to mid-sized companies a full spectrum of marketing, advertising and public relations services. Owned and operated by Lisa Clair and Beth Darman Stone since 1988, the company has grown to include expertise in a variety of service-oriented domains, such as home care (interior designers, painting companies, contractors, architects, realtors, garden designers), healthcare (in-home care services, assisted living facilities, skilled nursing centers, message therapy), retail, and not-for profit organizations. When small businesses need a structured, goal-oriented strategic approach to communications, they rely on ClairStone’s wisdom, experience, practical style and personalized service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Register go here!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.asmpnewengland.org/events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.asmpneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: EP Levine, 23 DRYDOCK AVE BOSTON MA 02210 - 617-951-1499 - directions&lt;br /&gt;Time:  Social hour &amp;amp; Food: 6:00; Program: 7:00&lt;br /&gt;Cost:  Members: $1; Students: $5; All Others: $20 (Food, beverage provided)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register by Paypal - to qualify for door prices &lt;br /&gt;closing December 08th, 2008:&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229649622000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227626276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Putting Your Business in Focus-A Strategic Approach to Marketing Photographers </name><id>9228516</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228863600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9228516/</event_url></item>