<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>389 Boston Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.410175</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Tufts University-Medford Campus</name><city>Medford</city><id>11435612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119644</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on the Tufts campus this Thursday, January 31st at 3 pm for the 10th annual tapping of sugar maples for the Somerville Maple Syrup Project! Families, neighbors, students, maple syrup enthusiasts, and anyone interested in participating in this fun, FREE outdoor event should gather at the bottom of Memorial Steps across from Anderson Hall, 200 College Avenue. You’ll learn how we tap maple trees, help us hammer in the spiles, and see how we collect sap used to produce our own hyper-local, super-sweet syrup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 3 pm, we’ll climb the steps and begin to tap the trees growing on the sloped lawn to the left of the steps behind Miner Hall; look for the Groundwork Somerville banner. Attendees are encouraged to dress warmly, since we’ll be outside for an hour. For more information, check out our Somerville Maple Syrup Project page at www.groundworksomerville.org or call 617-628-9988.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Note: This is a separate event from the "Making Maple Syrup" workshop, a longer, more in-depth, adult-focused, and specialized event for those interested in delving deeper into tapping, sap collection, the history of maple sugaring, and syrup production. You can check out that Meetup here: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/99925442/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/99925442/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lee Dwyer</member_name><member_id>49562932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359666859000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359486347000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maple Tapping Day!</name><id>101992442</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>3600000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359662400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/101992442/</event_url></item>