<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 W Brookline St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.340148</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blackstone School Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>698342</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.073133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us every Monday this summer for Salsa in the Park, starting June 30!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These fun outdoor events are sponsored by the Mayor's Office and are FREE and open to everyone?bring the whole family if you'd like! Whether you've been dancing salsa for years or you'd like to learn how?or if you'd just like to relax after work to the sounds of salsa music, join us in the park on Monday&lt;br /&gt;nights!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each night will feature live performances, dance instruction for all levels (beginner to advanced), and lots of time to dance and socialize. There will be food and drinks for sale, as well as other items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note:  If it rains, the party will be inside the Community Center&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsors include:  SalsaBoston.com, El Show de Fernandito, Teddy's Shoes, BostonSalsero.com, Harry O's Pizza, MetaMovements and Boston ROCKS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Blackstone Park in the South End; 6:30 PM - 9:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;SPECIAL KICK-OFF PARTY with DJ Hernan: Monday, June 30th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Corner of W. Brookline &amp;amp; Washington Streets, in the South End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: On-Street parking available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation:a) Orange line to Back Bay, exit Dartmouth&lt;br /&gt;Street side. Take a left on Dartmouth and walk about 10 minutes&lt;br /&gt;down, till you pass Tremont Street and cross onto W.Dedham Street,&lt;br /&gt;take left on Washington St., walk down and park is on right. b)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Line bus leaving from Dudley Station to W. Newton stop, park&lt;br /&gt;is on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information:  www.metamovements.com&lt;br /&gt;Telephone:  617 983-1418&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anara</member_name><member_id>2988644</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215038327000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214844303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa in the Park--tonight and every Monday!</name><id>8246453</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214865000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/8246453/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/global_522835.jpeg</photo_url></item>