<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Main St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.133133</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 868-1230</phone><name>Durham Community Church</name><city>Durham</city><id>946481</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.922752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wednesday, July 1, at 7 pm: 
Cindy Sheehan speaks on Myth America at the 
Durham Community Church, 17 Main St., Durham NH. 

Cindy Sheehan began her anti-war activism after her oldest son, Casey, was killed in Iraq in 2004.  She rose to international prominence when she camped on the doorstep of George Bush's Crawford Ranch in August 2005.  Cindy recently published an Internet Booklet titled: Myth America: 10 Greatest Myths of the Robber Class and the Case for Revolution.  Cindy is currently on tour with this book to spark the dialogue and activism we need to separate ourselves from oppressive Robber Class Systems. She will also talk about countering military recruitment of our youth. Free and open to the public.  Donations welcomed.  

Sponsored by Seacoast Peace Response and Durham Students for a Democratic Society. For more information contact afreid09@yahoo.com or 603-749-9159.  Also see www.cindysheehanssoapbox.com  for more on Cindy Sheehan. 

The Case for (peaceful) Revolution.
There Ain't no Power like the Power of the People!
Myth One: America: Greatest Nation in the Universe!
Myth Two: Elections Matter
Myth Three: There's a huge Difference Between Dems and Repubs
Myth Four: It is Noble to Die in Robber Class Wars
Myth Five: The Central Banking System is good for the Robbed Class
Myth Six: It's a Privilege to pay Income Taxes to the Robber Class
Myth Seven: Housing, Health Care and Education are Privileges, too
Myth Eight: America has a Free Press
Myth Nine: The Environment, Who Needs it?
Myth Ten: 19 Muslims with box cutters were responsible for 9/11</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246714741000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245616892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cindy Sheehan speaks on Myth America</name><id>10702282</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246489200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/10702282/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>