<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Opening night&lt;/b&gt; of the &lt;b&gt;Salve Regina French Film Festival&lt;/b&gt; held in Newport RI between &lt;b&gt;22 March to 2 April 2009&lt;/b&gt;.  All films are being shown to the public for no charge thanks to the support of the French American Cultural Exchange (FACE).  I have set an RSVP limit of 15 to make sure we have enough seats in the theater given its freely available to all.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film featured for the festival on the opening night is &amp;quot;Ne le dis à personne/Tell No One&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;Full schedule of films can be found on the Salve Regina University website at &lt;a href="http://www.salve.edu/frenchfilm/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.salve.edu/frenchfilm/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.salve.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details about the Meetup for &amp;quot;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ne le dis à personne/Tell No One&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;quot; (per the Salve website).&lt;br /&gt;• Date &amp;amp; Time: &lt;b&gt;7 p.m. Sunday, March 22&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Location: &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Opening night at the Jane Pickens Theater&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;A powerhouse thriller that takes an unexpected turn when Alex receives an anonymous e-mail suggesting that his brutally murdered wife is actually alive.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NB:&lt;/b&gt; Festivities begin at &lt;b&gt;6:30 p.m.&lt;/b&gt; with wine reception compliments of &lt;span style="color: cyan"&gt;Newport Vineyards&lt;/span&gt; and traditional French music by accordionist &lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;Renata Adams&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Further details about the film (taken from the FACE Tournées Festival information at &lt;a href="http://www.facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms/neledisapersonne.html" target="_blank"&gt;www.facecouncil.org/tournees/fichesfilms&lt;/a&gt;): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Alex, a pediatrician, has been devastated since his wife Margot, his childhood sweetheart, was savagely murdered eight years ago. One day he receives an anonymous email: when he clicks on the inserted link, he sees a woman's face standing in a crowd, being filmed live. Alex is in shock: he is looking at Margot's face… Is she still alive? Why does she instruct him to tell no one? As soon as Alex raises the lid of this Pandora's box, the police reopens the murder case. They are sure that Alex is the perpetrator of his wife's gruesome murder since he was actually with her when she was killed. He finds himself on the wrong end of the investigation. He must lead his own to prove his innocence and find out what really happened to his wife. The film plunges into the past, stirring old memories of happier times in Alex's mind. The investigation also forces family and friends to remember details they'd rather keep buried. Alex's unrelenting questioning will unravel a sordid story that will incriminate unscrupulous family members and ultimately reunite him with his wife.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DIRECTOR&lt;/u&gt; – Guillaume Canet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;SCREENPLAY&lt;/u&gt; – Guillaume Canet &amp;amp; Philippe Lefebvre. Based on Harlan Coben's novel Tell No One.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;CAST&lt;/u&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alexandre Beck: François Cluzet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Margot Laurentin: Marie-Josée Croze&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jacques Laurentin: André Dussollier &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Helene Perkins: Kristin Scott-Thomas&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eric Levkowich: François Berleand&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Elysabeth Feldman: Nathalie Baye&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gilbert Neuville: Jean Rochefort&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Philippe Meynard: Philippe Lefebvre&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anne Beck: Marina Hands&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;AWARDS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best Director, Best Actor (François Cluzet), Best Editing, Best Music (Matthieu Chedid), César Awards (2007)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best Film and World Audience Award, Lumière Awards (2007)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Running time&lt;/u&gt;: 125’&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Production&lt;/u&gt;: France, 2006&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rating&lt;/u&gt;: Not rated&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gauge&lt;/u&gt;: 35mm, DVD (color)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;GENRE&lt;/u&gt; – Thriller&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DISTRIBUTOR&lt;/u&gt; – Music Box Films&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“François Cluzet's performance is superb - accurate and restrained.” Charlotte Lipinska, Le Nouvel Observateur&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;__________________________&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being organised by Stevie Worthington as part of a &lt;b&gt;6 part Meetup event&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;for the Providence French Language Meetup group based in NEWPORT RI.  If you can't make this night, hopefully you can make it to at least one of the other films in the Film festival on either &lt;b&gt;24 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;26 Mar&lt;/b&gt;,&lt;b&gt; 29 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;31 Mar&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;2 April&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, send Stevie an email - merci!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be inside the lobby from 6.30pm wearing a pink jacket holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237936835000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236698743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film Festival in Newport - Film 1 "Ne le dis à personne/Tell no one"</name><id>9923184</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237761000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9923184/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/5/global_7622421.jpeg</photo_url></item>