<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Members of this meetup should have multiple opportunities to see the best films.  This is a film that cannot be missed.  Since I cannot make the group's viewing on Super Sunday, I'd like to invite anyone to see this film with me on Wednesday, February 6 for a matinee priced showing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing better than to leave work and enjoy a gut wrenching, emotionally draining film!  Afterwards, we'll go to a local place to eat, drink, and process the experience.  This is the kind of film that requires an emotional outlet afterwards!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winner of the Palme d'Or at the 2007 Cannes Film Festival, this unforgettable drama is so gripping it plays like a thriller. Set during the last year of the Ceauçescu dictatorship, ironically called the &amp;quot;Golden Age of Romania,&amp;quot; life has become a nightmare for the hard-pressed citizens.  The film reveals how oppression infects every aspect of the culture. A political, moral and spiritual knockout. Written and directed by Cristian Mungiu&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transpiring over the course of a single day, Mungiu's film is a masterwork of modern filmmaking, by parts poignant and shocking. Nominated for 4 European Film Awards including Best Picture and one of the standout hits of the Telluride, Toronto and New York Film Festivals, 4 MONTHS, 3 WEEKS AND 2 DAYS is a modern classic that will stay with you long after you've left the theater. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before you leave the theater, look for me down front holding 2 meetup signs.  Or, I'll hold one sign in 2 pieces.  I  tried to do this 3 weeks ago, and have wanted to see this film four months.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing at the front of the theater near the 4th seat in the 3rd row holding 2 Meetup signs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>What better way to experience a film that is said to 'floor you' but with a group of film fans to discuss it afterwards?</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201886570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4 Months, 3 Weeks and 2 Days   </name><id>7241495</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202334300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7241495/</event_url></item>