<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Event Organizer: Joe Ciarcia - 415-480-4335&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please RSVP only if you are attending.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;If you do not plan to attend, an RSVP is &lt;strong&gt;not required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (simply do nothing :-) ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Because of the advanced nature of this hike (steep climb, above treeline travel, lots of miles, and lots of elevation gain) all potential participants need to answer the questions and &lt;strong&gt;sign-up for the waiting list&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Only sign-up if you have similar experiences THIS winter&lt;/em&gt; - I will give preference to people who have hiked with us this winter. I will let people know if they will be added to the trip within 24-48 hours of them joining the wait list.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The limit for this trip will be 12 people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take two, the initial version of this hike had a small oversight (the road to the lot where I intended to park is closed, D'OH). That would have added a ~2+ mile road walk and I'd rather be in the woods so instead of that, we're adding a mountain! It's the last weekend in winter and the plan is to climb &lt;span style="text-decoration : line-through"&gt;three&lt;/span&gt; four of the 4,000 foot summits in NH. Starting along the Crawford Path we ascend 2354 feet to Mt. Pierce &lt;strong&gt;(#27 @ 4,310').&lt;/strong&gt; From Pierce we continue along the Crawford Path and hit Mt. Eisenhower &lt;strong&gt;(#11 @ 4,780')&lt;/strong&gt;, via the Eisenhower loop trail. From Eisenhower we work our way back to the Crawford Path taking a detour at the Monroe Loop Trail to the summit of Monroe &lt;strong&gt;(#4 @ 5,384')&lt;/strong&gt;. From Monroe with hike just under 2 miles and ascend about 1250 feet to the summit of Mt. Washington &lt;strong&gt;(Numero Uno @ 6,288')&lt;/strong&gt;. If we can get a repeat performance of this past weekend's weather, we're going to have an unbelievable day! No guarantees but one can be hopeful. From the summit of Mount Washington we hop on the Gulfside Trail and continue the rest of the way down via the Jewell Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike given the current conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; trip we will hike about &lt;strong&gt;~13.85 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and climb  &lt;strong&gt;5,834 feet&lt;/strong&gt; - Book time is &lt;strong&gt;9 hours, 49 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;. Book time is based upon summer conditions and does not account for breaks and winter conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, elevation gain and alpine zone exposure. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for the &lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/summit_forecast.php"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; (mountwashington.org)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need things like warm layers, wind protection, goggles, snow shoes, traction and sunscreen. I will update everyone if weather conditions dictate that we bring more than what is described here. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click for a &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Winter_Day_Hike_Clothing_and_Gear_List.pdf"&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/a&gt; (Appalachian Mountain Club)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Current conditions require mountaineering snowshoes, Microspikes/Hillsounds, as well as full mountaineering crampons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;It's getting toasty out there. Don't forget to bring enough water to stay hydrated for the entire trip. Also, don't forget your sunscreen. On days like we had last week, the sun doesn't only shine down upon us, it shines up as well.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be meeting in the parking lot of the Cog Railway Station where we will be spotting cars. Once everyone has arrived we will leave a few cars behind and carpool to the trailhead. According to Google Maps this spot is about 162 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 48 minutes to drive there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For driving directions, &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=boston,+ma&amp;amp;daddr=44.268237,+-71.353047&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.268236,-71.353047&amp;amp;sspn=0.008351,0.018915&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFc16owIdKT2_-w&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;z=9"&gt;click here and enter your starting address&lt;/a&gt; (google.com)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;a href="https://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;daddr=43.914150,-71.364632(Dicey's+Mill+Trailhead)&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;ll=43.91415,-71.364632&amp;amp;spn=0.006295,0.008739&amp;amp;source=embed" style="color : #0000ff ; text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ciarcia</member_name><member_id>40840452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363527000000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363064501000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Pierce, Eisenhower, Monroe, WASHINGTON! (ADVANCED)</name><id>108846852</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>39600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363429800000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/108846852/</event_url></item>