<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please note that this hike is being held in conjunction with the 4 Seasons Hiking Group.  There is no need to sign up with both groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike will start at the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trailhead on Route 16 just north of the Mount Washington Auto Road.&lt;br /&gt;Please read the below carefully prior to signing up. Know your abilities. Microspikes are required. Winter clothing is also required.&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read, understand and agree to the Hikers responsibility code and waiver/liability listed on this web site.&lt;br /&gt;Hikers must be able to hike at a pace of two miles an hour non stop for a minimum of two hours.&lt;br /&gt;Leaving NH 16, the trail follows the northeast bank of Nineteen-Mile Brook on the remains of an old road. The main trail passes a dam in the brook, and the Carter Dome Trail diverges left for Zeta Pass. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Carter Dome Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.70 mi/1 hr 24 min/+1072 ft on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;Here the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail crosses a tributary on a footbridge, and it crosses another brook at a small cascade, also on a footbridge. The trail crosses a small brook and begins to ascend more steeply to the height-of-land, where the Wildcat Ridge Trail diverges right (west). &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Wildcat Ridge Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.14 mi/4 min/-110 ft on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;The Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail then drops steeply to the larger Carter Lake, passes the Carter-Moriah Trail left. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.06 mi/2 min/+10 ft on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;Here, the trail crosses between the lakes, and reaches Carter Notch Hut and the junction with the Wildcat River Trail. &lt;br /&gt;to AMC Carter Notch Hut &lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 3.80 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 2 hr 53 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +1991 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -175 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +1815 ft &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.06 mi/2 min/-10 ft on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;From the Wildcat River Trail, the trail reaches Carter Notch Hut then crosses between the lakes. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.20 mi/36 min/+1539 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;The trail begins on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail at the shore of the larger Carter Lake, north of Carter Notch Hut. It climbs very steeply at first, then moderates, and a side path leads 30 yd. to the right to an excellent outlook over Carter Notch. The trail continues to climb at a moderate grade, passing a side path that leads to the left 60 yd. to a fine spring, and it reaches the partly open summit of Carter Dome, where the Rainbow Trail enters on the right. &lt;br /&gt;to Carter Dome &lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 5.06 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 3 hr 31 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3537 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -193 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +3344 ft &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.39 mi/18 min/-222 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;The Carter-Moriah Trail descends steadily, and the Black Angel Trail enters on the right. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Black Angel Trail and Carter Dome Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.01 mi/1 min/-28 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;In another 25 yd., as the Carter Dome Trail continues straight ahead, the Carter-Moriah Trail bears right, passes through a shallow sag, and ascends moderately to the summit of Mt. Hight. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Carter Dome Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.40 mi/13 min/+93 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;At this bare summit, which commands the best views in the range, the trail makes a very sharp left turn; great care must be exercised to stay on the trail if visibility is poor, particularly going north, because a beaten path that soon peters out continues north from the summit. &lt;br /&gt;to Mt Hight &lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 5.86 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 4 hr 3 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3680 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -493 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change +3188 ft &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions &lt;br /&gt;Show in Google Earth &lt;br /&gt;Download to GPS &lt;br /&gt;Back to here hike 0.40 mi/30 min/-616 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;The trail descends steeply and rejoins the Carter Dome Trail. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Carter Dome Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 0.20 mi/11 min/-147 ft on the Carter-Moriah Trail &lt;br /&gt;The two trails continue to Zeta Pass, where the Carter Dome Trail turns left and descends toward NH 16. Water may occasionally be available in a small stream (usually dry in midsummer) that is accessible from the Carter Dome Trail 80 yd. below this junction. &lt;br /&gt;to Zeta Pass &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.90 mi/1 hr 47 min/-1582 ft on the Carter Dome Trail &lt;br /&gt;The Carter Dome Trail leaves Carter-Moriah Trail at Zeta Pass. It passes a good spring right then descends by a series of seven switchbacks. It crosses a tributary of the Nineteen-Mile Brook at a small, attractive cascade. It recrosses the brook and arrives at the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail. &lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;hike 1.90 mi/1 hr 23 min/-843 ft on the Nineteen-Mile Brook Trail &lt;br /&gt;The trail follows the northeast bank of Nineteen-Mile Brook on the remains of an old road. The trail passes a dam in the brook, and the Carter Dome Trail diverges right for Zeta Pass then the main trail arrives at NH 16. &lt;br /&gt;to Nineteen-Mile Brook Trailhead &lt;br /&gt;Totals &lt;br /&gt;Distance 10.26 mi &lt;br /&gt;Time 7 hr 54 min &lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3795 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss -3795 ft &lt;br /&gt;Elev Change 0 ft&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a Black Four Door Echo with Maine Plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254579576000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253796172000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carter Dome</name><id>11455023</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253970000000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/11455023/</event_url></item>