<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get over that mid-week slump by coming out to this fun, new venue in Wakefield!  :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bob and Laurie are giving Wakefield Weeknights and More members exclusive use of the two bar areas (one side of the room is a raw bar).They have a special Beatles themed drink menu including $9.09 martinis!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early or come later...this can be a sort of drop in event where you can stop by anytime throughout the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see lots of the familiar faces and lots of new ones as well.  This type of meetup is a really great way to mingle and hang out with both old members and newbies!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plenty of parking in the lots on Tuttle St.!  And since this place is ON the train platform, here is the Commuter Rail scoop - Check out the MBTA Haverhill/Reading Line Schedule. Trains leave North Station Boston at 5:15, 5:35, 5:55, 6:20, and 7:20. It's a 20 minute ride to the Wakefield stop in front of Laurie's. Trains depart from Wakefield to Boston at 8:05, 9:09, 10:19 and 10:59&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've heard nothing but great reviews of their food.  Here is a link to their menu and the rest of their website: &lt;a href="http://wakefieldsteakhouserawbar.com/dinner/" class="linkified"&gt;http://wakefieldsteakhouserawbar.com/dinner/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$1 oysters 5-7 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you come in the door take a left and then you'll see the bar areas to your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please MAKE SURE maintain your own tab or pay as you order and PLEASE tip your servers.  Credit cards will be held by the servers at Laurie's if you want to have a tab.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you have an easily recognizable FACE PHOTO of YOU as your main profile pic on your page in this group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wear my gold Realtor name tag so you can easily spot me!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melody Joy Gaeta, Realtor</member_name><member_id>3036353</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362683650000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357401524000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Laurie's 909 Steakhouse/Raw Bar Exclusive happy hour/dinner/drinks for our group</name><id>98043672</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362610800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/98043672/</event_url></item>