<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>83 Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.135017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-859-7306</phone><name>University of New Hampshire, Memorial Union Building (MUB)</name><city>Durham</city><id>884091</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.928329</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The YAL Campaign Bootcamp is put on by Young Americans for Liberty, Campaign for Liberty and other grassroots organizations.&amp;nbsp; Both YAL and CFL were created from the Ron Paul 2008 campaign so I can assure you that they are fantastic organizations.&amp;nbsp; Ron Paul is informally involved with both organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an all ages, full day political training event starting at 10:00 AM and ending at 7:00 PM.&amp;nbsp; All materials, lunch and even dinner are included for the nominal fee of $20.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ever thought about running for office or even helping someone else run for office (including Ron Paul), this is your lucky day.&amp;nbsp; This Bootcamp will be the best political training event put on by pro-liberty organizations in New England all year.&amp;nbsp; Feel free to invite your friends from all over the area as they will not find anything this good anywhere else in NE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early registration is encouraged and you do not have to attend the entire event if you want to leave early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For additional information and to register for the event, please check out this link, &lt;a href="http://www.yaliberty.org/campaignbootcamps"&gt;http://www.yaliberty.org/campaignbootcamps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are driving yourself, I was told to pass this info along, "&lt;span&gt;Parking at the MUB at the University of New Hampshire in Durham on Saturday, October 1st is free, as long as you're in C lot on Mill Rd. across from the Rite Aid plaza"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live in the Keene, Concord or Manchester areas and would like a free ride to the event, email me at keithcarlsen@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317538113000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317180004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>YAL Campaign Bootcamp</name><id>35258212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317477600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/35258212/</event_url></item>