<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>524 Allen Ave</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.704494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Unitarian Universalist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>924759</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.282819</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>MOAC - Maine Outdoors Adventure Club&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm a MOAC member. Come join MOAC for their monthly meeting. This event is free and open to the public. You do not need to be a MOAC Member to attend. Each month they have a regular meeting that discusses what's going on in MOAC as well as an interesting travel story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to learn more or become a member of MOAC, please visit their website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.moac.org" target="_blank"&gt;MOAC Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;May's Trip Story&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;18 Days on the River - A Grand Canyon Adventure &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MOACer Fran Leyman will recap an extraordinary 18 day private rafting trip through the Grand Canyon which she organized in September 2006. Fran’s trip had a total of 3 rafts and 10 people, including Jim, a 70 year old solo canoeist and the only hard boat in the group. Low water levels on the Colorado River made some of the rapids much more technical and others much easier. Weather was the typical Grand Canyon experience of extremes, from cold 30 degree F mornings to afternoons in the 90s; from sunny and dry to severe thunderstorms that turned the canyon walls into a series of red slurry waterfalls. All of it was awesome in scale and grandeur. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Fran: I got myself on the wait list for a private Grand Canyon trip while working for the Nantahala Outdoor Center in Tennessee as a river guide and cook in 1993. It took 13 years for my number to reach the top of the list and to get a coveted permit. Our trip was the last year that the wait list was in full effect. Since then the system has switched to a lottery. It’s time for another try at getting a slot. The trip is that good!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be waiting right outside the entrance at 6:45.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241824285000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239061209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MOAC General Meeting</name><id>10130743</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241650800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/10130743/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/b/global_7133307.jpeg</photo_url></item>