<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>956 Chapel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.306775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-562-5566</phone><name>Ivy Lounge </name><city>New Haven</city><id>770601</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.927702</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: &lt;br /&gt;The Ivy Lounge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Ivy Lounge is a hip club and lounge located in the temple plaza (former location of Backroom Bottega).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a completely redesigned interior, The Ivy includes a two-level bar and lounge along with a downstairs club featuring New Haven's most talented DJ's. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The third floor lounge features a more intimate and tranquil setting with private party availability and balcony views. Unlike other area clubs, The Ivy Lounge has a decidedly adult-feel, starting with its 21+ admission policy and continuing through its extensive menu of drinks and delights.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Typically closed on Mondays, the manager Mike has agreed to open his doors just for the NHC and friends, as long as we have at least 25 members in attendance that evening.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to encourage good attendance and to guarantee us a great happy hour, Mike has agreed to offer us the following specials for the evening:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$3 - All Well Drinks&lt;br /&gt;$3 - All Domestic Beer&lt;br /&gt;$4 - All Import Beer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a complimentary selection of food items from their new tapas menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact is Jeanie (860) 942-4708&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the only people in the bar!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244501419000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242666004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour - The Ivy Lounge</name><id>10437880</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243893600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/10437880/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/8/global_8692600.jpeg</photo_url></item>