<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>(pretty much anywhere)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.373615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Earth</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10564542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109734</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free On-Line Courses @ Harvard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(and at a couple of other places too; one is called MIT or something like that ... ... the other one I can't remember.)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edx.org/"&gt;LINK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: This is not a meetup, just a reminder that Harvard is offering free on-line courses.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;EdX is a not-for-profit enterprise of its founding partners Harvard University and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology that features learning designed specifically for interactive study via the web. Based on a long history of collaboration and their shared educational missions, the founders are creating a new online-learning experience with online courses that reflect their disciplinary breadth. Along with offering online courses, the institutions will use edX to research how students learn and how technology can transform learning–both on-campus and worldwide. Anant Agarwal, former Director of MIT's Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence Laboratory, serves as the first president of edX. EdX's goals combine the desire to reach out to students of all ages, means, and nations, and to deliver these teachings from a faculty who reflect the diversity of its audience. EdX is based in Cambridge, Massachusetts and is governed by MIT and Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard University is devoted to excellence in teaching, learning, and research, and to developing leaders in many disciplines who make a difference globally. Harvard faculty are engaged with teaching and research to push the boundaries of human knowledge. The University has twelve degree-granting Schools in addition to the Radcliffe Institute for Advanced Study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Established in 1636, Harvard is the oldest institution of higher education in the United States. The University, which is based in Cambridge and Boston, Massachusetts, has an enrollment of over 20,000 degree candidates, including undergraduate, graduate, and professional students. Harvard has more than 360,000 alumni around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/e/4/event_184207652.jpeg" width="565" height="207" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; display : block ; margin : 0px auto"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355587540000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354418143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free On-Line Courses @ Harvard</name><id>qczxwdyqqbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355576400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/93686582/</event_url></item>