<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Revolve Nation is proud to present the first in a monthly CEO Breakfast Discussion Series! We are proud to welcome this month's speaker, Robert S. Duboff, of HawkPartners, LLC (&lt;a href="http://www.hawkpartners.com/)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hawkpartne...&lt;/a&gt;.  Robert will speak to us about the trials he faced in growing his boutique marketing firm and how he overcame those challenges. He will also focus on beginning to establish how you can effectively go about communicating the brand message of your start up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;-7:30am-8:00am: Networking/Continental Breakfast&lt;br /&gt;-8:00am-8:40am: Special Guest lecture on his journey and employment matters, plus a Q&amp;amp;A roundtable discussion about the topic&lt;br /&gt;-8:40am-9:00am: Networking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revolve Nation is the largest community of entrepreneurs and business owners in the city of Boston, offering networking, discussion groups, seminars, business plan hot-seats, and more! Join us here, where professionals and entrepreneurs meet in mutual support of business to network, socialize, learn, and promote a thriving community of entrepreneurs. Coffee and Doughnuts will be served!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like anything in life, what you put into a networking group is what you get out of it. Revolve Nation is designed for entrepreneurs and professionals who are serious about building their business, investing in relationships, and helping each other to succeed. You will get the most out of this group with regular attendance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The way the group seeks to achieve these outcomes:&lt;br /&gt;1) Regular attendance (when possible)&lt;br /&gt;2) Create a fun and supportive environment!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPONSORS:&lt;br /&gt;Revolve, Inc: www.revolvethis.com&lt;br /&gt;Exemplar Law Partners: www.exemplarlaw.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See all of you next time!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223552056000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222456283000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunrise Meeting: Revolve Nation CEO Breakfast!!!</name><id>8839873</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223379000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/8839873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/f/global_1065599.jpeg</photo_url></item>