<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Corner of Franklin &amp; Broad Streets)</address_2><address_1>99 Broad Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.357517</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 357 -8287 </phone><name>J.A. Stats Restaurant &amp; Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>563345</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052730</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been invited by the Aussie Expat group to join in their annual birthday festivities! Here are the details from their site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gday all....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The becoming legendary Boston Aussie Day party is ON AGAIN and this year we are ramping it right up with a really cool new venue close to Boston’s historic Faneuil Hall, LIVE AUSSIE MUSIC during the early afternoon and a DJ kicking things on later on playing all your Aussie favorites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year we encourage AUSSIE COSTUME! Come dressed as your favorite Aussie sports star, movie or tv personality or political identity or get creative! Cool prizes will be given out for the best costumes on the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Up for grabs in the raffle this year are great Celtics Tickets, massive Aussie food and wine Hamper, the good Aussie meat tray, Smith optics pack, Monster Energy Drink stuff, Aussie wine and lots of other cool stuff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Host bar JA STATS will be opening for lunch at 12, they have great food (awesome burgers) at great prices and also rumors abound of pies making an appearance on the menu, stay tuned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Print out the attached flyer and pass it out to all your mates, non Aussies are not only welcomed but encouraged to get involved!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE ENTRY!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JA STATS BAR, 99 Broad St, Boston MA 02110 is open for lunch at 12.30, party kicks off at 2&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Closest T Stops:&lt;br /&gt;Blue Line: Aquarium Stop&lt;br /&gt;Green Line: State Street Stop&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line: Downtown Crossing&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce Turnbull</member_name><member_id>4018534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266369407000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263000323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Move over St Paddys Day and Cinco de Mayo....Aussie Day is here!</name><id>12265907</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264273200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/12265907/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/c/global_12540524.jpeg</photo_url></item>