<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Located in three towns, this forest contains 1,140 acres including 180 acres of ponds, swamps, and wetlands. It is the probable site of a Native American village prior to colonial settlement and later was acquired to obtain granite for canals and factory foundations. The forest has six miles of trails offering hiking, bicycling, horseback riding, cross-country skiing, and snowmobiling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lowell-Dracut-Tyngsboro State Forest is located in north-east Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: Take Rt. 495 to Rt. 3 north. Follow Rt. 3 North to exit 32. Go right at the end of ramp, onto Drum Hill Rd. go 5 sets of lights you will cross over the Rourk Bridge. Go left at the lights on the other side of the bridge. Go 500 yards then take a right at lights onto Old Ferry Rd. Take a left onto Varnum Ave. After ½ mile, go right onto Trotting Park Rd. Parking lot is at the gate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet in the parking lot.  Look for the crowd of people hanging around. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we'll have lunch at the Lobsterboat.&lt;br /&gt;440 Middlesex Rd&lt;br /&gt;Tyngsboro, MA 01879&lt;br /&gt;(978) 649-1995&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry, they don't have a website to checkout, but you can Google them to see reviews and such.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193273310000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190660182000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lowell-Dracut-Tyngsboro State Forest</name><id>6418972</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192977000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6418972/</event_url></item>