<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Tiger Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01754</zip><lat>42.420506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fowler Middle School</name><city>Maynard</city><id>1596890</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.456688</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The MaynardCAN! Energy and Sustainability Fair is from 12PM to 4PM&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.maynardcan.org"&gt;www.maynardcan.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be showing&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Meat the Truth&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;at 1:30&amp;nbsp;followed by a&amp;nbsp;brief discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The documentary &lt;em&gt;Meat the Truth &lt;/em&gt;is the first major project undertaken by the Nicolaas G. Pierson Foundation. &lt;em&gt;Meat the Truth &lt;/em&gt;is a high-profile documentary, presented by Marianne Thieme (leader of the Party for the Animals), which forms an addendum to earlier films that have been made about climate change. Although such films have convincingly succeeded in drawing public attention to the issue of global warming, they have repeatedly ignored one of the most important causes of climate change, namely: intensive livestock production. &lt;em&gt;Meat the Truth&lt;/em&gt; has drawn attention to this by demonstrating that livestock farming generates more greenhouse gas emissions worldwide than all cars, lorries, trains, boats and planes added together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Nicolaas G. Pierson Foundation chose to compile the best scientific information on climate change and livestock farming, which is presently available and to translate this for a broader audience. The film was produced by Claudine Everaert and Gertjan Zwanikken. The calculations on greenhouse gas emissions used in the film derive from and have been validated by the Food and Agricultural Organisation of the UN (FAO), the World Watch Institute, the Institute for Environmental Studies of the Free University Amsterdam and numerous other authoritative sources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meatthetruth.nl/en/"&gt;http://www.meatthetruth.nl/en/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1304272296000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302133262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DVD: Meat the Truth  - Presentation at MaynardCAN!'s Energy Fair</name><id>17212615</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1304184600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/17212615/</event_url></item>