<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Hedley Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02919</zip><lat>41.830712</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Fred Lippitt Woonasquatucket River Greenway</name><city>Johnston</city><id>904337</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.468087</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE TAKE THE POLL TO LET US KNOW WHAT YOU ARE GOING TO DO...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WALK, JOG, RUN, BIKE or ROLL. Click the link below to vote&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Bicycling/polls/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My meetups are just for fun and pleasure. &lt;br /&gt;Anyone and everyone is welcome. &lt;br /&gt;So don't get stressed about having to complete the whole path, just come on out, enjoy the outdoors and meet some new folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Fred Lippitt Woonasquatucket River Bikeway: 5.1 miles between Providence Place Mall and Lyman Ave. in Johnston.&lt;br /&gt;A bicycle/pedestrian path links recreational areas, green spaces, destination sites, and the neighborhoods of Manton, Hartford, Olneyville, Valley, and Smith Hill to each other and Waterplace Park in downtown Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go at your own pace&lt;br /&gt;Go as far as you want&lt;br /&gt;Stop where ever you want&lt;br /&gt;Stay for as long as you want &amp;amp; leave whenever you want.&lt;br /&gt;NO STRESS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking for the Fred Lippitt Woonasquatucket River Greenway is available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Hedley Ave. in Johnston - abutting the bike path. From I-295 North take Exit 6A (Route 6 EAST) or via  I-295 South take Exit 6 (Route 6 EAST) to Rte. 128 Killingly St. exit - follow Killingly St. to intersection with Greenville Ave. Turn right onto Greenville Ave - approximately 1/4 mile turn right onto Hedley Ave. Parking area is on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car. We won't leave until 10 AM&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a White Toyota SVU. I will have a Red Towel unfold over the hood</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243695258000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237150537000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Woonasquatucket River Path - 5 Miles Long - 10 Miles Total Trip Back &amp; Forth</name><id>9960425</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242482400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/9960425/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/global_5864541.jpeg</photo_url></item>