<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 Lexington Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01742</zip><lat>42.460152</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish In Concord</name><city>Concord</city><id>1591498</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.348610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Concord-Area Humanists invite all who wish to attend to join them for refreshments, socializing, and the screening of a movie about the 14-billion year evolution of the cosmos and the life within it. (See who else is going: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/concordareahumanists/events/43264042/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/concordareahumanists/events/43264042/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A talented impersonator of Charles Darwin will accept questions at the Birthday Party, about his life and times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A discussion will follow the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_ _ _&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group will meet in the Parlor of the First Parish church building, on the ground floor (below the church). The entrance is on the right side if you're looking at the building from the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_ _ _&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the movie, "Journey of the Universe" by Mary Evelyn Tucker and Brian Thomas Swimme:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We live in a universe of remarkable creativity that has evolved over some 14 billion years. The goal of Journey of the Universe is to tell the story of cosmic and Earth evolution drawing on the latest scientific knowledge, in a way that makes it profoundly relevant and deeply moving to the viewer. What emerges is an intensely poetic story, which evokes emotions of awe, excitement, fear, joy and belonging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This story told in Journey of the Universe is a dramatic one. Throughout billions of years of evolution, triumph, and disaster have been only a hair's breadth apart. Violence and creativity are pervasive. The ability of matter to organize and re-organize itself is remarkable - from the formation of the first atoms to the emergence of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The message of Journey of the Universe shows how we are not just a part of this astonishing process, we are at the very edge of evolution, a primate species that has found in its language and symbols the power to take over the very evolutionary process itself. But this control that we now exercise comes with a responsibility; and viewers of Journey of the Universe will not only be imbued with a sense of astonishment at all that has taken place, they will also come to feel the excitement in learning that now we live in a time when the human species is being asked to play a central role in activating the flourishing powers of Earth&amp;rsquo;s living systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"One of the aims of this project is to use the art of storytelling to capture the grandeur and drama of this epic of the universe - from the Big Bang, to where we are today in a moment of great transition."&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329075486000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328800826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Darwin Day 2012: Celebration in Concord</name><id>51693982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329069600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/51693982/</event_url></item>