<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street, 2nd Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1065386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183899</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am excited to once again co-host the Human Awareness Institute presenting a mini-workshop on Love and Intimacy. For anyone who has not yet experienced their work, I highly recommend taking advantage of this FREE opportunity to drop into sweet connection with yourself and others in a very safe and respectful space. And if you attended previously, you are of course welcome to attend again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover how your beliefs about love, intimacy and sexuality affect your relationships, sexual satisfaction, marriage, body image and ability to find love. Our personal relationship workshops are about:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Making the right relationship choices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Discovering greater depths of intimacy and love&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Finding love, being honest and creating intimacy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; Creating the relationships you&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt; relationship mini-workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have the opportunity to connect with others through verbal sharing and exercises designed to open your heart. Come and get a taste of what you&amp;rsquo;ve been craving, in a totally safe, non-sexual environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, September 18, 2-4:30 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FREE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Human Awareness Institute (HAI) welcomes singles, couples, traditional and non-traditional relationships, without regard to sexual choices or preferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will sell out. Please RSVP to save your spot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(If your plans change please update your RSVP to make room for someone else.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info about HAI visit &lt;a href="http://hai.org/love_is_a_miracle.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://hai.org/love_i...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Brynn, I want to thank you again for introducing me to the Human Awareness Institute Workshops. After attending the mini workshop you hosted last year I felt a closed heart begin to open again (my it felt good). Since that workshop I've attended two weekend workshops and will be attending a third this April. I wholeheartedly feel these experiential workshops are some of the best I've ever participated in. Combining a new loving sense of myself, along with new wonderful friends I've made, I can say my life is richer and will never be the same." -Ben&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316472873000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313080798000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enhancing Love and Intimacy in Your Life: A Free Mini-Workshop</name><id>29124681</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316368800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/29124681/</event_url></item>