<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We continue what has become the monthly nightlife event not to miss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us Sunday July 19th to enjoy the lively powerful sound of Bloco AfroBrazil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil is a 12-piece percussion ensemble that guarantees a spectacular show combining traditional Brazilian grooves like Samba and Axé with Funk, Rock, Jazz and even Hip Hop; add to this explosive mix of sultry vocals and three beautiful dancers and you got a recipe for FUN, Brazilian style!! Bring your dance shoes and leave your worries at the door!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friends....I guarantee a funtasitc time, that is if you like your music strong and your party loud.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Johnny's D's &lt;u&gt;kitchen closes at 7:30PM&lt;/u&gt; so you're not be able to order any food during the show.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You must be at least 21&lt;/b&gt; but you don't have to drink, just enjoy each others company and an amazing show. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 PM Conversation at the high tables in the dining area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:00 PM FREE Samba and Brazilian Afro Dance Class&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:30 PM Music begins&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once the drumming, singing and dancing begin, group conversation is difficult. Let's just enjoy the party! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$10 cash cover charge at the door&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/artist/blocoafrobrazil.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bloco AfroBrazil details&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/menu_drinks.html" target="_blank"&gt;Johnny D's drinks&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/parking.html" target="_blank"&gt;Map of Nearby Municiple Parking Lots&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge (Harvard Square): &lt;br /&gt;From Harvard Square travel north on Massachusetts Avenue and pass the porter Square T-Station and the Porter Square Shopping Center on the right. From Porter Square, continue on Massachusetts Avenue through seven traffic lights; at the seventh light turn right onto Cameron Avenue. At end of Cameron turn right onto Holland Street. 5 streets down on the right hand side, turn onto Buena Vista Road. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West (Route 2 or Route 16 Watertown): &lt;br /&gt;Head west on Route 16 past the Alewife T-Station and continue to the intersection of Massachusetts. Turn right onto Massachusetts Avenue. At the third set of traffic lights, take a left onto Cameron Avenue. *Follow Cameron Avenue directions below. At end of Cameron turn right onto Holland Street. 5 streets down on the right hand side, turn onto Buena Vista Road. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North (traveling South on Interstate 93): &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 32 (Route 60, Medford Square). Bear right at end of ramp proceeding through Medford Square and follow signs to Route 16 West. Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South (traveling North on Interstate 93): &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 31 (Route 16 West/Mystic Valley Pkwy). Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: &lt;br /&gt;Travel on Route 16 West (Revere Beach Pkwy – Mystic Valley Pkwy – Alewife Brook Pkwy). Follow Route 16 (for approximately 2 miles from the Route 93 exits) until you reach the intersection of Route 16 and Broadway (Somerville). Turn left onto Broadway. At the second set of traffic lights (Teele Square), bear right onto Holland Street. Parking is available in the metered municipal (city) lot which is immediately on your left and in other lots nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Create your route at &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subway - Red line to Davis station and exit from the Holland Street side (just turn right after you've exited the turnstiles). Johnny D's is directly across the street as you exit the station. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bus -  Routes: 87, 88, 90, 94 and 96&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Seated at the high tables in the dining area.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248482620000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Portuguese Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>portuguese-316</urlname><id>454600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston/Cambridge Portuguese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242812206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Johnny D's - Conversation and Show at  8:30PM on Sunday July 19th</name><id>10453396</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248049800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portuguese-316/events/10453396/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/4/global_7454068.jpeg</photo_url></item>