<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;WWW.EASTERNMASSREIA.COM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This Thursday August 14th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rockland Hotel  Formally The Radisson   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: Hotel ownership is in transition. The temporary name of the hotel is the Rockland hotel. It will soon become the Holiday Inn. So we are in the same location, and the name has changed.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;929 Hingham St.  &lt;br /&gt;Rockland, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting time is 6:00PM  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Thursday August 14th&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;EASTERN MASS REIA&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Rockland Hotel     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;929 Hingham St.  &lt;br /&gt;Rockland, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting time is 6:00PM &lt;br /&gt;Come Join Us  - Thursday, August 14th &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With foreclosure rates continuing to rise and lending guide lines more stringent the obvious need over the next 5 years will be affordable rental units. Current numbers suggest that an additional 1.5 million units will be rented over the next three years to those families being displaced by foreclosure. Developers have scaled back in recent years as the demand for new construction has waned, creating a potential shortage in the rental market. What does this mean to investors in this current market cycle? Opportunity!! This month we will analyze various multi-unit projects from the local area. We will do quick number screens on various properties to learn our maximum allowable acquisition cost. These formulas can be applied over and over again in any market. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting: 2nd Thursday of each month - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Rockland Hotel 929 Hingham St. Rockland, Ma.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: Registration and networking begins @ 6:00 pm. &lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting: Members are free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Visitors $25 at door. Pre-register online by the day before each monthly meeting and save $10! Go to www.easternmassreia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;On July 9th we hadour all-networking summer event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a tremendous turn out for the month of July. Even with all the vacations and the fact was a beautiful night, I am glad to see people are still putting forth the effort it takes to continue to move forward in Real Estate. Great connections were made and relationships deepened.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In June we had our Mentors and Deal Makers, Build Your Power Team Forum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We Learned from those in the know &lt;br /&gt;Local Area Investors and Resources &lt;br /&gt;AboutSubject to's, Trusts and Contracts  &lt;br /&gt;Hard Money &lt;br /&gt;Structuring the &amp;quot;Deal&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Buy and Hold &lt;br /&gt;Exit Strategies &lt;br /&gt;Legislation that effects your business &lt;br /&gt;And MUCH MUCH MORE... &lt;br /&gt;STAY INFORMED, KNOWLEDGE IS POWER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting and Seminar location: Rockland Radisson Hotel, 929 Hingham St., Rockland, MA. Map&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Thursday  May 8th: Supercharge you investing career by creating multiple streams of passive income. We all understand the power of the web; now put it to work for you. Join us as our guest speaker, Tampa Bay, Florida, Real Estate Investors Association founder and ?Marketing Magician? Dan Stojadinovic shares his proven strategies to take your investment business to the next level. You?ll want to be a part of this modern day Gold Rush. Just using a couple of Dan?s suggestions have already increased our site traffic, after all, you?re reading this, aren?t you? Networking begins at 6:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;EASTERN MASSACHUSETTS REAL ESTATE INVESTORS ASSOCIATION&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rockland Radisson Hotel 929 Hingham St. Rockland, MA (Exit 14 Rt 3) Thursday March 13th 2008 from 6:00-9:30 pm SEE YOU THERE &lt;br /&gt;Food and Refreshments &lt;br /&gt;For more info contact us info@easternmassreia.com &lt;br /&gt;1 888 588 REIA Ext.701  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The door fee for monthly meetings is $25. Pre-Register online for $15!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to www.easternmassreia.com to preregister&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Become a member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Individual $160   Partner/Spouse  $275&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Business Resource Providers interested in learning about opportunities for sponsorship e-mail us businessresources@easternmassreia.com  or call 1 888 588 REIA Ext.701 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Mass REIA is evolving.  &lt;br /&gt;Come be a part of the change &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;I look forward to us having a very prosperous 2008. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s. This is Our monthly networking, education, and deal making event, here at Eastern Mass REIA,  if you have a deal let us know. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investors Association    &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Massachusetts REIA does not claim to give expert advice in investing, nor do we endorse what featured speakers say. We do not give professional, legal, financial or tax advice. We suggest that you get competent licensed counsel before putting into effect anything you hear in our club, whether in private conversation or something said publicly. The ideas presented are only meant to stimulate your thoughts in the field of real estate investing and are not to be taken as professional advice. All investing comes with risk; therefore, as adults, it is your responsibility to exercise due diligence before making any purchase, great or small. We encourage you to be careful when ordering coffee at a McDonalds drive through window...coffee is usually hot.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek Ebrecht</member_name><member_id>4695117</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223590738000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestate-730</urlname><id>598232</id><group_lat>42.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9100036621</group_lon><name>EMREIA-Eastern Mass Real Estate Investors Assoc.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218757035000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eastern Massachusetts Real Estate Investment Association September Meetup</name><id>8546944</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221172200000</time><rsvp_limit>99</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestate-730/events/8546944/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/8/e/global_3350446.jpeg</photo_url></item>