<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Take a post-holiday break...for&amp;nbsp;a relaxing day of&amp;nbsp;making art! No formal instruction today--just&amp;nbsp;a chance to hang out, make stuff and chat with old and new friends.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME:&lt;/strong&gt; 1 p.m. to whenever. Come and leave whenever you like. We'll head to the wine tasting at 5:30 and possibly to dinner at the crepe place nearby after that--then resuming art-making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Yourself, your art supplies and whatever project you&amp;rsquo;d like to work on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$10 per person, regardless of when you arrive or depart. Cash is preferred, but we can accept a check made to ArtStudio 360. Your contributions help cover the Studio's expenses. For that reason, we&amp;rsquo;re unable to accept IOUs or partial payments. We&amp;rsquo;re happy to provide directions to a nearby ATM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.) and some supplies including acrylic paints, collage materials, etc.&amp;nbsp;Access to a microwave, toaster oven, refrigerator, kitchen sink and restroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND&lt;/strong&gt;: Anyone (18+ only, please). Just sign up through the NE ATC+ Meetup Group. Membership in the Meetup group is free; joining simply allows you to reserve a space in events at ArtStudio 360.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;These smaller sessions&amp;nbsp;often fill&amp;nbsp;quickly.&amp;nbsp;Reserve a place by RSVP-ing "yes" using Meetup's RSVP function. If your plans (or your guests' plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly so that your space becomes available to someone else. Please do this right up to the start time of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;In the unlikely event that we need to cancel due to bad weather or other reasons---or even if we're just getting a late start--we'll post a message on the Web site and e-mail everyone who's RSVP'd "yes." So to be on the safe side, please check the Web site and your inbox before departing for ArtStudio 360!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325446442000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321546314000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Between-the-Holidays Open Studio</name><id>41511842</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325268000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/41511842/</event_url></item>