<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>11th floor  (Across from Border's Book Store)</address_2><address_1>294 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.357275</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 227-1855 </phone><name>Optaros</name><city>Boston</city><id>847473</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058369</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come share your experiences with PHP and other technologies and show us how you have applied it to your projects. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is your chance to come up to the podium and have 15 minutes to present what interesting things you have done. Please - no powerpoint. Just demo your cool stuff, have fun, and answer questions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have done this in the past and it was a huge success and a lot of fun. It's really amazing to see what others are doing. Sharpen your presentation skills and show off the cool innovations your working on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have something to show?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please &lt;a href="mailto:michael.bourque@gmail.com" target="_blank"&gt;send me a note&lt;/a&gt; and let me know your interested in doing a show and tell. Remember you don't really need to prepare a presentation. Just show or demo something interesting you have done with PHP and other technology.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People signed Up to show:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adam Cassel&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like to do a brief demo of running a PHP based application within MSFT's Azure cloud services and storage environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adam Green&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm developing a Twitter application that collects all tweets about stocks and presents them as a browseable, database Web app. It uses PHP on the back end to capture tweets from Twitter's streaming API, parse them, store them in MySQL, and return them as XML to Ajax calls from the front end. Javascript and jQuery are used on the front end to display the tweets in a scrolling, real-time display. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to present the architecture and some of the code to the group to get feedback and suggestions for improvements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michael Bourque&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be demoing a great prototyping and mockup tool and will be raffling off free copies of the software to those who attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Andrew Drane&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; I'm excited for show-and-tell on the 2nd and would love to show off BetterLesson which is written in CakePHP (www,betterlesson.org)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've been working on some exciting integration with other services - this weekend we are switching to Amazon cloud hosting and are beginning to use SOLR to power searching&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ernie Gillis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be demonstrating the Online Reserve web application I developed for my day job at Berklee College of Music. This project, now in the early stages of its second version, is written within the Symfony framework. The Online Reserves is an electronic version of the traditional library classroom reserves. While running on PHP, the project also incorporates MySQL, Sybase (via ODBC), Amazon Web Services, QuickTime Streaming Server, Flash, and AJAX technologies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can park at the Pi alley parking (&lt;a href="http://www.pialleygarage.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pialleygarage.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.pialleygar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;).  $12 if you enter after 5:00.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260216124000</updated><rating><average>4.30000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258130451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SHOW n' TELL night...</name><id>11866800</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259798400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/11866800/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/c/global_11786540.jpeg</photo_url></item>