<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>229 Main Street</address_2><address_1>Alumni Recital Hall (Redfern Arts Center)</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03435</zip><lat>42.930000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Keene State College</name><city>Keene</city><id>441720</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.279999</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Merrimack Valley 911 Truth is glad to be supportive of our sister groups' coup in getting &lt;a href="http://www.ae911truth.org/aboutus.php" target="_blank"&gt;Richard Gage&lt;/a&gt;, founder of &lt;a href="http://www.ae911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Architects and Engineers for 911 Truth&lt;/a&gt; to come to Keene State College to speak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard has been a practicing architect for 20 years and has worked on most types of building construction including numerous fire-proofed steel framed buildings. He became interested in the 9/11 WTC high-rise &amp;quot;collapses&amp;quot; after hearing the startling conclusions of a reluctant 9/11 researcher, David Ray Griffin, on the radio in 2006, which launched his own unyielding quest for 9/11 Truth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard will present a slide show which provides evidence that the three World Trade Center buildings were felled by controlled demolition. The pieces of evidence include expert corroboration, foreknowledge of collapse, whistle blowers, government documentation and video documentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monadnock 911 Truth Alliance and Student Scholars for 911 Truth are organizing this event and we will assist in the promotional efforts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will post more details here as they become available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------&lt;br /&gt;CAR POOL DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;No official carpool has been set up, but call or text 603-828-8306 if you want to try to arrange something.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------------------&lt;br /&gt;PARKING:&lt;br /&gt;Head North on Main Street and then turn Left onto Wyman Way to get to the parking lot right outside the Redfern Arts Center.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3581956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542446000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193170778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Richard Gage @ Keene State College</name><id>6604205</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197590400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/6604205/</event_url></item>