<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>17 Water Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502523</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-245-1525</phone><name>Harrington's Food &amp; Spirits</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>1143502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;***Please Update your RSVPs and indicate approximate ETA. Arrive early if you can to avoid&amp;nbsp;any lines. A bunch of people should be there mid to late afternoon. The place will be packed after 5pm. E Mail other RSVPs attending to coordinate. If you plan to be there for a while and need to eat I strongly suggest putting your name in for a table.***&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Red Sox Natives are going Green on Thursday, March 17 to celebrate St Patrick's Day at Harrington's Food and Spirits in downtown Wakefield. Harrington's is a cozy Irish Restaurant and Pub with two floors. We have been there before. The food is great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harrington's is all Irish, all day, all night, on both floors. There is live entertainment all day at Harrington's with Sligo Road, Outside Madra, Casterbridge Union, Dave O'Sobol and Traditional Irish Seisiun. There is a $10.00 cover after 2 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear your Green and be there at 5 pm or whenever. Please RSVP and let us know approximately what time you will join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking in downtown Wakefield in the public lot across from Harrington's and along Water and Main Streets. The location is T accessible by the 136 and 137 Bus from the Orange Line in Malden Center. And Commuter Rail accessible from North Station via the Reading and Haverhill Trains stopping at Wakefield with a less than 10 minute walk up Albion to Main to Water Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to pay in cash as you order or maintain your own bar tab and settle with your server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harringtonspub.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wear Red Sox Hats, Ask Dan or the Hostess or Security, Check the second floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jon</member_name><member_id>6918204</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300499040000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>A large group of us attended last year and we had a blast making new friends and... stuff happened. Get there early. Avoid the lines.</why><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293595842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Green Sox Natives Celebrate St. Patrick's Day at Harrington's Irish Pub</name><id>15845592</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300395600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/15845592/</event_url></item>