<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Introduction to ActionScript 3.0: Thinking OOP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you new to Flex? Are you new to ActionScripting? Need a primer on AS3 to get started. This presentation is an introduction to the AS3 language and how to start using it in a proper Object Oriented manner. Bill Sanders will give a great introduction to explain the ActionScript language and how you can get started using i in your projects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ActionScript 3.0 Design Patterns&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knowing and understanding design patterns is critical to become a proficient programmer. In the second part of Bill Sander's presentation. He will demonstrate some of the more commonly used design patterns found in the ActionScript language. If you want to start programming in ActionScript correctly and avoid some of the common pitfalls, you simply can't miss this month's meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bill Sanders is a Professor of Multimedia Web Design and Development (MWDD) at the University of Hartford (a department he helped start in 1999--it's a combination of Computer Science, Art, Communications, Engineering Technology and internet/web design and development). He is interested in and involved with Flash, ActionScript,  Design Patterns, Flash Media Server, PHP, ASP.NET/C# and all things relating to Web business. He has served as a consultant for and developed software for different companies. One of the most recent was a Flash Media Server application  for a string of newspapers in the Midwest, but has done consulting work for ActionScript architecture and has worked for Macromedia in developing testing software for their video player component. He is active as an alpha/beta tester for software products. His Blog on ActionScript 3.0 Design Patterns can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.as3dp.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.as3dp.com...&lt;/a&gt; where he and Chandima attempt to extend their own and others love of ActionScript 3.0 design patterns. Main web site (&lt;a href="http://www.sandlight.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sandlight....&lt;/a&gt;. More information than you need( &lt;a href="http://uhaweb.hartford.edu/WSANDERS" target="_blank"&gt;http://uhaweb.hartfor...&lt;/a&gt;) He lives in Bloomfield, Connecticut with his wife, a compulsive obsessive Greater Swiss Mountain dog and neurotic Basset Hound.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234916050000</updated><rating><average>4.13999986649</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>52</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229040474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Actionscript Design Patterns</name><id>9323957</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232582400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/9323957/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/f/global_5719263.jpeg</photo_url></item>