<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I am scheduling this Black Friday hike.  The timeline should appeal to those of you who have the day off.  You can still make the 5 a.m. door busters and then head out to the real world for a refreshing hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Almost 1,000 forested acres with light hiking with some hills. Interesting surface mining features worth exploring from long ago that are 3 gully-like features. Some tails go down to and along the Connecticut River. The feature we will head for is called Split Rock with views of the Connecticut River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike will be not more than 3 hours and will cover about 4 miles on the outer loop of trails. This should be a gentle hike in the woods with nothing scarey or dangerous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please plan on wearing sturdy shoes or hiking boots.  Bring water and snacks.  I highly recommend using a backpack to have hands free.&lt;br /&gt;Park in the area on the right near the pavillion.  We will meet at 11:00 and be done no later than 2:00 (for those of you not willing to do the bad math).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park information and map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325224&amp;amp;depNav_GID=1650" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford area:&lt;br /&gt;1. Take I-91 South.&lt;br /&gt;2. Take Exit 22S onto CT-9 South (5.5 miles).&lt;br /&gt;3. Take Exit 16 to Middletown, CT-17/ST. JOHN’S SQ. Go around sharp curve and onto the bridge over Connecticut River (1.1 miles).&lt;br /&gt;4. After the bridge, take RIGHT following CT-66 East (5.0 miles).&lt;br /&gt;5. In Cobalt, take RIGHT onto CT-151 (2.5 miles).&lt;br /&gt;6. At stoplight, take RIGHT FORK onto Hurd Park Rd (about 0.3 miles) &lt;br /&gt;7. Park entrance will be on right.&lt;br /&gt;8. Follow park road to RIGHT side road to the pavilion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259510740000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257980493000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Friday hike to Hurd State Park, East Hampton, CT</name><id>11853839</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259337600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11853839/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/f/global_705503.jpeg</photo_url></item>