<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>At my most recent event this past sunday afternoon, there was a BIG interest for a games night. I personally do like the idea and am personally happy to hostess this event. However, I am requesting to PLEASE BE RESPECTIVE as I am planning this event in my home. I honestly am a bit nervous about doing so, however I personally had gone to Meet Up events at other peoples homes and 99 percent it has not been a problem. If you are concerned and don't feel you have a good comfort level, please feel free to e mail myself personally and we can certainly talk.  &lt;br /&gt;I also thought it's Spring time already and it might be fun to do a pot luck too! I had created a list and when you RSVP, please quote what number you will be bringing to avoid duplicate food items. (cut and pate if that may work). &lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to bring any kinds of games whether it's Taboo, Settlers of Catan, Boggle, etc..... I personally have Apples to Apples, Scrabble, Clue, Scattergories, and some others that may be of interest. &lt;br /&gt;Here is the list for the pot luck: &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;     3. Appetizer #3 (enough for 6 people)- cheese/crackers (would like from one of    the attendees)&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;      5. Main dish with meat (enough for 6 people)&lt;br /&gt;      6. Main dish with out meat (enough for 6 people)&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;      8. Garden Salad (enough for 12 people) (would definitely like from attendee)&lt;br /&gt;      9. Ceasar/other type of salad (enough for 12 people)&lt;br /&gt;     10. Side dish #1(enough for 6 people)&lt;br /&gt;     11. Side dish  #2 (enough for 6 people)    &lt;br /&gt;     12. Side dish #3 (enough for 6 people) (bread/rolls would like from an attendee)&lt;br /&gt;     13. Dessert #1 (cake/pie enough for 12 people)&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;     15. Dessert #3 fruit platter/ fruit salad enough for 12 people&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;      &lt;br /&gt;     18. beer- one 12 pack&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I, the hostess will provide all the paper products and Will take appetizer #1 &lt;br /&gt;I will be updating the list as people respond. Please be sure to bring enough as i had attended some other pot lucks where the selection was very slim.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My place is T accessable. You can take Bus #71 to Mt Auburn Street and Bigelow Ave if coming by &amp;quot;T&amp;quot;. There is plenty of parking around as the meters are free after 6:00 PM. Please use mapquest in regards for directions to my place. I will distribute my phone number to people who do sign up as a &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; closer to the date as it is a private number in case if you do need to call if lost. Please look on your email thru out the say on satruday for my number.     &lt;br /&gt;Looking foward to my 3rd event and hopefully that this will be a success. &lt;br /&gt;Lastly, Please be sure to help with clean up before you depart and also PLEASE be 90 percent you are attending as this IS a pot luck event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please ring door bell #14 , say you are part of meet up, and I will let you in</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>krista</member_name><member_id>3604506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241916456000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-1958</urlname><id>1096649</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge and Boston Singles Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238681838000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last minute Spring Pot Luck/ Games Night </name><id>10097209</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238886900000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-1958/events/10097209/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/8/global_3699192.jpeg</photo_url></item>