<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>226 Hanover St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02113</zip><lat>42.363045</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-742-9200</phone><name>Lucca Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>1079624</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055285</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Lucca (http:www.luccaboston.com), named after a town in Tuscany, serves superb Northern Italian cuisine. Our holiday banquet will have a fixed price of $55. That includes 3 food courses: Appetizer-Bibb salad, prosciutto or squash and apple bisque, Entree-Rigatoni Bolognese, gnocchi, roasted chicken breast or pan-roasted salmon, Dessert-tiramisu or bread pudding. It also includes either red wine-2004 Saniovese/Canaiolo/Montepulciano or white wine-2010 Soave Classico. Tax and tip are also included. What it does not include is a pre-dinner drink or any drinks during the meal that aren't either of the 2 wines listed above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please have cash of $55 up front, as we won't be getting a bill. My credit card will be charged automatically. The restaurant is located on the first&amp;nbsp;block of Hanover Street on the left side as you're coming from the Greenway. Haymarket (Green &amp;amp; Orange lines) is the nearest T-stop and the Parcel 7 Garage (136 Blackstone St.-entrance on Sudbury St.) is the best place to park. The restaurant also has valet parking. For those who arrive before 7:00, join us downstairs for a cocktail hour and mingling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's extremely important to attend if you've signed up, or cancel by noon the day before. It will be a festive evening in the North End. Please try to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim S.</member_name><member_id>4216983</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324855833000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM</urlname><id>1397251</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>North End Eating Meetup (NEEM)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323462249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lucca-Holiday Banquet</name><id>43959222</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324166400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-End-Eating-Meetup-NEEM/events/43959222/</event_url></item>