<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Tonight we are in for an educational and fun adventure as Herb Pearce teaches us the Enneagram of Personality at his studio in Arlington.  Many of us are familiar with Myers-Briggs but do not know the Enneagram of Personality which some people argue is equally if not more important.  This particular workshop is reserved for Unique People and Herb has generously reduced his rate to $10.00 per person. Refreshments will be served.  We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it.  Due to the size of the studio, a RSVP limit has been set.  Below is a much more detailed description from Herb Pearce’s website.  Herb has come strongly recommended from several people in the group and I am excited about the workshop!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***** Details from Herb Pearce’s website *****     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About the Enneagram **&lt;br /&gt;The star-shaped Enneagram (Greek for &amp;quot;nine&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;drawing&amp;quot;) groups human emotions and behavior—positive and negative –into nine personality types. According to the Enneagram theory, personality develops as a result of a unique combination of genetics, cultural influence, family and childhood experience, and spiritual growth inclination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About the workshop **&lt;br /&gt;Learn about the Enneagram and identify your own core type. Understand your relationship to others based on their types. Herb &amp;quot;acts out&amp;quot; each type (very entertaining and loads of fun), interviews each person for correct core type and points out growth and relationship tips unique to each type. If you haven't done an Enneagram workshop yet, this is essential for understanding types and it's an entertaining and insightful experience even if you've done it a bunch of times!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About Herb Pearce **&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce, M. Ed is a Boston-based, individual, couples and family therapist, with over 26 years experience. A leading expert in the Enneagram, he has led over 1,500 Enneagram experiences in the last 15 years with talks, public workshops, counseling, and teambuilding trainings in corporations and organizations. Herb's trainings, talks and workshops provide a wealth of understanding and clarity regarding personality differences and his presentation style is direct, but gentle and humorous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam</member_name><member_id>4049831</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1236989192000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233898060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Enneagram of Personality</name><id>9685594</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236384000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/9685594/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/8/global_7203288.jpeg</photo_url></item>