<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Science Shaping Our World (SHOW)- The Role of Academics in Drug Discovery- Filling the Gap&lt;br /&gt;When:              Thursday, November 11, 2010 from 6:00 p.m. to 9:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Where:             Microsoft New England Research &amp;amp; Development Center &lt;br /&gt;                        1 Memorial Drive &lt;br /&gt;                        Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;Register:           &lt;a href="http://shownovember2010.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://shownovember20...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;November’s SHOW will focus on the role of academics in drug discovery. Particularly, we will be discussing how the relationship between academia and industry is evolving relative to bridging the gap between the research bench and commercialization. Further, the event will focus on the Laboratory for Drug Discovery in Neurodegeneration (LDDN) which was established in 2001 as a model for how academia can apply its research findings to drug discovery especially in diseases and approaches that are not commonly found in the pharmaceutical industry. The LDDN has developed a strategy which complements the efforts in industry and has an established track record of progressing projects along the drug discovery pathway, from assay development and high-throughput screening through medicinal chemistry on lead compounds and testing candidate drugs in animal models of disease. The unique aspects of establishing academic drug discovery will be discussed with specific case studies highlighting specific projects.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289572383000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289350269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Role of Academics in Drug Discovery- Filling the Gap</name><id>15398158</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289516400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15398158/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>