<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Arlington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.352940</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Taj Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>537127</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>BOSTON?Sen. John McCain is heading to Boston next week as he works to replenish his campaign war chest after securing the Republican presidential nomination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Arizona senator will be the guest of honor Wednesday evening at the Taj Boston hotel overlooking the Public Garden.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An invitation offers a private reception with McCain in exchange for contributing $2,300, the maximum donation allowed. The price for a follow up reception is $1,000 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the hosts are Peter Nicholas, a co-founder of Boston Scientific; Richard Egan, a co-founder of EMC Corp.; and former acting Gov. Jane Swift.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Proposed idea:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will stand across the street from the hotel, along the Public Garden, which happens to be the location of the 9-11 Memorial. Given the sacred location, this meetup will be billed as a &amp;quot;Silent Vigil for 9-11 Truth.&amp;quot; We will make an extra effort to be polite and respectiful, even if people treat us disrespectfully.&lt;br /&gt;To maximize our impact, we will standardlize our appearance for this vigil, with everyone using the black and white 9-11 Truth Now signs (which will be provided by the meetup organizers.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given that McCain is a terrible war hawk, we will likely cross paths with peace activists again. Let us continue to build bridges with the antiwar movement. Let our silent vigil serve as a mega-watt bullhorn for truth and justice.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205532306000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204950622000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Big-ticket Boston fundraiser for McCain 3-12-08 evening</name><id>7488602</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205359200000</time><rsvp_limit>528</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7488602/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>