<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Bridge Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03076</zip><lat>42.723297</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chunky's Cinema Pub</name><city>Pelham</city><id>5387602</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.319054</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;another FYI, we've got the BIG theater, and I went and took a look, there's at least 120 excellent seats!!!&amp;nbsp; yikes, we've got a crowd of a solid 90 people...we'll feel like we're in INDY...lol&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GO PATS!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have my&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;own theatre for this. Admission is free and popcorn complimentary. Be there at 5pm for a good seat, and eat/order from their delicious menu (much different from when they first opened ;) full cash bar, even includes martinis. please let me know by Monday, January 30th by noon, if you will be coming and how many people...I'm sooooo excited to see this on the BIG SCREEN! Kick off is at 6:30.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;email me for questions,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GO PATS!!!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;susan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as you probably know by now....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AFC Champion Patriots face Giants in Super Bowl XLVI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By New England Patriots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The New England Patriots will seek their fourth Super Bowl title when they face off against the New York Giants in Super Bowl XLVI on Feb. 5.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;img src="http://www.patriots.com/assets/images/sbxlvi/325-game-prev-sbxlvi.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATRIOTS (13-3) vs. GIANTS (9-7)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Sunday, February 5, 2012 - 6:30 p.m.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Lucas Oil Stadium (*63,000)&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The New England Patriots will seek their fourth Super Bowl title when they face off against the New York Giants in Super Bowl XLVI on Feb. 5. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;PATRIOTS ADVANCE TO SEVENTH SUPER BOWL OVERALL; SIXTH OF THE KRAFT ERA&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

New England has advanced to its seventh Super Bowl in franchise history, a total that ranks third in NFL history behind only Dallas and Pittsburgh (8 berths each). The Patriots' appearance in Super Bowl XLVI will be its sixth Super Bowl appearance since Robert Kraft purchased the team in 1994, a total that is the most in the league over that span (Pittsburgh, 4). Kraft is the first owner in NFL history to have his team in six Super Bowls. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALL-TIME SUPER BOWL BERTHS&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

8 Dallas &lt;br /&gt;

8 Pittsburgh &lt;br /&gt;

7 New England &lt;br /&gt;

6 Denver &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;SUPER BOWL REMATCH&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Super Bowl XLVI in Indianapolis will be the fifth Super Bowl rematch in NFL history. The New England Patriots and the New York Giants faced each other in Super Bowl XLII on Feb. 3, 2008 in Arizona with the Giants prevailing 17-14. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;SUPER BOWL REMATCHES&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Miami vs. Washington - Super Bowl VII and Super Bowl XVII Pittsburgh vs. Dallas - Super Bowl X, Super Bowl XIII, Super Bowl XXX San Francisco vs. Cincinnati - Super Bowl XVI, Super Bowl XXIII Dallas-Buffalo vs. Super Bowl XXVII, Super Bowl XXVIII &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BROADCAST INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;TELEVISION:&lt;/strong&gt; The game will be broadcast by NBC and can be seen in Boston on WHDH-TV Channel 7. Al Michaels will handle play-by-play duties with Cris Collinsworth providing color. Michele Tafoya will serve as the sideline reporter. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;NATIONAL RADIO:&lt;/strong&gt; This week's game will be broadcast to a national audience by Westwood One Radio Sports. Kevin Harlan and Boomer Esiason will call the game. James Lofton and Mark Malone will provide sideline analysis. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;RADIO:&lt;/strong&gt; 98.5 FM, The Sports Hub, is the flagship station for the Patriots Radio Network. Play-by-play broadcaster Gil Santos is in his 35th season as the voice of the Patriots and will call the action along with Patriots Hall of Famer Gino Cappelletti. Scott Zolak will provide sideline analysis. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SERIES HISTORY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.patriots.com/assets/images/sbxlvi/325-tale-of-the-tape.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The Patriots and Giants will meet in their second Super Bowl on Feb. 5, 2012 in Super Bowl XLVI at Lucas Oil Stadium in Indianapolis, Indiana. The game will be a rematch of Super Bowl XLII played on Feb. 13, 2008 in Glendale, Ariz. The Giants 17-14 win in that game snapped the Patriots' perfect season. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The Super Bowl will be the third time in 2011 that the Patriots and Giants will square off. They met in the 2011 preseason-finale at Gillette Stadium with the Giants taking an 18-17 win. They met in the regular season when the Giants ended a 20-game home winning streak for the Patriots with a 24-20 win on Nov. 6 at Gillette Stadium. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The two teams have met nine times in the regular season since their series was inaugurated in 1970. The Patriots claim a 5-4 edge in regular season play The series dates back to 1970, the year of the AFL-NFL merger and includes some memorable games despite the relative infrequency of the matchups. In 1996, the Patriots stole a 23-22 win to clinch a playoff berth after trailing 22-3 in the fourth quarter. In the 2007 regular season, the Patriots captured a 38-35 win to finish a perfect 16-0. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The first preseason game between the teams was the first NFL game played in Foxborough, as the Patriots opened Schaefer Stadium with a 20-14 win. The clubs have been frequent preseason opponents recently, squaring off in the preseason openers for three straight years from 2001-03 and in preseason finales for seven straight seasons from 2005- 11.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>ask which theatre the meetup group will be in ;)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328631294000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>95</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327696159000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriots in the Superbowl on the BIG SCREEN!!</name><id>49898262</id><headcount>90</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328479200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/49898262/</event_url></item>