<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Bolton, Then Gloria's hike, then dinner at Wickham park ??&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:30....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thats right,&lt;br /&gt;Get your Gohst Busting/Hunting Gear, and some spray paint..&lt;br /&gt;I hear you can spraypaint gohsts to make them visible and then chase them..&lt;br /&gt;if you are too much of a seniour for the chasing bring the spraypaint anyway, be a senoiur dellinkwint by spraypainting your name on the mountain rock indicating you can still make it to the top, werent taken by the gohst, or got lost in the cave. Well we might be able to outline your body shape if you become a gohst..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HISTORY:Now to the ghosts of Notch Hollow.. What causes the seeming rapid weather changes that occur just at the Notch? Drivers have reported their car windows misting over and sometimes freezing solid white as they pass over the abandoned railroad line in the deepest part of the Notch. I know that to be a fact for it has happened more than once to my family. Who watches over the painted rock? Who painted the flag there after 9-11? Who puts the Christmas tree and flag up on the rock? Whose eerie voice is heard singing up on the rocks when the moon moves across the sky on some lonely summer nights? There are ghostly stories of quarrymen, the Dutchman, Chief Miantinomah, and many more, all of whom died untimely deaths in Notch Hollow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Former Bolton historian Larry Larned (now a ghost himself) showed me that of the 26 Notch Hollow buildings that still existed as late as 1913 only one remains today. Notch Hollow is now a specter of the past, a part of old Quarryville that no longer exists. Most people now call it Bolton Notch from the deep trench left by more than 200 years of quarrying untill wiggeling skellatons were found. But in the 1600s the Mohegan Indians knew the area to be the highest land in the region, dominated by an enormous sacred flat rock, Wiashguagwumsuck, at the northwestern border of their territory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Intermarriage in the Massachusetts Bay colony was illegal. The first recorded untimely death at Wiashguagwumsuck was that of Peter Hager, a young Dutchman who lived there with his Podunk Indian wife Wunnee in a cave on the southwest side. Peter was fatally wounded at Wiashguagwumsuck but his body has never been found. Later, in 1643, at the conclusion of the Pequot war with the British, Mohegan Chieftain Uncas had his prisoner, the Pequot Chief Miantinomah, executed as they passed sacred Wiashguagwumsuck. Miantinomah's body, with a tomahawk protruding out the back of its skull, also has never been found. Quarrying also claimed several lives over the years. These are all possible suspects in the old Notch ghost tales.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The railroad executives built a clubhouse for themselves and their influential friends at the west end of Notch Hollow. The trains would stop there when signaled, as well as at the usual stop at the station in the Notch. Steam from the train would condense and in the winter sometimes frosted over nearby windows. The story goes that four lawyers who were wheeling and dealing in the booming thread mill industry had met at the clubhouse to strategize. A big hulking man entered from the howling snowstorm and silently stood before the fire rubbing his enormous hands, trying to warm himself. They could not see his face but worried that the stranger may have heard some of their schemes and wondering if he was from Willimantic, they demanded, &amp;quot;Where are you from, sir?&amp;quot; Suddenly the room was as cold as all outdoors. The man spun around, and with eyes like burning coals he snarled, &amp;quot;From Hell, where you four are going.&amp;quot; Then he threw open the door and disappeared back into the swirling snow and was never seen again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ghost train has been reported in many places along both abandoned and operating rail lines. The legend says that the ghost train's steam, wheels, and carriages make not a single sound as they sweep along on invisible rails. Sometimes people in Bolton have seen a white steamy mist sweep down the greenway trail as though it was from an old ghostly steam train. Could the sudden condensation on car windows in the summer, and the sudden winter frosting over of car windows as they cross the abandoned rail line at the Notch, be caused by the steam of Bolton's passing ghost train? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now Ghosts and Gobblins like sweet things so we will meet at Munsons Chocolate Factory Store on RTE 6 right in Bolton to get our supplys and plot our strategy so they wont hear us coming or set up BOOOby traps..&lt;br /&gt;Bring some lunch for the top to share with the hungry spirits...or spirits to raise the spirits..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Geting to Munsons Chocolates, from Hartford :&lt;br /&gt;rte 84 East to rte 384 (exit #59)&lt;br /&gt;Take 384 to the end, rte 44 and 6 split there..&lt;br /&gt;TAKE THE RIGHT FORK ONTO RTE 6. &lt;br /&gt;as you decend down the hill less than a quarter mile on the left is MUNSONS,&lt;br /&gt;I habe a dark blue toyota avalon and will have the orange traffic cones in view.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193759308000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193081852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GOHST BUSTERS, Cave Visitors, and Senior Dellinkwints Walk</name><id>6596952</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193586300000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/6596952/</event_url></item>