<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Greenwoods Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06063</zip><lat>41.942890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Peoples State Forest</name><city>Barkhamsted</city><id>804801</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.997727</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>As far as rain ,think positive and it will not rain, ok, a little rain Gore Tex, mucho rain or snow, stay in bed and read a book. I will know the weather closer to the hike date and make a decision then&lt;br /&gt;Thanks &lt;br /&gt;Joe&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The loop hike combines history ,nature, incredible mountain views, and features Manitou stones, glacial boulders, and a beaver meadow.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds like a nice hike, I have never been here so I will give it a go,&lt;br /&gt;This is a 6.2 mile loop, some portions steep, I will meet at the commuter lot on Route 34 and Route 15, exit 58 in Orange at 7:45AM .We depart here at 8:00, we should arrive by 9:30, stretch out and start at 10:00 AM. You are more than welcome to drive up and meet at the parking lot at the main entrance.&lt;br /&gt;We will hike to the nature center, pick up the blue blazed trail, follow it north, then take the blue w/yellow dot to Greenwoods road, hike south down the road and pick up the yellow blaze trail on the left, head south eastto the orange blaze and head back to the nature center.&lt;br /&gt;4.0 hours at a moderate pace. &lt;br /&gt;Bring water, at least one liter, high calorie, quick-burn energy food, trail mix, dried fruit, bagel, etc.&lt;br /&gt;Have enough layers to keep you warm, hat, gloves, wool or synthetic socks, fleece, jacket, it may get nippy !&lt;br /&gt;Direction, From the junction of Routes 44/318 turn onto 318, cross the Farmington, River and turn left onto East River Road to parking area.&lt;br /&gt;I encourage all to carpool, it is a good way to meet your fellow hikers, be green, save gas and shorten your carbon footprint.&lt;br /&gt;Any questions email me at ganski223@aol.com and I hope I can answer them.&lt;br /&gt;Optional  after the hike, lunch, a cold beverage, warm up, I am open to suggestions for a place to eat up here, so hikers who are going this  your homework, extra credit if they brew there own frosty cold ones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on the 22nd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227712246000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hiking-575</urlname><id>1282762</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Walks in the Woods</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225757757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HIKE AT PEOPLES STATE FOREST, BARKHAMSTED, CT</name><id>9087962</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227366000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hiking-575/events/9087962/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/0/global_5551936.jpeg</photo_url></item>