<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/7/a/event_216149562.jpeg" width="150" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This game is generously on loan from our very own &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/members/14511146/"&gt;Katie&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From boardgamegeek.com:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Manufacturer &lt;br /&gt;

 Imagination Pickles to Penguins Board Game, the totally new and hilarious party game where you need a fast hand, mind and mouth if you’re going to win. Take a deep breath and let the action and chaos begin. Two cards are turned over and placed alongside the center deck. These are the cards which all players will play to. Players frantically place cards from their own deck on top of either card, but they must say out loud an aspect of commonality between their card and the card in the center. For example: A train picture on a airplane picture “Modes of transport.” The first player to get rid of all their cards wins the game. 6 and above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Product Description &lt;br /&gt;

 Take a deep breath and let the action and chaos begin. The totally new and hilarious party game where you need a fast hand, mind and mouth if you're going to win. 2+ players Ages 6+&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will send out my number the day before for those that don't have it, will be in the lobby (ticket sales lobby, not concession stand lobby) at least 30 minutes before the movie starts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1365960436000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363823536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night: Pickles to Penguins</name><id>110259012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365463800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/110259012/</event_url></item>