<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Pleasant View Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02828</zip><lat>41.881096</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Anna Mc Cabe Elementary School</name><city>Smithfield</city><id>1677221</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.541580</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many distances are available,&amp;nbsp;11/17/23/33/53, ride the length you feel comfortable with. &amp;nbsp; Route is marked on the road with paint, and route maps are distributed at the beginning of the ride. &amp;nbsp;There is no fee, and after the ride, there is a Social tent that I'll be manning with some light snacks. &amp;nbsp;Bring a chair and some extra beverages to enjoy after the ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ride starts at 10AM, it is advised to arrive around 9:30 in order to get situated, do some pre-ride socializing and hear the ride announcements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the route map is being updated, so I can't link to the PDF of the route to give you an idea of the terrain, but it is a little bit hilly, largely quite low traffic country roads, with only a few short sections where auto traffic is much present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No speed is too slow, ride at your own pace, many NBW riders take it nice and easy and spend most of the day enjoying being outdoors, not racing through the route as fast as they can.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the social/hospitality tent throughout the day</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305551411000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>An opportunity to see something other than the usual bike path, quite country roads in Northwest RI, and NBW social tent will be up as a chance to get to know the local riding club that hosts rides every Sunday.</why><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305073528000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Road Ride with Narragansett Bay Wheelmen</name><id>17922791</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305466200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/17922791/</event_url></item>