<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Berkeley philosopher &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALVA NOE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;discusses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Out of Our Heads: &lt;br /&gt;Why You Are Not Your Brain, &lt;br /&gt;and Other Lessons from &lt;br /&gt;the Biology of Consciousness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome Berkeley philosopher ALVA NOE for a discussion of his newest book, in which he re-examines the problem of consciousness and proposes a startling solution: Do away with the two hundred-year-old paradigm that places consciousness within the confines of the brain.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noë is one of a new breed—part philosopher, part cognitive scientist, part neuroscientist—who are radically altering the study of consciousness by asking difficult questions and pointing out obvious flaws in the current science. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“As a neurologist, confronted every day by questions of mind, self, consciousness, and their basis, I find Alva Noë’s concepts—that consciousness is an organismic and not just a cerebral quality, that it is embodied in actions and not just isolated bits of brain—both astounding and convincing. Out of Our Heads is a book that should be read by everyone who thinks about thinking.” —Oliver Sacks, Professor of Neurology and Psychiatry, Columbia University Medical Center &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“A provocative and insightful book that will force experts and students alike to reconsider their grasp of current orthodoxy. Out of Our Heads is a vivid, clear, and very knowledgeable critique of some of the main ideas in cognitive science, and those of us who disagree with some of its main conclusions have our work cut out for us.” —Daniel C. Dennett, Professor of Philosophy, Tufts University&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296256057000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240252852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Noe on the Biology of Consciousness</name><id>10227193</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240614000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/10227193/</event_url></item>