<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>HOLIDAY INN SELECT WOBURN</address_2><address_1>15 Middlesex Canal Park </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.497452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-897-4000</phone><name>Scoreboard Sports Bar and Grill </name><city>Woburn</city><id>1173954</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.158722</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of my favorite groups, Wildfire, is playing at TP's Scoreboard, in Woburn (same plaza as the Holiday Inn select?) (tps' website is www.tpsscoreboard.com).  It's right off the highway and only about a 40 minute ride for me, from the Windham/Pelham line (carpool available from my house for at least 3 in my car), and I just love this place, and &amp;quot;It's my Birthday, and I'll do what I want to, do what I want to, sure hope you come...and have a good time too&amp;quot;  Isn't that a song? ;) lol &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TP's is VERY accommodating to our meetup group, it's spacious with a huge sports bar, plus a big dining area, and a good size dance floor.  We can even reserve tables.  Come early (7pmish) for dinner and please indicate so. PLEASE put in your reply if you will have dinner with us at 7pm. My friend Chuck will be sending me a menu they put together for us which will range, including tip, up to $15 for dinner. Will update later.  we can &amp;quot;pay as we go&amp;quot; for drinks.  I just love this place!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The band probably doesn't start until 9ish, if you're just coming to dance.  But remember introductions stop, when the band starts, so look for me on the dance floor :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As your illustrious hostess, in lieu of presents...I'll collect $1 from everyone, as I'd just love a free meal on my birthday night (we'll call it annual dues ;)  I was so honored last year, by your attendance, presents, and showing of love, on my birthday, words cannot express, but no presents needed this year, I'm doing this for your PRESENCE, not your PRESENTS.  As the artist Prince, once sang...&amp;quot;you don't have to be cool to rule my world...I just want your extra time and your &amp;quot;KISS&amp;quot;, lol. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've got to admit, we've had some great times this past year...and we'll continue to &amp;quot;party hearty&amp;quot; in the year 2011.  Sure, I've been out of commission these past months...BUT I'M BACK!!!!  &lt;br /&gt;thank you again, to all my asst. organizers this past year, for keeping my meetup calendar full, and esp. in the &amp;quot;active&amp;quot; stage during my &amp;quot;sabatical&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;And a special thanks to those of you, who have used my REALTOR services, and helped keep my head above water, in these economically challenging times.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;hope to celebrate my birthday, with all of you, who I've come to love, and enjoy these great times with!  &lt;br /&gt;to my BEST friends, &lt;br /&gt;suz&lt;br /&gt;ps...if you're a maybe, then reply &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and put in your reply that you're a &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot;, since meetup has eliminated the &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; feature.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetup signs on table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295111831000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293722683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Susan's Birthday choice!!</name><id>15858729</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295049600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15858729/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/d/b/global_20507083.jpeg</photo_url></item>