<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 York Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.330002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203.624.TOAD</phone><name>Toad's Place</name><city>New Haven</city><id>119483</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.940002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Some of us are going to catch the show at Toads tonight. Tix are $30, but the performer is supposed to be some post Hendrix era guitar hero legend guy from the 70s. If you don't like it, Will has offered to personally refund your ticket [1]. Doors open at 7:30, show starts at 8:30. We'll probably show around 8:00-8:15ish. See you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;[1] - Except for not really.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.toadsplace.com/wp/shows/1365" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.toadsplace...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROBIN TROWER &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robin Leonard Trower (born 9 March 1945, Catford, South East London, England) is an English rock guitarist who achieved success with Procol Harum during the 1960s, and then again as the leader of his own power trio. Perhaps Trower's most famous album is Bridge of Sighs (1974). This album, along with his first and third solo albums, was produced by his former Procol Harum bandmate, organist Matthew Fisher. Despite differences, Trower's early power trio work was noted for Hendrixesque influences. In the early 1980s, Trower teamed up with former Cream bassist Jack Bruce and his previous drummers Lordan and Isidore, for two albums, BLT (Bruce, Lordan, Trower) and Truce (Trower, Bruce, Isidore).Trower's album, Living Out of Time (2003), features the return of veteran bandmates Dave Bronze on bass, vocalist Davey Pattison (formerly with Ronnie Montrose's band Gamma) and Pete Thompson on drums - the same lineup as the mid 1980s albums Passion and Take What You Need .With the same bandmates Trower gave a concert on his 60th birthday in Bonn, Germany. The concert was recorded by the German television channel WDR. It was then released on DVD and subsequently on CD throughout Europe and later the US under the title Living Out Of Time: Live. In 2007 Robin released a third recording with Jack Bruce, Seven Moons, featuring Gary Husband on drums.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253574031000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253161870000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Robin Trower - Rock show at Toad's</name><id>11394280</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253232000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/11394280/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>