<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Cynthia, a member from the Night Life Group is having a BBQ on Saturday.  She is leaving Boston but wanted to share her send off celebration with the rest of the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the details from Cynthia:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vegetarian BBQ Extravaganza (meat friendly!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address: Hancock Street (Porter Square) Cambridge, near subway&lt;br /&gt;Date:  August 16th, 2008, 5:00 pm to midnight  &lt;br /&gt;Cost:  Please bring $5-$10 for food/drinks if you are not bringing anything&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We [Jimmie and I] are going to have bring-your-own -everything *vegetarian* BBQ on Saturday, August 16th at 5pm. In the spirit of tolerance, those who think it's not a BBQ without meat will be allowed to bring their own meat and cook it themselves on the small grill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A RSVP is requested ASAP, and guests are welcome, but make sure you get back to me with numbers. (We are estimating about 30-40 people throughout the evening). The grill will fire up at 5PM, so food will start being done by 6ish. If you need to use the kitchen, I would suggest to show up before 5, as it will fill up quickly. If you will be picking up food on your way here, just bring whatever you'd like to eat or drink. If you want to be helpful, give us a call and we'll tell you if we need anything (or if we already have enough of something). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be providing drinks (soda, diet soda, water, juice; beer and alcohol until it runs out). We aren't going to bother with organizing who brings what, so if you plan to arrive before 5:30, please bring $10 worth of food (preferably veggie) for the grill and/or a side dish. If you arrive after 5:30, please bring $10 worth of dessert or alcohol (beer, wine, liquor - we already have mixers). We are also going to have a $2 collection for supplies and cleaning up (anything left we'll donate to CS).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~Cynthia and Jimmie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Message from Jimmie, the grill-cook:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unlike the last major grill event, I am going to only worry myself with manning the vegetarian grill. If you think you NEED meat on the grill, then you need to come and get schooled and find out what you are missing, and why you won't even miss it. If you think you are going to be eating crappy fake hot-dogs and vegeburgers, you are also wrong (though I'm sure some will make an appearance). If you have been to one of my grilling events in the past, you fully understand the feats of grilling prowess that I am going to unleash upon our guests. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What should you bring? Anything that's a vegetable, or anything that's vegetarian. You bring it, I'll grill it. Fruit, pizza, fake meats, whatever it is, I can cook it on the grill. Seriously, give me a challenge! You can make something, or you can prepare things at my place. We have a fully stocked kitchen, so if you bring something, you will have all the tools and spices you need. Also, beer is greatly appreciated. We are minutes from Porter Square, so you don't even need to drag anything through the T that you don't want. There is both a large grocery store and good liquor store right in the Porter Square shopping center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  The exact address and our phone numbers will be sent to those who RSVP ASAP to the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219114071000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218603104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cynthia's BBQ in Porter Square this Saturday, Aug 16, 5pm</name><id>8533871</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218920400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/8533871/</event_url></item>