<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>27 Temple St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06513</zip><lat>41.303829</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kudeta</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1067402</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928955</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You are cordially invited to the 2nd Annual Libra Extravaganza hosted by &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Jason V. Watts  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; My Birthday Celebration &amp;amp; UPN Networking Event will be held&lt;br /&gt;at Kudeta - Asian Fusion Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;27 Temple St. Downtown New Haven,CT. 06513 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Friday September 25th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Admission: This is a FREE event &lt;a href="http://ctupn.com/birthday2009" target="_blank"&gt;w/RSVP&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dress: Fashionable &amp;amp; Classy Attire  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Time: 7pm-10pm UPN &amp;quot; Meet &amp;amp; Greet&amp;quot; - Cocktails, Appetizers, Social Networking, Business Card Exchange &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Special Invited Guest Speaker - 9pm&lt;br /&gt;Corey J. Brinson Esq.- The Youngest &amp;amp; 1st African American Candidate for Secretary of the State in Connecticut. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;         10pm-2am Enjoy DJ Dooley-O in the Soul Lounge&lt;br /&gt;w/ R&amp;amp;B,Soul,Jazz,Old School, &amp;amp; more.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As summer comes to an end, please join The UPN &amp;amp; BlackinCT.com Family at this fabulous venue as we enter into the fall in style. Register Here as this will ensure your name on the guestlist for FREE admission. You can invite your co-workers, family &amp;amp; friends, as this is a FREE event. Don't wait to RSVP, guestlist closes on September 23rd. This will be an event that you do not want to miss. Special guest will be in attendance from all over Connecticut and New England. Come early to experience social &amp;amp; business networking at it's best with the return of The Authentic UPN &amp;quot;Meet &amp;amp; Greet &amp;quot;. If you are a business owner or entreprenuer &lt;a href="http://www.ctupn.com/birthday2009" target="_blank"&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt; to enter a special drawing, you do not want to miss this opportunity to meet Urban Professionals from all over Connecticut, Massachussetts, Rhode Island, and New York. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the night All Libras will receive a complimentary gift&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Invited Guest from the following companies &amp;amp; organizations :&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;AT&amp;amp;T, The Urban Professionals Network, Community Network of AT&amp;amp;T, CT State Workers, New Haven Firebirds, NAACP, Urban League, The Law Office of Attorney Ed Farrow, Organix Soul, 88.7 FM The New Gospel Exchange, Trump Tight Ent., Inner City News, Ficklin Media Group, Southern CT Black Chamber of Commerce, Yale Repertory Theatre, Uzima Wellness, Remember The Lilies, The Blue Pearl, Liedle's, Matt Jones Foundation, Blue Print the Magazine, T.C. Brantley Ministries, Tri-State Realty, Aetna, Travelers, DreamGrlz, Ethnic Online, MP &amp;amp; Associates, Entourage Events,Trinity on Main Performing Arts Theatre, Twentity.com, Poetz Realm, ESPN, Young Studios, One Self Magazine, Verizon, Comcast, Local Fraternities &amp;amp; Sororities, Southern CT Black Nurses, Cigna, Mass Mutual, New York Life, ADT, LAS Productions, The Hartford, UBS, Sikorsky, Pfizer, BlackinCT.com, and much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing you at my Birthday Celebration!&lt;br /&gt;Jason V. Watts&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason V. Watts</member_name><member_id>3552331</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256243336000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Black Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>blackbiz-256</urlname><id>691497</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Black Professionals Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253130999000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>End of Summer Statewide Meetup hosted by Jason V. Watts</name><id>11389858</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253919600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/blackbiz-256/events/11389858/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/2/5/global_10744645.jpeg</photo_url></item>