<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 W Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.341803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-268-5748</phone><name>Mul's Diner</name><city>South Boston</city><id>1056249</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055519</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Suggested Cap on Attendance: 8 people plus Amy Morganti (Organizer)&lt;br /&gt;Photo Field Trip:  “Southie” by South End&lt;br /&gt;Diner Breakfast and SoWa Open Market Trip&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, October 18th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;(weather permitting-I'll post on the meet-up site by 8a.m. on the event day if it is canceled due to rain)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00a.m. to 2:30p.m.&lt;br /&gt;==================&lt;br /&gt;10:00-11:30a.m. Meet us there by 10a.m. and we'll get a table together.  They don't take reservations :)  This is a great place to see the locals and enjoy a 'greasy spoon' breakfast in Southie.  Free parking available diagonally across the street at Amrhein's, or along West Broadway; bring cash (no credit cards accepted) to cover what you'd like to eat. ($10-$15 would be fine) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:45a.m. to 2:30p.m. Meet at the free parking lot for the SoWa Open Market, then we'll proceed over to the market.  I'll be driving a black Toyota RAV4 with FM53 on the license plate.  We'll meet at my car by 11:45a.m. and walk to the adjacent market at noon.&lt;br /&gt;======================= &lt;br /&gt;If coming to breakfast: &lt;br /&gt;Mul's Diner, 75 W Broadway, South Boston, MA 02127-1015;(617) 268-5748&amp;#8206;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If meeting up with us at the SoWa Market:  &lt;br /&gt;Check out this link to see what the market is all about:  &lt;a href="http://www.sowaopenmarket.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sowaopenma...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking-hang a sharp left at 500 Harrison Avenue, Boston, MA 02118; Parking lot is about 1 block down that no-name side street, on the right.  Marked with a sign.  Open Market General info Line:  (800) 403-8305&lt;br /&gt;Market is at 540 Harrison Avenue- you cannot miss it!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I used to live in Dorchester and spent many Sunday mornings at THE local diner for ‘Southie’ (South Boston) residents:  Mul’s Diner.  I’d love to introduce you to Mul’s, and enjoy a grilled, homemade muffin or a full-on breakfast, before heading over to the SoWa (South of Washington Street) Open Market to take photos.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I recently visited the Open Market in Boston’s South End and was impressed by all the incredibly rich photo opportunities that exist there.  From the antiques mart located inside the ‘shell’ of an impressive brick façade, to the dozens of vendor tents set up to sell hand-crafted artwork, clothing, jewelry, farm-stand produce, baked goods and a variety of other one-of-a-kind items.  I’d love to bring a group of photographers with me to one of the last open markets of the year and take photos of the wares, the browsers, the vendors, the area and post them up on our Worcester Photography Flickr site.  If you'd like to share your photos with the vendors in the market. Do so on Flickr so they would be able to see and download the photos and use any images that they would like—with proper photo credit, of course! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The open market organizer, Mr. Chris Mascio, is suggesting that we take photos from 12noon - 2:00p.m., to capture the place at it's shopping peak.........but you are also welcome to browse, linger and enjoy yourself!  Bring your reusable shopping bags (so you can squirrel away the treasures you find!) and enjoy the day in Boston.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the diner- Amy's photo is shown here.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256047564000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252067724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Diner Breakfast and SoWa Open Market Photo Field Trip</name><id>11288256</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255874400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/11288256/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/global_10536331.jpeg</photo_url></item>