<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok its time to get walking on a good day and watching the sunset atop Case Mountain and before the sunset we can share a glass of wine, grape juice, or whatever you want to bring to drink or eat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Im bringing some things..(1 bottle of white Zinfindel, some snack stuff) others can bring other things, it is supposed to be a social fun time on the way up at the top as the sun sets and a reward for the walk up..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a small bench area up there to put things on...&lt;br /&gt;And that will be mostly by the main dirt road to the top..if we have time then maybe a bit of exploring up there too..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford: &lt;br /&gt;* Take I-84 E to I-384 &lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 4 off of I-384 (Highland St.) &lt;br /&gt;* From the end of the Exit ramp, right onto Spring St. &lt;br /&gt;* Go about 0.2 mile and make a sharp left and you'll see a small parking lot at the bottom of the hill on your left right after the narrow bridge.&lt;br /&gt;As always look at a map just in case you are comming from a different way and to get a visual look of other roads in the area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177538668000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176915674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset/Wine and Cheeze Social at Case Mountain Summit</name><id>5683438</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177365600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5683438/</event_url></item>