<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Join Us!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join your friends and neighbors for the 15th Annual South End Garden Tour on Saturday, June 21, 2008. This year's rain-or-shine, self-guided tour will kick off at the South End Branch of the Boston Public Library at 685 Tremont Street at 10 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour will feature many beautiful, diverse gardens in the South End - from pocket-sized patio spaces to rooftop terraces to neighborhood parks and community gardens.  All of the gardens show the creativity of the owners and gardeners, and the joy they receive from developing and caring for a city garden. The tour, a major neighborhood event, attracts garden lovers from all over the city as well as the suburbs, who are often surprised and amazed to find such creative use of outdoor urban space. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Gardens Every Year&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the biggest attractions of the South End Garden Tour is its yearly variety of gardens. Because the South End encompasses such a large area, the tour visits a different area of the neighborhood every year. The tour revisits the same portion only every 4 to 5 years. Within that cycle, the gardens have changed dramatically. It's never the same tour twice!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2008 South End Garden Tour will feature private and open space gardens within the following area:&lt;br /&gt;Tremont St. --&amp;gt; West Canton St. --&amp;gt; Southwest Corridor --&amp;gt; West Newton St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the &lt;a href="http://southendgardentour.org/map.html" target="_blank"&gt;TOUR MAP&lt;/a&gt; or the Official web page at: &lt;a href="http://southendgardentour.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://southendgarden...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214230088000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonCreative</urlname><id>919281</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Creative People</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212244470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South End garden tour</name><id>8048368</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214056800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonCreative/events/8048368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/f/global_2903839.jpeg</photo_url></item>