<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever have dreams of sex or sexual attraction? What do sexual dreams mean? Are they literally about our sexual desires or are they symbolic? How can we learn from them? How do we feel about them? We will be exploring the territory of sex dreams at our next Meetup. This is an opportunity to share and learn from sex dreams in a confidential and supportive group. We will be offering interpretation for those who want it. There is no requirement to share your dreams if you don't want. Participation is always voluntary. So come join us if you desire, for a fascinating meeting on a hot topic. Not to be missed! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This meeting will be facilitated by Deerheart. Deerheart is a spiritual guide, visionary artist, and tantric shaman. People are drawn to him to share their life stories, life challenges, and dreams. He provides gentle guidance, understanding, and intuitive healing love energy. His heart of compassion looks upon all with unconditional love. An experienced explorer of the dream realms for for over 25 years, he has researched and studied many books and studied under many teachers. For more information about him, visit his website, &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com"&gt;Visionary Dream Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot  afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the  group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people.  RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to  allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307127387000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303778784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sexual Dreams</name><id>17432094</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305673200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/17432094/</event_url></item>