<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>59 Jfk St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.491.9851</phone><name>Redline</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>692091</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120694</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the folks at Science in the News:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;How does the wiring in our brains lead to complex behaviors, such as reading this page? Our guest this week for Science by the Pint is Professor Florian Engert, who studies the neural circuits that lead to behavior in zebrafish (a small &amp;quot;model organism&amp;quot; commonly studied in the lab).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Buy 1 get 1 free appetizers and a door prize courtesy of our sponsor, Narragansett Beer!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture starts at 7:00 pm at Redlines in Harvard Square. Let's grab dinner at 6:15 pm. T.J. will be making reservations under &amp;quot;T.J. Maher&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Nerd Fun Meetup&amp;quot;, and needs a mostly accurate count probably by Monday so he has made this event YES/ NO. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, wish short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and will be placing red MEETUP table tents on the tables he has reserved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science by the Pint:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Science by the Pint' is SITN's [Science in the News] rendition of a nationwide project called 'Science Cafes', a movement to provide more informal discussions between scientists and non-scientists on relevant scientific and social issues. Rather than the usual seminar format we provide during our fall lecture series, Science by the Pint will feature one or more leading researchers who give no more than a 5 minute, conversation stirring, introduction to their work. The rest is up to you! After the short introduction, you may ask our researchers questions, bring up discussion points and see where it all leads&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Gee... I wonder which tables most of the questions will be coming from?  ;)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science in the News:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We are a graduate student public service organization at Harvard University. Our mission is to delve into the science behind the media reports we hear everyday and to bring that information to you so you can better distinguish scientific fact from pure speculation and put the knowledge to use in your daily life. We accomplish our mission through the following avenues:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Evening seminars&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Each fall, Science in the News hosts a free, 9-week evening seminar series for the public aimed at explaining and discussing today's hottest scientific topics without hype, exaggeration, or over-simplification. The program is run entirely by graduate students from the Harvard community. Each seminar consists of three individual 30-45 minute interactive presentations on a single topic; an introduction to the background you need to understand the topic, a presentation about recent research or innovations, and a discussion of the ethical or societal ramifications of this research. Different graduate students present each section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A major benefit of our seminar series is the accessibility of the speakers: we take as much time as needed to discuss and answer your questions! Often, the audience plays as large a role in the seminar as the speakers themselves&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florian Engert’s Zebra Fish School :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Harvard University, Molecular and Cellular Biology, News and Events&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://golgi.harvard.edu/NewsEvents/News/Engert2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://golgi.harvard....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tadpoles don’t behave, but zebra fish do, and that’s why newly promoted Associate Professor Florian Engert is switching the focus of his neuroscience experiments to fish. In the &amp;quot;wild,&amp;quot; the small, silvery zebra fish avoid large, dark looming objects that might be predators and they hunt tiny moving objects that might be food. They can also learn to avoid completely neutral visual cues, such as a geometrical pattern on the bottom of their tank, should Engert surprise them with a mild electric shock when they swim over it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The point of this fish obedience school is to link behavior to learning, and learning to synaptic plasticity, which refers to the changes in the structural connections among neurons. It’s generally believed that strengthening those connections is the underlying basis of learning and memory, and that a &amp;quot;lesson&amp;quot;—whether associating a shock with the color red or learning the ABCs—causes the neurons to fire in such a way that strengthens synapses. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Researchers study the synaptic strength by measuring the electrical impulses that one neuron receives when another one is stimulated. Typically, they use microelectrodes inserted directly into neurons to record those impulses. But inserting the electrodes inside the neuron is technically difficult in intact and awake animals. And stimuli delivered through these electrodes do not necessarily simulate the physiologically relevant neuronal activity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Just as the big push in neuroscience is to study the human brain noninvasively with fMRI brain scans, Engert also wants to spare his fish the invasive electrode in the brain. To that end, he has developed light-based technologies that he credits to his early background in physics as an undergraduate at the Ludwig-Maximilians University of Munich, Germany. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'The big questions in modern biology can often be narrowed down to the underlying principles of physics,' Engert explains. 'In many cases, we’re no longer going out into the field to observe organisms. We’re creating concise models of the systems we want to understand, and we probe these models with specifically designed experiments. That requires the quantitative and modeling skills of physics.' &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Engert began applying the principles and skill of physics while investigating the role of synaptic plasticity in memory during his PhD studies with Tobias Bonhoeffer at the Max Plank Institute in Munich. Using 1/2-millimeter-thick slices of the rat’s hippocampus, the brain region where new memories form, he used electrodes to measure the connections between two individual neurons. 'We could record from one and stimulate another, and then do experiments to study the changes in their synaptic strength,' he recalls. &amp;quot; [ &lt;b&gt;A LOT MORE:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://golgi.harvard.edu/NewsEvents/News/Engert2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://golgi.harvard....&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Dr. Florian Engert's BioLab:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hms.harvard.edu/dms/neuroscience/fac/engert.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hms.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our lab's interest lies in activity-dependent synaptic plasticity with respect to its relevance for learning and memory as well as the underlying physiological and molecular mechanisms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;On order to bridge the gap from changes in cellular connectivity to behavioral consequences, and furthermore, to get a better grip on the molecular mechanisms involved, we decided to shift our attention from brain slices in rat to the zebrafish. The obvious advantage being that this is one of the most promising models for forward genetic screens, thus connecting mutations on the molecular level with behavioral or morphological defects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The aim of our work will be to use patch-clamp recordings and 2-photon imaging in in vivo preparations of tadpole and zebrafish as model systems to examine the development and activity dependent plasticity of retinotectal connections&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You have to go to the Engert Lab Website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mcb.harvard.edu/Engert/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mcb.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look on the picture on the first page. Hover your cursor on the picture. Take it off the picture. Hover your cursor on the picture. The fun never ends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Research&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.mcb.harvard.edu/Engert/research.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mcb.harvar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The general goal of the laboratory is the comprehensive identification and examination of neural circuits controlling behavior using the larval zebrafish as a model system. To that end, we have established and quantified a series of visually induced behaviors and analyzed the individual resulting motor components. Using these assays in combination with various calcium indicators and two-photon microscopy we have monitored neuronal activity throughout the fish brain in an awake and intact preparation. An extended goal is the study of how changes or variations in the behavior are reflected in changes in the underlying neuronal activity. To that end, we have developed several quantitative learning assays and tools for in vivo monitoring of neural activity in freely swimming larvae&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Redlines:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.redlinecambridge.com/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redlinecam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Located in the heart of Harvard Square, Redline caters to a hip cross-section of the city with its casually refined menu, buzzing bar scene and late night entertainment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Redline's 'approachably stylish' cuisine is as diverse as the clientele it draws, boasting creative entrees as well as a variety of apps and sandwiches perfect for sharing, makes Redline a great choice for a social gathering or a casual dinner for two&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Every Monday evening, Redline has stump trivia at 8:00 pm. On Social Fun, Amy Hughes has been getting together people every Monday since June for what has to be the longest running continuous weekly event in the Boston area meetups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Redlines menu&lt;/b&gt; (in Adobe Acrobat PDF Format): &lt;a href="http://www.redlinecambridge.com/menu/menuContent.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redlinecam...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268349467000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267809075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Florian Engert, Neural Circuits in the Brain @ Science By The Pint, Redlines</name><id>12792962</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268176500000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12792962/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/f/global_13461167.jpeg</photo_url></item>