<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have chosen SUNDAY as the most appropriate day for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 61. . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Back up put in location if not enough water flow is start at BARTS..we decide at Strawberry's Park)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anticipate this trip  taking the entire afternoon, bring extra water , a snack, and proper clothes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Following is the up stream water flow data feeding to the dam -- and if the dam is releasing, it can relate to the level at Strawberry Park being adequate enough for a good run downstream if above 1.75 foot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;120 day level chart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://waterdata.usgs.gov/ct/nwis/uv?cb_00060=on&amp;amp;cb_00065=on&amp;amp;format=gif_default&amp;amp;period=120&amp;amp;site_no=01189995" target="_blank"&gt;http://waterdata.usgs...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5 day level chart&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://waterdata.usgs.gov/ct/nwis/uv?cb_00060=on&amp;amp;cb_00065=on&amp;amp;format=gif_default&amp;amp;period=5&amp;amp;site_no=01189995" target="_blank"&gt;http://waterdata.usgs...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;__________________________________________________________________-----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Strawberry's Park is our meeting spot, and we have to move cars to the take out spot for a one way trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone unloads here, THEN Everyone drives to THE WINDSOR BOAT RAMP on East Barber st Windsor, then a few drive us back to Strawberry's park,  (yes some can stop at windsor boat ramp first..etc, and waite for us, but it will be really difficult to coordinate things this way unless its a small group).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barts is the snack and rest stop at apx the half way point of the trip if we start a Strawberry's Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once the paddling event ends back at The WINDSOR BOAT RAMP, some drive the people that drove us back to Strawberry so they can get their cars, its simple and it works, no complaining now !!, then the BUFF A is in Wethersfield at the Far East Chineeze food place for the few that are interested in going, the cost is about 7 bucks. Best deal in any town.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;################################################################&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok getting to Strawberry Park, *the put in and meeting place*.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS use # 50 River Street Windsor  to get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford: &lt;br /&gt;take I 91 North to exit # 38,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is the exit for rte 75. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right off of the exit and go North on rte 75 toward Bradley Airport Direction, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;go 2.25 miles, cross the river bridge and the first right is RIVER STREET, &lt;br /&gt;go apx 1,000 feet and the Park entrance is on the right..&lt;br /&gt;go into the drive way around the little circle, we will be unloading in the grass a bit further into the park nearer the river..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ending Spot:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting from Strawberry Park to the  Windsor Boat Ramp, (Use # 300 East Barber Street Windsor to get you close enough)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Leave Strawberry Park, take a left onto River Street, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a left onto rte 75, head toward I - 91, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get onto 91 South .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit # 35  for rte 218 (Putnam Hwy)  at end of exit take a left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go apx .5 mile to Windsor Ave  then take a Right towards Hartford,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go apx .25 mile --- Then  take a left onto East Barber St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Got to end to the boat ramp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember and PRINT these directions...ya might get lost if you don't print em..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*******************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Paddle &amp;amp; Paddle Leash, Life Jacket with whistle is included with any of my yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doughnation of  $ 20.00,  bucks for my kayaks reserved for this particular event.&lt;br /&gt;Its way less than what sport shops charge and the yaks &amp;amp; Paddles are top quality delivered and picked up at the site etc..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please make sure you are familiar with the yak you choose and can fit in them since i don't have any &amp;quot;Wide Butt&amp;quot; (greater than 17&amp;quot;~18&amp;quot; butts) yaks anymore.&lt;br /&gt;Don't laugh, its serious, some will not fit in a yak thats too small (ie the Greenlander Pro--maximum butt and hips width of 12 inches limit) of an opening and i will feel sad you cant go..etc..the other option is to maybe trade with someone, etc, if you need to.&lt;br /&gt;This has worked in the past very well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please if using my yaks avoid stepping on the floor of them to get in and out and NEVER DRIVE UP ON SHORE WITH THEM LIKE YOU ARE GOING TO A DRIVE IN MOVIE. (Kate has to repair all the damage you make to the fiberglass and Gel coatings by doing this.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only Novices in short wide cheap plastic boats do that kind of thing because they simply don't know any better or don't care.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;READ THE INFO ON THE FOLLOWING LINK: I will also show you the correct way &amp;amp; you will look like a intelligent seasoned pro to impress the others who don't know how. Then you may laugh at the ones that fall in on entry - exit who don't know how.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ehow.com/how_5660364_enter-kayak.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ehow.com/h...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hint: Always enter- exit any kayak while being parallel and close to shore.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Please review the links below for the equipment specifications to be at least familiar with which boat or equipment you would be best suited for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheap LIfe Jackets with a whistle is all i have for most of you since a GOOD QUALITY LIFE JACKET should be chosen for your particular body shapes , paddling  style, and  fit adjusted, if you have your own please bring it.&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;I only have one &amp;quot;GOOD&amp;quot; life jacket for someone that can fit in it.&lt;br /&gt;Its a Medium Kokatat* Ladies MsFit  Tour: (this is also purchased by guys since it has a great fit and versatility) Its really too small for me, but i like the way it works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/product/751058" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/pr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;All my yaks come with the &amp;quot;CHEAP&amp;quot; Werner Carbon Kalliste Paddles because they are Hollow and light (my recommended brand and type). Different lengths (220-230) and types (strait, or ergonomic bent, small and normal shaft dia's.) of the same version are in the bucket.&lt;br /&gt;You choose your preference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wernerpaddles.com/paddles/touring/performance_core/kalliste/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wernerpadd...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(No ya cant use these paddles for paddle float entry practice. i have some  SOLID metal ones for that.)&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also for comfort is my favourite &amp;quot;Yak Pad's&amp;quot; optional accessory to all yaks on trips that we are actually going somewhere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yakpads.com/11-paddle-saddle-with-high-backrest.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yakpads.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOW DECK BAGS are now placed on kayaks to hold water , accessories and other items needed  for quick and easy access:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kayakproshop.com/SL_deckbag.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kayakprosh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;Eddyline Wind Dancer 18', Red, Rudder Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;For almost any sized paddler apx (100 to 240 lbs) with beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epinions.com/otdr_Kayaking_Touring_Sea-Eddyline-Wind_Dancer" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.epinions.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;highly stable (initial &amp;amp; secondary) comfortable Sea kayak, 18'=&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR EMILY   ---&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Red, Skeg Equipped.&lt;br /&gt;Medium sized paddler (150-200 lbs) with Intermediate to Advanced skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is not a beginners boat but in calm conditions will be a good skills learning boat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/retail/boats/ndk/Greenlander-Pro.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fast Greenland style Sea kayak, moderated stability, 18'= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--- if you are ready for it..---  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; --Maybe AVAILABLE to a experienced sea paddler--&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR MARY--.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Advanced Composite  (Un Modified), Red and White, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the medium size cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (43 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;-----  ----&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;---RESERVED FOR CYNTHIA ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Composite Ultra Light Version (Very Thin Fiberglass and floor reinforced), Yellow, Skeg Version 15.25'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the lightest of the Eliza Series and also with the smallest cocpit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.belhavencanoe.com/Necky/Eliza%20Comp/Elizacomp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.belhavenca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type Light weight (40 LB) Ladies Kayak, 15'3.0&amp;quot;= &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;--------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR HOPE--&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Necky Eliza Plastic, Fire Color, Rudder Equipped 15.3'.&lt;br /&gt;Small to Medium sized paddler (100 - 175 lbs) with Beginner and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;This is the heaviest model and largest cockpit of the Eliza series.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neckykayaks.com/kayaks/touring/eliza_polymer.shtml" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.neckykayak...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;stable and predictable Transitional type moderate weight (50 LB) ladies kayak, 15'3.5&amp;quot;= &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; ----RESERVED FOR JOHN CZ.   ----&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;####&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cedar Strip Night Heron by Guillemot Kayaks 18'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenland Paddle available also if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Medium Sized Paddler (apx 150 - 220 Lbs)  with NOVICE/INTERMEDIATE and up skills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.guillemot-kayaks.com/guillemot/node/51/detail" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.guillemot-...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overall a stable and predictable Sea  kayak with Greenland style hull (50 lbs),  18' =&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;----------&lt;b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;----RESERVED FOR  CHERI'S GUEST --&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last yak is Kims, its for sale and i have it &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;RESERVED FOR  ALEX&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;OF COURSE ON THE DAY OF THE EVENT SOME OF YOU CAN SWITCH AROUND TO DIFFERENT YAKS AND EQUIPMENT..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; RIGHT NOW IM MOSTLY MAKING SURE I HAVE ENOUGH FOR THOSE THAT ASKED AND THE AMOUNT I CAN safely CARRY..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buff -A location :&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/place?hl=en&amp;amp;expIds=17259,17291,22881,26637,27023&amp;amp;sugexp=ldymls&amp;amp;xhr=t&amp;amp;cp=16&amp;amp;um=1&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;q=far+east+buffet+wethersfield+ct&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=far+east+buffet&amp;amp;hnear=Wethersfield,+CT&amp;amp;cid=10327470725636912216" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or just follow me from Windsor Boat Ramp if you are interested...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there.&lt;br /&gt;AL-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear my Bright Orange Hunting Hat near the put in spot and while paddling.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289056172000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286193373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*KAYAKING* from STRAWBERRY'S PARK TO Windsor Boat Ramp, BUFF A in Wethersfield.</name><id>14992582</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287331200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14992582/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/1/global_13936689.jpeg</photo_url></item>