<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 S. Commercial Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.985446</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-296-0706</phone><name>Commercial Street Fishery</name><city>Manchester</city><id>887238</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467427</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Note:  This event requires a reservation and it may or may not require a deposit by the organizer so all cancellations within 48 hours of the event requires a reason.  Please do not sign up unless you are sure that you can make it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The membership has voted! The March Restaurant of the month is Commercial Street Fishery.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CSF was formerly the Starfish Grill which closed in early 2006. The new owners/operators include a former partner of Starfish Grill and together they have invested in remodeling the space, bringing it a bit more upscale than its previous incarnation. The interior is warm and inviting, still allowing the historical charm of the old mill building to show through, yet it doesn't feel like your sitting in an &amp;quot;old mill building&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The space is large and open with those cool warehouse high ceilings and that subdued, groovy decor one might find in Pottery Barn, with plush, upholstered booths in faux tan suede, starched gauze wall and ceiling hangings, just a smidgen of art and some simple classy lighting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There’s a bar and a lounge as well, with little tables and a long couch. Cool, yes, but thankfully not over-the-top slick urban.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hip, cool, eclectic, fun are all words heard from people when describing CSF.  Chef Justin Lyonnais loves to take traditional seafood dishes and turn them upside down adding his creative signature to each dish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu is varied and well balanced, designed to appeal to educated diners, who appreciate good food and understand the importance of how a relaxing yet fun ambiance adds to their overall dining experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.csfishery.com/menu.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.csfishery....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.csfishery.com/directions.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.csfishery....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1238543499000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235534203000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Restaurant of the Month</name><id>9818098</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238281200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9818098/</event_url></item>