<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>193 Bay Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01035</zip><lat>42.330079</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hartsbrook School</name><city>Hadley</city><id>1123027</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.564157</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our friend &lt;i&gt;Meagan&lt;/i&gt; is the Stage Manager for Shakespeare's The Tempest being presented by the Hampshire Shakespeare Company. We should support her by checking it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price and Meet Up Location:&lt;/b&gt; Tickets can be purchased at the door and are $16 for adults, $10 for students/military/seniors. Lets meet at the Theater at say 7:15PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Date:&lt;/b&gt; Posting this event for this Friday. If this day does not work for the majority of folks who liked the idea perhaps we can shoot for either Saturday or Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7:30PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: All shows start at 7:30pm and are performed at the Hartsbrook School in Hadley, MA (193 Bay Road). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Play by:&lt;/b&gt; Hampshire Shakespeare Company is an outdoor community theater company - our main stage is behind the Hartsbrook School. If the weather doesn't cooperate, we move the show to an indoor space inside the Hartsbrook School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tempest is a play by William Shakespeare, estimated to have been written in 1610–11,[1] although some researchers have argued for an earlier dating.[2] The play's protagonist, Prospero, the rightful Duke of Milan, has been deprived of his throne by his usurping brother Antonio, aided by Alonso, the King of Naples. Before the play's opening, Prospero and his daughter Miranda  were put into a tiny boat and sent away to a deserted island far from civilization. When Prospero came ashore, he found two inhabitants there: Ariel, a spirit, and Caliban. The witch Sycorax, who had died years before Prospero's arrival, had imprisoned Ariel in a tree. Prospero freed Ariel, who became bound to serve him. For the next twelve years, Prospero practiced his sorcery, ultimately raising a tempest that drives Antonio, Alonso and their entourage ashore to open the action of the play. The entire play takes place on the island, where the native inhabitants, Ariel and Caliban, aid or hinder his work. While listed as a comedy when it was initially published in the First Folio of 1623, many modern editors have since re-labelled the play as one of Shakespeare's late romances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No obvious single source has been found from which Shakespeare may have derived the plot of the play. The play does seem to draw on several then-contemporary accounts of shipwrecks in the New World, as well as the works of Michel de Montaigne and Ovid's Metamorphoses. The play's basic structure reflects that of the then-popular Italian commedia dell'arte. It is one of two Shakespearean plays which follow the neoclassical three unities (the other is The Comedy of Errors). During the 1950s and 1960s, The Tempest attracted much attention from post-colonial critics for its portrayal of Ariel's and Caliban's reactions to foreign control of their island.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It did not attract a significant amount of attention before the closing of the theatres in 1642, and only attained popularity after the Restoration, and then only in adapted versions.[3] In the mid-19th century, theatre productions began to reinstate the original Shakespearean text[4] and, in the 20th century, critics and scholars undertook a significant re-appraisal of the play's value, to the extent that it is now considered to be one of Shakespeare's greatest works.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meagan</member_name><member_id>6521348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280938497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280187045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Play: Shakespeare's The Tempest</name><id>14222040</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280532600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/14222040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/9/global_16741801.jpeg</photo_url></item>