<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Temple St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.304740</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 498-2500</phone><name>Criterion Cinemas</name><city>New Haven</city><id>664405</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.928310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, Criterion Cinema's in New Haven puts on a selection of the SHORT Films nominated for the Oscar Awards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I (A.J.) Plan to go to Tuesday Night's 6:50 showing of the Shorts in the &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Live Action&lt;/span&gt; Category.  &lt;em&gt;Everyone is in charge of getting their own ticket.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will plan to get to the lobby by 6:30 to meet/greet and if anyone wants to chill before hand.  I'll move into the theater at about 6:45. (Unless there appears to be a stampede in which case earlier.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss us in the lobby, &lt;strong&gt;I will keep my phone (315-345-9348) on until they dim the lights, but after that you're on your own.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are SHORT films, not full length features, they're each in the 10-25 minute range. (So 5 of them add up to your normal full length feature time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, I'm seeing the "Live Action" category on this evening, so be sure you get the right one as there is also a set of Animated and Documentaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a Criterion Club Card you can also take advantage of &lt;a href="http://www.bowtiecinemas.com/programs/super-tuesday/"&gt;Super Tuesday&lt;/a&gt; which offers $6 tickets and $5 Tubs of Popcorn!  (You need to sign up for that days ahead of time though if you haven't already.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357"&gt;If people wish to socialize about the films afterwards and it's early enough, we can go next door to Kelly's after.  (Time dependent, it is a work night.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some thing to keep in mind: Everyone's got to start some where, and many great directors have had shorts nominated before they were famous for full length films.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #6e1919"&gt;Parking: Temple Street Garage is directly across the street, and Criterion offers a discount on parking there (I do not know how much).  Alternatively there is a lot of Metered parking on Temple and the surrounding streets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look at Kelly's before hand or wait in the Lobby till 7:05.  If you miss us you can try to call AJ before the lights Dim: 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360727597000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360168279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Criterion Movie: 2013 Oscar Shorts Live Action Category</name><id>103323112</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360711800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/103323112/</event_url></item>