<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let me ask you something...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have you ever gone to a social gathering and met someone you were really interested in, but you didn't know how to let them know?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you have lots of polite conversations that never really move beyond small talk?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have you ever met someone who seemed to have a knack for being outgoing and flirtatious, and you wished you had a little bit of that magic too?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you answered "yes" to any of these questions, then you're going to love this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt;REVEALED: &amp;nbsp;THE "SECRET" LANGUAGE OF FLIRTING
 &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if I told you that there was a "secret" language that men and women use to communicate romantic interest in each other?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And what if I told you that if you knew this language, you'd be able to make the people you're interested in 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;feel attracted to you instantly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; ... but if you didn't know this language (and many people don't), the people you're interested in are likely to "turn off" and move on to someone else... never looking back or giving you a second chance?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look, here's the bottom line. &amp;nbsp;If you tend to have lots of polite conversations that fizzle out and go nowhere, 
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;then this is going to change your life!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why? &amp;nbsp;Because once you understand how flirting 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;really&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; works (and how to use it yourself), you'll find yourself effortlessly attracting the people you desire as if it was the easiest and most natural thing in the world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this unique event, I'm going to pull back the curtain and give you an inside look at what flirting really is, how to recognize it, and how to use it to let someone know that you're interested in them (but do it in a safe, fun, and effective way).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt; HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN: *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Revealed: The "invisible language" being spoken in every flirtatious interaction. &amp;nbsp;This has been hidden from you all your life, but now you'll always be able to spot it, and 
  &lt;em&gt;use it&lt;/em&gt; to attract the people you really want to date.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to instantly tell if someone is flirting with you (and what to do if they are).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A simple technique that compels people to flirt back with you (and automatically makes them more interesting dating you).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to let someone know that you're interested in them without saying it directly (they'll get the message loud and clear when you do 
  &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The #1 mistake that 
  &lt;strong&gt;automatically&amp;nbsp;kills any attraction&lt;/strong&gt; a person has for you. &amp;nbsp;Hint: If you've had someone suddenly "go cold" on you and stop returning calls, you might have done this without realizing it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to flirt with someone using text messages. &amp;nbsp;This works amazingly well whether you're just starting out with someone, or you've been dating them a long time and want to spice things up.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A step-by-step template for asking someone out once they're interested in you. &amp;nbsp;This method works for every single time, and is almost completely rejection proof.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt; PERSONALITY FEEDBACK
 &lt;br /&gt; *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that's just the first part of the seminar! Then we will go into one of the most popular activities that we do in this social skills group... 
&lt;strong&gt;personality feedback!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have an opportunity to participate in small group evaluations of other members, and you'll also get to experience what it's like to receive both positive encouragement and constructive feedback about how you come across to others. This is often the most revealing part of the workshop, because it's so personalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some members became aware of things they were doing for years that were turning people off, and some learned that they come across much better than they realized (which dramatically boosted their confidence in all social situations).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/span&gt; I want you to know that exercise is done very gently, kindly, and in the spirit of personal growth. We are all there to help each other. So if this section makes you a little nervous, don't let it. I promise that you will find this to be one of the most educational and 
&lt;em&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;enjoyable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; parts of the seminar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************
 &lt;br /&gt; HOW TO GET INVOLVED
 &lt;br /&gt; *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Where is it? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line. Please plan on arriving by 3:15pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 3:30 and go until 5:30 (with a break in the middle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;How much? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Cheap. &amp;nbsp;If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and&amp;nbsp;that's assuming there even 
&lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a class that could offer you all this, which there isn't. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No other class offers you this kind of cutting edge information plus the ability to get personality feedback. &amp;nbsp;What if one small change is all it takes to immediately and effortlessly begin attracting high-quality friends and dating prospects into your life? &amp;nbsp;I've seen it happen many times in this group, and it can happen for you too.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;Because I want to help as many people as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to. &amp;nbsp;The cost for this event is only $25, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about it... 
&lt;strong&gt;that's 83 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;What else do you spend 83 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In order to make sure I can personally help as many people as possible, the class is limited to the first 25 people who RSVP. &amp;nbsp;We're going to be moving around and doing lots of fun exercises, so I have to limit the size. &amp;nbsp;There are over 800 people seeing this message, so be&amp;nbsp;sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$25 cash&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot. &amp;nbsp;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warmly,
 &lt;br /&gt; Jason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311651160000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310545914000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flirting 101 - How To Create Instant Attraction + Personality Feedback</name><id>25570561</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311535800000</time><rsvp_limit>38</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/25570561/</event_url></item>