<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5350 E Marriott Drive</address_1><state>AZ</state><zip>85054</zip><lat>33.683479</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>JW Marriott Desert Ranch</name><city>phoenix</city><id>4668802</id><country>us</country><lon>-111.966110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bring in the New Year in Phoenix, AZ at a two day Raw Spirit Festival!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;For the first time, Raw Spirit Participants can bring in the New Year in an exquisite desert paradise just north of Phoenix, Arizona in the most elegant, sweetly-spiritual, healthful, cutting-edge, fun-loving, conscious, abundant, musical, interconnected way imaginable December 30, 2011 to January 1st, 2012 at Arizona's most magnificent 5 star resort, the JW Marriott Desert Ridge. It features 300 Audubon Society-approved acres, lush lawns, mountains views, trails, 4 acres of heated palm-lined swimming pools and rivers, plus a gilded Wildflower Ballroom reserved exclusively for the Raw Spirit New Year's Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/a/b/e/event_76551902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;With a theme of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;"Inspiration, Education, Meditation &amp;amp; Celebration"&lt;/em&gt;, participants can expect to have plenty of fun while learning the latest information in health, eco and spiritual living via dynamic presentations and musical performances, including educational sessions by an eclectic array of doctors who are also research authors on natural health. Plus, raw vegan chefs will offer organic raw vegan demos &amp;amp; tastings, amidst a plethora of playshops on yoga, dancing, meditation, singing and more. Meanwhile, attendees can sample an assortment of organic raw vegan dishes and shop at vendor booths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;According to festival founder Happy Oasis, "&lt;em&gt;This is much more than a vibrant vegan festival. Our vision is to integrate healthy living, eco-sustainable solutions, music, art, and world peace while creating a community of fun and lovingkindness, because together these comprise a comprehensive strategy for positively addressing current global challenges. We feel that our Raw Spirit Festival belongs to the entire ever-expanding, international community."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/b/2/2/event_76552002.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Billed as "the world's leading, largest and longest-lived raw vegan-eco-peace celebration," the Raw Spirit Festival is a 501c3 educational non profit that offered it's first festival in Sedona, Arizona in May of 2005. The non profit has offered more than 200 celebrations since its inception, most of them entirely free to the public. Raw Spirit organization gives freely to several other non profits and groups in need including Women's Shelters, Department of Veterans Affairs, Native American groups, Big Brothers Big Sisters and more. Raw Spirit welcomes sponsors and donors so that it can continue to serve for many years to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Fri. Dec. 30th - Sun. Jan. 1st weekend celebration price is only $125 until December 1st, and $150 thereafter, or $75, $85 each day. The group hotel rate is $149 per room. To register and for more information, phone &lt;a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #184fae ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;480.363.2731&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;(480) 363-2731&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;(928) 308-2146&lt;/a&gt;. You can email us at &lt;a href="mailto:info@rawspirit.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #184fae ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;info@rawspirit.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Tickets are limited. Pre-registration is recommended. You can Buy Tickets and view the Schedule at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.rawspirit.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #184fae ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;www.RawSpiritFest.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325254596000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322929625000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Eve Raw Spirit Festival in Phoenix, AZ</name><id>43259952</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325250000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/43259952/</event_url></item>