<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Purchase your tickets for the 7:20 pm show today&lt;/strong&gt; at&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/conan-obrien-cant-stop"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/content/conan-obrien-cant-stop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;I'll be arriving at Coolidge Corner around 6:15 pm to meet-and-greet people, and will be getting in line at 6:30 pm for this 7:20 pm show. Doors open probably at 7:00 pm, but by that time, the line&amp;nbsp;will definately wrap&amp;nbsp;down the alley where people wait, and around the block.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;From the Coolidge Corner Website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/conan-obrien-cant-stop"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/content/conan-obrien-cant-stop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Conan O'Brien Can't Stop&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Opens Friday, June 24&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"What do you do when you get your dream job, only to lose it six months later? If you&amp;rsquo;re Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien, you get angry for a while&amp;hellip;and then you go to work. As he is contractually forbidden to be funny on TV, he mounts a live variety show and takes it on the road. The success of the venture is by no means guaranteed; after years of seeing him onscreen for free, will people pay to see him in the flesh?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Anyone who was lucky enough to catch the tour when it hit the Wang Center last fall knows the answer to that question. But the Conan who emerges in this documentary is a surprising one indeed. On stage, we see the familiar public figure: affable, quick witted, self-deprecating, wildly energetic, and intelligent. More revealing are the offstage scenes, which show the entertainer&amp;rsquo;s vulnerable side as he wrestles with the insecurity and exhaustion that a lengthy tour can induce. The flip side of the public&amp;rsquo;s adulation is that they are never satisfied, and the more thinly Conan is stretched, the further his patience is eroded.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"However, off stage or on, Conan&amp;rsquo;s mind is constantly working: he never misses an opportunity to squeeze a laugh from his audience, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a sold-out theater or just a handful of his trusted staff. And Rodman Flender&amp;rsquo;s camera catches it all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"It is impossible to not be inspired by O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s work ethic. He is a dervish, constantly striving to improve his performance. By providing unique insight into this critical transition point, Conan O'Brien Can't Stop reminds us that endings are opportunities for new beginnings. It also is a side-splittingly funny documentary about one of the most hilarious and hard-working people in the industry".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Tickets: The show isn't scheduled yet. I assume it should be soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;T.J. Maher will be arriving at Coolidge Corner around 6:15 pm, and will be getting in line at 6:30 pm for this 7:20 pm show. Doors open at 7:00 pm, but by that time, the line wraps down the alley where people wait, and around the block.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;About the Coolidge Corner Theater:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/about/us"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/about/us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Widely regarded as one of New England&amp;rsquo;s most beloved cultural landmarks, the Coolidge Corner Theatre is one of the nation&amp;rsquo;s most prominent independently operated movie theatres, run by the not-for-profit Coolidge Corner Theatre Foundation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Since 1933, audiences in the greater Boston area have relied on the Coolidge for the best of contemporary art house and independent film. The Coolidge also presents the prestigious annual Coolidge Award; high-definition broadcasts from London's National Theatre and Europe's Grand Operas; Big Screen Classics; Midnite cult films and sing-alongs; weekend kids' variety shows; and sneak previews and discussion of upcoming films as part of Talk Cinema. In 2008, the Coolidge was selected among distinguished arts organizations to be awarded significant funding from the Cultural Facilities Fund, a program administered by MassDevelopment and the Massachusetts Cultural Council. The Coolidge has won numerous awards and recognitions for creative and innovative programming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Location&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"The Coolidge Corner Theatre is fully accessible and is located at 290 Harvard Street in the heart of Coolidge Corner, Brookline, Massachusetts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Admission Prices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Adult: $9.75&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Member: $6.75"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/about/directions-and-parking"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/about/directions-and-parking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Centre Street one block from Harvard Street) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 8:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space. We strongly recommend public transit for events and films you anticipate will be very busy! Additional parking at an hourly rate is available across Beacon and Centre Streets at the Courtyard Marriott Hotel garage on Webster Street.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Public Transportation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"By train: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309403912000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306526259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: "Conan O'Brien Can't Stop" @ Coolidge Corner Theater</name><id>19986271</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1308954600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/19986271/</event_url></item>