<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We live on the northshore and it's not easily accessible by T. There is a bus that runs once an hour from Wonderland Station if you're that intrepid!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a household with birds and a rabbit for those who may have allergies to fur, feathers, aspen shavings, and/or hay dust. The birds will be in a different room but the rabbit will NOT. &amp;nbsp;She probably won't be running around but she WILL be in the living room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is on street parking available and maybe even a fireworks show. Our neighbors up the street usually have a big fireworks display every year on July 4th but that's a Monday, so they may move it to this day, who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to bring a snack to share, that would be much appreciated but not required. &amp;nbsp;We will have some dinner items available. &amp;nbsp;If it's not enough we are close to several restaurants with reasonably priced food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;End time for this is Sunday, 11:30 pm&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Unfortunately, Josh and Kieran function poorly without sleep so this will not be an all nighter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Address will be emailed to those attending as of Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Becki</member_name><member_id>4147212</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kieran</member_name><member_id>6071263</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309791714000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boardgames-434</urlname><id>521103</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Beantown Gamers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309378640000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Play games at Josh and Kieran's House</name><id>24002481</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309712400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boardgames-434/events/24002481/</event_url></item>