<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>306 Northern Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.348064</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-888-HARPOON</phone><name>Harpoon Brewery</name><city>Boston</city><id>669000</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.037100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The first weekend in October is time for our German style Octoberfest, one of the biggest in New England. Come enjoy fresh Harpoon Octoberfest beer, German food, and German Oompah music. Ja!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All About Harpoon Octoberfest:&lt;br /&gt;The 20th anniversary of Boston’s favorite Octoberfest celebration&lt;br /&gt;A festival of beer, music, and Fall in New England at the Harpoon Brewery&lt;br /&gt;A wide selection of fresh Harpoon beer including IPA and UFO Hefeweizen&lt;br /&gt;Plenty of German food sold by a local guest restaurant&lt;br /&gt;The best Chicken Dancing this side of the Alps and the famous keg bowling game&lt;br /&gt;Three stages of music including New England’s premiere German Oompa bands&lt;br /&gt;Come celebrate the original New England-style Octoberfest&lt;br /&gt;When is Harpoon Octoberfest (Remember - Rain or Shine):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, October 2nd, 5:30 pm to 11:00 pm (Doors close at 9:30 pm)&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, October 3rd, 2:00 pm to 9:00 pm (Doors close at 7:30 pm)  &lt;br /&gt;Where is Harpoon Octoberfest?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the Harpoon Brewery, 306 Northern Ave., on Boston's Waterfront&lt;br /&gt;Click Here for Map/Directions&lt;br /&gt;How to get to Harpoon  Octoberfest?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE SHUTTLE - from the South Station area. Departs from behind the Federal Reserve along the Fort Point Channel off Summer Street.  Look for the Shuttle Sign.&lt;br /&gt;TAKE THE &amp;quot;T&amp;quot; - hop aboard the the Silver Line at South Station. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mbta.com...&lt;/a&gt; for schedules, rates and bus routes. Take SL2 or SL3 and get off at Harbor Street.&lt;br /&gt;PUBLIC PARKING - available for a fee at the Brewery in garage across the street&lt;br /&gt;Harpoon Octoberfest Admission:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cover charge $20.00 and includes a souvenir Pint Cup and one (1) drink ticket (does not include food or additional beers&lt;br /&gt;Must be 21 or older and have proper I.D.&lt;br /&gt;Cash bars offer a selection of fresh Harpoon &amp;amp; UFO beers for $5.00 a pint&lt;br /&gt;Plenty capacity, come anytime!&lt;br /&gt;For more info, call 888-HAR-POON ext 3&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Designated Drivers:&lt;br /&gt;Remember to plan ahead and figure out how you will be getting home. Harpoon supports a Designated Driver program at each Festival. All designated drivers should visit the Customer Service booth when they arrive at the Festival where they will receive complimentary non-alcoholic beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.harpoonbrewery.com/index.cfm/page/Octoberfest-Boston/pid/28569" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.harpoonbre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254692645000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253303412000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>20th Annual Harpoon Octoberfest</name><id>11407898</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254519000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/11407898/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/9/global_10766393.jpeg</photo_url></item>