<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;In our August meetup we talked about and &lt;i&gt;deeply&lt;/i&gt; experienced how relaxing opens you to the flow and perspective of Source Energy/Spirit, and thus how you see things changes.  By relaxing, you can almost seamlessly shift from problem consciousness to solution consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;But how do you create &amp;quot;drama&amp;quot; and problem consciousness that gets you stressed out in the first place? You know those &amp;quot;Whoa is me...&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I can't stand this..&amp;quot; and other similar feelings and thoughts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be the topic of this month's meetup.  We'll discuss how you create &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;stressful emotions and reactions to the&lt;/span&gt; dramas in your life, and &lt;i&gt;how you can prevent them&lt;/i&gt;.  We'll be covering ideas that are different than the usual &amp;quot;use positive language and focus on positives&amp;quot;, and leading you through some experiential exercises to learn how you can do this on your own in the future.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Hope you'll join us to add some more strategies to your repertoire for leading a joyful, easy life!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Thank you so much to those of you who have RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; and showed up!  PLEASE, PLEASE, only sign up if you know you can and will attend. We can only take a maximum of 20 people in our space, and do not want to exclude anyone unnecessarily because of a no-show. Help us reach our goal of 100% attendance for those who rsvp &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun! Please join us and &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;stay &amp;quot;connected&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; by participating in our community's message board discussions and receiving our e-mails (which will include our &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&amp;quot;Good Vibrations&amp;quot; tips and news&lt;/span&gt;). To be able to do so, go to your account, and under &amp;quot;Your Groups&amp;quot;, each one has an &amp;quot;Edit email settings&amp;quot;. Set your preferences there. Hope to hear from you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're down a very long driveway, with mailbox at street end.  Please check files for further important instructions.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285183578000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282767411000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seeing the world through "soft eyes" continued</name><id>pkmcpynmbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285110000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/14541041/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>