<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This months meeting will be something a little different. We wil have two of our own CFIIs talk with us on an open forum of sorts. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pete Coolidge CFII,&amp;nbsp;will talk with us about some of the regular issues he runs into  &lt;br /&gt;during flight training and Issues during BFRs and everything in between. As well  &lt;br /&gt;as some refreshing How To's of flight maneuver. Pete is the king of Trim Flying.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will then take a short break and we will have some Member Profile sheets  &lt;br /&gt;available.&amp;nbsp; Everyone has a few good stories. Left seat or right. Let's hear more  &lt;br /&gt;about our members. Ed Bruce's last story was incredible. Thanks Ed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a part of this group by sharing, we really are interested!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/4/2/event_5277922.jpeg" width="225" height="170" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After the break, Gary Rabidou CFII,&amp;nbsp;will talk to us about basic IFR training. What they look for? How they train us, some basic flight training you can do on your  &lt;br /&gt;own to test your IFR ability. As well as where the issues seem to be during IPC's and more.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This will be a fun open forum meeting. So, please bring your questions and participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OSH Raffle Tickets will be on sale. They are actually selling better than ever! We are limiting the sales to 50 tickets maximum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll pick up some discussions on our many&amp;nbsp;upcoming events as well..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, food at 6:00 and meeting at 7:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where else can you have this much excitement for $25 bucks a year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fly Often and Fly Safe,  &lt;br /&gt;Charley&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299873605000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268852408000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association EAA Chapter 1454 Monthly Meetup</name><id>lrkdnypfblb</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299625200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/15979257/</event_url></item>