<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here is an awesome place, on the coast of Portsmouth &amp;amp; Kittery, to picnic, have fun with the whole family, and learn some history at the same time...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.portsmouthharborlighthouse.org/history.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.portsmouth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Out be the Coast Guard Station in Newcastle, have a picnic at Fort Constitution, FKA Fort William and Mary, utilized during the revolutionary war. &lt;br /&gt;then actually, climb up to the top of the Portsmouth Harbor lighthouse, and for a small donation (suggested $4 per adult $2 per child), you can continue to help in the cause of the tremendous upkeep involved in this voluntary venture. &lt;br /&gt;See the picture of the current restoration of the lighthouse, now going on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the actual address of the Coast Guard Station is 25 Wentworth Road, Newcastle, NH for GPS users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the first open house of the season, on May 30th, and I wish I could attend, but I have a former obligation. I believe the tall ships are coming into Portsmouth that day as well. What a great opportunity to see them, the lighthouse and fort, AND then go welcome out troops in with Steve at 5:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will meetup will repeat, and you will more than likely see me there, at open houses through the summer, as a volunteer, when I can get away from Real Estate...lol. &lt;br /&gt;Have a wonderful Memorial Day weekend and stay safe!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286734765000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274578708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portsmouth Harbor Lighthouse tours 1-5 pm</name><id>nnmrnynnbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286730000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15061553/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/9/global_15203833.jpeg</photo_url></item>