<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>T&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Combine suburban alienation, philosophical inquiry, moral seriousness, a mixture of respect for and utter indifference to Torah, and, finally, a ton of dope, and you get one of the most remarkable oeuvres in modern film.-&lt;/i&gt; David Edelstein, New York Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry Gopnik, a Jewish academic, lives in a middle-class Jewish neighborhood in St. Louis Park, Minnesota in 1967. His wife is on the verge of leaving him for one of his colleagues, his students are defaming him and putting his tenure at risk, and a beautiful neighbor distracts him by sunbathing in the nude. Faced the possibility of his life coming apart at the seams Larry begins to question the value of his existence as he seeks advice from three different rabbis in an attempt to solve his problems and become an austere and devoted man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2009/10/02/movies/02serious.html" target="_blank"&gt;NYT CriticsPick Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the dude abides, we can't miss the latest film by the Coen brothers.  An 86% rating on rotten tomatoes, at the very least, we'll have plenty to talk about, afterward.  I guarantee that the discussion will add to your appreciation of this film as we are A Serious Meetup with A Serious Group of Cinephiles who make each event A Serious Good Time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will make reservations for us at &lt;b&gt;Zaftigs&lt;/b&gt; (Deliciously plump, or carrying your extra weight very well)&lt;br /&gt;for the post film discussion as, seriously, is there any other possible place to discuss this film?!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254696973000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Serious Man</name><id>11546337</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255734900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11546337/</event_url></item>