<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>405 Capitol Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.763733</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>La Paloma SAbenera</name><city>Hartford</city><id>966778</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689034</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Can’t Stop the Serenity fundraiser to support Equality Now. Donation: $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE FILM:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A passenger with a deadly secret. Six rebels on the run. An assassin in pursuit. When the renegade crew of Serenity agrees to hide a fugitive on their ship, they find themselves in an action-packed battle between the relentless military might of a totalitarian regime who will destroy anything - or anyone - to get the girl back and the bloodthirsty creatures who roam the uncharted areas of space. But, the greatest danger of all may be on their ship. From the mind of Joss Whedon (Buffy the Vampire Slayer, Angel) comes a new edge-of-your-seat adventure loaded with explosive battles, gripping special effects and fantastic new worlds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE CAUSE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equality Now&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;There are two ways to fight a battle like ours. One is to whisper in the ear of the masses, try subtlely and gradually to change the gender expectations and mythic structures of our culture. That’s me. The other is to step up and confront the thousands of atrocities that are taking place around the world on an immediate, one-by-one basis. That’s a great deal harder, and that’s Equality Now. It’s not about politics; it’s about basic human decency.&amp;quot; — Joss Whedon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Equality Now was founded in 1992 to work for the protection and promotion of the human rights of women around the world. Working with national human rights organizations and individual activists, Equality Now documents violence and discrimination against women and mobilizes international action to support their efforts to stop these human rights abuses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through its Women’s Action Network of concerned groups and individuals around the world, Equality Now:&lt;br /&gt;• distributes information about human rights violations &lt;br /&gt;• takes action to protest these violations &lt;br /&gt;• brings public attention to human rights violations against women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Equality Now, please visit the website: &lt;a href="http://www.equalitynow.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.equalityno...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>It's small I'll be there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246665091000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243120883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Serenity - The Movie (based on the series Fire Fly)</name><id>10479387</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245196800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10479387/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>