<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A new regular meeting for the Hartford Spanish Meet-up!&lt;br /&gt;Join international film buffs as well as Spanish language speakers and learners at Trinity College's free weekly showings of Iberian and Latin American films. All Spanish and Portuguese language films will have English subtitles, and post-film discussions will be in English.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS WEEK'S FILM IS: HABANA BLUES&lt;br /&gt;Director: Benito Zambrano&lt;br /&gt;Spain, Cuba, 2005      115 m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cuba is a land of music, and consequently a land of musicians. Longtime friends and collaborators Tito and Ruy are preparing for a big concert when they learn that two Spanish record producers want to hear them play; this could be the break they’ve been waiting for. Will Ruy accompany his wife and children to Miami ? What will happen to Tito’s grandmother if he goes off on the worldwide tour the Spaniards have been talking about? Habana Blues is full of lots of extraordinary music, but what makes it so special is the way Zambrano details the lives of these artists, and the choice they might be forced to make regarding their music, their families and their country.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker --- Anne Lambright.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Film start at 7:00 in the Life Sciences Building. &lt;br /&gt;For directions to Trinity, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/AboutTrinity/VisitingTrinity/DirectionsToTrinity.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or call (860) 297-2053.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a campus map, see&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trincoll.edu/NR/rdonlyres/92062DC6-138A-430E-9ADA-5A209B506787/0/campusmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.trincoll.e...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can come earlier than 6:45, please join me for supper in the Cave cafeteria (basement of Mather Hall, no id required). Prices are reasonable and the food is quite good. I usually get there by 5:15.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be displaying a "Meet-up" sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Margaret Vincent</member_name><member_id>1777042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235481540000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232555394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: "Habana Blues" at Trinity</name><id>9570421</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233792000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/9570421/</event_url></item>