<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 Plum Island Turnpike</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.799107</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-465-5753</phone><name>Parker River Rufuge Headquarters</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>879211</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847862</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;**Account for about 4 hours for the ride if you stop frequently along the way and on the beach. Total distance round trip is about 13 miles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Hybrid bikes or mountain bikes suggested (gravel road after parking lot 4)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Bring insect repellent!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plum Island is a 6-mile long barrier beach that extends south of Newburyport. Most of it makes up the Parker River Wildlife Refuge, which nearly 300 bird species visit seasonally. &lt;span&gt;The Plum Island section of the refuge is accessible via a 6.5 mile roadway. The first 3.5 miles is &lt;strong&gt;paved&lt;/strong&gt; while the remainder is &lt;strong&gt;gravel-surfaced&lt;/strong&gt;. For your safety, roadside parking is prohibited and a 25 mph speed limit is in effect at all times.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Restaurant tbd at a closer time to event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;ENTRANCE FEE: A daily entrance fee of $5/car $2/walk or bike on is in effect year-round at the Plum Island section of the refuge. When the refuge entrance gatehouse is not staffed envelopes and an “iron ranger” pipe safe are available for fee deposition. Annual passes are available for $20 at refuge headquarters and the entrance gatehouse when staffed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SAFETY PRECAUTIONS: During the warmer months at the refuge, mosquitoes and other biting insects can be very bothersome. Greenheads, an aggressive blood feeding horsefly, occur in large numbers on the refuge from July through mid-August. Ticks are common on the refuge and can transmit Lyme disease and other serious human infections. Please stay on all designated trails and take appropriate precautions to avoid ticks and other insects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Poison ivy is also common on the refuge and is contagious during all seasons. Staying on established trails is the best way to avoid poison ivy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the refuge beach is open, ocean swimming is permitted. However treacherous undertows, currents, and heavy surf may be present and lifeguards are not provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Carry In/Carry Out Policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The refuge is a carry in/carry out facility, this means any trash or items you bring in with you, must leave with you. The trash people leave behind can have negative impacts on the marine life and wildlife that call the refuge home. Also, collecting anything living or non-living on the refuge (shells, sand, plants, rocks, nests, etc) is prohibited. Please leave only footprints, take only memories!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**BRING WATER, SNACKS, BUG SPRAY, AND IF YOU WANT BINOCCULARS/CAMERA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parker River National Wildlife Refuge....&lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/visit.html"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/visit.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plum Island Info...&lt;a href="http://www.plum-island.com/description.htm"&gt;http://www.plum-island.com/description.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map...&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/czm/coastguide/online/maps/map_plum_island_vicinity.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/czm/coastguide/online/maps/map_plum_island_vicinity.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Map...&lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/pdf/Parker%20River%20Map.pdf"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/pdf/Parker%20River%20Map.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Info on Sandy Point State Reservation...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/sndp.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/sndp.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ectaonline.org/wp-content/uploads/SandyPointStateReservation.pdf"&gt;http://www.ectaonline.org/wp-content/uploads/SandyPointStateReservation.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;The refuge is located ~35 miles north of Boston near the City of Newburyport. From Route 95 take exit 57 and travel east on Route 113, then continue straight onto Route 1A South to the intersection with Rolfe’s Lane for a total of 3.5 miles. Turn left onto Rolfe’s Lane and travel 0.5 miles to its end. Turn right onto the Plum Island Turnpike, and our visitor center will be shortly on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim</member_name><member_id>7717713</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347646066000</updated><rating><average>4.92999982834</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339303753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plum Island, Newburyport</name><id>68514602</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347123600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/68514602/</event_url></item>