<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Front Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03833</zip><lat>42.981155</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Town Hall Gallery</name><city>Exeter</city><id>1625121</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.947128</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Challenge:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Our challenge for this month's meeting is &lt;strong&gt;Lights, Camera, Action!&lt;/strong&gt; This challenge is a bit different than previous challenges in that we need a full three, and exactly three, photos from you. One photo will speak to "lights", a second to "camera", and a third to "action". Bonus points if you tie them all together in a creative way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between now and the the meeting, take and email 3 photographs which somehow speak to your interpretation of the subject - please feel free to take great liberty with your interpretation of the subject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't be shy, we have a very encouraging group of critics and we'll all learn something from the experience. Most of all,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;have fun shooting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send monthly challenge photos via email to John. Photos should be JPEGs, no less than 1000 pixels high.&amp;nbsp;A PDF with full details, an FAQ, and email details for the Monthly Challenge is located in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://meetup.rumdoodle.com/files/"&gt;File Library&lt;/a&gt;, available to members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;But wait there's more...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brown Bag Bingo - Month 1:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

This night will be our first of four swaps in our annual Brown Bag Bingo challenge. Participants should bring their object in a paper lunch bag. At this first meeting, we'll move your object into an official Brown Bag Bingo bag, which is actually white because that's how we roll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should also have taken and emailed two photos to John - one reference shot and one creative shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not yet participating but would like to, please contact John ASAP, put your object in a paper lunch bag and bring it to the meeting, and email your reference and creative shots to John.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to find out more, read the rules and track the discussion on our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://meetup.rumdoodle.com/messages/boards/thread/10040983#38581071" target="_blank"&gt;Brown Bag Bingo Discussion Board&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But wait there's even more...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Challenges - a Year in Review&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

We'll take just a bit of time to view the "best of" monthly challenges from the entire year of 2011. Help winnow the photos down to a select few for later presentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ffff00"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But wait, can you believe it, there's even more than that...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annual Celebration&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

As voted at our last meeting, we'll fit in a bit of a celebration this month. We'll supply pizza, soda, wine and beer, and snacks. Much of this will be funded by a monthly contributions surplus, the remainder of which will benefit our sponsor and 501(c)3 charitable art organization, the Seacoast Artists Association.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to contribute your time, dollars, or food/drink (hint, Thanh, hint), your contribution will be greatly appreciated and rewarded with the love and adoration of your fellow photographers. Especially the hot ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're now meeting at the beautiful Town Hall Gallery building, directly across from the bandstand and Town Hall Offices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park on the street or in the nearby&amp;nbsp;municipal&amp;nbsp;lot and walk on over. Walk around the left side of the Town Hall Gallery building (on the side facing the Citizens Bank drive-up windows), and enter the door on the left hand side. Take the elevator to the second floor. Make a left out of the elevator, and enter the room on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Other: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt; Bring other photos if you'd like feedback or critique, and be prepared to [helpfully] critique others'. It would be preferable to email the photos to John ahead of time so they can be displayed on the screen for all to easily see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything photography- or photographer-related is fair game.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The gallery is in historic downtown Exeter. The door will be open, come on in.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327621157000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323380131000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seacoast Photographers Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>dvhkccyqcbzb</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327015800000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/43862142/</event_url></item>