<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Faneuil Hall Marketplace</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359656</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-248-8800</phone><name>Ned Devine's</name><city>Boston</city><id>442998</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055944</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>SOLD OUT-- Sorry everyone we sold this one out.  Keep an eye out for future events though! &lt;br /&gt;-If you did not purchase a ticket at our site, unfortunetly we will not be able to let you join.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;St. Patrick's Day Pub Crawl&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things To Do Boston has teamed up with Tenon Tours to bring you the premier St. Patrick's Day Pub Crawl event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us and hundreds of your closest friends for the 2009 Boston St. Patrick’s Pub Challenge; Saturday, March 14th. We will be going to eight of Boston’s best Irish pubs for a warm-up to the International Irish Pub Challenge which takes place in Ireland each year. The best part is, eight lucky pub crawlers will win a free flight to Ireland for the main event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date: Saturday, March 14th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Time: 12pm - 8pm&lt;br /&gt;Registration: 11:00am - 3pm at Ned Devine’s&lt;br /&gt;Schedule:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 11:00 -12:00 Ned Devine’s&lt;br /&gt;* 12:00 -1:00 Ned Devine’s&lt;br /&gt;* 1:00 - 2:00 Paddy O’s&lt;br /&gt;* 2:00 - 3:00 Hennessy’s&lt;br /&gt;* 3:00 - 4:00 Purple Shamrock&lt;br /&gt;* 4:00 - 5:00 McFaddens&lt;br /&gt;* 5:00 - 6:00 Kitty O’Sheas&lt;br /&gt;* 6:00 - 7:00 Jose McIntyre’s&lt;br /&gt;* 7:00 - 8:00 Trinity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price Includes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Your Official Pub Challenge T-Shirt (Collector’s Edition)&lt;br /&gt;* Your Official Pub Challenge Pub Cup&lt;br /&gt;* Free Shamrock Beads, Paddy Hats, and other free swag (limited quantities)&lt;br /&gt;* Your Official Pub Crawl Map&lt;br /&gt;* 8 Chances to win a Free Flight to Ireland*&lt;br /&gt;* $50 off the Spring or Fall International Irish Pub Challenge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Flight Giveaway Terms: No purchase necessary. One prize will be given away at each scheduled location on the 1/2 hour at each location beginning at 12:30pm and ending at 7:30pm. Winner will be chosen from written submitted entries collected at the registration desk. Winners must claim their prize in person within 30 minutes of announcement. Each prize will be one (1) free flight voucher valid for airfare from Boston to Dublin International Airport (DUB) departing May 2nd, 2009 and returning to Boston from Shannon International Airport (SNN) May 10th, 2009. Actual flight including airline, flight number, and times will be chosen by Tenon Tours. Value of the voucher should include base fare and fuel surcharge, but not exceed a retail of $500.00 USD. Flight voucher does not include departures taxes or fees. Prize must be used in conjunction with the purchase of the “land package” offered by Tenon Tours for the International Irish Pub Challenge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Attire: Your best St. Patrick's Day Green and comfy shoes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $20.00&lt;br /&gt;Go To: www.thingstodoboston.com to purchase your tickets today!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the registration table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Meghan</member_name><member_id>7970205</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238882066000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235679784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>St. Patrick's Day Pub Crawl</name><id>9831640</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237046400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/9831640/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/9/global_5450809.jpeg</photo_url></item>