<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Off Raffia Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.966488</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Shire</name><city>Enfield</city><id>10318262</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.566055</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Kelly and I had been thinking about having a Yule celebration at our place, and after Lore Night it sounded like other people thought it could be a good idea. So we're opening our home for Yule! Details below on rules, food, and celebration plans. Some people will be holding vigil the night before, so we'll get things started in the afternoon but progress well into the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules: Though this is a public event, please contact me if you have not met us before. If you have someone local who knows you (like the organizer of the meetups, Karl, Mike, Annie, etc) then a positive word from them is all we need. If you haven't met anyone just drop me a line and we can meet someone for a cup of coffee for introductions prior to Yule. Feel free to bring spouses/children/significant others/etc. If you want to invite a friend, that would generally be fine as well, though if we haven't met you maybe bring that friend to coffee. If you haven't been here, just message me for the address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food: We'll be doing this pot-luck style. Just put in the comments what you might like to bring. We'll provide both some crock pots of food and some beverages. Bringing beer/mead/wine for sharing is always appreciated as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebration: We'd like to hold blot and sumbel. We could do a viking gift exchange but that depends on whether people are interested. It's been a rough year for a lot of people and the only cost of entry I want there to be is a dish or something to share. We also have a fire pit if anyone is interested in braving the probable cold to burn a log or two, but that is in no way required.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356221608000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Followers of Asatru</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>asatru-242</urlname><id>369297</id><group_lat>41.8600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut &amp; Western Mass Asatru Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352901027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT &amp; Western Mass (and beyond) Public Yule</name><id>91348032</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356210000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/asatru-242/events/91348032/</event_url></item>