<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Tuesday, September 16, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Selling Vision and Innovation in the Life Sciences Sector - &amp;quot;Senior executives and investors speak out on how to get your first early stage sale&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register Online at &lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.entretechf...&lt;/a&gt;, walk ins are welcome too&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Overview&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The September 16th EntreTech forum kicks off the Forum's monthly panel series for 2008-2009 with a focus on the real-world challenge of managing early-stage sales in the bio-pharma sector. As academic researchers attempt to commercialize their work, perhaps the most relevant acid test is the first sale. The September 16th EntreTech Forum panel members will explore the issue of early product sales, bringing together the leadership and backers of early stage biopharma innovators. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panelist:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Omar Amirana, M.D., Investment Manager – Oxford Biosciences, &lt;a href="http://www.oxbio.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.oxbio.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Amirana is an Investment Manager for Oxford. Prior to joining Oxford in 2005, he served as the Vice President of Business Development at St. Jude Medical (STJ) in the Cardiology and Daig Divisions where he was responsible for mergers, acquisitions and licenses in the areas of electrophysiology, interventional cardiology and peripheral vascular intervention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining St. Jude Medical, Dr. Amirana was the CEO of Resolution Medical, a privately held cardiology company in Silicon Valley. He has helped raise over $60M in venture financing and was part of the management team in four start-up healthcare technology companies. Three of those companies have held IPOs: EP Technologies, Cardima, and MedicaLogic/Medscape. He received a B.S. in Mechanical Engineering from Tufts University and an M.D. from Eastern Virginia Medical School. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Errik Anderson, VP Operations &amp;amp; Finance – Adimab, &lt;a href="http://www.adimab.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.adimab.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Anderson is a founding member of Adimab, a privately held company, and current serves as Vice President of Operations &amp;amp; Finance. Adimab is changing the discovery, maturation and production of fully human therapeutic antibodies. By integrating all aspects of antibody discovery and developing sophisticated screening methods, Adimab rapidly selects high affinity human antibodies with improved formulation and manufacturing characteristics. Their proprietary library design and presentation technologies enable the discovery of full-length human antibodies with broad epitope coverage and high affinity - faster than any known technology platform.  Prior to Adimab, Mr. Anderson was at Lehman Brothers Venture Capital in New York City and in 2003 was the founding President of a small venture capital consulting and investment partnership, Seven West Ventures. Errik pursued graduate studies in bioengineering at the Thayer School of Engineering, received his MBA from the Tuck School of Business at Dartmouth College and his A.B. in Economics from Dartmouth College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Glenn Batchelder, President and Chief Executive Officer – BIND Biosciences, &lt;a href="http://www.bindbio.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bindbio.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Batchelder leads BIND Biosciences as president and CEO of this biopharmaceutical company developing therapeutic targeted nanoparticles.  BIND leverages the convergence of polymeric biomaterials, nanoparticle engineering, and combinatorial synthesis to enable optimally targeted nanoparticles for specific indications, concentrating the drug at the site of disease while minimizing systemic exposure. Initial product development efforts are in cardiovascular disease and cancer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining BIND Biosciences, Mr. Batchelder was CEO of Acceleron Pharma, a company developing biotherapeutics for cancer and musculoskeletal disorders. He grew Acceleron from a research start-up to a clinical stage company with promising bone loss therapy in the clinic and a robust preclinical pipeline.  Mr. Batchelder is on the Board of Directors of the Massachusetts Biotechnology Council. He received a B.S. in Chemical Engineering from Lehigh University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas M. Fitzgerald, CEO CellTraffix, &lt;a href="http://celltraffix.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://celltraffix.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As CEO of CellTraffix, Mr. Fitzgerald leverages his 25+ years of sector experience to direct the strategic activities of this privately held development-stage medical technology company.  CellTraffix is focused on bringing novel kits and therapeutic products to market to serve the oncology and adult stem cell markets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to CellTraffix, Mr. Fitzgerald has served as President and CEO of Oyagen, a biotechnology company focused on discovering, developing, and commercializing novel pharmaceutical therapies exploiting RNA editing and DNA editing enzymes.  Mr. Fitzgerald has also previously served as internal counsel at SmithKline Beecham plc (SKB; formerly, Beecham, Inc.), eventually attaining the position of Assistant General Counsel.  Mr.Fitzgerald has also been internal legal counsel at Mobil Corp. and Hertz Corp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Register Online at &lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.entretechf...&lt;/a&gt;, walk ins are welcome too&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Open to all</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Georgia</member_name><member_id>6917121</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221777160000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213745935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northeastern University's EntreTech Forum September Meetup</name><id>8161754</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221604200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/8161754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/3/global_4559507.jpeg</photo_url></item>