<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 10 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting south of Falls Village, CT off of Rte. 7 at an AT parking area and heading northbound along the Housatonic River, gradually up over Mount Prospect, then over Wetauwanchu Mountain, finally a steep decent to the ending point (about 400 ft. down) on the Rte. 44 AT parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Note 4/4/08 in PM: 30% chance of showers for start of hike at 43 F, 82% humidity. Drops to 10% by Noon! 0% by 3 PM at 51 F, 50% humidity. Some sun possible starting at 1 PM at 46 F, 61% humidity!  Winds light to moderate at 6 - 11 mph. So, some low chance of rain in morning just at the start but cool and humid (fog?). Improves to mostly cloudy, warm, and comfortable in afternoon. ***&lt;br /&gt;*** Note 4/4/08: 40% chance of showers at hike start at 42 F with 9 mph winds, going down to 10 % chance by 1 PM at 48 F with 11 mph winds, then 0% chance by 3 PM (and on to hike end) at 50 F with 11 mph winds. So, cloudy all day, fair chance of a shower to start hike but clearing up. ***&lt;br /&gt;*** Note 4/3/08: 50% chance of rain for the start of the hike, don't have afternoon prediction yet. ***&lt;br /&gt;*** Note 4/2/08: 40% chance of rain, most likely in the morning. 53 F for a high but about 41 F to start. We'll hike rain or shine.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at 9 AM at the Rte. 44 AT parking area on shoulder of road (see below) and shuttle to the hike starting location south of Falls Village, CT off of Rte. 7 on the shoulder of the road. We'll hike the 9.5 miles with a lunch at the Limestone Spring Lean-to for shelter and to replenish our water. Finally, we end at the Rte. 44 AT parking area where we started and most vehicles are located. I figure we will end the hike at about 5 PM. Some of us will shuttle back to the other end to get our vehicles. We'll stop for dinner at a local establishment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If more than 7 people go, we will need assistance in driving people between the meeting location and starting point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we should come in earlier than I estimated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Daypack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Rain parka/jacket -MUST have, 40% chance rain, rain pants optional&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold morning &amp;amp; possibly &amp;quot;hot&amp;quot; afternoon, avoid cotton as it stays wet.&lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart water min., 2 quarts suggested max.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail lunch. High energy meal should be planned.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay -may need this but likely still too early&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor **leaving** at a 7 AM for those interested. There will be a blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. Return at about 7:30 PM. It is advised to call Kevin S (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool. Approximate location/directions for the carpool meetup can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/69+Prospect+Hill+Rd+East+Windsor+CT+06088-3600/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the meetup location &amp;amp; AT ending point on Rte. 44 (Canaan Rd.) north of Salisbury, CT via MapQuest (park on side of road):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/%5B91-106%5D+Canaan+Rd+Salisbury+CT+06068/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT hike trailhead, intersection of Rte. 7 (Sharon Canaan Rd.) and Rte. 112 (Lime Rock Rd.) south of Falls Village, CT via MapQuest (Close as I could get w/service, go south on Rte. 7 past intersection):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/299+Lime+Rock+Rd+Falls+Village+CT+06031/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the parking area on the shoulder of the road on Rte. 44 (see event description). A dark BLUE Grand Caravan Sport (mine) and a silver Jeep Liberty will be there (our member Janice's).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207573926000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It's finally time to start hiking some long hikes! This segment isn't too long and a great opportunity to get a taste of AT hiking. Let's enjoy the woods and trails of CT. :-)</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207172410000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT over Mt. Prospect &amp; Wetauwanchu Mtn. near Falls Village CT</name><id>7660314</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207400400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7660314/</event_url></item>