<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Buddha Collapsed Out of Shame by Hana Makhmalbaf (France, 2008, 81 min.). The beauty and grief of present-day Afghanistan receives epic, poetic treatment in this remarkable film. Baktay, a six-year-old Afghan girl, attends school, taking her mother's lipstick for a pencil. On her way to school, she encounters boys playing games that mimic the violence they have witnessed in their daily lives. Buddha Collapsed Out of Shame is an exotic and frightening journey into the minds of the children who live in areas where violence is everywhere. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's The Guardian review: As the youngest member of the Iranian film-making clan, Hana Makhmalbaf is not yet 20, but has already chalked up her second film, coaxing a winning performance from a five-year-old Afghan girl, Nikbakht Noruz. She plays Bakhtay, a determined little madam who stomps off in search of this school business she's been hearing about. Scripted by Makhmalbaf's mother, Marzieh Meshkini, there are some playful snapshots of a child's fancies and half-grasped ideas of the world. The mood darkens when she runs into a pack of older boys playing at Taliban, who rip up the notebook she has spent all morning bartering eggs to buy. Their act of mindless cultural vandalism is a miniature of the Taliban's destruction of the two giant stone Buddhas in the Bamyan cliffs, where the film is set. What kind of men will these brutalised boys make, Makhmalbaf is asking - but her film builds up an overwrought symbolism that fails to hit the mark dramatically. Still these are big issues to be taken on by a young director whose clear-cut sense of injustice make this an ideal film for older kids. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll head to a near by restaurant for conversation.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will hold up a sign in the front of the auditorium at the end of the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris</member_name><member_id>3926531</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225152471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddha Collapsed Out of Shame</name><id>9043469</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227374100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9043469/</event_url></item>