<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Here's an opportunity for us to picnic at this beautiful festival to:&lt;br /&gt;- enjoy time together,&lt;br /&gt;- share and remember in appreciation our family and friends who have journeyed on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;organized by Forest Hills Educational Trust&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foresthillstrust.org/calendar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foresthill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 6 - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;( Join us when you can.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring: a potluck dish to share &amp;amp; your own refreshment.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional: Bring blanket, bug spray and a flashlight to help guide your exit from the Cemetery, as there is no electrical lighting after dark.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting place:&lt;/b&gt; We'll be inside the Main Front Gate (to the right) until 6:15 pm.  After 6:15 pm, to locate us, call Chew-Hoong at 781-820-3285 or Mark Hoffman at 617-504-7090.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If weather is iffy &amp;amp; we decide not to attend: email will be sent to you at 4 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission&lt;/b&gt;: FREE, with a $10 suggested donation per lantern.  Getting a lantern is optional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;11th Annual Lantern Festival&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a moving memorial ceremony inspired by Buddhist rituals. Inscribe a lantern with a personal message to friends or family and float it across Lake Hibiscus at sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this breathtaking ceremony of remembrance, visitors to this lush, Victorian landscape make paper lanterns and set them afloat on the peaceful waters of a small lake. &lt;b&gt;This ritual is based on the traditional Japanese Bon Festival, a time when a door opens to the world of the ancestors, allowing us to send messages to the other side.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People enjoy picnics on the grass and a multi-cultural program of music and dance. They decorate their lanterns with calligraphy and notes to those who have died. At sunset, a candle is lit in each lantern, and the glimmering lanterns are set afloat. Drifting and flickering with the wind, the lanterns symbolize the soul’s journey when life ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy performances by Master Tsuji's Samurai Taiko Drummers, gospel singer Ron Murphy, the Chinese dance of Tsai-Fong Dance Troupe, Quincy Choral Society, traditional Balinese dance by Sanggar Kinanthi, and students from Showa Institute.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; is $10; taking the T is encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.foresthillstrust.org/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.foresthill...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details provided  later</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248218425000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242879750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picnic at the Lantern Festival- Ceremony of Remembrance</name><id>10460676</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247781600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/10460676/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/global_9558313.jpeg</photo_url></item>