<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Battle Road Trail walk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MINUTE MAN NATIONAL HISTORICAL PARK is located 22 miles outside of Boston within the towns of Lexington, Lincoln and Concord. The park commemorates the opening battles of the American Revolution on April 19, 1775 by protecting, preserving and interpreting the significant historic sites, structures, landscapes, events and ideas embodied by these events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need a ride please say so in your rsvp and what area you live in. Anyone travelling by T can be picked up at the Alewife subway stations pick up/drop off area at 9:30.  Please email me if you need a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Meet at 11 am in the Minute Man Visitor Center parking lot&lt;/span&gt;.  From I-95: Take exit 30B. You will be on Route 2A west. Continue west on 2A for 3 quarters of a mile. (see all of this on the map at the link below).  Afterwards we will go to Lexington for Japanese food.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/mima/planyourvisit/upload/MIMA%20Park%20Map.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/mi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After leaving the visitor center, we will walk along the Battle Road Trail. This five mile trail connects historic sites from Meriam?s Corner in Concord to the eastern boundary of the park in Lexington. The main theme of the trail is the Battle of April 19, 1775, that launched the American Revolution. More over, the trail interprets the broader human story of the people whose lives were altered by the events that took place here. Much of the trail follows original remnants of the Battle Road; other sections leave the historic road to follow the route of the Minute Men, traversing farming fields, wetlands, and forests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On April 19, 1775, British soldiers and American militia, &amp;quot;minute men&amp;quot; met in a series of skirmishes along a 22 mile stretch of road that ran from Boston to Concord. The American Revolution began at Lexington and Concord with a clash of arms known to history as &amp;quot;the shot heard round the world.&amp;quot; At the Park the opening battle of the Revolution is brought to life as visitors explore the battlefields and witness the American revolutionary spirit through the writings of the Concord authors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minute Man National Historical Park is home to many unique and interesting historic structures, interpretive walking trails and cultural landscapes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The park supports a variety of habitats. Forests are dominant, covering approximately 500 acres of the park, including about 200 acres of forested wetland. Non-forested wetlands, including several ponds, cover approximately 180 acres. Meadows and fields cover an additional 250 acres, including approximately 100 acres farmed under the park's agricultural leasing program. Shrubland also is present at the park, particularly at the interface of fields and forests. Developed areas, including roads, parking lots, and buildings, cover the remainder of the park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will have lunch at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teppanyaki in Lexington&lt;br /&gt;27 Waltham Street                                                &lt;br /&gt;Lexington, MA 02420&lt;br /&gt;781-274-6068&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.teppanyakiasiancuisine.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.teppanyaki...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202832249000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201573805000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Battle Road Trail walk</name><id>7217689</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1202659200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7217689/</event_url></item>