<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>NH Rt 25/118</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03282</zip><lat>43.828666</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Atwell Hill Rd.</name><city>Wentworth</city><id>884598</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.894947</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This backpacking trip is the first in a series of section hikes on the Appalachian Trail in Vermont, New Hampshire and Maine.&lt;/b&gt; Please read full details below before RSVP-ing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a &lt;b&gt;3 day/2 night backpacking trip&lt;/b&gt;, beginning on Friday morning, April 24 and ending on Sunday afternoon, April 26. We will start in Hannover, NH near Dartmouth College and hike northward 36 miles to Atwell Hill Rd, climbing Moose Mtn (2,250 ft), Smarts Mtn (3,200 ft) and Mt Cube (2,911 ft) along our route. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants should have experience backpacking and camping in early spring in sub-freezing temperatures and should bring cold temperature gear. Night time temperatures could be as cold as 10-20 F. It is likely that we will encounter some snow, ice, or mud along the route, so gaiters, waterproof footwear, and additional traction are recommended. While we will try to camp at designated shelters and established campsites, conditions may require us to stealth camp at natural sites, and we will follow LNT guidelines to reduce our impact. Please make sure you bring adequate shelter if such a case should arise.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The daily mileage plan is listed below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day 1: 11 miles. Camp at Moose Mtn Shelter on summit&lt;br /&gt;Day 2: 13 miles. Camp at Smarts Mtn Campsite on summit&lt;br /&gt;Day 3: 12 miles. Hike to Atwell Hill Rd trailhead parking. Then shuttle. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is recommended that you bring a copy of Appalachian Trail: Map 4, NH 25 (Glenncliff) to Connecticut River (Hannover) from the New Hampshire and Vermont set published by the Appalachian Trail Conference. These can be purchased in the ATC store at &lt;a href="https://www.atctrailstore.org/catalog/itemlist.cfm?atcmem=1&amp;amp;catid=42&amp;amp;pcatid=0&amp;amp;compid=1" target="_blank"&gt;www.appalachiantrail.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip starts on Friday morning at 8:30 AM at the intersection of Atwell Hill Road and Rt 118/25 (Moosilauke Rd) just north of Wentworth, NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Boston:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I93 N, 109 miles. Take exit 26 for US-3/Hwy 3A/RT-25 toward Rumney/Plymouth, 0.4 miles. Merge onto RT-3A, 3.9 miles. At the traffic circle, take the 1st exit onto RT-25/Rumney Route 25. Continue to follow RT-25, about 11 miles to Atwell Hill Rd. Total 126 mi – about 2 hours 15 mins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From there we will drop a car at the Atwell Hill Road parking lot on the AT and drive down to Hanover to start our hike. The trip will end when we finish the reverse shuttle at the end of our hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you RSVP YES, you will be asked some questions. Please answer these or I may be forced to decline your participation on the trip. I will try to accommodate people as best I can based on experience and availability. There will be a limit of 6 on this trip to limit impact to the trail and crowding at shelters. A minimum of two cars is required for the shuttle. I will provide one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a moderately challenging trip hike, so in the best interests of all, I reserve the right to decline RSVPs if I do think you will be a good fit. On the other hand, everyone should realize this is a group hike and we will work together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 36 miles &lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: ~6500 ft &lt;br /&gt;Trails: Appalachian Trail, New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. It is very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that you're late or lost.  Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that you are qualified to join us on this Appalachian Trail hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/What_to_wear_on_a_hike/?name=What_to_wear_on_a_hike"&gt;What to wear on a hike&lt;/a&gt; and pack water and food. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-New-England-Hiking-Meetup/pages/disclaimer/?name=disclaimer"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Black Mazda 3 with Ski Rack and Lots of Bumperstickers</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip</member_name><member_id>5187997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241461482000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235322143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AT Section Hiking Series: Western New Hampshire</name><id>9795965</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240576200000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9795965/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/7/a/global_7539706.jpeg</photo_url></item>