<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;.. BLIZZARD WARNING IN EFFECT FROM NOON SUNDAY TO 6 PM EST MONDAY...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE IN TAUNTON HAS ISSUED A BLIZZARD WARNING... WHICH IS IN EFFECT FROM NOON SUNDAY TO 6 PM EST MONDAY. THE WINTER STORM WATCH IS NO LONGER IN EFFECT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* LOCATIONS... ALL OF RHODE ISLAND EXCEPT BLOCK ISLAND AND ALL OF EASTERN MASSACHUSETTS EXCEPT CAPE COD AND THE ISLANDS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* HAZARD TYPES... HEAVY SNOW AND POTENTIALLY DAMAGING WINDS... WITH CONSIDERABLE BLOWING AND DRIFTING OF SNOW AND NEAR ZERO VISIBILITIES. SCATTERED THUNDERSTORMS WITH SNOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* ACCUMULATIONS... 15 TO 20 INCHES OF SNOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* TIMING... LIGHT SNOW WILL START IN THE EARLY AFTERNOON AND BECOME HEAVY BY EVENING. VERY HEAVY SNOW WILL FALL THROUGHOUT SUNDAY NIGHT WITH UP TO 2 TO 4 INCHES PER HOUR LIKELY AT TIMES. THE SNOW WILL TAPER TO FLURRIES EARLY MONDAY AFTERNOON. WINDS WILL PEAK FROM LATE SUNDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH MUCH OF MONDAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* IMPACTS... EXTREMELY DANGEROUS TRAVEL CONDITIONS WILL DEVELOP BY SUNDAY EVENING. STRONG WINDS WILL COMBINE WITH THE SNOW TO CREATE BLINDING CONDITIONS WITH NEAR ZERO VISIBILITY AT TIMES SUNDAY NIGHT. WIDESPREAD POWER OUTAGES ARE EXPECTED DURING THE HEIGHT OF THE STORM SUNDAY NIGHT FROM BOTH THE STRONG WINDS KNOCKING DOWN POWER LINES AND THE WEIGHT OF THE HEAVY SNOW. SHOVELING SHOULD NOT BE DONE BY ANYONE WITH HEART CONDITIONS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* WINDS... NORTHEAST TO NORTH WINDS WILL INCREASE TO 25 TO 35 MPH WITH GUSTS AS HIGH 50 TO 60 MPH ESPECIALLY ALONG COASTAL RHODE ISLAND AND COASTAL MASSACHUSETTS FROM LATE SUNDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH MUCH OF MONDAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* TEMPERATURES... WILL RANGE FROM THE MID 20S TO LOWER 30S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* VISIBILITIES... ONE QUARTER MILE OR LESS AT TIMES.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRECAUTIONARY/PREPAREDNESS ACTIONS...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A BLIZZARD WARNING IS ISSUED WHEN SUSTAINED WINDS OR FREQUENT GUSTS OVER 35 MPH ARE EXPECTED WITH CONSIDERABLE FALLING AND/OR BLOWING AND DRIFTING SNOW. VISIBILITIES WILL BECOME POOR WITH WHITEOUT CONDITIONS AT TIMES. THOSE VENTURING OUTDOORS MAY BECOME LOST OR DISORIENTED... SO PERSONS IN THE WARNING AREA ARE ADVISED TO STAY INDOORS. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will gather the group after close of credits in the hallway outside the theater.  Look for him to be holding a red meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293470713000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290875456000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>True Grit</name><id>15566815</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293401700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15566815/</event_url></item>