<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Washington &amp; Hyde Park Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.299938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Forest Hills subway stn.</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>183700</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.113548</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come out for some fresh air and exercise! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover Boston's Emerald Necklace park system.  We will walk through the Arnold Arboretum and the Jamaica Pond park, then head back to the Dogwood Cafe for lunch at noon.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have listed the event elsewhere and aticipate a group of 20 for this walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet inside the Forest Hills subway station, in the main lobby across from the donut shop. There is $4 parking at the subway station's lot.  We will walk through the arboretum, around Jamaica Pond, then back through the Arboretum to the Dogwood Cafe for lunch. This is near the Forest Hills station and I have a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;Visit these sites for driving directions and the Dogwoods menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.arboretum.harvard.edu/visitors/map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.arboretum....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.arboretum.harvard.edu/visitors/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.arboretum....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.dogwoodcafe.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Arnold Arboretum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Arnold Arboretum is a park for both outdoor enjoyment and scientific exploration. North America's first public arboretum, it is owned by the City of Boston and leased to Harvard University for 1,000 years, beginning in 1882. The 265 acres of rolling land includes meadows, forest and ponds with 4,000 different varieties of woody plants and 14,000 trees, shrubs and vines along with world-renowned horticultural collections. &lt;br /&gt;Peter's Hill, the highest point in the Necklace, provides a glorious view of the Boston skyline. The Hunnewell Center has a visitors center and bookstore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jamaica Pond Park &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Olmsted and most everyone else agreed that Jamaica Pond belonged in Boston?s system of parks, and very few alterations were needed to improve upon this natural feature. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The pond plunged to more than 50 feet in depth, a kettlehole formed by an ancient glacier. Natural springs make it the largest and purest body of water in Boston. The state stocks the pond, and fishermen come here to catch trout and indigenous fish: pickerel, bass, hornpout and perch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today Bostonians flock to Jamaica Pond for concerts, children?s programs, theater performances, rowing, sailing, fishing, running and biking with a view. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boathouse and bandstand were added in 1912. The first concert attracted 6,000 listeners. Earlier, rowboats and canoes had been put into service, selected as much to enhance the idyllic scene as for their recreational value. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today boats are for rent at the Pond in the summer season. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1163430592000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162174521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Emerald Necklace park system, take 2</name><id>5231476</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1163257200000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5231476/</event_url></item>