<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;PLEASE READ THIS IN ITS ENTIRETY&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;So what is Trash the Dress? Trash the dress, fearless bridal, and rock the frock - refers to photography that contrasts elegant clothing with an environment in which it is completely out of place. Usually brides decide to have pictures taken on the beach, but possibilities are endless. City streets, rooftops, garbage dumps, fields, and abandoned buildings are only few examples of trash the dress session locations.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;A model often wears a ball gown, prom dress or wedding dres&lt;/span&gt; s, and may effectively ruin the dress in the process by getting it wet, dirty or in extreme circumstances tearing or destroying the garment.  &lt;br /&gt;

 It may also be done as an additional shoot after the wedding, almost as a declaration that the wedding is done and the dress will not be used again. It is seen as an alternative to storing the dress away, never to be seen again. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 And this is exactly what we are going to do... Gather models - both Male and Female- to come Trash some Dresses and other clothing- while us photographers create images of it all! This is going to occur in Marlborough. There will be shooting on the waterfront, a beach and plenty of trails.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Models, email me at chris@worcesterphotostudios.com to confirm you are coming. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We are currently looking for Stylists - both hair and makeup as well as a clothing stylist.... the more we have the better the event will be!! So please send out your search parties and see what you can gather for this area. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 There is a cost to participate in the event. It is $60.00 per photographer. It goes toward dresses we purchase, drinks for the day, paperwork that needs to be printed and the list goes on and on. We all benefit from these kinds of events and we see it as a portfolio building exercise for all involved. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Money must be given by September 1st. Methods of payment- Paypal (payment@worcesterphotostudios.com, reference Trash the Dress), credit card or cash. We need to know what models are able to participate that day. This is only so I'm not stuck with 20 dresses that i bought if people don't show up. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Photographers- here is the DEAL! So that means you have to give each model you photograph a min of 3-5 images for their portfolios. Fully retouched and useable for their promotional uses. They are not allowed to resell the images to anyone - only for promo use. You have one month to get images to the models or studio. That means by Oct 29th, 2012. We will have tracking to make sure everyone knows who has the pictures.  &lt;br /&gt;

 Any questions? Chris@worcesterphotostudios.com &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Patrick and Chris&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Rinne</member_name><member_id>47667932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350319249000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344869414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trash The Dress</name><id>77536252</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>32400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348930800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/77536252/</event_url></item>