<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Ok, more details on the race for next Saturday.  This, from the Race Director (?):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Photographers are always welcome. The only thing we would ask is that you stand off the trail a few feet so that dogs won't get spooked. Some are prone to that. The other thing that I would ask, is that please encourage folks to share their photos because drivers seldom get to view their teams in action. Have fun. I think you will find the race site to be very photogenic.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave from the parking lot across from the IOKA theater in Exeter, NH at 6 a.m. sharp.  Our timing is to be there before the 8:30 drivers meeting.  For more information about this event, check out:  www.nesdc.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you Saturday ~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cynthia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Cynthia from the Seacoast Photographers group is managing this event. Details will be updated here as well for CAPE group members who are interested in this great photo opportunity.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever see a dog sled race? Me neither.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever want to go to one and photograph? Me too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, so here's the deal. Saturday, January 29 (as long as there is snow), Tamworth NH is hosting a Sprint and Skijor Sled Dog event. The purse is $3,000.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The day begins at at 7:30 a.m. when drivers pick up their bibs; at 8:30 there is a drivers meeting and at 9 a.m. the Skijoring begins (sort of like, &amp;quot;let the fun begin&amp;quot;). Rankings include Dog Junior, Dog Pro, and Open categories. I have emailed the contact person - he said photographers are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will email him closer to the date to let him know how many of us to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving time is about 2 hours so I would plan on leaving Exeter at 6 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting place: Downtown Exeter NH parking lot across the street from IOKA Theater at 6 a.m. - January 29.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cynthia</member_name><member_id>8758507</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296303713000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295446769000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tamworth Dog Sled Races</name><id>16105337</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296298800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/16105337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/4/1/global_20910577.jpeg</photo_url></item>