<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The theme for February is sex.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a tip. When the theme is sex, DO NOT Google images for “sex” to find a graphic for your meetup. You may file this tip in your “well duh” file for future reference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is sexy food?  Well, here in Connecticut I am happy to say, it can mean almost anything you want it to mean as long as your food is willing and fully ripe. I’d stay away from veal dishes if I were you... just saying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be back at my place for this month. If you don’t know or remember the location in West Hartford, no worries, I will send it out a few days before the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in cooking up some delicious sexiness in February.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1267902314000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262999033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes February Meetup</name><id>gwhmhyndbqb</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266019200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/12265735/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/9/4/global_12563268.jpeg</photo_url></item>