<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>****The meetup this month is 12/12, NOT 12/5, and it will NOT be at Bentara - read below***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Designers - this month we will be having a special Meetup at Phoenix Press.  They have graciously agreed to host us, give us a tour of the facility, teach us about pre press and printing, and give us FREE FOOD.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE RSVP so they know how much free food to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks!!&lt;br /&gt;David&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;December 12th ?Meet Up? Host&lt;br /&gt;Phoenix Press, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;15 James Street&lt;br /&gt;New Haven, CT  06513&lt;br /&gt;Quality Printing since 1982&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are a full service family owned &amp;amp; operated Offset Printer, we employ 47 greatly skilled people in a 60,000sf facility, offering the following IN-HOUSE: Complete Electronic &lt;br /&gt;Pre-Press Department (CTP); Conventional &amp;amp; Digital Presses (up to 40?) 1-6 Colors with Perfecting Capabilities; Print on Demand &lt;br /&gt;Dept (B&amp;amp;W and Color) with in-line finishing;  Full Service Conventional Bindery; Complete Mailing Dept.; Warehousing, Inventory &amp;amp; Fulfillment Services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for a drink and a bite to eat this December 12th at 5:30pm.   &lt;br /&gt;While you?re here you can sit in on an abridged version of our Monthly Seminar:&lt;br /&gt;~ Quick overview of how files run through or Pre-Press Dept., FTP, email, preflight, proofing&lt;br /&gt;~ Understanding the difference between Raster and Vector&lt;br /&gt;~ More focus on troubled files: common mistakes, spot colors in RGB, poor resolution images, registration text&lt;br /&gt;~ Quick PDF overview: why PDF?, common pdf questions&lt;br /&gt;~ Open Floor &amp;amp; Facility Tour&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Fischer</member_name><member_id>3013881</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197956658000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New Haven Creative People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NHDesignTech</urlname><id>283863</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven Design &amp; Technology Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194479267000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GNH Design and Marketing Holiday Party!</name><id>6697853</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197498600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NHDesignTech/events/6697853/</event_url></item>