<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;PRIVATE by Saverio Costanzo &lt;br /&gt;Italy, 2004, 90 min &lt;br /&gt;Actor Mohammed Bakri will be present. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A psychological drama about a Palestinian family of seven, suddenly confronted with a volatile situation in their home that mirrors the larger ongoing conflict between Palestine and Israel.  ?Private's vision of domestic dread is more raw and real than anything Hollywood fantasy can offer?this is powerful stuff, performed with conviction.? ?Mathew Leyland, BBC &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Private, Italian director Saverio Costanzo's stunning human drama, would seem like something out of Kafka if it weren't based on real events and a relatively common fact of contemporary Palestinian life.  NY Daily News&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Selected as Italy's entry for best foreign film at this year's Academy Awards, Private was disqualified for not being predominantly in Italian. A pity, since this meticulously nonpartisan film, even as it makes the case for passive resistance, shows what devastating lack of appeal the strategy has for young Palestinians. &lt;br /&gt;LA Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this is a one time only screening and has replaced Eastern Promises as a group event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.eyeforfilm.co.uk/reviews.php?film_id=10735" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eyeforfilm...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film and the Q and A session by the actor, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191351795000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190246224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Palestinian Film Festival at Kendall : Private</name><id>6391858</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191178800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6391858/</event_url></item>