<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>In July, we had a wonderfully transformational evening with our topic on Abrahadabra - the magic of creating as you speak.  It was so, so good, we want to do it again, and in a way that anyone who wants to participate, can.  We're going to do it as a tele-meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note: Have a pen and notebook with you for the call!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Abrahadabra is actually an Aramaic based word that roughly translated means &amp;quot;I create as I speak.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are you creating? Is it what you &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to be creating?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this call we'll be discussing the &amp;quot;stories&amp;quot; you tell (how you talk and think about a topic) and how to best language them so that you'll be creating the experiences you want to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a part of this, we'll also be covering how to speak and how to use affirmations in a way that is &lt;i&gt;truly believable&lt;/i&gt; to you. &lt;i&gt;Otherwise, you will still create what you don't want!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll take some time to uncover a story you might be carrying that's holding you back; and then you'll get to shift it to something that will be more effective and will feel better, too!  One way we'll be doing this is by having me guide you through a meditation into a &amp;quot;vortex of expanding love&amp;quot;.  From there, you'll experience how your stories naturally and easily change.  It's a beautiful experience.  Even if you joined us in July, wouldn't you love to do this again?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; will later receive the call-in number. &lt;i&gt;And, please be considerate and remember to let us know if your plans change, so we won’t be waiting for you unnecessarily.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's nothing better than feeling good and having fun! Please join us and stay &amp;quot;connected&amp;quot; by participating in our community's message board discussions and receiving our e-mails (which will include our &amp;quot;Good Vibrations&amp;quot; tips and news). To be able to do so, go to your account, and under &amp;quot;Your Groups&amp;quot;, each one has an &amp;quot;Edit email settings&amp;quot;. Set your preferences there. Hope to hear from you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eagerly looking forward to co-creating with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285287211000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282856542000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's a tele-meetup!  Abrahadabra encore presentation!</name><id>14554093</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285282800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/14554093/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>