<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>35.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us at the Center of Light as modern mystic and Christian Master Teacher, Father Peter Bowes, presents three in depth seminars on how to heal.  Using the wisdom teaching of the ages Father Peter will teach about how to practically heal emotional wounds and grow in spiritual consciousness.   When we are more connected into the great love and light of God, we have the courage and energy to approach painful parts of ourselves; in turn we become more emotionally healthy and have more space for God. When the spiritual healing and emotional healing processes are joined, they create a powerful momentum for transformation of our bodies, minds, hearts and lives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 13, 10 am - 2:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Healer or Agitant? How to be a Spiritual Student&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just prior to healing, the physical body will often trick you into feeling your condition is getting worse. The itch will get worse or the pain will exacerbate, signaling healing is on its way. In the spiritual world, it is the same way, the priest or Teacher, is the healer that may move your condition to a place of increased agitation prior to the healing settling down fully. During this seminar, Father Peter Bowes will guide you through this process so you can fully comprehend and accept the healing process and move through it with more grace.&lt;br /&gt;$35 includes lunch. Bring a friend for free.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350347932000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289226567000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Healer or Agitant? How to be a Spiritual Student - a seminar</name><id>15377700</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289660400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/15377700/</event_url></item>