<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Soldiers Field Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.360067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Doubletree Suites</name><city>Boston</city><id>968618</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is our lineup: 5:30 pm - OPEN NETWORKING - get there early, first 20 to show up get a special opportunity later in the meeting! &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

6:30pm - Meeting will include: &lt;br /&gt;

Market update &lt;br /&gt;

Special Networking opportunity &lt;br /&gt;

Vendor Spotlights &lt;br /&gt;

Timothy O'Leary will talk about the Asset Debt Buying Business, he will give an industry overview, will educate us on the debt buying process and how this down economy creates a unique investing opportunity for you.&amp;nbsp; Kinda like note-buying, just different. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; NIGHTMARE ON DUNLAP STREET! &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Boston AREIA November Monthly Meeting &lt;br /&gt;

Thursday, Nov 17th&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

5:30pm - Networking, 6:30 - meeting &lt;br /&gt;

Doubletree Suites, 400 Soldiers Field Rd, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;

parking always validated &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Bruce Decker's presentation, Nightmare on Dunlap Street, is designed to serve as a cautionary tale for new investors, but seasoned investors should also be able to acquire some nuggets as well. Bruce will recount the details of how he came to own a property which went very, very bad, very, very quickly. He will share the incorrect thinking that led to a poor decision. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

He'll share: &lt;br /&gt;

What he did right &lt;br /&gt;

Investing pitfalls for the new investor:&amp;nbsp; poor thinking patterns &lt;br /&gt;

What to do when you get in over your head &lt;br /&gt;

What he learned from the experience and what he's still investing in real estate &lt;br /&gt;

Bruce Decker grew up in a home that preached, "Stay in school, get good grades, get a good job, and they'll take care of you" - solidly entrenched in the "E" quadrant of the Cash Flow Quadrant. Bruce followed his parent's advice, and became a successful electrical engineer and eventually re-invented himself as a software engineer as microprocessors became popular. After raising two boys who are currently serving their country on active duty, he and his wife noticed that the old saw wasn't cutting it, and so they decided they needed to start thinking about investing for their retirement. Bruce started reading books by Robert Kiyosaki, and in December of 2006, went to the Boston Wealth Expo to hear him and Donald Trump speak. In July of 2007, with much fear and trepidation, Bruce bought his first investment property on Dunlap St. in Dorchester, and the nightmare was on. &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

Bruce lives in the Seacoast region of New Hampshire with his wife, Holly. He is a part-time real estate investor, which he does while building an engineering service business and teaching at the Wentworth Institute of Technology in Boston. Bruce is a member of the New England, Boston, and New Hampshire REIAs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321640230000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>NIGHTMARE ON DUNLAP STREET!</why><group><who>Serious Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonreia</urlname><id>358354</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Real Estate Networking/Education Meeting in Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>93</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320946714000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston AREIA meeting TONIGHT</name><id>lpnmqyppbwb</id><headcount>70</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321569000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonreia/events/40697492/</event_url></item>