<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a great opportunity to revive our community of Tantrikas in the southern NH and Massachusetts area!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These monthly&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Tantra Together &lt;/strong&gt;gatherings&amp;nbsp;are an opportunity to connect with yourself and others who are on a similar personal growth path. Come and renew your connection to Tantra practices -- for yourself and with others -- as together we consciously create more love in the world, heal what is needed and have fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join in breathing, meditation, yoga and more in the presence of other divine beings in a safe and sacred space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beginners are welcome. Meet new friends and leave feeling peaceful, open, and joyful!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover how to truly experience new levels of pleasure in your life. This ANCIENT and REVOLUTIONARY work will teach you powerful tools that will allow you access to your own BLISS and JOY!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DETAILS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* We are meeting at The Watertown Center, 22 Mt. Auburn Street, Watertown, MA (there's plenty of parking on the street and in the back lot!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please arrive at 5:30 pm as we will start right at 6 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Workshop will end at 8 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please bring $20 in cash to pay for the workshop&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please wear comfortable clothing and something colorful and celebratory&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please let your friends know and bring them along!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come right up the stairs!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299465153000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Anything healing and fun is completely worthwhile and at the top of my list!</why><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297890375000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra Together:  Your Authentic Self</name><id>16591337</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299366000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/16591337/</event_url></item>