<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The presence of the majesty of our natural world can unleash feelings that come from deep sources within us. These enchanted and spiritual moments often lead to a refreshment of the soul and to unforgettable memories. Numerous individuals from a universal spectrum of humanity have described such experiences, termed collectively &amp;quot;Nature mysticism.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hunter's Trance explores the phenomenon of nature mysticism from the perspectives of the recorded experiences of outdoors people and others; the increasing knowledge of our psychic and biological roots; the theoretical and experimental studies by neuroscientists; and the thoughts of philosophers and psychologists such as William James. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can this inherent spiritual power help us along a path toward curbing the widely acknowledged threat of global environmental disaster? Our ancient bond with wild nature is threatened by the ever-increasing urbanization of the world population and human alienation from fellow life. As Stephen Jay Gould has said, however, we will fight to save only what we love. Thus we are in danger of losing our source of spiritual and material nurture, our wilderness, and, to a great extent, our present quality of life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No book can provide a magic solution to this dilemma, but The Hunter?s Trance raises our awareness of the importance of our spiritual relationship to this Earth, while showing that all life on Earth must be part of any rational search to resolve our environmental crisis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carl François von Essen was born in 1926 and raised in Northern California. After medical studies in California and Sweden, he practiced and taught in the United States, India, and Switzerland and served the World Health Organization in Sri Lanka and Zimbabwe. Throughout a long professional career spanning the globe, he devoted available time to exploring the natural world and pursuing his passion for angling. He is also the author of The Revenge of the Fishgod: Angling Adventures around the World. Carl von Essen now lives in Cambridge, Massachusetts, with his wife, the Jungian psychoanalyst Manisha Roy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195776440000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195345269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hunter's Trance: Nature, Spirit &amp; Ecology (Reading)</name><id>6761207</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195603200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/6761207/</event_url></item>