<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Lansdowne Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.247.1222</phone><name>The Lansdowne Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>1088408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094957</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have some books that you enjoyed and want to share with someone else? Or perhaps you have some books that you don't plan on reading. Want to get some new books for free? Join us for dinner and book swap. The Pub will also be providing our group with complimentary appetizers and a private room for our group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we will be swapping books. You can bring as many books with you as you would like. Each member swaps for the same number of books that he/she brought (ex. bring two books, take two books home). Please note that once you swap books, your original books will NOT be returned to you. Please use the following guidelines when choosing books to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Books must be in excellent condition (paperback or hardcover)- without tears, stains, writing inside or other damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No textbooks, magazines, teen/children's books or encyclopedias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book swap is optional- you can still come and have fun with our group! Each guest pays for their own food/drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I must give the venue an accurate headcount, so only sign up if you can definitely attend. If your plans change, please update your RSVP as soon as possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you for a fun night!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the private room on the left.  Please call/text Catherine at 774 232 0000 if you have trouble finding us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363063761000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360536178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and Book Swap with Comp Apps at Lansdowne Pub</name><id>103990592</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361923200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/103990592/</event_url></item>