<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360256</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>702-280-3583</phone><name>Evan's Place</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1168917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085655</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Rumor has it that my 11th floor apartment at 100 Memorial Drive has one of the best views of the Boston 4th of July fireworks display in the whole city. I don't have a big apartment, but since I also don't have any family here in Boston I decided to open my place up to a select few (those who RSVP first) who would like to hang out with godless heathens while avoiding the crowds on the riverfront. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you were planning on going to see the fireworks on the riverfront anyway, then this is an opportunity you don't want to miss out on. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space is limited so only RSVP if you will definitely be coming! I reserve the right to make room on the RSVP list by booting people that have a bad track record and don't confirm the reservation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alcohol is welcome (hint: I like white wine). I will have chips and stuff for those who want it, but you should definitely BYOB or anything else you might want to lighten the mood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The events is scheduled starting at 8pm, but the fireworks don't start till 1030. Don't plan to drive because parking will be scarce. There is easy access from the red line (Kendell Square). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call me at 702-280-3583 before coming because the concierge will not let anybody in (especially on this day) unless you have the name and apartment number of the guest you are seeing.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S. I seldom check the email that I have linked to meetup, so you won't have much luck contacting me through this medium.  If you prefer to email me, you can use trustyatheist@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>4427039</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278341170000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277600864000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston riverfront fireworks (exclusive view)</name><id>13921573</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278288000000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/13921573/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/d/global_9053837.jpeg</photo_url></item>