<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>24.9500007629</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello this is Anthony J Pasquale Master Networking Professional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come have coffee,muffins and such on us, take notes meet some great folks who know this business well!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I truly love this business! It is the way to change your life. Unfortunitly sometimes your left holding "The Bag" and you just are not sure what to do to make this work. Well I want you to know that I am on a mission to teach people how to do this business right. AJP&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;span&gt;The Three Most Powerful Words In The English Language "Yes! I can Do This" Learning to network like a professional! Learn the secrets of how to fill a room. How to develop CONFIDENCE, Learn the Professional way of creating interest in your business, Learn how to create a team!&amp;nbsp;So you will experience wealth in your Profession!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look it all starts with investing in yourself. You need a place that is objective from your business group, your company or your Up or &lt;span&gt;Downline&lt;/span&gt;. Somewhere that you can practice the art of Professional Networking for your business, how to prospect the right people, form what you are going to say without tripping over your own words, WHERE DO YOU GO TO BUILD THE CONFIDENCE YOU NEED? Here, with me and my group of experts who have been doing this for years and with success. Now it's your turn to be successful! Come join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what we are going over for 1 hr 30mins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creating a "Why I. &lt;span&gt;Q&lt;/span&gt;. that will give you the power to do what is necessary to become successful!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to create the GREATEST fear busters so you can build your business everyday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn how to create the daily,weekly,monthly and yearly plan to help you stay organized and ready for wealth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to create MOMENTUM so in no time at all you are on the road to success!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creating a fail Safe Follow Up System.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...And the best part, how to present your business to anyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now look, your going to read this and you are either going to pass this by or you will do what The Successful do.... They Do, they learn, they create a plan with others and work it with a mastermind group, well here it is YOUR GROUP outside of your company, your business, your &lt;span&gt;upline&lt;/span&gt;. This is the place where you will practice, learn and put into action YOUR PLAN with Professionals!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I am only doing this with 10 people, it doesn't matter what company you are from or what &lt;span&gt;MLM&lt;/span&gt;, direct sales program, network marketing group,&amp;nbsp;This is&amp;nbsp;will change your business forever. How do I know this, well this was done to me. I was coached by a very successful person and I am passing this along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of this workshop I am going to setup a Mastermind Group of 10 people out of the 10 that I think will get the BEST out of a 12 week program of coaching. Good Luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself: Am I better off than when I join my_________, and if not why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This could be the MasterMind Group you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting Monday Morning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;October 24th 8:15am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$24.95,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Includes coffee, muffins and such.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Printed Materials&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ideal Business Center&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20 Locist Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Danvers, Mass 01923&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All The Best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ready to Create Wealth through Network Marketing !!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319462578000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316544403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bring a willness to be Successful and a notebook!</name><id>34295972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319458500000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/34295972/</event_url></item>