<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Purgatory chasm is a State Park  In Sutton, MA.  There are picinic tables and charcoal grills.  Either pack a lunch, or we can stop at the pizza/sub shop just up the street.  You may even want to invite your families to come; there is a playground for the children.  For the adventurous, there is a 1/4 mile long hike over the boulders in the chasm - &lt;b&gt;wear good boots&lt;/b&gt;.  Or, take a gentle stroll along any of their other trails.  (Bring bug spray, just in case.)  &lt;br /&gt;     The ride will be all secondary roads. I would like to meet at the 7-11 gas station, on the corner of Rts 106 and 138 in Easton, just a little ways north on 138 from the Mobil station off 495 at exit 8.  It is also just west of Route 24 at exit 16  (the route 24 exit closest to Bettencourts). We will leave there at 9.  The next pick-up stop will be at the &lt;b&gt;Stop &amp;amp; Shop&lt;/b&gt; on Main St ( &lt;b&gt;on Rt 140&lt;/b&gt;) in Foxboro just east of Route 1, and just west of I-95.  We would arrive there @  9:30.  I expect that we'll arrive at Purgatory @ 10:45 - 11 ish, depending on how long we're at the sub shop.  Weathermen say it will be a hot one, so also bring plenty of water.  And, of course, there will be an ice-cream stop afterwards!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary H </member_name><member_id>8947310</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283196999000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Bikers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>South-Shore-Women-on-Wheels</urlname><id>1366699</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>South Shore Women On Wheels®</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266608434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Purgatory Picnic</name><id>12649481</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283085000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/South-Shore-Women-on-Wheels/events/12649481/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/b/global_9177195.jpeg</photo_url></item>