<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Kneeland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.349878</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 426-6397</phone><name>Splash Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>1171690</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>***BEGINNING FRIDAY MAY 21 BOSTON HAPPY HOUR MEMBERS ARE INVITED BY BOSTON EVENT GUIDE AND THE RED SOX NATIVES, TO A ROOF DECK PARTY AT SPLASH ON THE THIRD FRIDAY AND FIRST THURSDAY OF EACH MONTH THROUGH SEPTEMBER***  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have arranged a special Happy Hour/Roof Deck Party at Splash Ultra Lounge for Boston Happy Hour members. This is an amazing venue with a plush lounge and one of Boston's best and largest roof decks with cabanas, complimentary hors d'oeuvres and billiards. A perfect place to hang out and enjoy a few drinks on a warm night, watch the Sox game at 7pm or sit inside in our reserved section. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join the Red Sox Natives and other groups for a Rush Hour at Splash Ultra Lounge from 5 pm to 9 pm on Friday, May 21. This is one of Boston's newest hotspots with up to 4 hours of complimentary food buffet and cash bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is free for those who RSVP here and  to www.bostoneventguide.com/rushhour  &lt;a href="http://www.bostoneventgiude.com/rushhour" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get added to the guest list. Please follow these directions. Invite friends, guests, co-workers and groups. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Splash has a Dress Code: Dress to impress, no sneakers, t-shirts or hats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ask the hostess for the Red Sox Natives reserved section when checking in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All guests must be 21 plus with proper ID. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearest MBTA stops are Red Line at South Station or Orange Line at Chinatown.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metered street parking is available in the area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valet parking is $20.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember to maintain your bar tab or pay cash for your drinks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.bostoneventguide.com&lt;a href="http://www.bostoneventguide.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.splash-boston.com&lt;a href="http://www.splash-boston.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.redsoxnatives.com&lt;a href="http://redsoxnatives.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274751184000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273117313000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rush Hour at Splash Sponsored by Boston Event Guide and Red Sox Natives </name><id>13400732</id><headcount>33</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274475600000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/13400732/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/8/global_6854760.jpeg</photo_url></item>