<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;CHIME in from 9 - 10 pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; &amp;amp; the Phone # will be sent to you&lt;br /&gt;*Note: This is a long distance call; not toll-free.&lt;br /&gt;****************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;Last Friday at our Celebration gathering, we were fortunate to have the opportunity to enjoy the presentation by &lt;b&gt;Yasuhiko Genku Kimura&lt;/b&gt; on cultivating passion, vision, and the mastery of life through the creative act of &amp;quot;authentic thinking&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are delighted that Kimura-san is able to join us tomorrow on a special TELE-Meetup to&lt;br /&gt;- share more with us about the creative act of &amp;quot;authentic thinking&amp;quot; in relationship to Law Of Attraction and other Universal Laws and&lt;br /&gt;- answer questions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Yasuhiko Genku Kimura&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.via-visioninaction.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yasuhiko creates &amp;amp; leads transformational programs around the world using his Zen-like Socratic method of philosophical inquiry. He is widely recognized for his unique ability to integrate advanced Western scientific thought with intuitive Eastern spiritual insight to bring about radical and lasting transformation in individuals and organizations. His numerous writings and seminars are acclaimed for their originality and spiritual depth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yasuhiko is a transhumanist philosopher, an ordained Zen Buddhist priest &amp;amp; scholar. He is considered one of the most original, visionary thinkers in the field of integral and evolutionary philosophy. He is a creator and leader of transformational programs; consultant-advisor to leaders in business, science, and cultural organizations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for us all to meet an enlightening and inspiring visionary and thinker who has dedicated his life to creating heaven on earth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***********************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;WOW&amp;quot; comments from folks who were at the celebration:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yasuhiko is an amazing presenter, knowledgeable and easy to follow.&lt;br /&gt;Information he shared was valuable knowledge which needs to be practiced daily&lt;br /&gt;to live a balance healthy happy life. &lt;i&gt;- Michelle Gallant&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What an inspiring evening of philosophy and performance in a beautiful space&lt;br /&gt;with interesting people! - &lt;i&gt;Mark Hoffman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234312055000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233749842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special TELE-Meetup with Yasuhiko Genku Kimura</name><id>9670498</id><headcount>36</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233885600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/9670498/</event_url></item>