<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let’s kick off the warm season with a “grab a date” party at the Red Sky Restaurant and Lounge in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.redskybost..." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redskybost...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the skinny:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grab an ex or friend of the opposite sex that you think is “datable” or two or three. Maybe you didn’t hit it off with this person but someone else may. We have a private area at Red Sky with dancing, food available to order off the menu, and yes, a few bars. If you don’t happen to know someone just ask a person at work, the gym or on one of your meetup groups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are otherwise attached-bring your mate we don’t discriminate…we are all out to meet new people on every level. If you can't find a guy/gal to &amp;quot;grab&amp;quot;-bring a friend or just yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a joint event with 4 different groups so please only RSVP for one. Tickets are $5 pp. payable via paypal (please include your full name [and guest if you pay for both] when you pay in the comment area) and $10 at the entrance by cash only (inside the restaurant).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Online payments can be made at: www.paypal.com &lt;br /&gt;Payable to beantownevents@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;Remember to put your full name in the comments area and you will be added to the list .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have the entire back area of Red Sky to mingle and meet all sorts of new people. Do not RSVP until you have purchased your ticket(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://singles.meetup.com/1169/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a Lei-the private party will be in the back area-just ask</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243811172000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242663188000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grab-a-date party at Red Sky!</name><id>10437523</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243638000000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10437523/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/9/global_8691625.jpeg</photo_url></item>