<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2800 Lafayette Rd.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.028616</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.430.0222</phone><name>Jumpgate : The Science Fiction/Fantasy Store</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>914137</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.789766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a LMM Edition (Last Minute Meetup) Sunday @ Noon Meetup!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP by Tonight. I will cancel tomorrow around &lt;u&gt;10am&lt;/u&gt; if we do not have enough players. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Need at least 2 others.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be able to play a few (1-3) rounds of this fantastic game that I just picked up. Adding some advanced rules as we go. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There can only be &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;3 spots&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; open so RSVP fast! This is going to be a small group with just the one game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description &amp;amp; Photo from BGG (Boardgamegeek.com):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;You are specialists at the CDC/Atlanta where you watch several virulent diseases break out simultaneously all over the world. The team mission is to prevent a world-wide pandemic outbreak, treating hotspots while researching cures for each of the four plagues before they get out of hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players must plan their strategy to mesh their specialist's strengths before the diseases overwhelm the world. For example, the Operations Specialist can build research stations, which are needed to find cures for the diseases. The Scientist needs only 4 cards of a particular disease to cure it instead of the normal 5. But the diseases are breaking out fast and time is running out: the team must try to stem the tide of infection in diseased areas while developing cures. If disease spreads uncontrolled, the players all lose. If they can cure all four diseases, they win.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The board shows earth with some big population centers. On each turn a player can use four actions to travel, cure, discover and build. Cards are used for this but the deck also contains Epidemics...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions let me know, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Wayne</member_name><member_id>1411667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266945404000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>sagesofrpg</urlname><id>747276</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth, NH / Seacoast Boardgames Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266689008000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Learn Pandemic! LMM Edition (Last Minute Meetup)</name><id>12656475</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266771600000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sagesofrpg/events/12656475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/f/e/global_13207534.jpeg</photo_url></item>