<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boston Film Screening and Live Show: Bombino &amp;amp; Agadez&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Agadez, the Music and the Rebellion &amp;ndash; a film that features the music of  the extraordinary Tuareg musician &amp;lsquo;Bombino&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; will be playing at the  Brattle Cinema in Cambridge on Tuesday, July 12 at 7:30.  Bombino will  be playing a concert at the Brighton Music Hall on July 14!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://zerogravityfilms.com/"&gt;Learn more at Zero Gravity Films&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/3/9/event_29452281.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Agadez, The Music And The Rebellion, documentary film-maker Ron  Wyman has done an excellent job of not only depicting life in the desert  of Niger without romanticizing or sentimentalizing it, but showing what  people are doing to preserve it in the face of increasingly difficult  odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow his camera into one of the harshest environments on earth and  meet the people who not only live there, but cherish the freedom it  brings them. You will also meet the remarkable young musician, Omara  &amp;ldquo;Bombino&amp;rdquo; Moctar, whose story of exile and return is typical for his  generation, but whose talent is unique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Descendants of the Berber tribes of North Africa Bombino&amp;rsquo;s people were  named Tuareg, Arabic for rebels, for their initial resistance to  adopting the Muslim faith, but refer to themselves as the Kel Tamsheq  after their language. The life of the Kel Tamsheq is not easy, but it is  the life they have chosen to live and desire to keep on living in as  much as the modern world will allow them to do so.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet at the box office at before the show.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310526685000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1307239875000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AGADEZ, THE MUSIC AND THE REBELLION documentary</name><id>21003591</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310511600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/21003591/</event_url></item>