<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 Audubon Way</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03032</zip><lat>42.983557</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603) 668-2045</phone><name>Massabesic Audubon Center</name><city>Auburn </city><id>762116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.365221</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Get a close-up look at a live Bald Eagle, Turkey Vulture and other birds of prey in this exceptional presentation by Tom Ricardi, a licensed rehabilitator and wildlife biologist. You rarely get a chance to be this close to some of these phenomenal birds! Learn about the great work done by the Massachusetts Bird of Prey Rehabilitation Facility, which cares for injured birds and operates a successful captive-breeding program. Tom's groundbreaking work with Bald Eagles has resulted in captive-bred bald eagles reproducing in the wild and captive-bred chicks being adopted into wild nests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was in contact with the Audubon this morning (11/6) and they have 15 tickets available for the 11:00AM show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;To attend the show &lt;u&gt;You Must Call The Audubon&lt;/u&gt; at (603) 668-2045 ASAP to reserve a place at the 11:00AM Show!  The fee is $10.00 and they will accept a credit card. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meetup Group can not be involved with the payment and refund policy.  Inquire with the NH Audubon when you call about their policy.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can meet for breakfast at 9:30AM in Chester, NH at the Ye Olde Post Restaruant, view the show at 11:00AM and hike the three mile trail at noon to complete the afternoon.  The last time we hiked this trail we saw our own Birds of Pray, a beautiful Osprey made several passes while we were at the observation hut. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is listed as a family event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;NH RT 93 North to exit 5 State Hwy 28 (Rockingham RD)&lt;br /&gt;Take a right at the end of ramp&lt;br /&gt;go 300 feet and take a left turn onto Auburn Road (by the Poor Boy Restaurant)&lt;br /&gt;Go 2 miles then continue on Beaver Brook Rd&lt;br /&gt;Turn left at Londonderry Turnpike (By-Pass 28)&lt;br /&gt;go 2.6 miles and right turn at Spofford Rd&lt;br /&gt;Aububon Way is on the left, we will meet at the NH Aububon Lake Massabesic Audubon Center&lt;br /&gt;26 Audubon Way&lt;br /&gt;Auburn, NH 03032&lt;br /&gt;603-668-2045&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Ye Old Post Restaurant in Chester, NH:&lt;br /&gt;NH RT 93 to exit 4, State Hwy 102&lt;br /&gt;East on RT 102 toward Derry&lt;br /&gt;Travel three miles and at the traffic circle, take the 3rd right off the circle, Chester Rd, (this is a continuation of RT 102 East)&lt;br /&gt;Continue to follow RT 102 6 miles from the traffic circle and at the intersection of RT102 and RT 121 (blinking yellow light) take a left&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Ye Olde Post&amp;quot; is on the left next to the hardware store.&lt;br /&gt;We will be 15 min. to Lake Massabesic from there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258819733000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256654003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Birds of Prey Show and a Hike at Lake Massabesic Aububon Auburn, NH</name><id>11722837</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258214400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11722837/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/3/global_11666131.jpeg</photo_url></item>