<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>124 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02061</zip><lat>42.170750</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 878-7850</phone><name>Cherrywoods Barbeque</name><city>Norwell</city><id>285383</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.877174</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Jambalaya and a crawfish pie and a filet gumbo; Cause tonight I'm a-gonna see my cher-a-mi-o...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Okay, please excuse Mike - He gets excited whenever he finds a way to work a song lyric in!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But all kidding aside, &lt;a href="http://cherrywoodsbbq.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Cherrywoods Barbeque&lt;/a&gt; in Norwell bills itself as an &amp;quot;authentic New Orleans-style barbeque restaurant&amp;quot;, and does indeed offer jambalaya and gumbo, as well as crawfish prepared at least three different ways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for an intimate lunch at noon on Saturday, June 9th as we broaden our culinary horizons once again by exploring the cuisine of the Southeast. The food at Cherrywoods is both tasty and affordable: Only three selections hit the $20.00 barrier, and even those are available in smaller portions for smaller appetites or budgets. Most entrees come with your choice of two side orders (called &amp;quot;Lagniappe&amp;quot;), which include things like &amp;quot;dirty&amp;quot; rice and BBQ baked beans. There are also good selections of appetizers (&amp;quot;Mardi Gras&amp;quot;) and Sandwiches (&amp;quot;Po' Boys&amp;quot;), plus a few Southern dessert specialties. The menu is online, for those who wish to peek.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cherrywoods is fairly small establishment in a strip mall on Route 53. Since seating is limited, we are capping the group size at 10 diners. If you've got a hankerin' for fritters or a cravin' for crawfish, RSVP today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, June 9 @ 12:00PM&lt;br /&gt;124 Washington St (Route 53)&lt;br /&gt;Norwell, MA 02061&lt;br /&gt;781 878-7850&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: Max of 10&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 8:00 PM on Thursday, June 7th. (At this time the Organizers will close registrations at the current number of Yes RSVP's or they will set a maximum which will allow a couple more people to RSVP up until the morning of the event. Please note if you RSVP after this deadline you may not be on the attendee list if the Organizers are unable to print an updated list the day of the event.)&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer: Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we reach the maximum we will go to a wait list. Here's how it will work. &lt;br /&gt;1. RSVP No and state in your comments &amp;quot;if a space opens up I would like to attend&amp;quot; and include the DATE of your RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;2. As space opens up please allow those who are on the waitlist to update their RSVP to Yes and follow step 1.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cherrywoods is located on Route 53 in Norwell, just a few minutes from Exit 14 from Route 3. To reach it from Route 3, get off at Exit 14 and and head east toward Route 53. This will bring you to a busy intersection at a traffic light (Queen Anne's Corner). Go right (south) onto Route 53, keeping the mall where Hannaford's Supermarket is located to your right. You will quickly pass 53 South (another restaurant) on your right, and shortly thereafter Hight St will bear off to the right, at which point you need to be careful to keep going straight and remain on Route 53. Just after High St you will pass Marsh's Liquor Store on your right. The next businesses on your right are in a small strip mall. Cherrywoods is the building farthest to the left in this mall.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312746541000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1179628234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Barbeque for Lunch!</name><id>5797360</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1181404800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/5797360/</event_url></item>