<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>153 North St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01568</zip><lat>42.215515</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-529-2000</phone><name>Sweetwilliam Farm</name><city>Upton</city><id>1299243</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.621009</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL NIGHT THIS FRIDAY! &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Enjoy a fun, relaxing evening listening to the music of Clara Kebabian, electric violinist. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come any time from 6 pm on and enjoy the daylight before the sun goes down.  Music starts at 7 pm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great event! Sit outside and listen to great music.  The farm is set on top of a hill with great views and a peaceful, serene feeling.  You will also enjoy browsing their quaint country store. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may bring your own food and beverages (alcohol is allowed). &lt;br /&gt;Great food is also available for sale: burgers, dogs, pizza and ice cream. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a chair or use one of theirs (if you get there early enough) &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to bring a sweater - it gets chilly as soon as that sun goes down. &lt;br /&gt;Sorry - no dogs allowed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no charge for this event, but donations are appreciated for the entertainment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Directions, click here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sweetwilliamfarm.biz/id5.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sweetwilli...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;My cell is 508-381-1529. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about the entertainment:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Clara Kebabian - began playing violin in the classical tradition steeped in the standards of solo and orchestral repertoire but her passion always lay in contemporary styles. Since 2000 she has performed nationally and internationally in a variety of genres.  Her festival performances include SXSW, Muzine Festival (Greece), DUMBO Art Under the Bridge, and the Boston Cyberarts Festival.  She also enjoys teaching violin to students of all ages and levels.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacki</member_name><member_id>6777705</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286745383000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285418647000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Sunset Concert at Sweetwilliam Farm - Upton</name><id>14890489</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286575200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/14890489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/5/global_17134773.jpeg</photo_url></item>