<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The word on the street is....... if you are interested in raw food or you are already a raw foodie this is the place to be!  There is no other place you can go and have incredible raw food,  meet some really cool people of all ages....  and learn that in order to eat healthy you don't have to just chew on lettuce leaves.  Our numbers are growing by leaps and bounds.......which is wonderful!!!  This may be one of the last meetups at my house.  I can only hold so many inside the walls.  It has been a great summer using the yard!  We can talk about options at the meetup.  The meetup will go on ...where is the question.....I am so proud of this group because so many people have really been taking the time to make some incredible food!  I am also so proud of our brand new members who don't know what the heck to bring and come anyway.  It is tough walking into a situation that you know is going to be good for you but you have no clue what it is all about...a salad is always good....fruit or green.  The only thing that I ask is please make sure it is organic.  &lt;br /&gt;Make a Dish enough for 6 to 8 people.  That way everyone can have a &amp;quot;taste&amp;quot;.  Can't wait to see all my old and new friends!  Cheers!  KO&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>KO Bisson</member_name><member_id>4565632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248626000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawfood-ManchNH</urlname><id>1292928</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Food Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252109208000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manchester Raw Vegan Pot Luck!  October Meetup</name><id>11293348</id><headcount>39</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254524400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawfood-ManchNH/events/11293348/</event_url></item>