<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Clearing your Path for Success&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;with Joanna Scaparotti&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a transformation process that every practitioner has to go through, like a caterpillar becoming a butterfly, to shift the energy around her business so she can attract (paying!) clients who love to work with her.  Clearing your Path for Success is a step by step process through this transformation, and we will look at some of the key techniques in the program and how established practitioners can use them to deepen their authenticity and fulfillment from their current practice. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joanna Scaparotti is a Reiki Master Practitioner, Teacher &amp;amp; Coach that helps practitioners find the courage and confidence to experience a fulfilling practice. Her passion is creating mindful entrepreneurship and soul-centered authentic businesses in the wellness industry that seamlessly integrate values such as abundance, service and wellness with the freedom of flexible lifestyles and the benefits of creative community collaboration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We begin with a potluck and networking time at 11:30 am.  The presentation begins at 12:30 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let us know what you are bringing to the potluck when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will welcome you at the front door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266190390000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257455980000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name><id>11805768</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265992200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/11805768/</event_url></item>