<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>425 Congress St</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.658363</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Parish Unitarian Universilist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>515380</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.257900</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>donation</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is a six week course for all levels of meditators, from the seasoned to the true blue beginner, and will run from 6:00 to 8:00pm. The course includes pre-recorded audio instructions, discussion and feedback, and (gulp) homework - no worries, we’re not grading. We’ve used these recordings before and find them to be clear, insightful, and well measured. The teacher of the course is Gil Fronsdal, principal meditation teacher at the Insight Meditation Center in Redwood, California. You can attend one or all of the session although there is a progression of learning and we encourage all six to get the full sense of mindfulness practice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s a brief description from the website - &lt;a href="http://audiodharma.org/" target="_blank"&gt;audiodharma.org&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 “At the heart of insight meditation is the practice of mindfulness, the cultivation of clear, stable and non-judgmental awareness. While mindfulness practice can be highly effective in helping bring calm and clarity to the pressures of daily life, it is also a spiritual path that gradually dissolves the barriers to the full development of our wisdom and compassion. During the six-week introductory course, the basic instructions in insight meditation are given sequentially, each week building on the previous one. The first week focuses on the basics of meditation and on mindfulness of breathing. The second week discusses mindfulness of the body and expands the area of attention to include all our physical experiences. The third week introduces mindfulness of emotions, the fourth week mindfulness of thinking, the fifth week mindfulness of mind, and the sixth week focuses on the role of mindfulness in daily life and in deepening one’s spiritual life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course will be facilitated by Tom Cannon, licensed counselor at Community Counseling Center, and Kerry Dunn, Professor of Social Work at UNE.  We join the group both as facilitators and learners, and our intention is to co-create an inspiring and safe environment to learn from our teacher Gil as well as each other. Following completion of the course, the Monday meetings will continue, providing an opportunity for us to hear from other teachers and share the joys and challenges of mindfulness practice. We hope you can join us in this exploration and look forward to meeting you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location TBA</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>TomC</member_name><member_id>7931343</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kerry Dunn</member_name><member_id>12146459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362446046000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357931644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Introduction to Mindfulness - Last of Six Week Course</name><id>qptgkfyrfbgb</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362438000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/99283042/</event_url></item>