<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>38.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The organizer of the Boston Ethnic Dining Meetup (Al) contacted me wanting to know if our group would be interested in a group event. I said, of course!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be visiting Boston's Italian North End for some authentic cuisine at Dom's Restaurant (www.domsboston.com). Dinner will be family style, and we will ask everyone to pay a set price ($38 including tax and tip), which includes appetizers and the main course.  PLEASE BRING CASH, as we get a discount for cash only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the menu we have selected:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizers: salad and mozzarella with proscuitto and tomatoes&lt;br /&gt;Main courses:  fish with puttanesca sauce, chicken Sienese, veal Parmagiana, and ravioli.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They also have a good wine list, and excellent desserts can be found at any number of Italian bakeries in the area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few of us will be heading to Boston earlier that day to enjoy the city for a bit before dinner. If you are interested in this, please let me know in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**PLEASE RSVP YOUR FINAL RESPONSE BY TUESDAY, SEPTEMBER 5 so that we can make the appropriate reservation.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dom's has been around for over 30 years and has received excellent reviews from Zagat's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.domsboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.domsboston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.domsboston...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155590132000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Taste of Italy--Dom's in BOSTON's North End</name><id>5077435</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1157925600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/5077435/</event_url></item>