<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the good map for the area: &lt;a href="http://www.leominster-ma.gov/pdf/geocaching-maps-2009/lh_monoosnoc_middle.pdf"&gt;http://www.leominster-ma.gov/pdf/geocaching-maps-2009/lh_monoosnoc_middle.pdf&lt;/a&gt; If there's a problem with that, if you google monoosnock trail middle section you can download the pdf. This hike connects with the Monoosnock Trail, a 10 mile ridge trail in Leominster, of all places.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Claude Maddox organized a hike here a few days ago, and it was great! Carol and myself haven't discussed this hike in detail, though I have to work in the afternoon so I want to be back to my car by 1pm the latest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Monoosnock and surrounding trails are varying and interesting. Up and down hills, around turns, past old quarries, and so on. While the summit is in the middle of the woods, a lovely view of Mt. Wachusett is just on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mary Albertson Trailhead is located on Lake Road in Leominster. While there is no marker or sign, it is easy to find.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 12 to the center of downtown Leominster. Go West on West Street. Take your third left, which is Pond Street. (There is a white building with large parking lot on the corner which houses the Leominster Senior Center and Leominster Veteran's services.) Pond Street crosses Lake Road; turn right onto Lake Road headed West.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a ways, look for a horse farm/Richard's Luxury Kennels on your right. It has white-fenced pastures. Very shortly, you'll see the opening to the trail on your right. If you pass a small reservoir on your left, you've gone too far. You can see the pump building from the trailhead. We can park 4 or 5 cars on the side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If going East on Lake Road, look for two small reservoirs, right in a row, on your right. You will see the trail very shortly on the left side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a white Dodge Stratus, and Carol drives a white Volvo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318786638000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318636180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Monoosnock Hike</name><id>37439542</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318684500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/37439542/</event_url></item>