<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Fellow patriots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are currently at a major turning point in the liberty movement, and I'm asking your help to make sure it turns the right way.  Two pro-liberty candidates have recently sparked significant national attention: Peter Schiff in Connecticut and Rand Paul in Kentucky.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter Schiff is a nationally known and respected financial adviser, and indeed was an economic adviser to the Ron Paul for President campaign.  He says he will run for Senate if he gets significant financial support, so his fans are organizing a major money bomb on August 7.  Their goal is to have 10,000 people donate an average of $100 each, setting a new fundraising record of $1 million for a Senate campaign in a single day.  So far almost 7,000 people have pledged, so the goal is definitely within reach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It would be hard to overstate the importance of making this $1 million goal.  It sets the tone not only for the rest of Peter's race, but for all the pro-liberty races across the country.  A success in Friday's money bomb for Peter Schiff sets the stage for a more successes, like perhaps $1 million for Rand Paul on August 20.  The world is watching, and on Friday we either make a very loud bang, or a very embarrassing splat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I believe the pro-liberty movement today has the clout, the organization, and the sheer numbers to make a difference in the 2010 election.  I believe we can send Ron Paul some friends in Congress.  And I believe we'll show the world on Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This particular turning point is more important than just $100, so I'm maxing out for Peter Schiff.  Will you join me?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please pledge at &lt;a href="http://www.schiffathon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.schiffathon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.schiffatho...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; today, and donate at &lt;a href="http://www.schiffforsenate.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.schiffforsenate.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.schifffors...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on August 7!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you,&lt;br /&gt;John Cunningham&lt;br /&gt;Ron Paul Republican&lt;br /&gt;candidate for the U.S. House of Representatives in 2008&lt;br /&gt;from the Massachusetts 7th Congressional District&lt;br /&gt;www.johncunningham2008.com&lt;br /&gt;campaign@johncunningham2008.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Cunningham</member_name><member_id>1757740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249829725000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249519676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Million dollar money bomb for Peter Schiff</name><id>11046242</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249646400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/11046242/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/b/global_2993979.jpeg</photo_url></item>