<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be a south-to-north rendition of the classic Presidential Range Traverse, done at a fast pace.  The trip entails 24 miles of hiking, along with 9200' of elevation gain.  Starting at the southern end of Crawford Notch and the Webster Cliff Trail, this trip also leaves until last a challenging descent of Mt. Madison.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the length, elevation gain and intended pace, this will be an extremely strenuous hike, and one you should not consider unless you are an experienced hiker in top condition.  To ensure your enjoyment on a compatible hike, we are screening carefully and targeting a very small group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be arriving the afternoon before, in order to spot cars, get to bed early, and start very early in the morning -- well before sunrise.  We will be traveling light, but will carry all the gear necessary to ensure that we are a self-sufficiently safe group: this is a hike, not a run. Depending on conditions, we expect to complete the trip in 12-14 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further details available closer to the trip date.  If signing up, please be sure to answer all 4 of the registration questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RAIN DATE:  Wednesday, June 6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  ANSWERS TO THE RSVP QUESTIONS ARE REQUIRED FOR THOSE WHO WISH TO JOIN THE HIKE.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Exact meetup location tbd</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David (Ped Xing)</member_name><member_id>4566112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338808385000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337976839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Presidential Traverse - Cancelled due to inclement weather</name><id>66353252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338796800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/66353252/</event_url></item>