<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;It is time for the Greater Portland Area to have its own raw meetup!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summer is coming and with all the lush abundance of the farmer's markets we have plenty of raw bounty to enjoy together. Lets create a place to share raw vegan food with each other, share our stories, experience and raw miracles and get to know each other as we begin to join together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;We'll be meeting one Sunday a month at 5PM in Yarmouth Maine (just 10-15 minutes north of Portland off of I 295 between exits 15&amp;amp;17). Ususally it will be on the 3rd Sunday of the month however due to scheduling conflicts  June will be later and July earlier (Yarmouth Clam Fest fall on the 3rd Sunday).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;Please bring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A RAW VEGAN DISH (and ingredient list or full recipe to share)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A plate and/or big bowl, a cup &amp;amp; utensils&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Before Pictures (if you have some that you would like to share)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your open heart &amp;amp; mind&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Voicemail 1-866-625-0082&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the red door on the first floor in the back of the building next to the parking lot. 
We'll have a sign up for RAW MAINE.
It will be obvious, I'll be next to all the beautiful raw food we bring to share with each other!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216012423000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Enjoy yummy raw creations, make connections with others to share excitement, passion and experiences about the raw &amp; living foods lifestyle, get information, find support, most of all HAVE FUN hanging out because you know how awesome raw food is!</why><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>rawmaine</urlname><id>1161576</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Raw Maine: The Way Food Should Be!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211522963000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Maine: The Way Food Should Be! the Maiden Voyage (June Meeting)</name><id>7996937</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214773200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rawmaine/events/7996937/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/0/global_4217936.jpeg</photo_url></item>