<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Littleton Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01886</zip><lat>42.564060</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Westford Regency Hotel</name><city>Westford</city><id>598806</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.431610</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sunday Brunch and a visit to the Butterfly Place...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A reservation for brunch, up to 30 people has been made for Noon at the Westford Regency Hotel, Sunday June 15th. Conveniently located on Route 110 in Westford, the hotel will provide us a room with round tables and the cost will be $19.99 plus 18% gratuity. Menu choices include a lavish display of cheeses, pates, fresh tropical fruits, omelets &amp;amp; waffles made to order, pastries, seafood entrees, carving stations of Roast Sirloin of Beef, fresh ham and turkey, along with a delicious selection of side dishes. A dessert station features a chocolate fountain surrounded by fresh fruit &amp;amp; cookies, cakes and pies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.westfordregency.com/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westfordre...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you reply yes but have a last minute change of plans please change your response asap so others can join this event.&lt;/b&gt; (also I have reserved this on my personal credit card and definitely hope to have 30)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After brunch we will caravan across town to the Butterfly Place located at 120 Tyngsborough Road. As a resident of the village association nearby I can visit for a reduced rate of $5.00 per person....&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you would like to visit the Butterfly Place with us, there is no limit but I will call ahead to confirm that I may bring all of you as my guests.... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.butterflyplace-ma.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.butterflyp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Reservations for our own room are under my name...Sandy!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213718842000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209917312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch and Butterflies...</name><id>7869779</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1213545600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7869779/</event_url></item>