<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clear Conscience Cafe/Harvest Co-Op Market</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>687911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Straight from the polls for our October reading (although we'll have a fall revamping soon and get your new title suggestions out there :-), the Agony and the Ecstasy by Irving stone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://us.penguingroup.com/nf/Book/BookDisplay/0,,0_9780451171351,00.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://us.penguingrou...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(sorry, it was the best I could find:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Celebrating the 500th anniversary of Michelangelo’s David, New American Library releases a special edition of Irving Stone’s classic biographical novel—in which both the artist and the man are brought to life in full. A masterpiece in its own right, this novel offers a compelling portrait of Michelangelo’s dangerous, impassioned loves, and the God-driven fury from which he wrested the greatest art the world has ever known.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As darkness falls earlier and earlier in Harvard yard it saddens me to say we are headed back indoors (although, it's not like we would have stuck it out through snow:-)  Back to the Clear Conscience Cafe in Central Square, a block from the T stop.  This is the mass ave side of the Harvest Co-op, great guys offering organic fare and, if we're lucky and early enough, couches.&lt;br /&gt;  Occasionally their popularity is so vast, there is no room for our humble bookclub, and we are forced to the more sterile chair and table environment of Au Bon Pain, kitty corner and a few blocks down in Central square heading in the Harvard direction (684 Mass Ave).  I'll throw out my cell number a few days prior, so if you don't see the book on a table or our familiar faces, give me a buzz and I'll give ya our locale (which might be &amp;quot;running late&amp;quot; :-)&lt;br /&gt;  With the great limitations of the Cafe's I do ask that you keep your RSVP's accurate.  I try to limit the number to 20, so please be respectful of your fellow readers and open up your spot if your plans change.  Thanks!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Happy reading!&lt;br /&gt;  Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255043122000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252508392000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: The Agony and the Ecstasy by Irving Stone</name><id>11327860</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254870000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/11327860/</event_url></item>