<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Tremont street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353199</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(888) 262-4386</phone><name>AMC Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>895111</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064232</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ok.  After the long year that they have been saying they are going to have an IMAX theater at the Tremont St Theater it is going to happen for Iron Man 2.   So let's check it out and see if it is as cool as the other imax theaters.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although sequels are not usually as good as the first film, the first one was so much fun that I am willing to take a chance on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show time is 6:15.   But we are going to want to start gathering around 5:30 and head in a half hour before the show starts to grab seats.   &lt;b&gt;An alert member notified me that I made a mistake and the movie is showing in Theater 2 Downstairs, so we should meet downstairs.  I will be near the bottom of the escalator, at first.  But as soon as they start letting people in to line up, we should get in line.   Please note it is going to be crazy and noisy. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I&lt;b&gt; strongly recommend buying your tickets in advance.  Remember, if you use Fandango, they have separate links for the Imax vs. the regular viewing of the movie.  &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If for some reason you miss the group before the show, we will hang out in the hallway for a bit to discuss the movie, allow people to visit restrooms, and to get a head count of those who want to go out after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie Details:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iron Man 2Release Date: May 7, 2010 (conventional theaters and IMAX) &lt;br /&gt;Studio: Paramount Pictures, Marvel Studios &lt;br /&gt;Director: Jon Favreau &lt;br /&gt;Screenwriter: Justin Theroux &lt;br /&gt;Starring: Robert Downey Jr., Gwyneth Paltrow, Don Cheadle, Jon Favreau, Mickey Rourke, Sam Rockwell, Samuel L. Jackson, Scarlett Johansson, Garry Shandling, John Slattery, Kate Mara, Clark Gregg, Olivia Munn &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 (for sequences of intense action violence and some language) &lt;br /&gt;Official Website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ironmanmovie.marvel.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://ironmanmovie.m...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Summary: Paramount Pictures and Marvel Entertainment present the highly anticipated sequel to the blockbuster film based on the legendary Marvel Super Hero &amp;quot;Iron Man,&amp;quot; reuniting director Jon Favreau and Oscar nominee Robert Downey Jr. In &amp;quot;Iron Man 2,&amp;quot; the world is aware that billionaire inventor Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.) is the armored Super Hero Iron Man. Under pressure from the government, the press and the public to share his technology with the military, Tony is unwilling to divulge the secrets behind the Iron Man armor because he fears the information will slip into the wrong hands. With Pepper Potts (Gwyneth Paltrow) and James &amp;quot;Rhodey&amp;quot; Rhodes (Don Cheadle) at his side, Tony forges new alliances and confronts powerful new forces. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a Boston Movie Group Badge.   The movie will be showing upstairs, so I will try to grab a table near the windows at the top of the escalators.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293825596000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272290403000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Iron Man 2:  (The IMAX Experience)</name><id>13293005</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273354200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/13293005/</event_url></item>