<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.733029</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bow Tie Cinema City</name><city>Hartford</city><id>684699</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.661139</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;What Just Happened&amp;quot; is about two nail-biting, back-stabbing, roller-coaster weeks in the world of a middle-aged Hollywood producer--as he tries to juggle an actual life with an outrageous series of crises in his day job. This is the tale of a man besieged by people who want him all to be sorts of things--a money maker, an ego buster, a bad news breaker, an artistic champion, a loyal husband, an all-knowing father, not to mention sexy, youthful and tuned-in--everything except for the one thing he and all the preposterously behaved people he's surrounded by really are: bumbling human beings just trying to survive by any means necessary. Ben is already in over his head trying to balance the tug-of-war of having two ex-wives and two different families with his latest business venture--the boldly &amp;quot;visionary&amp;quot; movie &amp;quot;Fiercely,&amp;quot; starring Sean Penn--when everything that can go wrong goes completely screwy. Somehow amidst all the madness, treachery, deceit, runaway egos, rampant commercialism, personal politics and atrocious behavior of America's dream-making machinery, Ben has to find a way not just to make it to Cannes with a finished film, but to cope...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REVIEWS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;De Niro is in top form here as a Hollywood producer being pressured at every turn of his life both professional and personally. Barry Levinson has given us a scathing look at the film business and all who are a part of it. Bruce Willis is at his self mocking best as he throws a fit over shaving. Micheal Wincott's fit on hearing that he has to recut the end of his film is over the top and perfect. In fact, everyone here seems to throw a fit at one point or another. And they should. Its a pressure cooker of big budgets and big ego. Like he did in Wag the Dog, Levinson portrays the heart of the insanity known best by insiders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a stressful film to watch but its worth it for the fine acting and directing.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Slow moving and very deliberate, but definitely not for the average audience member. The movie includes a lot of scenes that play out as a certain kind of reality. The humor of this movie is not on the surface, but in the way in which people talk and react to one another. Overall, an enjoyable experience, but you really have to pay attention to see this kind of movie.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Let's meet in the lobby at 7 pm!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228530648000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226785427000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What Just Happened</name><id>9169387</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227226500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/9169387/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/c/global_6318540.jpeg</photo_url></item>