<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>26 S Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.858061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-866-9228</phone><name>LARCHES INN</name><city>CARVER </city><id>749981</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756751</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>150.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;We have only a few seats left ~ please RSVP today if you want to attend this amazing workshop!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the silence of our collective heart, women all over the world are listening and responding to this summons, to make a difference, to shape our communities in ways that honor our connection to the Earth and therefore to each other. We are calling a gathering of women to become a circle with a “leader in every chair.” &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The vision that grounds this gathering is the creation of an inter-generational and interdisciplinary learning community that supports each person’s summons in order to co-create the best possible future, and cultivate a community that lives the “spirituality of hospitality” and cooperation.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Birute Regine, author of “Iron Butterflies: Women Transforming Themselves and the World,” will guide you through the process of composing your stories, where you will listen to your wisdom. Each person will co-create the story of her summons/call with others, a story to be shared at the end of our time together… a story to take home, live fully, for becoming the leader you are.  It will be a time for planting the seeds of the future.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will gather Saturday September 11 from 8:30 am-5:00 pm and reconvene on Sunday  Sept 12 from 8:30am-12:00 pm at the beautiful Larches Inn, 26 South Main St Carver MA 02330&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The fee is $150. Morning snacks are included each day and lunch on Saturday. Please bring a journal, your favorite art materials. Wear comfortable clothes. Preregistration required by September 7. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact Rain Philips rainhphilips@yahoo.com 508 866 9228 or Birute Regine at &lt;br /&gt;biruteregine@comcast.net&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“Alone we can do so little; together we can do so much.”&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>rain phillips</member_name><member_id>7240421</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284396935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY</urlname><id>1248021</id><group_lat>41.8800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7699966431</group_lon><name>Larches Inn Women's Exchange Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281914307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Workshop: Iron Butterflies: Women Transforming Themselves and the World </name><id>14432115</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284208200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LARCHES-INN-SISTERHOOD-COMMUNITY/events/14432115/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/7/global_10366711.jpeg</photo_url></item>