<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;3rd Meeting on Thursday Nov. 4, &lt;br /&gt;Middletown, Ct @ 7 p.m.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This will be another organizational meeting&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are extending to you another opportunity to help the BFF of Ct set up a unique and cutting edge Buddhist group in Connecticut that will be dedicated solely to mindful and healthy eating and exercising. Don’t be shy and give yourself another excuse for not coming. Come along and join the adventure of healthy eating and moving. You need to buy the book Savor to participate. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On November 4th, Thursday evening will include some of the following. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. modify &amp;amp; finalize our format &lt;br /&gt;2. talk about outreach &lt;br /&gt;3. plan web site content &lt;br /&gt;4. talk about sangha location&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you interested? Then, attend this organizational meeting in Middletown on Thursday November  6 at 7 p.m. to 8:30 p.m. If you can’t come, then look for future announcements and check out our web site, when it will be officially inaugurated late November. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact us in order to attend Thursday’s meeting&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in attending this organizational meeting, then e-mail the Buddhist Faith Fellowship at &lt;a href="http://d68@snet.net" target="_blank"&gt;d68@snet.net&lt;/a&gt; to get easy directions to meeting at our new location in Middletown. This Meetup will not meet at the Mansfield Freeman Center but at a private home. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This meeting is not held at the previous Cromwell address but at a private home in Middletown. Please e-mail for directions. </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Senpai Daishin</member_name><member_id>5221830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288915961000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-563</urlname><id>797062</id><group_lat>41.5499992371</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6600036621</group_lon><name>Buddhist Faith Fellowship in Middletown, Ct</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287969026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mindful Eating Group meeting - Middletown</name><id>15215990</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288911600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-563/events/15215990/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/7/0/global_11872720.jpeg</photo_url></item>