<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Change of plans! Rather than a field trip this will now be a regular ol' book discussion at our favorite hangout, Chaibo in Fitchburg. We'll discuss Shutter Island by Dennis Lehane and meet on our usual night and time - the last Thursday of the month (Sept 29th) at 7pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hoping that now that it's officially fall, Chaibo will have their pumpkin whoopie pies! Yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a description of &lt;em&gt;Shutter Island&lt;/em&gt; by Amazon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;The year is 1954. U.S. Marshal Teddy Daniels and his new &amp;shy;partner, Chuck Aule, have come to Shutter Island, home of Ashecliffe Hospital for the Criminally Insane, to investigate the disappearance of a patient. Multiple-murderess Rachel Solando is loose somewhere on this barren island, despite having been kept in a locked cell under constant surveillance. As a killer hurricane bears relentlessly down on them, a strange case takes on even darker, more sinister shades&amp;mdash;with hints of radical experimentation, horrifying surgeries, and lethal countermoves made in the cause of a covert shadow war. No one is going to escape Shutter Island unscathed, because nothing at Ashecliffe Hospital is remotely what it seems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317341707000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315082197000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - Shutter Island by Dennis Lehane</name><id>dcslbcypmbgc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317337200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/32155002/</event_url></item>