<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Milk Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358387</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 451- 7415</phone><name>Coogans</name><city>Boston</city><id>533322</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053375</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Happy hourers will hang once again at Coogan's in the Faneuil Hall area to imbibe social lubricants.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get there when you can. Don't be shy...Say hi, to the friendly folks hanging at the end of the bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Aquarium (blue line), Haymarket (green &amp;amp; orange lines), State (orange &amp;amp; blue lines), Government Center (blue &amp;amp; green lines), and South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail). These subway stations are no more than a ten (10) minute walk.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.irishconnection.com/index.php?id=45" target="_blank"&gt;Coogan's Web Page&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come hungry here's &lt;a href="http://www.irishconnection.com/pdf/coogansmenu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Coogan's Menu&lt;/a&gt;. Great burgers, steak tips, and pizza. Specials $10 lobster &amp;amp; $2 beer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Put the insignificant information in your head to use in the trivia contest, which begins at 7. Some previous categories have been Science, Music, History, Geography, Literature, Sports, TV, Art, Business, &amp;amp; Movies.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stump! Trivia rules:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) To be eligible for prizes, teams are limited to six players. Be aware, teams with less than six players and have one of the top three scores, win first or second place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) The trivia jockey (TJ) provides Stump! sheets, on which to keep your team score. Write the categories as the TJ reads them, and keep track of the points you've wagered. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) When the TJ asks a question, you have one song to write your team name, your answer, and your wager on an answer ticket and hand it in. You can wager 1, 3, 5, or 7 points in the first two quarters, and 2, 4, 6, or 8 points in the last two quarters. You can only use each value ONCE per quarter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) There are three bonus rounds where you can earn lots of extra points! Your TJ will explain how they work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) No shouting out any answers, and absolutely no using cellphones or other devices to look up answers! Teams breaking this rule are disqualified.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the friendly group at the end of the bar furthest from the entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250474117000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245596578000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Thirsty Thursday, So It's Time For Coogan's Again on August 6th</name><id>10700318</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249594200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/10700318/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/6/global_6210534.jpeg</photo_url></item>