<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Michael Blair @ 978-808-1932&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to read the entire event listing before you RSVP - then answer the questions that are part of the RSVP process. While the objective of this event is to enjoy ourselves, your safety, and the safety of the others, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands, overestimate your skills and abilities, or come unprepared you may put yourself and/or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: The clothing and equipment section has been updated to address the potential conditions that we may encounter in late fall/early winter.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;I had to postpone this hike twice during the winter and it's about time to get back there to finally do it. We will be hiking&amp;nbsp;Passaconaway (4,043 feet - #42 on the NH4K), the easternmost 4,000 footer of the Sandwich Range Wilderness, which shares a prominent ridge with Mt. Whiteface (4,020 feet - #45 on the NH4K). A lookout ledge just below Mt. Passaconaway&amp;rsquo;s wooded summit offers great views of the Tripyramid massif to the west and South Hancock and Carrigain to the north.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike provided they are well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, you clean up after them, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace&lt;/strong&gt; one-way trip we&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 11.8 miles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 4,400 feet&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;- for perspective the top floor of the Empire State Building is about 1,250 feet. We will follow the Dicey's Mill, Tom Wiggin, Blueberry Ledge, and Rollins Trails to Whiteface and then continue on the Rollins Trail and Dicey's Mill to Passaconaway. We will then follow the Dicey's Mill Trail to get back to the trailhead.&amp;nbsp;Without including time for breaks it should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 8 hours 15 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip. It is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;I have never used these trails but did all of my research for this trip using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become familiar with this information since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=7002"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for more information about Whiteface from Peakbagger.com &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com/NH-4000.php#whiteface"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for trail conditions near Whiteface from TrailsNH.com &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6999"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for more information about Passaconaway from Peakbagger.com &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for trail conditions near Passaconaway from TrailsNH.com &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. &amp;nbsp;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, or other situations and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here - meaning we might not reach the summit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the current weather conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Sturdy hiking boots or trail shoes. &amp;nbsp;The rocks and ledges may be slick so you will need some form of traction too - microspikes work best in these conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater (even in summer). ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when dry it doesn't dry easily and is a great conductor when wet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: Fleece hat and gloves/mittens. Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder conditions). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Optional Items&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof pants. Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;According to Google Maps this spot is about 133 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 31 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://local.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=43.914150,-71.364632(Dicey's+Mill+Trailhead)&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFaYTngId6A-_-w&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;sll=43.91415,-71.364632&amp;amp;sspn=0.007404,0.019205&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the driving directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #468357 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1322355182000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317427586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Whiteface &amp; Passaconaway (ADVANCED) ...</name><id>35661792</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321706700000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/35661792/</event_url></item>