<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 N Main St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.826285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 454-6500</phone><name>RISD Museum of Art</name><city>Providence</city><id>777518</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.408308</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Meet me at the RISD Museum in the main entrance on Benefit Street - Sunday Dec. 19 at 11:30am.&lt;br /&gt;We are going to check out the sculptures created by Lynda Benglis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;American sculptor Lynda Benglis (American, b. 1941) is known for pioneering and challenging work that questions the rigors of Modernism and Minimalism by merging material, form, and content. Spanning 40 years, this exhibition represents the breadth of Benglis’s extraordinary creative output, including wax paintings and poured latex and polyurethane foam sculptures of the late 1960s; innovative videos, installations, and “knots” from the 1970s; metalized, pleated wall pieces of the 1980s and ’90s; and more recent works in a variety of mediums, such as the monumental cast-polyurethane The Graces. The exhibition also features documentary material underscoring Benglis’s interest in performance and self-promotion through magazines and invitation cards, including her infamous advertisement in Artforum in November 1974 that galvanized the art world. For RISD, Judith Tannenbaum, Richard Brown Baker Curator of Contemporary Art, will reunite the five-part installation Phantom and add ceramics from the 1990s and several other more recent works. A 450-page fully illustrated hardcover monograph, produced by Les Presses du Réel, accompanies the exhibition. Lynda Benglis is organized by the Irish Museum of Modern Art, Dublin, in collaboration with Van Abbemuseum, Eindhoven; Le Consortium, Dijon; Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design, Providence; and New Museum, New York. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The exhibition tour is made possible by Bank of America Merrill Lynch. Along with their financial support of the international tour and of the exhibition’s stop at The RISD Museum, Bank of America Merrill Lynch has also promised a gift of one of the works in the exhibition, Pleiades (1982), to the Museum. The presentation at The RISD Museum is supported in part by contributions from Agnes Gund, Bank of America Merrill Lynch, the Bafflin Foundation, Locks Family Foundation, John Cheim (RISD BFA ’77),and Howard Read (RISD BFA ’76).&lt;br /&gt;Hours and Admission&lt;br /&gt;open: Tuesday through Sunday, 10am-5pm.The Museum stays open until 9pm on the third Thursday of the month (except December)&lt;br /&gt;Admission is &amp;quot;pay-what-you-wish&amp;quot; every Sunday, 10am-1pm; free to all: 5-9pm on Gallery Night, the third Thursday of each month (except December); and Free Saturdays the last Saturday of each month (except December).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;General Admission  &lt;br /&gt;Members, children under 5:  free&lt;br /&gt;Adults: $10 &lt;br /&gt;Senior citizens (age 62+): $7&lt;br /&gt;Youths (ages 5-18): $3&lt;br /&gt;RISD, Brown students, faculty, staff: free&lt;br /&gt;College students with valid ID: $3&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be in the main entrance at 11:30am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Germaine</member_name><member_id>10481143</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292851255000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Exciting People Having Some Fun!</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mingle-with-singles</urlname><id>1452082</id><group_lat>41.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Mingle with singles 45+ Socializing and dancing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292598211000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RISD Museum</name><id>15758533</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292776200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mingle-with-singles/events/15758533/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/7/0/global_10652416.jpeg</photo_url></item>