<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/f/event_8882879.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;April is Waterfall Month in the Whites: Join us for a Casual Breakfast and a light hike afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This light Sunday hike is suitable for families and hikers who want an easier social hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hike to Bridal Veil Falls via the Coppermine Trail in Franconia Notch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coppermine Trail itself is a pleasant walk on the western side of Cannon Mountain. Most of it grades gently uphill along Coppermine Brook. Even though this hike is a easier one, please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail could be muddy, trekking poles are useful at the cold stream crossings. Wear proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 1 quart of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a nice shelter by the falls to take a break at. The trail takes you along Coppermine Brook to Bridal Veil Falls, one of the most beautiful waterfalls in the White Mountains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coppermine Trail has an aura of mystery and romance about it. But the mystery does not come from the waterfall itself. Our challenge for our explorers will be to find along the way, a plaque on a large boulder along the brook with an enigmatic inscription: &lt;em&gt;In Memoriam to Arthur Farnsworth &amp;ldquo;The Keeper of Stray Ladies&amp;rdquo; Pecketts 1939.&lt;/em&gt; Presented by a Grateful One. For the rest of the hike, you can ponder who Arthur Farnsworth was, whether he met a tragic fate along Coppermine Brook, why the tribute was placed in such an obscure place, and who was this &amp;ldquo;grateful one&amp;rdquo; who chose to eulogize Mr. Farnsworth in this manner (read on and find out!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your not meeting us for breakfast but want to hike, &amp;nbsp;The Coppermine Trailhead is located on the east side of Route 116 at Coppermine Road in Franconia, New Hampshire. Figure on a 12 noon arrival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April Showers will postpone this hike for better weather&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From I-93: * Take Exit 38 off of I-93. The exit is signed "18, 116, 117, 142, Franconia, Sugar Hill". * Turn west which will be towards Routes 18, 116, and 117. * After barely 0.1 mile you will reach a flashing traffic light in downtown Franconia which is the junction of Routes 18 and 116. * Go straight through the intersection (after stopping at the light) onto Rt. 116 and follow that road for 3.4 miles. * Turn left onto Coppermine Road and park close to Rt. 116. From the Jct. of Routes 112 and 116: * From the junction of Routes 112 and 116 in Easton, head north on Rt. 116. * The trailhead will be on the right 3.0 miles after passing the town hall in Easton center. * Turn right onto Coppermine Road and park close to Rt. 116. Trailhead and parking: * After turning onto Coppermine Road, park as close as possible to Rt. 116. Don't bother driving farther down this road as it is a private development and trail parking is not allowed elsewhere. * The "trail" follows Coppermine Road for 0.4 mile before turning onto a woods road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Restaurant. Could be busy, first one arriving list table as MEETUP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334112072000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329751433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast and  Hike to Bridal Veil Falls!   family/easy/photo</name><id>53035862</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333895400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/53035862/</event_url></item>