<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>75 Allison St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.191335</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>223-0335</phone><name>Liberty Books</name><city>Concord</city><id>682917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.538397</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://thedarklegacy.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Dark Legacy &lt;br /&gt;George Bush and the Murder of John F. Kennedy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;George Bush killed Kennedy&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; Or was it the Mafia? Maybe Castro did it.  Who cares? It was 40 years ago. What difference does it make?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It matters&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/2/5/7/event_22837463.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/em&gt;The day he died we lost an invaluable treasure. This video  documents that we lost a man of peace, who tried to cool off the cold  war, and to get the American people to see their Russian enemies, not as  despicable inhuman monsters, but as people like us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On November 22, 1963, you lost the man who saved your life  on October 17, 1962. At the height of the missile crisis, Kennedy&amp;rsquo;s  generals and advisors were urging him to launch a first strike attack  against Cuba. They assured Kennedy that the Russian missiles in Cuba  were not nuclear and were not ready; but that he and they should quietly  slip away to the safety of bomb shelters anyway, just to be safe; and  then launch an attack, leaving the rest of us out to die. Kennedy  thought about it. And then he told them that nobody was going anywhere.  If anyone died, they would be the first to go, sitting as they were in  the Whitehouse, the prime target of those Russian missiles. Together  they then figured out a safer plan.  Robert McNamara, Secretary of  Defense at the time, recently learned from the Russians that the  missiles were armed, were ready, were nuclear, and that their commanders  were authorized to use them in case of an attack. If you live in the  northern hemisphere, the lives of your parents, and your future, were  certainly saved by John Kennedy on that day. It matters that his killers  be exposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his farewell address, President Eisenhower had warned  Kennedy, and the rest of us, of the threat posed to democracy by what  Eisenhower called &amp;ldquo;the military industrial complex.&amp;rdquo; And while Kennedy  famously went after the CIA, and refused to commit troops to Vietnam, I  always wondered why he didn&amp;rsquo;t more openly attack this military  industrial complex. And then I stumbled upon a speech he gave at the  United Nations. As you will see in the video, he called upon the  Russians, and United Nations, to help him to take on this military  industrial complex, in order to &amp;ldquo;abolish all armies and all weapons.&amp;rdquo;  But he was swept away. And in the years since, millions have died in  needless wars, trillions of dollars have been wasted on &amp;ldquo;defense&amp;rdquo;, and  millions more people have lived and died needlessly in poverty. It  matters that we lost him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2007, Bruce Willis told Vanity Fair magazine, "They  still haven&amp;rsquo;t caught the guy that killed Kennedy. I'll get killed for  saying this, but I'm pretty sure those guys are still in power, in some  form. The entire government of the United States was co-opted.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now Willis probably would not mind my suggesting that he&amp;rsquo;s  no genius. At best, his observation is common sense. 80% of the American  people agree with him.  Indeed, this video, proving that Kennedy was  brought down by the most powerful men in the world and their hired  thugs, is not based on secret documents. It is all information that has  merely been suppressed. Oswald allegedly shot Kennedy from behind. But  the day he died, the NY Times carried the story, told by the doctors in  Dallas, that Kennedy had an entrance wound in his throat, another in his  right temple, and a large gaping exit wound in the back of his head.  After talking to the emergency room doctors, Kennedy&amp;rsquo;s press secretary  described, to the assembled press, a shot to the right temple from the  right front that went &amp;ldquo;right through the head.&amp;rdquo; All of the witnesses  near the right front, the grassy knoll, described hearing shots from  that direction, and dozens of witnesses raced up the knoll in pursuit of  the shooters.  These witnesses talked to the press.  But all of this  information has been suppressed for the last 50 years.  By whom?  Who  could?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will also see in this video the overwhelming best  evidence, from the best witnesses, proving beyond a reasonable dispute,  that Kennedy's body was stolen from Air Force One, and the wound to his  right temple was mutilated, before the autopsy.  Jackie Kennedy kept  watch over an empty casket on the flight from Dallas to Bethesda Naval  Hospital.  Then the body was quietly taken to Bethesda for the autopsy,  arriving 20 minutes before Jackie and the empty casket.  Who had the  power to arrange this?  Who HAS the power today to suppress all this  evidence?, and to continue to bombard us with ridiculous lies about a  lone gunman?  It's a short list, isn't it?  It doesn't include the  mafia, or the Russians, or Castro.  It does include the Bush family - or  rather their masters in Big Oil; the banking elite; the backbone of the  military industrial complex.  These men, and their successors, carried  out the attacks of 9-11.  &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It matters.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;========================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We gather at Liberty Books and Comics in Concord at 6:30 - be sure to bring a snack or a box of your favorite tea. Jim will have hot water and a pot of coffee on for us. Socialize and mix a bit, then a little current events in the truth movement and any business to deal with and then on with the show a little after 7. You won't see the world the same way after your eyes have been opened to What Really Happens and How the World Really Works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see you there for &lt;strong&gt;Dark Legacy&lt;/strong&gt;. Our meetings are free of charge, but we have some costs associated with running this meetup site and acquiring our videos, so any donations are greatly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we'll be in the meeting area in the back.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1305778240000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>If you wonder about "hidden history" and "deep politics", you'll want to come to this meetup.</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1302097209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concord - Dark Legacy</name><id>17204373</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305671400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/17204373/</event_url></item>