<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, ladies and gentlemen, I've had many requests for another barbecue to happen to so I've decided what better way to send off the summer than with games and grillin' on Labor Day weekend. &amp;nbsp;However, you guys deserve more than just a repeat of last time. &amp;nbsp;To thank everyone for being such an awesome fun group and coming to my themed Mini-Meetups, we are going to kick this party up a notch and attempt to do the impossible: offer something for everyone! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mini-Meetups have been about connecting people with&amp;nbsp;similar&amp;nbsp;gaming tastes. &amp;nbsp;However, this time we are going to create convergence. &amp;nbsp;Whether you like thoughtful games like Scrabble or Chess, social games like Hearts and Spades, throwing a frisbee around or hitting a soccer ball, acting out in Celebrity, Quelf or Pictionary, planning strategic victory in Euro games, button mashing hardcore style in video games or you enjoy gambling your money away at poker, we are going to create a veritable buffet of gaming entertainment with the space to do it all at once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what we are going to do:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;2:00-4:00pm - "Warm-up Phase"&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 2. &amp;nbsp;The backyard will be set up so you can jump right into a game of Bocce or Frisbee or sit under a table and deal some cards. &amp;nbsp;Feel free to shun the sun and stay inside too. &amp;nbsp;Grab a drink and mingle with your fellow guests!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;4:00-6:00pm - "All Fired Up"&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;I'll start the grill up at 4 and will be cooking meats, fake meats, vegetables or whatever you guys bring me to put on top of an open flame. &amp;nbsp;Grab a table indoors or outdoors and enjoy our potluck barbecue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;6:00-8:00pm - "If You Can't Take the Heat..."&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;It's throw down time with your favorite game. &amp;nbsp;Think you can dominate in Ticket to Ride or Scrabble? &amp;nbsp;Make a fool of people in Quelf? &amp;nbsp;Fastest draw in Pictionary? &amp;nbsp;Get your gaming on in whatever groups you choose while you digest. &amp;nbsp;We'll allocate space based on noise level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;8:00pm-??? - "Too Hot to Handle"&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;When the sun sets, the night party begins. &amp;nbsp;Come on back for music, singing and dancing (or at least games involving them). &amp;nbsp;Night tag with flashlights. &amp;nbsp;Shady casino games going on backrooms. &amp;nbsp;Anything goes when we break out the desserts and wine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll try and have some surprise entertainment there as well. &amp;nbsp;Could it be a giant bouncy castle? &amp;nbsp;A fog machine to compliment your karaoke performance? &amp;nbsp;Who knows?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the event of rain, the party will still happen. &amp;nbsp;I'll just manifest some giant tarps or plenty of folding chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;INSTRUCTIONS FOR SIGNING UP - PLEASE READ&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have one very simple request. &amp;nbsp;You guys can show up and leave whenever you want and pretty much do whatever you want save for damaging personal property. :-) &amp;nbsp;All I ask is one thing: that when you RSVP you describe what food you are bringing. &amp;nbsp;Since this is a potluck barbecue, everyone needs to bring something as I can't afford to feed 30 people. :-) &amp;nbsp;A dish, a wine, a dessert, whatever. &amp;nbsp;Otherwise all we will be eating is hot dogs and potato chips. &amp;nbsp;And please list the item in your RSVP so we don't end up with 5 kinds of potato salad this time. &amp;nbsp;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: There will be two cats on the premises, however, they will be isolated to the third floor. &amp;nbsp;They won't be mingling with the guests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how about it? &amp;nbsp;Shall we keep the spirit of summer alive in our group? &amp;nbsp;Can we make this the highest attended meetup so far in 2011? &amp;nbsp;Hope to see you there! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send out directions a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315918385000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313371954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Mini-Meetup Sizzlin' Summer BBQ Blowout</name><id>29497551</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315159200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/29497551/</event_url></item>