<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Andy and Isabeau this week on Intellectual Spirituality Radio Show as we will be interviewing an expert in the UFO field, Kathleen Marden. Kathleen Marden was thirteen on September 20, 1961, when her aunt Betty Hill phoned her nearby home to report that, the previous evening, she and Barney had encountered a flying saucer in New Hampshire’s White Mountains. A primary witness to the evidence of the UFO encounter and the aftermath, Kathy has intimate knowledge of the Hill’s biographical histories, personalities, and the never before published historical data pertaining to their sensational story. She recorded hours of taped interviews with Betty and the two made several research trips along the close encounter route through New Hampshire’s White Mountains. Additionally, Kathy transcribed the audio tapes of the hypnosis sessions Betty and Barney participated in with renowned psychiatrist Dr. Benjamin Simon and conducted a comparative analysis of the Hills’ individual testimony versus Betty’s infamous dream material. Kathy believes that there is conclusive evidence that the Hills were abducted. This new information, along with the Hills’ historical records and scientific reports, became the foundation for her book Captured! The Betty and Barney Hill UFO Experience coauthored with scientific ufologist/ nuclear physicist Stanton T. Friedman. For ten years Kathy served on the MUFON Board of Directors as the Director of Field Investigator Training. In 2003, MUFON publicly recognized Kathy for her outstanding contribution of advancing the scientific study of the UFO phenomenon and demonstrating positive leadership. She has appeared on numerous radio and television shows and lectured at colleges and conferences across the U.S.. Kathy resides in Stratham, New Hampshire and can be contacted at Kmarden@aol.com . Her website is as follows: &lt;a href="http://kathleenmarden.googlepages.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://kathleenmarden...&lt;/a&gt; To purchase an autographed copy of her book (by both authors), mail $18.99 (U.S.) to P.O. Box 93, East Kingston, NH 03827.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.blogtalkradio.com/isabeauesby" target="_blank"&gt;www.blogtalkradio.com/isabeauesby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256432983000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253852117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kathleen Marden, author of Captured!  </name><id>11462201</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256259600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11462201/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/f/global_11311583.jpeg</photo_url></item>