<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Meet at 10:30 outside the snowshoe rental shop. Bring you own snowshoes if you have them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter Trails Day is a national event each January focusing on introducing people to the great fun of getting outside in the winter on cross-country skis or snowshoes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paddleboston.com/skitrack/skitrack.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.paddlebost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Our snowmaking almost guarantees that we can hold the event even without natural snow. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snowshoeing&lt;br /&gt;For 2008, all snowshoe events will be free and do not require pre-registration. Everyone will receive a free snowshoeing trail pass, there will be free snowshoe demos, and we will be leading a number of free guided tours. Snowshoes will be available from Tubbs, MSR, Redfeather, and Atlas. There will be a limited number of demo snowshoes available; those who want to use snowshoes for more than 15-20 minutes can rent them from us at the regular rate ($12 for snowshoes and poles).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A day of outdoor fun with free snowshoe demos from top snowshoe companies, guided tours, food samples, raffles, and music! Pre-registration is not required for snowshoeing events.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This is a perfect opportunity to try out snowshoeing or skiing for the first time or to check out and compare the latest equipment from the leading manufacturers. Experienced snowshoers and skiers will be on hand to get you started and to answer questions. Free snowshoe trail pass, free snowshoe demos, and free guided tours will be available. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston: Take the Mass Pike to exit 15. Stay left after the toll booth. At the end of the ramp, turn left onto Park Road, following a sign for Route 16. The Ski Track is a quarter mile down the road on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;from the west: Take the Mass Pike to exit 14 (Rt.128 North and South). After the toll, follow signs for Rt.128 North and Rt.30. Take exit 24, Route 30. Turn left onto Rt.30 West. Turn left at the second set of lights onto Park Road. The Ski Track is a half mile down the road on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the north: Take Rt.128 South to exit 24 (Rt.30). Make a left turn at the end of the ramp onto Rt.30 West. At the next set of lights turn left onto Park Road. The Ski Track is a half mile down the road on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the south: Take Rt.128 North to exit 21 (Rt.16). Turn left at the end of the ramp and follow Rt.16 West for 1/2 mile. At the second set of lights, turn right onto Concord Street. The Ski Track is one mile up the road on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the Green Line: See the walking map below. Take the Green Line (D train) to Riverside. Cross the parking lot and make a right onto Grove St. Cross over Rt.128 and take the fourth right onto Pine Grove Avenue. Continue on Pine Grove Avenue until it intersects with Concord St. Turn right onto Concord St. and cross over the Charles River. The Ski Track is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at:&lt;br /&gt;Bison County BBQ &amp;amp; Grille&lt;br /&gt;www.bisoncounty.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;275 Moody St&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02453&lt;br /&gt;(781) 642-9720&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200324809000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1197831414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowshoeing at Weston Ski Track</name><id>6922200</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200151800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6922200/</event_url></item>