<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, Apr 10 from 2 to 4 PM we will have a recreational/low         intermediate level meetup at the Cambridge Recreational Center. There will be two courts available for rec level games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recreational - Players possessing basic skills/fundamentals of the      game.    Laid-back game with focus on repetition of the basics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low   Intermediate - Players with some experience playing in informal         settings (family gatherings, etc) Should be familiar with 4-2      formation    (middle front setter).  The entrance to the gym is on      Cambridge Street   opposite Harvard Market.  The nearest intersection  to     the entrance is   Cambridge Street and Roberts  Road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INSTRUCTIONS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please RSVP if you  plan on attending. RSVP's will close on the day       of  the game at 11 AM.  If you show up at the game but do not have  a      "Yes"  RSVP, you will not  be guaranteed to get playing time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Please be serious about RSVP's. If  you RSVP "Yes" and don't show       up,  it means you have prevented someone  else from attending. Also,       please  change your RSVP if you find out you  can't play, as soon  as      possible.  Changing the RSVP a few hours before  the game time   means     that there will  be less people who can play, as  most people   prefer     some advance notice  that there are spots available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cost of the meetup will be $5. Please pay the organizer when you         arrive before the meetup starts. The money goes to cover the cost    of    the   court rental.  The nearest T stop is Harvard Square. The   gym  is    about a  ten minute walk  from the T stop.  Parking near the    school  on   Sundays  is generally easy to find, as meters  and    residential  parking   rules are  generally not enforced on Sundays     (parking signs  should say   "EX SUNDAY"  or similar).&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lilly</member_name><member_id>10355700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1303080800000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301868147000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Recreational/Low Intermediate Indoor Volleyball</name><id>17168140</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302458400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/17168140/</event_url></item>