<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a spectator event but if you are brave..well then join in with the canoe bangers yakers..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have not picked out a meeting spot yet, so this is of general information as of now,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like to hike at the McLean Game Preserve hike That Steve has listed first then go to this event and observe near the finish area. I am expecting lots of people here so parking is an unknown factor...Heck...park anywhere and walk a bit.....&lt;br /&gt; follow the crowd...&lt;br /&gt;So i will just leave the website and let you decide.. &lt;br /&gt;Perhaps a few of us can link together at the hike or here...about 12:30/1:00 apx and do a later lunch/dinner...&lt;br /&gt;Exchange cell numbers..etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.scanticspringsplash.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scantic Spring Splash is growing as a spectator event. Hundreds of spectators will line the Finish Area. Great fun for all ages to watch the canoes and kayaks come down the rapids just off South Maple Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The boats will start to arrive into the area around 12:30pm - 1pm acording to the website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think they mean the rapids area here...the finish is a bit further down and should take a bit longer i would expect.... &lt;br /&gt;But look at the map on the web site if you are interested... &lt;br /&gt;Maps of spectator areas are available in the Race HQ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174927017000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174339944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Observe the Scantic River Splash Event</name><id>5584685</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174753800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5584685/</event_url></item>