<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come for one of the best burgers in the entire area of Boston. You love this Harvard landmark.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scene&lt;br /&gt;For one of the Boston area's most unique--and beloved--dining experiences, visitors must cross the Charles and head toward the edge of Harvard Square, where Mr. Bartley has lured people to his &amp;quot;cottage&amp;quot; for more than four decades. Mr. B can still be found seating students and area workers in his hectic single-room restaurant that's jam-packed with young, eclectic waiters and humorous posters from bygone eras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Food&lt;br /&gt;Bartley's has satisfied cravings of many a hippie, yuppie and celebrity by taking seven ounces of freshly ground sirloin, grilling it to perfection, slathering on any number of toppings and giving it a humorous, politically tinged billing (the &amp;quot;Dick Cheney's only a heartbeat away&amp;quot;). Every once in a blue moon, someone passes on a burger to nosh on a gigantic, fresh salad or comfort dish like franks with Boston baked beans. Almost as popular as burgers are tangy raspberry-lime rickeys and extra-thick frappes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at Mr. Mr. Bartley's!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246322308000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244155872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's have lunch: The Best Berger is at Mr. Bartley's Burger Cottage, Cambridge</name><id>10578680</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246125600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/10578680/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/f/global_8976863.jpeg</photo_url></item>