<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Central Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Simons IMAX Theater - Aquarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1245284</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050826</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From The Boston Harbor Association (TBHA) website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tbha.org/events.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tbha.org/e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join The Boston Harbor Association (TBHA) in examining the impacts of climate change on Boston Harbor. Specially prepared maps showing potential impacts of sea level rise and climate change in Boston Harbor and local neighborhoods will be presented. Gina McCarthy, EPA’s Assistant Administrator, will give the keynote address. Open mike sessions will allow for public comments and questions. Free; reception following&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Oooh! A public forum? With questions? I wonder if there will be any cool drama as people try to debate the findings that are presented in the Q &amp;amp; A portion?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time&lt;/b&gt;: 6:00 PM to 7:45 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: Free, but TBHA wishes you to register at &lt;a href="https://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/eventReg?oeidk=a07e31z7je016c30762" target="_blank"&gt;https://events.r20.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Nerd Fun is not affiliated with TBHA or any other organization besides Meetup.com, which we use for organization and scheduling purposes. We don't usually run the events we go to... we just crash 'em. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Photo: Gina McCarthy, of the EPA, Keynote Speaker&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you keep track of nerdly type events in the Boston area? Want to gather people together? Contact the original Scruffy Nerd Herder, Heather, the Organizer of Nerd Fun &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/members/74173/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; to become an Event Host.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting inside the lobby of the IMAX theater building next to the New England Aquarium starting at 5:20 pm if people want to drop by. He is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should probably grab seats at 5:40 pm. Can't make it until just before 6:00 pm? Let us know and we can try to save seats with the group. After, let's group up and check out the reception. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bio of Gina McCarthy, on the EPA's Air and Radiation site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epa.gov/air/aabio.html"&gt;http://www.epa.gov/ai...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Prior to her confirmation, Gina McCarthy served as the Commissioner of the Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection. In her 25 year career, she has worked at both the state and local levels on critical environmental issues, helped coordinate policies on economic growth, energy, transportation and the environment, and has extensive experience with the Regional Greenhouse Gas Initiative, the nation’s first market-based, greenhouse cap-and-trade system. In her new post at the Office of Air and Radiation, Gina will be a leading advocate for win-win strategies to confront climate change and strengthen our green economy&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Climate Change Indicators report:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epa.gov/climatechange/indicators.html"&gt;http://www.epa.gov/cl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Just in case anyone wants to read the April 2010 report Gina McCarthy will probably be talking about...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Collecting and interpreting environmental indicators play a critical role in our understanding of climate change and its causes. An indicator represents the state of certain environmental conditions over a given area and a specified period of time. Examples of climate change indicators include temperature, precipitation, sea level, and greenhouse gas concentrations in the atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;i&gt;EPA's Climate Change Indicators in the United States&lt;/i&gt; (PDF) (80 pp, 13.3MB) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.epa.gov/climatechange/indicators/pdfs/ClimateIndicators_full.pdf"&gt;http://www.epa.gov/cl...&lt;/a&gt; report will help readers interpret a set of important indicators to better understand climate change. The report presents 24 indicators, each describing trends related to the causes and effects of climate change. It focuses primarily on the United States, but in some cases global trends are presented to provide context or a basis for comparison. EPA will use these indicators to collect data and generate analyses to:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;* Monitor the effects/impacts of climate change in the United States &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;* Assist decision–makers on how to best use policymaking and program resources to respond to climate change &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;* Assist EPA and its constituents in evaluating the success of their climate change efforts&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About The Boston Harbor Association:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tbha.org/about.htm"&gt;http://www.tbha.org/a...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Boston Harbor Association (TBHA) is a non-profit, public interest organization founded in 1973 by the League of Women Voters and the Boston Shipping Association to promote a clean, alive and accessible Boston Harbor. TBHA brings together diverse interests -- harbor users, environmentalists, developers, waterfront businesses, and decision makers -- to develop balanced solutions for maritime industrial activities, commercial development, environmental protection, and public access around Boston Harbor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;TBHA cares about Boston Harbor as New England's maritime port, as a recreational and tourist asset, and as the centerpiece of the area's natural and urban environment. TBHA advocates for greater public access and open space along Boston Harbor, promotes the Port of Boston's economy, educates urban youths about Boston Harbor and related career opportunities through our&lt;br /&gt;Harbor Bound program, promotes affordable public water transportation throughout the Harbor, monitors water quality improvements, and works for the restoration of Boston Harbor Beaches&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the New England Aquarium's IMAX theater:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/visit_planning/imax_theatre/now_playing/index.php"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have to put some of the stuff going on now on the Nerd Fun calendar! SeaRex 3D! Hubble 3D! Inception in IMAX! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maps, Directions, and Parking at the Aquarium:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neaq.org/visit_planning/maps_directions_and_parking/index.php"&gt;http://www.neaq.org/v...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I wonder if they will validate parking? They do with IMAX tickets, so if you park for under 4 hours, it only is $10.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289408458000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288898945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Harbor Sea Level Rise Forum @ Boston Harbor Association, Aquarium IMAX</name><id>15340817</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289343600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15340817/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/0/0/global_19385376.jpeg</photo_url></item>