<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1100 Lexington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.412483</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 547-5655</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739900</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.233269</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our group liked LAMB so much and the writing of Christopher Moore that we decided to read another book by this author.&amp;nbsp; I looked for You Suck but only found Bite Me at the library which is along the same lines as You Suck. Happy reading!&amp;nbsp; Kim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city of San Francisco is being stalked by a huge shaved vampyre cat named Chet, and only I, Abby Normal, and my manga-haired love monkey stand between the ravenous monster and a bloody massacre of the general public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whoa. And this is a 
&lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; story?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yup. 'Cept there's no whining. But there is everybody's favorite undead couple, Tommy and Jody, who've just escaped from imprisonment in a bronze statue. And now that they're out they've joined forces with Abby, her boyfriend Steve, the frozen-turkey-bowling Safeway crew, the Emperor of San Francisco and his trusty dogs Lazarus and Bummer, gay Goth guy Jared, and SF's finest Cavuto and Rivera to hunt big cat and save the city. Really.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be the group of people talking at the same time and enjoying it!!  I will have a book club sign for new members to find us.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314370576000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>thatotherbookgroup</urlname><id>1149392</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>That Other Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311958083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bite Me...by Christopher Moore</name><id>27503301</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314315000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/thatotherbookgroup/events/27503301/</event_url></item>