<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>99 Fordham Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01887</zip><lat>42.567093</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-665-6466</phone><name>Shriners Auditorium</name><city>Wilmington</city><id>695953</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.136884</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;On the track tonight is: Wicked Pissah vs. Nutcrackers + Massacre vs. Carolina&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;3/7/10 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; To purchase tickets on line go to &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/browse.html?keywords=boston+derby+dames" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brownpaper...&lt;/a&gt; and follow the directions.  Make sure that you order the tickets for the correct night.  OR you can still purchase tickets at the door.  Seeing that Janet and I have never been there for a roller derby event we are not sure what the seating arrangement are if you buy the tickets ahead of time or at the door.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEATING:&lt;/b&gt; Please note that I am thinking that the seating is on bleacher seats, so if you have a stadium chair you may want to bring it?! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After an amazing season that included the Pantsless Militia finishing 3rd in the East and earning their first trip to Nationals, it's time to look ahead. The Boston Massacre announces their 2010 roster, with some familiar faces and some new recruits!  Read about the skaters you'll be seeing on the track this seasonon their website: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonderbydames.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonderb...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;When:&lt;/span&gt; March 20, 2010: Season 4, Bout 2&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;DOUBLE HEADER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bout #1, 5 pm: Boston Massacre vs. Carolina (Raleigh, NC)&lt;br /&gt;Bout #2, 7 pm: Wicked Pissahs vs. Nutcrackers&lt;br /&gt;After party in the Fez Room with DJ John Barera&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors at 4 pm, Bout #1 at 5 pm, Bout #2 at 7 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; Shriners Auditorium, Wilmington, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets $14 in advance, $16 at the door (good for both bouts of the double header)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bout #1:&lt;/span&gt; Continuing the home season, the first bout of the evening sees the Wicked Pissahs take on Season Three Champs the Nutcrackers. The Pissahs are thirsting for a victory after a rough season that ended with a playoff defeat. Will 2010 be another Year of the Nut, or can the two-time champion Pissahs bring back the championship ... fo' life?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Bout #2:&lt;/span&gt; The evening continues with an exciting rematch. The Boston vs. Carolina rivalry is so fierce, it was a nominee for best rivalry in Derby News Network's Best of 2009 Reader Poll. With Carolina defeating Boston in two consecutive heartbreakers, Boston was able to avenge those losses with a crushing defeat at the 2009 WFTDA Eastern Regionals. Without a trip to Nationals, Carolina is well-rested and ready for revenge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are in the process of finding out how to get the advance ticket price and will update the page as the date gets closer.  Please remember to check back for updated information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The auditorium has a small kitchen on site where you can purchase food such as popcorn, pizza and drinks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where to meetup:&lt;/b&gt; We will in front of the bathrooms which are to the right as you come up the stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; We will meetup at 4:00pm when the doors open, and as usual we will only wait 15 minutes pick out our seats.  If you are running late and don’t see us near the bathrooms then come into the arena and find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are welcome to this event but please use your judgment as this event runs until midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;br /&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On the landing near the bathroom.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269288921000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264372281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Go back in time to your youth and come on out to watch Roller Derby! </name><id>12410490</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269115200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12410490/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/c/3/global_12776243.jpeg</photo_url></item>