<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>845 Canal Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06902</zip><lat>41.042953</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-323-4153</phone><name>Loft Artist Association</name><city>Stamford</city><id>917330</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.532361</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Loft Artist Association Open Studios&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: olive"&gt;Check out their gallery, browse Artist studios, listen to live music..... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A 3-day art event where the public can visit artists in their studios and see how they make their art. &amp;quot;The energy is palpable&amp;quot;, says Alissa Siegal, president of the LAA, &amp;quot;people are really interested to see how artists create their work, and to watch the process unfold. Visitors can ask the artists questions about how they come up with their ideas, what it is like to commit to the life of an artist, and how it feels when they have to part with a piece they have really poured themselves into. We love talking about this stuff, and people are curious&amp;quot;, she continues, &amp;quot;it is just a whole lot of fun.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gathered under the roof of a former printing plant on Canal Street, the LAA is a group of professional artists of all stripes- from ceramicists to line artists and photographers, and including those who elude categorization. What unites us is a serious commitment to a life immersed in art, creating, convening with other artists, and sharing this passion with the community which houses us. LAA's Working Studios is a unique opportunity for artists and public alike to come together and share a curiosity about and love for life. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Loft Artists Association, the area's largest cooperative of working artists, is a non-profit organization dedicated to building connections within Fairfield County's visual arts community as well as working to educate and involve the general public in the arts. For over 30 years, the LAA has continually reached out to the public through its members, a diverse group dedicated to sharing their appreciation of the power of art with the community they work in. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the Gallery</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289245028000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284484360000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Loft Artist Association Open Studios</name><id>14767431</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288994400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/14767431/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/1/d/global_17966845.jpeg</photo_url></item>