<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>185 middle street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.657619</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>above Bards Coffee.  2nd floor right side enterence</name><city>Portland</city><id>5163112</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.254944</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;Help Jon Hinck become the next US Senator for Maine.&amp;#148; To launch this effort, we&amp;#146;re hosting a volunteer kick off party at our office in Portland on Thursday January 19th from 6:00-7:30pm. We&amp;#146;ll have food and refreshments and hope that you can bring a friend or family member. Our goal will be to have a meet and great and lay out an exciting grassroots effort. Helping to lead the effort is our Volunteer Coordinator Seamus Rodman. Seamus has been active with various causes in and around Portland since 2006. In his own words, &amp;#147;I feel there is a great future here in Maine, and I want to be a part of making it happen. My father may have said it best: If you want to complain, gripe, or put your two cents in, you must first get involved. And with the education, experience and skills I have acquired, I hope to help Jon Hinck become the next US Senator for Maine.&amp;#148; Please let us know if you can join us on January 19th, if travelling to Portland is difficult, have no fear. We will set up a conference call for those who cannot attend and will touch base individually if you cannot make it. We&amp;#146;ll send a reminder about the event next week, but don&amp;#146;t forget to mark it on your calendar and RSVP to Seamus at volunteers@jonhinck.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327087189000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>TT'rs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>TI-Portland</urlname><id>1233823</id><group_lat>43.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2900009155</group_lon><name>Tohidu Transition - Portland Maine</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326499026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Having a Volunteer KickOff pizza party. </name><id>48017122</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327014000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/TI-Portland/events/48017122/</event_url></item>