<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Wethersfield Ave     </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.746854</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Buckley high School</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1456807</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.671492</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is the Day of the CONCERT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;We looked at the space Yesterday and will have 2 tables one upstairs for the balcony  and one downs for all the other folks.  We will need 8 people to man the tables.  We also could use  some runners as well.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a special project for the bakers and wanna be bakers of The Hartford Cooking and Recipes Meet Up. We are forming a 'Cookies Committee' to provide the 'desert' table at a special non profit event: The People's Music Network, Winter Gathering 2011 to be hosted in Hartford on Friday, January 28th. In brief, for reasons to many to list, there will be limited food served at the concert, where 800 people are expected to attend. There will be a desert table, or as we have come to call it, a Cookie Counter. The plan is to organize, bake up a storm of treats and present and sell the treats at the concert. The Cookie Committee had its first team meeting on December 27 at 6:30 pm at the house of David Kaplan, a non baker with great aspirations. If you have interest in any part of this project: planning, organizing, shopping, baking, serving the goodies, please attend the meeting. Hey, we may only need the one meeting unless it is so much fun that we do two. Note that the concert is sponsored by the non profit PMN. The show has listed 8 acts performing with the headliner being Pete Seeger. All donations made at our Cookie Counter, after expenses, will go to PMN as a donation. Those lucky enough to be working the Cookie Counter are of course right there for the concert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be more meetings before the Event.  We have many ideas.  We met the other day and and many things were discussed.  We need at least 600 packages of cookies.  We Purchase the Wax Paper bags yesterday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They will be prepackaged the night before the concert  1/27/2011 at Avery St Christian Reformed Church.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Kinds  of cookies and who will make them and a wish list&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joyce           Chocolate Jumbles&lt;br /&gt;Caryl            Apple Coffee drops&lt;br /&gt;Susanne       &lt;br /&gt;Margo Lynn  Gluten free Gingersnaps&lt;br /&gt;Sandy           oatmeal raisin&lt;br /&gt;Gayle            Peanut butter Chocolate chips&lt;br /&gt;Jennifer &lt;br /&gt;Paul&lt;br /&gt;Nancy&lt;br /&gt;Cookies we would Like&lt;br /&gt;Snickerdoodles&lt;br /&gt;Rice Crispy treats&lt;br /&gt;Chocolate Chip&lt;br /&gt;apples&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be the one that looks like me.  I will send Phone # to Yeses</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297472736000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293643432000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pete Seeger PMN Cookie Counter Committee CONCERT DAY!!!!!</name><id>15849402</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296253800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/15849402/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/3/global_20359475.jpeg</photo_url></item>