<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>22.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/4/3/e/event_181525662.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3b74a4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arts &amp;amp; Creative Cultural Events Party&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;I always find the month of January can really drag and it is more of a challenge to find events for us to partake in. Lets celebrate four years of Cultural Events in a private party, with live music featuring Steve Asetta and the Ringers who will be playing for our dancing pleasure. This will be a nice chance to mix and mingle and get to know some of the truly nicest people you will ever meet in our own group. Anyone who has joined us for events at Lyric Hall, will tell you this is a wonderful venue with great atmosphere and charm, and always a good time. So join us for a glass of wine and light appetizers as we groove and mingle. I want to thank you all for sharing so many memorable experiences in our past four years and I am hoping to see you all there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #12466b"&gt;$22.00 per person for venue rental, band and refreshments. An RSVP will redirect you to Paypal. I need to start preparations, so a number of people attending is important so that we are well prepared, for food, beverage....Please let me know if you are coming in a message if you have not RSVPed already.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #c76924"&gt;We go to this venue often, it is truly a special place, you can park just across the street on West Rock ave near Manjares and the park. There is also more parking up the Whalley across from Soho Hair Salon. Our members are helpful and if you wish to be escorted to your car after the event, people are good like that. Also parking across from the old Blake Street andin back of Kehler Liddell - entered by way of West Rock ave on the right side of Whalley. &lt;strong&gt;Enter Lyric Hall through the LEFT SIDE ENTRANCE, THROUGH THE SIDE RAMP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>the place is ours for the night, will be easy...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358226418000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353367060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events Groove and Mingle Party</name><id>92095012</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358035200000</time><rsvp_limit>85</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/92095012/</event_url></item>