<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Do you feel an inner &amp;ldquo;tug of war&amp;rdquo; over some things, like, &amp;ldquo;I wish &amp;ndash;x-, but I also want &amp;ndash;y-.&amp;rdquo; (I want to be thinner; but I also want to eat what I want!&amp;rdquo;) One part of you wants one thing, but another part wants something else, creating inner resistance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Do you hear yourself saying, &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t.&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I wish I had the willpower or discipline to do that.&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Do you feel stuck in some part of your life you wish you could get on with?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;These are often signs of having an inner conflict or a limiting belief around what you want, and gives the Universe a very confusing "message", so to speak!  Would it be nice to end the suffering caused by what seems like an inner battle?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us for May&amp;rsquo;s FREE community evening:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connecting to your Inner Wisdom to Get &amp;ldquo;Unstuck&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;(&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;This public event is co-sponsored by Roots and Wings and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service. We're sharing it with you since we think it's so applicable for releasing resistance to allow what you want to manifest; and we hope you'll join us!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Tonight, through a combination of instruction and guided inner processes, you can discover how what &lt;em&gt;seem &lt;/em&gt;like inner enemies can actually be your inner &lt;em&gt;allies &lt;/em&gt;when you connect inwardly in the right way. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;By participating in this experiential class, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;How to reach a satisfying and comfortable resolution to your inner conflicts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;How to more easily and spontaneously act in ways that fit with who you want to be as a person, honoring &lt;em&gt;all &lt;/em&gt;parts of yourself, without any need for will power or discipline, but with ease and flow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;How to align, allow and open up new possibilities for yourself in something you&amp;rsquo;re currently feeling emotionally drained by.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;All are welcome to this free community event! The class is appropriate for everyone.  Please invite others to sign up and join you.  Share this with your friends, family and groups. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required.&amp;nbsp; Please plan on arriving around 7:05 to get settled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"I continue to be blown away by what happens to me when I come here.  Between the guided meditations and learning processes to address my own personal negative thoughts and behaviors, I am feeling so much stronger than before I was blessed to find you.  Thank you!"  Cheryl B.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;"Ann has been a huge source of support for me. Her powerful meditations allowed me to access inner guidance and confidence beyond what I was able to tap into on my own.  Meeting this part of me helped me shift a long held belief that was not serving me or my business.  It was so freeing personally and created instant bottom line results in my business."  Paula G.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : small"&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach.  Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success.  With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs in the Roots studio</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306367648000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304368198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connect to your Inner Wisdom to Get “Unstuck”!</name><id>17514862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305674100000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/17514862/</event_url></item>