<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Special Deaf Awareness Week event screening with director Ann Marie "Jade" Bryan in person!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;IF YOU COULD HEAR MY OWN TUNE&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in NYC, carefree Somalia (Sylvie Marc-Charles) seemed pretty content with life. She has a good-looking musician boyfriend, Zavier (Omar Jaslin); is in school to become a fashion designer; and has her own place. She likes to hit up the clubs just to feel the music, and has her own circle of friends who accepts her for who she is. A recurring complication soon becomes an issue between Somalia and her boyfriend that bifurcate their relationship. Her relationship with Zavier is put to the test when personal experiences becomes communal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film underscores the integration of the relationship between the hearing and the Deaf communities as well as other cultures. The director writes: "We believe in integration and interaction that places strong emphasis in addressing communication barriers and toppling them. There are issues we would like to address for the lack of representation, inappropriate exploitations, and negative stereotyping and ineffective exposure."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This screening is a co-presentation with the Deaf &amp;amp; Hard of Hearing Film Series, Northeastern University's ASL Program, Temple Emeth and Brookline Hearing Services, Inc. This is an encore presentation of the premiere screening from the 2011 Roxbury International Film Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This film will be presented with open-captioned subtitles for the Deaf &amp;amp; Hard of Hearing as well as for the ASL-impaired, making it fully accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BUY YOUR TICKETS ONLINE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/if-you-could-hear-my-own-tune" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/content/if-you-could-hear-my-own-tune&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Boston ASL Meetup folks!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth </member_name><member_id>8551199</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316655826000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>ASL Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonasl</urlname><id>1298565</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston ASL</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315086070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coolidge Corner Deaf and Hard of Hearing Film Series</name><id>32160012</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316559600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonasl/events/32160012/</event_url></item>