<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>145 Lang Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.899410</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Northwest Park</name><city>Windsor</city><id>664559</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.702910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lots of daylight after work, so let's get together for another walk at Northwest Park in Windsor.  We'll meet in the parking lot at 5:30 and start walking promptly at 5:45.  Expect to be out for about 90 minutes or so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a socially paced relatively easy walk over rolling terrain, with some interesting features and views.  If it's still hot, you may want water and bug repellant may not be a bad idea either.  Last time I was there, the trails had some muddy spots, so consider your footwear as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park information at &lt;a href="http://www.northwestpark.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.northwestpark.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids and dogs welcome.  Park rules require a leash (on the dogs, not the kids, use your own judgement there!).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking lot near my tan Ford Edge</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241267283000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240769828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another weeknight walk at Northwest Park</name><id>10270781</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240867800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10270781/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/e/global_2859934.jpeg</photo_url></item>