<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>@ 27th Street</address_2><address_1>233 Fifth Avenue</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>10016</zip><lat>40.744029</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>212-689-6337</phone><name>The Museum of SEX!</name><city>NYC</city><id>901720</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.987350</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>9.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>HEY MADAMS, I CHANGED INFO ON THIS EVENT PLEASE SEE DISCOUNTED TICKET PURCHASE CHANGE BELOW&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;OUR MEMBER DISCOUNT....TIX&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Tickets are usually &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;$18&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, but I have purchased 5 discounted tickets from Groupon before the sale ended a month ago for &lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;$9.00 from Groupon/b]&lt;/b&gt; So &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;u&gt;so please pay Romana the event host at the door when you get there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Diamond and Gold Member Madames, get first grab of the discount tix!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Payment Option for Discount TIX NOT ONLINE W/EVENT HOST ON SATuURDAY!&lt;/b&gt;s:&lt;/span&gt; You can purchase your ticket in person with Romana (event host) at our next event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more info on the Museum, read this...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Museum of Sex is devoted to the cross-cultural and historical study of human sexuality. The permanent collection houses more than 15,000 artifacts and chronicles the expression of our pheromones in art, photography, clothing and costumes, ultra-modern technology, and historical ephemera. Instead of ignoring, repressing, burning, or flagellating these items, the museum celebrates and studies them in an open-minded, intellectual, and titter-free environment. Current exhibits include Action: Sex and the Moving Image, which traces the way sexual imagery has impacted everything from film to advertising, and Rubbers: The Life, History, &amp;amp; Struggle of the Condom, which explores the history of the small but mighty prophylactic and its clumsily unfurled place in modern culture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;While stopping through, be sure to visit the museum's Mosex Store and peruse the purchasable plethora of titillating art, books, toys, and oddities—or indulge in the sensual aphrodisiacs available at the OralFix Aphrodisiac Café. A lusty Almond Mocha Love Bar ($3) goes particularly well with a potent Lucky Devil potion (cinnamon and cardamom with a honey gold crystal rim and an extra shot of saffron; $4.50). After an enlightening visit to the Museum of Sex, you’ll put aside staid notions of baby-delivering storks, as well as the puritanical idea that the human body should only be used to harvest grain and act as catapult ballast.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting outside...have a black coat on. My # 718 962-4086</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292202181000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Madams</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Multicultural-Womens-Network</urlname><id>1530786</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Multicultural Women's Network (MWN): Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288958249000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FOR ALL MEMBERS: Museum of Sex Event,5 Discounted Tix  Available, WILL Go FAST!!</name><id>15347915</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292097600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Multicultural-Womens-Network/events/15347915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/3/1/global_19397169.jpeg</photo_url></item>