<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>***I can't get a straight answer from showcase if they have officially ended bargain tuesdays, but they stopped advertising for it which makes me suspect they did.  So be warned....the movie may be full price****.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event: SPIDERMAN 3 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews: Amil raves &amp;quot;Eh&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location : NORTH HAVEN SHOWCASE (possibly former) Bargain Tuesday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: movie is at 7:15, I'll be at Barnes and Noble from 6:30, stop by there early or at the theatre round 7ish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: dave 499-7777&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An open letter to Kirsten Dunst:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dear Kirsten,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm sure you're aware that thanks to a single souless writer on &amp;quot;The Family Guy&amp;quot; your name has been smeered across the internet in the now all too often quoted catch phrase &amp;quot;That's like asking me to choose between Sarah Jessica Parker and Kirsten Dunst in a hot body, weird face competition.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Truly horrible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can only imagine the damage this has done to your ego and pray you will recover from this viscous blow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take heed that neither I nor Jake Gyllenhaal feel this way about you........well, then again maybe Jake does, I mean after all he did break up with you....so he must have had his reasons and I suppose it could have been your face.....but you know, Jake is a weird guy so who knows what's going on in his head.  Also to my knowledge he's never dated Sarah Jessica Parker....so on further reflection maybe he does think this way.     You know what, this is coming out all wrong, let's just forget I even brought Jake into this. Anyway, who cares? So what if he does think you have a weird face?  Screw him. What was the last hit movie he even had?  That cowboy thing?  Please. He just did that just to get attention. That phoney emo hipster.  Who does he think he is?  Just some dude with  sheep dog eyebrows who always looks like he's about to start crying because someone took away his doll.  You know what Jake....buy some tweezers and get over it already.  One things for sure, Jake saying that you have a weird face is truly the pot calling the kettle black, yessiree....he has some nerve.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But anyway....still, you can rest assured that despite what that low life Jake thinks, I do not feel this way about you....so at the very least you have that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerly - dave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event: SPIDERMAN 3 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reviews: Amil raves &amp;quot;Eh&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location : NORTH HAVEN SHOWCASE (possibly former) Bargain Tuesday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: movie is at 7:15, I'll be at Barnes and Noble from 6:30, stop by there early or at the theatre round 7ish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact: dave 499-7777&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178836805000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178461161000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spiderman 3...maybe more than $5</name><id>5747094</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178663400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5747094/</event_url></item>