<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Walnut Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02460</zip><lat>42.346506</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Church</name><city>Newtonville</city><id>1280079</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.206274</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Raw New England Community &amp;amp; Optimum Health Solution invite You To A Live Food Potluck/Movie Gathering for fellowship and to see and discuss the documentary: May I Be Frank - A film of Amazing Transformation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May I Be Frank documents the transformation of Frank Ferrante's life. Frank is 54 years old, obese, depressed and addicted. He stumbles into a local raw, organic and vegan restaurant in San Francisco, Café Gratitude. When Ryland, a server at Café Gratitude asks Frank &amp;quot;What is one thing you want to do before you die?&amp;quot; Frank replies, &amp;quot;I want to fall in love one more time, but no one will love me looking the way I do&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ryland, his brother Cary, and Conor, his best friend, are inspired by the possibility of helping Frank. For the next 42 days, Frank will eat only raw food, practice gratitude, visit local holistic practitioners, and get a weekly colonic. Ryland, Conor, and Cary get to support Frank's miraculous transformation. Frank gets a new body, a clearer mind, and most importantly, a soaring spirit. May I Be Frank documents the essence of the human condition and what it truly means to fall in love again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This film is truly amazing and has already changed the life of hundreds of people that have seen it. In fact, Grammy award winner Jason Mraz has screened the trailer at many of his concerts during the pre-show. He also contributed by writing a song that he generously donated to the movie. The song is appropriately called What would love do now. Alanis Morisette is another generous contributor, she blessed the creative team with the gift of one of her hit songs That I would be good. Just as recent as last week, the movie was acknowledged by the world renowned Michael Beckwith, one of the authors of the best selling book and dvd The Secret at the Wellness Film Festival in Los Angeles. All this to say: this movie is changing lives! It's inspiring ad becoming a phenomenon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See the trailer on &lt;a href="http://mayibefrankmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mayibefrankmov...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN:    Tuesday, November 16, 2010&lt;br /&gt;WHERE:  United Methodist Church of Newton,&lt;br /&gt;                430 Walnut St, Newton, MA &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.optimumhealthsolution.org/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.optimumhea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FEE: $10 at door to offset our expenses&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;· 5:30 p.m.  Sign-in, Socialize, Buy Supplements, Books, Water Bottles, Nut Milk Bags and pick up your wheatgrass and sprout order from Randy Jacobs (call Randy to order at 781-894-3183)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;· 6:00 p.m.  Potluck - Please bring a live, plant-based, organic (if possible), vegan, unprocessed, ready to serve dish with serving utensils for 8 people to enjoy. (Enjoy and experience the delicious foods and variety of plant-based foods.)&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;· 6:55 p.m.  Announcements&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;· 7:00 - 8:30 p.m. Film - &amp;quot;may I be FRANK&amp;quot; followed by discussion&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join us for an awesome-enlightening evening!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Questions: Call Betsy Bragg&lt;br /&gt;Hippocrates Health Educator&lt;br /&gt;781-899-6664, cell: 617-835-2913 or&lt;br /&gt;email: Betsy@OptimumHealthSolution.org&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ALL WELCOME - NO PREREGISTRATION NECESSARY&lt;br /&gt;BRING YOUR FRIENDS!&lt;br /&gt;Directions to new Dinner Speaker Location - United Methodist Church in Newtonville &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Location&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Fellowship Hall (Ground Floor) The United Methodist Church of Newton (Across from Newton North High School) 430 Walnut Street, Newtonville MA 02460 - Handicapped Accessible - Plenty of parking available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;15 minute walk from the Newton Highlands MBTA stop on the Riverside D section of green line, arriving on the East Side of Newtonville.. If you do not want to walk, you can take the #59 bus that stops at that station.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gbgm-umc.org/newtnumc/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gbgm-umc.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 11398866</member_name><member_id>11398866</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289953104000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289413629000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OHS/RNEC Potluck &amp; Film</name><id>15405458</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289946600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/15405458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/0/global_19535232.jpeg</photo_url></item>