<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Another walk designed to build an appetite for the main event - lunch! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the parking lot of Great Brook farm &lt;br /&gt;180 North Road &lt;br /&gt;Carlisle, MA 01741&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/gbfm.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chosen by Yankee Magazine's Travel Guide to New England as Editor's Pick 2000, Great Brook Farm State Park stands as a jewel in northern Massachusetts! Agriculture has been part of Great Brook's history for centuries. Holsteins have been kept here for over 60 years and current farmer Mark Duffy continues the tradition with his black &amp;amp; white ladies. Native Americans used sections of Great Brook Farm as sacred sites. Seventeenth century cellar holes comprise &amp;quot;the city&amp;quot; where early English settlers worked one of numerous mill sites on the 1,000 acre park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are over 20 miles of trails available for walkers, hikers, mountain bikers, and horseback riders. During the winter months, cross-country skiing is available and one trail is lantern lit for a &amp;quot;mooon light&amp;quot; experience! The ice cream stand is open through the month of October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 128: Take exit 31B. Follow Route 225 West for 8 miles to the Carlisle center rotary, then turn right on Lowell St. (following the sign to Chelmsford.) Fern's Market is on the corner. The Park entrance is 2 miles ahead on the right.  Make right hand turn onto North Road. Parking area is 1/2 mile down on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Jang Su BBQ&lt;br /&gt;260 Cambridge Street, Burlington, MA 01803&lt;br /&gt;(781) 272-3787 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hiddenboston.com/NewJangSu.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hiddenbost...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once inside New Jang Su, the first thing you will notice is the fact that the tables have barbecue grills built into them. (We wil) go for this option, as the food, as well as the overall experience, is unforgettable. The thin strips of prime rib are scrumptious, and the shredded chicken with onions is just as good. The waitstaff brings several sides to go with the grilled meats, including radish, fish cakes, sprouts in a tangy sauce, soy paste, and large pieces of lettuce that can be used as a kind of pocket to put everything in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the park to the restaurant:&lt;br /&gt;Turn right out of the parking lot on to North Rd, go 1/2 mile&lt;br /&gt;Turn left on to Lowell St, go 2 miles to the Carlisle center rotary&lt;br /&gt;Take 225 East (3/4 way around the rotary)&lt;br /&gt;Continue about 6 miles to Rte 62&lt;br /&gt;Take rte 62 East for about 4 miles to Cambridge ST (Rte 3A) and turn left.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227540834000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224970030000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Brook Farm state park &amp; Korean BBQ</name><id>9030996</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227367800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9030996/</event_url></item>