<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>340 Faneuil Hall</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02135</zip><lat>42.352100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-227-2038</phone><name>Durgin Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>1118147</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.164200</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I thought it would be fun to get together and have a traditional Thanksgiving dinner. So, we're going to have it at one of the oldest establishments in Boston.  &amp;quot;Durgin-Park is a centuries-old restaurant at Faneuil Hall Marketplace and it has been a &amp;quot;landmark since 1827.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In keeping with its long history, the concept of Durgin-Park maintains the tradition of communal seating at long tables. The menu is designed to offer traditional New England-style fare.&amp;quot;  It is well know for its waitstaff to be rude and talk back to the customer.  This is part of the whole experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Thanksgiving, Durgin Park will have a turkey dinner, a ham dinner, and a sea food dinner.  The dinners range from $19.99 (for the ham) to $35.99 (for the seafood).  Turkey dinner is $24.99.  This cost is for the whole meal not just an entree.  I will send out more specifics about the menus when I get that information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Durgin Park is accessible by T: Green or Blue Line to Government Center, Green or Orange Line to Haymarket, or Blue Line to Aquarium.  There is also parking under Boston Commons for $11/day on weekend and week days after 4pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will allow maybe RSVPs for now, but will change the maybes to nos closer to the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Noelle</member_name><member_id>4227453</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259624428000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257994560000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thanksgiving Dinner</name><id>11855918</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259280000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/11855918/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/2/3/global_7135059.jpeg</photo_url></item>