<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Lecture - Ghosts and Spirits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a Ghost? Is it somehow different from a Spirit? And can either manifest itself onto our earthly plane of existence? Join A. J. Kitt, founder and lead investigator of the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group, and Isabeau Esby, internationally known Psychic Medium, as they discuss the realities of hauntings and what possibilities may lurk in any home, business, or graveyard!  Paranormal evidence, both audio and visual will be presented during the lecture from a variety of ghost investigations performed in the New England area.  Are you ready to see a ghost?  Hear the dead?  If you are, join us for this informative, humorous and sometimes eerie event. &lt;br /&gt;AJ Kitt, professional artist, Mensan, and founder of the Seacoast Paranormal Research Group, has a University of New Hampshire Bachelors degree in Journalism. Together, Isabeau and Andy lecture on Spiritualism and Paranormal activity, and with a team of investigators they test the validity of claims of paranormal activity across New England.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The lecture on October 17th requires registration, please register with Open Doors at www.OpenDoors7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;List of appearances&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, October 7th, 2009&lt;/b&gt; - The Goodwin Library, 422 Main St, Farmington, NH&lt;br /&gt;Time - 6 PM to 7:30 PM, free, no registration required arrive early to guarantee a seat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saturday, October 17th, 2009&lt;/b&gt; -  Open Doors, 395 Washington Street, Braintree, MA &lt;br /&gt;Time - 7 PM to 8:30 PM, $10 Registration Required -  or click here to register Open Doors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Halloween! Saturday, October 31st, 2009&lt;/b&gt; - Eye of the Hawk, 5 Grove Rd, Rye, NH 03870&lt;br /&gt;Time - 9:00 PM to 11:00 PM, $15 in advance, $25 at the door, visit www.eyeofthehawk.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256248325000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252857596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ghosts and Spirits</name><id>11360269</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255820400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/11360269/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/a/1/global_2599441.jpeg</photo_url></item>