<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's try this again...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me on a walk to Massasoit State Park, just a few precious minutes from my house.  We'll be walking through paths in the woods.  These paths have a lot of roots and rocks, and there are a few minor hilly areas (a few ups and downs, nothing serious).  This isn't exactly a hike, but it may be considered a bit more than a walk, so please plan accordingly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be doing a loop, which will include paths along some very scenic lake areas.  The walk will be about 2 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is one thing of note:  Rest rooms are NOT available at the main parking area and the route that we are taking does not come upon any rest rooms until we near the end.  So, unless you don't mind heading off-trail for a little privacy, I strongly suggest you stop at a rest area/gas station if necessary before showing up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Massasoit State Park is located in south-eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;From Cape Cod or Worcester: Take Rte. 495 to Exit 5 in Middleborough. Take Rte. 18 South to the first intersection where there is a yellow flashing light. Turn right onto Taunton Street which becomes Middleboro Ave. Park entrance will be on the left, about 2.5 miles from flashing light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Take Rte. 24 south - Rte. 44 east. At first traffic light, turn right onto South St. E.. Follow to end. Turn left onto Middleboro Ave. Continue about 2 miles to Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Fall River/Providence: Take Rte. 195 East - Rte. 24 North - Rte. 44 East. At first traffic light, turn right onto South St. E.. Follow to end. Turn left onto Middleboro Ave. Continue about 2 miles to Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info: &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/mass.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On google maps:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;q=Massasoit+Park+Road+%26+Middleboro+Ave+Taunton+MA&amp;amp;sll=41.880457,-70.98597&amp;amp;sspn=0.014922,0.038581&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.88509,-70.994232&amp;amp;spn=0.00746,0.01929&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=addr&amp;amp;om=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch is at the Longhorn Steakhouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.longhornsteakhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.longhornst...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;800 US Route 44&lt;br /&gt;Raynham, MA 02767&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 508-821-9246 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send my cell # to the 'Yes' list</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Norm</member_name><member_id>3307175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224112955000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222645853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massasoit State Park</name><id>8852958</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223821800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/8852958/</event_url></item>