<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I'm starting a series of game nights at my place on the 2nd and 4th Monday of each month. They'll all start at 7:00. BYOB, BYOS(nacks).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to, bring $1 to contribute towards our Meetup fees.  It's much appreciated, but absolutely not required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll play a variety of games, but they'll mostly be Euros or strategy games rather than party games, mainly due to space issues.  (But also because I have an unmet craving for these types of games!)  Suggestions will certainly be accepted for future events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The attendee limit at each of these events will be determined by the maximum number of players the game can accommodate, so it will vary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests aren't allowed at these events for three reasons:  1)  A very limited number of spots are available due to the nature of the games we'll be playing.  2)  It's easy enough for someone to join our group if they want to come.  If you have a "guest" you wish you could bring, just have them join the group and sign up.  3)  If you sign up with a guest and then bail at the last minute, chances are your guest won't come either, so we're down two players from what we expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a waiting list available.  Please, if you sign up, be considerate of others and change your RSVP as soon as possible if you find you can't come.  No shows will be publicly derided.  If you're on the waiting list and get moved up on the day of the event, I'll try to contact you to make sure you're aware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing (and competing with!) you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;This time: &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power Grid.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/4/0/event_141754112.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an awesome game where you buy (at auction) power plants that operate on either coal, oil, garbage, uranium, or wind. Then you buy the resources you need to power those plants. Finally, you decide which of the cities you control are going to be powered by your plants, and receive payment for that power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lots of decisions to be made, such as:  Should I replace my old, inefficient coal plant with a nifty new nuke plant? Should I buy my resources this turn, or might they be cheaper next turn?  Should I move into a more expensive city just to cut off my opponent, or should I select a cheaper option?  How much is that Wind plant really worth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You're gonna love this game!  It's currently the number 6 ranked board game on boardgamegeek.com, with an outstanding rating of 8.02 out of 10.  Playing time is about 2 hours, although it'll take a little longer with new players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trust me:  Play it once and you will be back for more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send parking instructions and further info to "yes" RSVPs a few days before the event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344984491000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1343010388000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Power Grid @ Mitch's  (2nd and 4th Monday Game Series)</name><id>74480862</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344898800000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/74480862/</event_url></item>