<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>church st and railroad st</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01225</zip><lat>42.562023</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Mass AT: Ashuwillticook Rail Trail</name><city>Chesire</city><id>6648622</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.157060</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part 8 of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail! Join us on Saturday April 28th to do the eighth part of a series of hikes that I will be scheduling to do the entire length of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail. We will meet at the &lt;span&gt;Ashuwillticook Rail Trail&lt;/span&gt;, at the intersection of church st and railroad st in Chesire, which will be the ending location of our hike. We'll then leave half the cars and drive over to &lt;span&gt;the AT trail head on Gulf rd in Dalton&lt;/span&gt;(the ending location of the last hike). The total distance of this hike is 7.7 miles.....total elevation change is a gain of around 1000ft.  Based on our past hiking speeds this will be about a 6 hour hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Mass AT Hiked Before this section: &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;62.6 out of 89.7 70%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Mass AT Hiked After this section: 70.3 out of 89.7 78%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a long hike with some elevation change. Please bring plenty of water (I'm bringing 3 liters) appropriate hiking attire (no jeans or cotton, hiking boots not sneakers), rain gear in case the weather turns nasty, lunch, and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trailhead Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Providence 2 hours 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead lat/lon: 42.562212,-73.156881&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking lot is for the Ashuwillticook Rail Trail where Church st and Railroad st intersect in Chesire.   It looks like the parking is on railroad st just south of the intersection. Google Maps link to the location and directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=railroad+st+and+church+st&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=42.561565,-73.157102&amp;amp;spn=0.000854,0.001742&amp;amp;sll=42.562212,-73.156881&amp;amp;sspn=0.003418,0.006968&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;hnear=Church+St+%26+Railroad+St,+Cheshire,+Berkshire,+Massachusetts+01225&amp;amp;z=20" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?q=railroad+st+and+church+st&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=42.561565,-73.157102&amp;amp;spn=0.000854,0.001742&amp;amp;sll=42.562212,-73.156881&amp;amp;sspn=0.003418,0.006968&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;hnear=Church+St...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Route Information (starting from Gulf rd in Dalton)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 miles to an outlet of Gore Pond&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1.7 miles to the boundary between Dalton and Chesire&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.8 miles to the Ashuwillticook Rail Trail&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments section to coordinate with other hikers if you want to carpool. There is limited parking so car pooling is recommended....just remember that we do have to carspot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Massachusetts Appalachian Trail Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/2/2/event_109442082.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;MAP NOTE: What we have hiked is in black, current section in red, remaining trail red dots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ashuwillticook Rail Trail, railroad st and church st, Chesire, MA  look for a grey Nissan Juke with RI plates. Cell: 508-414-8544. See google maps ink below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335624330000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334185187000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massachusetts Appalachian Trail: Part 8</name><id>60193072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335619800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/60193072/</event_url></item>