<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This meetup will be held in the Center of Light house in Jamaica Plain. Refreshments will be provided. Fees for this meetup also cover airfare and accommodations for our speaker Mother Clare Watts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The topic for this meetup is the Love, Sex and God:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For centuries, churches dealt with the fiery energies that arose when men and women interacted by keeping genders in separate monasteries, or by pushing for rapid marriage, in order to avoid having to address sexual and emotional intimacy issues. Very little consciousness was brought to developing deeply loving relationships that were not to be romantic or physical. Nor was there hardly any advice given about where sexuality belongs in relationships that are romantic and physical, while seeking to have God at their center. Now, in the 21rst Century, we have been given the assignment to bring Light, consciousness, and god into these issues. We will be addressing both how to approach finding a mate and where spirituality and sexuality belong in an already-established relationship. We will also speak about being single, the celibate life, and deep, meaningful relationships that are platonic. Join us for this seminar, and get all your questions answered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this sounds good to you please also note these additional seminars with Mother Clare:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, February 14th: The Joy of Being Single ($25)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, February 16th: Devotion - The True Path to God ($35 includes lunch)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203295155000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>This workshop is for anyone looking for a deeper sense of connection. Join us for an inspiring seminar with Mother Clare Watts, Christian Mystic and master teacher.</why><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202700716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guest Speaker:  Mother Clare Watts discusses Love, Sex &amp; God</name><id>7307205</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203121800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/7307205/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/7/1/global_622209.jpeg</photo_url></item>