<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>New Haven</address_2><address_1>61 Lyon St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.308693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-415-4605</phone><name>GRAND PROJECTS</name><city>New Haven</city><id>327447</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since 2002, GRAND PROJECTS has provided site-specific solo exhibitions for emerging artists. Artists are invited to make ambitious interventions in this humble project space, &lt;br /&gt;located in a converted stone garage in Wooster Square.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now GRAND PROJECTS is pleased to present Killer Angels by Mark Williams, an installation of light drawings. Killer Angels examines the marketing of war to children.  With strands of lights, Williams depicts the uneasy hybridization of toy soldiers and Play-Doh molded animals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Williams has recently exhibited work at the Wadsworth Athenaeum in Hartford, CT, Atlantic Gallery in New York, NY, Roy G Biv Gallery in Columbus, Ohio, Artspace, and the Green Gallery at Yale University in New Haven, CT. In 2006 Williams was a fellow &lt;br /&gt;at the Vermont Studio Center in Johnson, VT.  He holds an MFA from UCONN and a BFA from Miami University in Ohio. Williams currently lives and works in New Haven, CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This exhibition is one night only: Friday, July 27 between 8pm and 10pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on GRAND PROJECTS, &lt;a href="http://www.grandprojects.com" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. For more information on Mark's artwork, &lt;a href="http://www.livepaint.org" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. Mark and his artwork are also featured in the new issue of Play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Williams is the contact for this event: (401) 261-9590&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541803000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1184954061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fri. 7/27 - GRAND PROJECTS featuring work by artist Mark Williams</name><id>6053269</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185580800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6053269/</event_url></item>