<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06088</zip><lat>41.907609</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 627-7709</phone><name>Jonathan Pasco's</name><city>East Windsor</city><id>712519</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.612971</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Captain Jonathan Pasco...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Jonathan Pasco was born on September 29, 1760 in East Windsor, George II sat on the the throne of England, and the thirteen original colonies--still under British control--were sixteen years from their independence. George Washington was 28 years old, and Abraham Lincoln would not be born for fifty years. America was a new and developing country and Jonathan Pasco would be a part of that development. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1776 Jonathan Pasco enlisted in Colonel John Patterson's Massachusetts regiment. He fought with that regiment in the battle of Trenton. The battle of Trenton, known as the Christmas campaign, was an important American victory because it renewed the spirit of the patriot forces and seriously disarranged the plans of the British. The battle was fought in the early morning of December 25, after the commander-in-chief of all the Continental forces, George Washington, crossed the Delaware River. They marched to the enemy's camp at Trenton and took the Hessians, by surprise. Nearly one thousand British prisoners were captured. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Legend contends that sometime during the Revolutionary War, Pasco and several other soldiers were captured by Indians. An unsuccessful escape attempt was made resulting in their recapture. As an example, one of the group was singled out, tortured and skinned alive. In order to establish his &amp;quot;parole not to escape,&amp;quot; Pasco was given a pocketbook made of the torture victim's skin and was forced to take an Indian women for a wife. Pasco eventually did escape and returned to East Windsor. He named his second daughter Cleons, after his Indian wife. The pocketbook has been handed down through the generations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After returning from the Revolutionary War, Captain Pasco constructed his home at 31 South Main Street in East Windsor. He married a local woman, Elizabeth Allen, and fathered eleven children while residing there. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the age of eighty-four, Jonathan Pasco died. (August 21, 1844) He is buried in East Windsor in the Town Street Cemetery (historical name for South Main Street), only a mile south of the Pasco House. He also has a headstone in the Scantic Cemetery that commemorates his revolutionary War service. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Events and happenings occurred, history was made and changed, and Jonathan Pasco's house continues at 31 South Main Street moving through the centuries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Tribute...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A collection of Pasco memorabilia is included in the decor of the restaurant, creating an interesting tribute to Jonathan Pasco. Pasco's decedents are scattered, but a few still remain in the East Windsor area. All have been helpful in creating the atmosphere of the restaurant and the accuracy of the history presented. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The House...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Jonathan Pasco House was built by its namesake in 1782 and completed for occupancy by his family in 1784. The original brick structure has been completely restored to serve as a restaurant dedicated to providing fine dining for dinner without altering the historical significance and traditional flavor of the Jonathan Pasco House. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us for a a bit of history...dining at Jonathan Pasco's. Enjoy the ambiance while breaking bread with friends ( old and new)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See You There!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup sign on the table/ ask for Terri Bruno's table!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257105958000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255105204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Night of Dining at Jonathan Pasco's!  Dine in history!!!  </name><id>11589120</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256857200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/11589120/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/9/6/global_11128758.jpeg</photo_url></item>