<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Please RSVP! Don't miss this one!&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
      &lt;span&gt;Investment Opportunities in a Risky World&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;
      &lt;span&gt;Presentation by Stephen Cucchiaro, Chief Investment Officer, Windhaven Investment Management, a subsidiary of The Charles Schwab Corporation&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Stephen Cucchiaro will give his outlook on current economic trends and market risks.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Stock markets face headwinds including the Japanese earthquake, unrest in the Middle East, and the European debt crises.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; In the U.S., we face growing national debt, our housing is recovering slowly, and high unemployment persists.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Nonetheless, the U.S. economy is improving, and corporate earnings are growing.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Steve will review the global dynamics that led to our current market conditions.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; He&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the ETFs that Windhaven uses to diversify its portfolios and limit risks.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Windhaven diversifies across global capital markets and asset classes, ranging from equities, fixed income, currencies, and hard assets like gold and agricultural commodities.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Windhaven adjusts asset allocations as conditions change to hedge against risks.
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; They strive to capture much of gains in rising markets, and limit losses in falling markets.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Bio of Stephen Cucchiaro&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;Stephen Cucchiaro is the Chief Investment Officer of Windhaven Investment Management, a Boston-based global asset management firm with over $6 billion in institutional and private client funds. Mr. Cucchiaro has conducted over 30 years of research and development of a proprietary model of the key economic, fundamental and behavioral relationships driving the global capital markets. 
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;He earned a B.S. in Mathematics at M.I.T. and an M.B.A. in Finance at Wharton, where he began to apply the principles of nonlinear dynamic systems from science and engineering to portfolio theory and investment management. Prior to founding Windward Investment Management (The portfolio management team of Windhaven Investment Management, Inc. was formerly with Windward Investment Management, Inc.), Mr. Cucchiaro held positions as a management consultant, senior economist and technology entrepreneur. He was president and co-founder of Datext which was sold to Lotus Development Corporation, and president of ICAD which he helped position for IPO and sale to Oracle Corporation. During the late 1970s, Mr. Cucchiaro was a member of the U.S. Olympic Team in yacht racing and became national champion of his class in 1978 and Gold Medalist in the 1979 Pan American Olympic Games.&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;
   &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING Announcement:
   &lt;br /&gt; The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets during the hour from 5:30 PM to 6:50 PM. Go to&lt;/span&gt; 
  &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;
    &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join our online discussion go to
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google.com/bostonibd&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312935415000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>88</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309878959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Group July Meetup - special speaker - Stephen Cucchiaro</name><id>24605231</id><headcount>121</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311807600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/24605231/</event_url></item>