<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Happy Holidays Fellow Organizers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get together for some holiday cheer to meet and get to know each other over lunch.  This will be a great opportunity to meet fellow Meetup Organizers from all over the Boston area - and beyond!  (All Organizer and Assistant Organizers in MA, as well as NH and RI, are welcome.)  Bring your Organizer cap, some success stories, some lessons learned, and some questions.  We'll do a round table of introductions and spend some time talking about being a Meetup Organizer and discuss success stories, lessons learned, and answer questions, all while getting to know each other in a comfortable casual environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;The Fours Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;15 Cottage Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Quincy Center&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;br /&gt;617-471-4447&lt;br /&gt;www.thefours.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time: 1:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Angela and Dale&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max:  At least 6 Yes RSVPs by December 12th.  No maximum.&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome, especially if they're fellow Orgs/AO's!&lt;br /&gt;Event Cost: Free, pay for your own food and drinks.  Food starts around $4 for Appetizers, and $7 for Meals/Entrees.  Please bring cash.  Small bills appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, December 14th @ 4pm (After this time the Organizer may not see RSVP changes.)  Please Note: Maybe RSVPs will not be allowed w/in 5 days of the Meetup and must be updated by the RSVP Deadline.  This is important as we will be meeting at a restaurant and want to make sure we can accommodate everyone accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Location: Please meet in the Lobby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: For door-to-door directions please use mapquest.com.  Directions are also posted on the restaurant's website.  The directions can be a little confusing once you get to Quincy Center.  The Fours is located across the street from the Quincy District Courthouse off a large parking lot surrounded by other restaurants and retail shops.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving Directions: &lt;br /&gt;From Routes 24/128: Follow Route 93 North to Exit 7/Route 3 South.  Take your first Exit (18-19) towards Burgin Parkway/Quincy Center.  Pick-up below at &amp;quot;From Burgin Parkway.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 93: Follow Route 93 South to Exit 18 towards Burgin Parkway/Quincy Center.  Pick-up below at &amp;quot;From Burgin Parkway.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;From Burgin Parkway: Follow the signs to Quincy Center.  Stay straight on Burgin Parkway going straight through 4 sets of lights.  At your 4th set of lights Star Market will be on your left and you will see the Stop and Shop HQ building straight ahead at the next set of lights.  At your 5th set of lights the Stop and Shop HQ building will be directly in front of you.  Get in the right-hand lane and take a Right at the light.  There will now be 3 lanes.  You want to get in the Center lane.  At the next light (this gets tricky) go straight past the Bank on the corner and take your first immediate right onto Chestnut Street.  Follow Chestnut Street 1/4 mile and take your 2nd right into the parking lot across from the Quincy District Courthouse.  The Fours is located on the right-hand side of the parking lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from the Quincy Center Redline/Commuter Rail Stop: Exit the T on the Hancock Street side where the bus pick-up is located.  When you leave the T there will be a building in front of you with a Bank on the corner and City Hall will be on your right.  You want to head to the right when you leave the T so the Bank (South Coastal) is behind you and City Hall is on your right so that you are walking into downtown Quincy Center.  At the 2nd light (it's a major intersection) you'll be standing in front of the Stop and Shop HQ and there will be a major Bank (Bank of America?) on the corner in a really tall building.  When crossing the street you can continue straight down Hancock or you can go diagonally across to Chestnut Street.  If you continue down Hancock Street you will need to get on the opposite side of the road as Cottage Street will be on the left.  Walk halfway up Cottage Street and take a right into the Parking lot.  You will go around the building that The Fours is in.  If you walk down Chestnut Street you can either take your first right onto Cottage street and then a left into the parking lot or walk past Cottage Street and turn into the parking lot.  Either way, The Fours is in the parking lot near a little alleyway/street.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you get lost please call the restaurant.  If you stop to ask for directions most people will know where The Fours and/or the Courthouse are located so you can use either one as a reference point.  Sorry directions are so confusing.  Please avoid using Exit 6 (Route 37/Braintree) at all costs if you get a little lost as that is the Exit for the South Shore Plaza and will set you back at least 5 to possibly 10 minutes.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>dale</member_name><member_id>3116571</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198009363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Organizers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NEOrganizers</urlname><id>321127</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2600021362</group_lon><name>New England Meetup Organizers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196214178000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Organizer Meetup!</name><id>6815179</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197743400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NEOrganizers/events/6815179/</event_url></item>