<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1296 Washington Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.349343</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 964 8074</phone><name>West Newton Cinema</name><city>Newton</city><id>837390</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.226648</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Location and time changed! The movie will only be showing at the West Newton Cinema on Saturday, so we have to go there instead. Sorry for the change but it is our only option.&amp;nbsp;If you are late or need to contact me, please&amp;nbsp;call me&amp;nbsp;at my cell: (508) 494-5472.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions from Rt 30 in Framingham to the West Newton Cinema: &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/?version=1.0&amp;amp;hk=7-GmIU93j1"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/?version=1.0&amp;amp;hk=7-GmIU93j1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website of West Newton Cinema:  &lt;a href="http://www.westnewtoncinema.com/index-2b.html"&gt;http://www.westnewtoncinema.com/index-2b.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plot&amp;nbsp;summary: A Spanish film crew arrives in Bolivia to make a film about Columbus in the New World. Idealistic director Sebastian (Gael Garc&amp;iacute;a Bernal, &lt;em&gt;The Motorcycle Diaries&lt;/em&gt;) wants to denounce the injustices of the past, focusing on exploitation of the indigenous people. Practical producer Costa (Luis Tosar, &lt;em&gt;Cell 211&lt;/em&gt;), working on a tight budget, has chosen Bolivia, one of Latin America&amp;rsquo;s poorest countries, to stand in for Santo Domingo because extras will work for only $2 a day. After an open casting call almost degenerates into a riot, Sebastian hires outspoken Daniel (Juan Carlos Aduviri) to play the rebel Indian leader. But when the locals begin demonstrations against a multinational's plans to privatize water&amp;mdash;even the rain&amp;mdash;Daniel is in the thick of them, endangering the film&amp;rsquo;s shooting schedule. The thought-provoking screenplay by Paul Laverty &lt;em&gt;(The Wind That Shakes the Barley)&lt;/em&gt; cunningly parallels the Spanish conquest of the Americas with the modern spread of capitalism. This fascinating mixture of past and present, fiction and fact, features spectacular scenes of the period film within a film. Directed by Ic&amp;iacute;ar Bolla&amp;iacute;n &lt;em&gt;(Take My Eyes)&lt;/em&gt;. (Fully subtitled)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Tambien La Iluvia (aka Even the Rain) was an official selection at the 2010 Toronto International Film Festival.&lt;a href="http://www.eventherainmovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Official Web Site&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of  Best Buy at Shopper's World at 5:00 pm and carpool from there. Otherwise, meet at 5:45 pm inside at the entrance of the West Newton Cinema</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Hill</member_name><member_id>1489154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301701639000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>¡Vamos al cine!</why><group><who>Castellano Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-581</urlname><id>232171</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>The MetroWest-Greater Boston Castellano Speakers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300334437000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie: Even The Rain (Tambien la Lluvia) - Location and time changed!!</name><id>16952397</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301175900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-581/events/16952397/</event_url></item>