<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Anyone interested in kayaking?  Anyone interested in Ultimate Frisbee?  How about both ... at the same time!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alright, no, we ARE NOT going to do both at the same time, but why don't you come out and join us for some kayaking on a gentle river and for some Ultimate Frisbee on a huge open field.  Now is a perfect time to see some of Massachusetts' fall colors, and to play a little bit more Ultimate Frisbee before it gets too cold for shorts and an aggressive &lt;a href="http://www.bofh.com/other/ultimate/ultimate.html#advanced.throwing.hammer" target="_blank"&gt;hammer throw&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will all be taking place over at Noble and Greenough School this Sunday.  Although all should go as planned, I will need to get your phone numbers just in case 1) it rains, or 2) the kayaks become unavailable (since these are school-owned kayaks, we cannot reserve them directly).  Bob will check for us on Saturday to make sure that kayaks are available for Sunday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many thanks to Bob Graham for suggesting this event, and for providing access to the kayaks and playing field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to Bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Food - bring a lunch with you; feel free to bring extra food for friends as well&lt;br /&gt;- Water - bring a water bottle with you, you may want it during Ultimate Frisbee or while kayaking&lt;br /&gt;- Pair of athletic pants  and sandals for the kayak (shorts may be fine as well).  &lt;br /&gt;- Change of clothes.  Although I hope no one ends up in the river, you may want to bring a change of clothes just in case&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;No Car?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you without a car, we can pick you up from Forest Hills T Stop at 10:30 AM.  Please let me know if you will need a ride from the T Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions to Nobles, see below, or go to: &lt;a href="http://www.nobles.edu/home/content.asp?id=93" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nobles.edu...&lt;/a&gt;. (There is a map on the website).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRAVELING SOUTH ON RT.128 (US 95)&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 18 (Great Plain Avenue)&lt;br /&gt;At end of ramp, turn right.&lt;br /&gt;Continue one mile and bear right at St. Susanna's Church onto Pine St.&lt;br /&gt;Continue 1/4 mile to the school entrance which is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRAVELING NORTH ON RT.128 (US 95)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 16&lt;br /&gt;Take Rt. 109 toward Dedham.&lt;br /&gt;Follow 109 to second traffic light and turn left onto Pine St. School entrance is the first left turn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRAVELING ON RT. 1/THE VFW PARKWAY (either way)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turn onto Rt. 109 West.&lt;br /&gt;Turn right at second traffic light onto Pine St.&lt;br /&gt;School entrance is the first left turn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once at Nobles, people should go straight past the first and second intersections, and park near the gym.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will start out at the large sports field.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224025677000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223348344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Autumn Colors Kayaking &amp; Ultimate Frisbee - More Details Added</name><id>8912530</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223823600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/8912530/</event_url></item>