<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302990</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Light</name><city>Framingham</city><id>7536472</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434044</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small"&gt;After Harvard expelled Richard Alpert for LSD experimentation in 1964, the former professor traveled to India and returned as Ram Dass. Now in his seventies, the author of &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be Here Now&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; continues to teach and inspire as he deals with a massive stroke.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small"&gt;Fierce Grace documents Ram Dass remaking his life. While the illness might have broken others, it provided Dass with a new passion: using an unexpected, uninvited challenge as a tool for spiritual transformation, and using what he learns to help others face issues of aging, death and dying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small"&gt;Conscious movies at the Centers of Light are an opportunity to connect with others who are looking for ways to positively change the world. These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! These events are free, and if you would like to give a donation, we will send it to an organization that’s truly helping the world. Come see a free showing at your local Center of Light and join in on the discussion to bring peace and consciousness to our world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small"&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It’s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people! These events are free, and if you would like to give a donation, we will send it to an organization that’s truly helping the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://click.icptrack.com/icp/relay.php?r=85339402&amp;amp;msgid=1053677&amp;amp;act=YPYC&amp;amp;c=370689&amp;amp;destination=http%3A%2F%2Fmovies.centersoflight.org"&gt;Watch the Traile&lt;/a&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : justify"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222 ; font-size : small"&gt;The donations accepted at this screening will support the Seva Foundation. Seva is sanskrit for service to others. Since 1978, Seva has been a leading innovator in building partnerships that deliver cost-effective, culturally informed health services for some of the world's most vulnerable-including women, children and indigenous peoples.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343918440000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342710475000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Conscious Movie Night - Ram Dass - Fierce Grace</name><id>74022002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1343516400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/74022002/</event_url></item>