<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Argilla Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.680200</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 356-4351</phone><name>Crane Beach on the Crane Estate</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>1122116</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.778364</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I don't know about anyone else, but I would rather be hiking on Thanksgiving weekend than shopping in the malls.  So----I checked out Crane Beach Monday (11/16) and its just what we need to exercise away all the turkey day calories.  We can hike the dunes for about two miles, the trail then turns onto the beach.  It's about a mile and a half back to the parking lot along the beach.  High tide is at 7:27am and low tide at 2:13pm so we will have plenty of beach to walk on.&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The trails:  this is what I would call mildly to moderately hilly, a lot of the trail surface is beach sand so the walking is slower.  I had regular hiking boots on that were fine.  Sneakers may not be enough support in the soft sand.  A lot of the trail is open so bring a wind-breaker just in case.  Again, we will go as fast as the slowest hiker, no one gets left behind.  If we need to stop and rest, we will do that, this is the NSNTIH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain will cancel this event.  Dogs are not allowed on the dune trails &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a seven dollar charge to park for non members of the Trustees of Reservations so this would be a good time to car pool and split the cost of parking, it's also environmentally friendly (carbon footprint).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your interested, the same parking ticket can get you into Castle Hill Estate after the hike.  The Crane's Great House is being renovated and is closed.  It's still a great place to walk around and take in the spectacular view. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From Rt. 128 North Exit 20A, take Rt. 1A north for 8 mi. to Ipswich. Turn right onto Rt. 133 East and follow for 1.5 mi. Turn left onto Northgate Rd. and follow for 0.5 mi. Turn right onto Argilla Rd. and follow for 2.5 mi. to entrance and parking (1,300 cars) at end of road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you on the trails!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking lot in a green Toyota 4Runner.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>8103242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259594204000</updated><rating><average>4.86999988556</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258427471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crane Beach</name><id>11891772</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259420400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/11891772/</event_url></item>