<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.842800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Splash Liquid Lounge</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>10531202</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.818153</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/9/4/0/event_183678752.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;You better watch out…You better not cry…You better not pout…Splash Liquid Lounge will close for the Winter season with a special Naughty or Nice Holiday Bash year end party.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;You've been nice all year, so don't you deserve a night that's a little bit naughty? And who says you can’t be both?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So on Saturday December 15th, which just so happens to be closing night, the fun goes down starting at 7:00 pm; there will be festive cocktails at the oversized circular bar, complimentary buffet. Reserve the leather couches in the VIP areas to mix, mingle and summon bottles of Champagne. There's tons of festive entertainment on the docket, too. The band&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;Brandy&lt;/span&gt; performs at 9:00 pm with a wide variety, ranging from the big band, swing and jazz era of the 40's, through the classics of the 50's and 60's, and all the revived 70's and 80's, as well as the 90's, the new swing sound, and continuing to the most current top 40 hits. &lt;span&gt;You can also watch the bartenders make a signature holiday cocktail (information that'll come in handy when you host your own holiday get-togethers), compete in a light-hearted naughty or nice costume contest with awesome prizes, pose for photos with Santa, and fill up our stockings with candy from the Winter Wonderland candy bar, so come ready to &lt;strong&gt;eat, drink, and be merry&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Splash’s year end bash is sure to put just about every other holiday bash you'll attend to shame. Be one of the lucky ones to experience t&lt;/span&gt;he 5,000 square foot liquid lounge with an over-sized bar, individual table seating, VIP areas and an incredible dance floor &lt;span&gt;before it closes for the season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Designated Meetup Table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Knight</member_name><member_id>4009572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355656564000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Men and Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-527</urlname><id>501015</id><group_lat>42.9099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Cocktail Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354212942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Splash Liquid Lounge Closing For Season Holiday Party-Free event</name><id>93353082</id><headcount>85</headcount><duration>21600000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355616000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-527/events/93353082/</event_url></item>