<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Loon Mountain Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.056585</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-229-7829</phone><name>The Mountain Club on Loon</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>1338803</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.625805</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>99.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Although we had a sign-up deadline for this trip it is still possible to join us.  If you are still interested in joining the trip please go to the sign up page and make your payment.  The resort will provide rooms at the same rate based on availability.  Once I receive your payment I will contact them to see if they have space.  You will receive confirmation or a credit based on what is available.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMAGE MAKERS PHOTOGRAPHIC WORKSHOP&lt;/b&gt; will be hosting an &lt;a href="http://www.testoftimephoto.com/WHITE-MOUNTAIN-PHOTO-WORKSHOP.html" target="_blank"&gt;Workshop&lt;/a&gt; workshop with professional photographer and Photography educator Dan Splaine in the White mountains of NH.  on Oct. 16 and 17, 2010.  This overnight trip to the White Mountains of New Hampshire is organized in partnership with &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhtours.com/" target="_blank"&gt;NH TOURS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop includes a guided photography hike to Black Pond, an evening photo review and mini-workshop, overnight accommodations in the &lt;a href="http://www.mtnclub.com/" target="_blank"&gt;MOUNTAIN CLUB on LOON&lt;/a&gt; (one night) and a voucher for the Loon mountain &lt;a href="http://community.loonmtn.com/video/gondola-skyride" target="_blank"&gt;Gondola&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;A great class for beginner and advanced photographers alike!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  The White Mountains in late autumn are vibrant and beautiful.  They provide an abundance of subjects and conditions to challenge and reward image makers of all skill levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WORKSHOP SCHEDULE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Oct 16&lt;br /&gt;• 10:00 a.m.—Meet Dan Splaine in lobby of Mountain Club on Loon, 90 Loon Mountain Rd, Lincoln NH (800-229-7829)  &lt;br /&gt;• Car-pool one-half mile to Lincoln Woods parking area on left on the Kancamagus Highway. ( National park service charges $3 fee per car for a one day parking permit) Hike along the Pemigewasset River. Picturesque Black Pond is a 3 mile hike. You can hike as far as you’d like. Pack a lunch/snack. Another lunch option is to drive into Lincoln or have lunch at our hotel.  Dan will walk with the group and offer photographic advice throughout the hike.&lt;br /&gt;• 3:00 p.m.— Check-in time at Mountain Club on Loon &lt;br /&gt;• Dinner on your own at our hotel or in Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;• 7:00 p.m.—Group will gather in Kinsman Room at hotel to review day’s photographs/plus mini-workshop&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Oct 17&lt;br /&gt;• Breakfast (not included) at the hotel (served 8 to 10 a.m.)—Full buffet or you can order lighter fare off menu&lt;br /&gt;• 9:30 a.m.—Loon Mountain gondola’s first run of the day—Dan will be at the top of the mountain for photography coaching till 11:30 a.m. (gondola runs till 4 p.m.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRICE FOR THIS PACKAGE/WORKSHOP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;$99/person/double occupancy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;       &lt;u&gt;$&lt;b&gt;159/person/single occupancy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Package includes one (1) night Mountain Club on Loon, voucher for Loon Mountain gondola ride, on-location photography coaching, photo critique Saturday night, access to spa &amp;amp; health club (extra fee for spa services), indoor pool, hot tub. Price does not include meals, beverages and transportation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;IMPORTANT INFORMATION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; -  Due to the unique features of this event we will accepting registration and payment through a separate web page.  The RESERVATION and PAYMENT DEADLINE  for this event is Thursday, September 30th.  For complete information, payment options and terms and conditions go to :&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.testoftimephoto.com/WHITE-MOUNTAIN-PHOTO-WORKSHOP.&lt;/b&gt;html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.testoftimephoto.com/WHITE-MOUNTAIN-PHOTO-WORKSHOP.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.testoftime...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Splaine</member_name><member_id>8817946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287242842000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Photography-Workshops</urlname><id>1540111</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>New England Photography Workshops</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280847960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WHITE MOUNTAIN PHOTO WORKSHOP- OVERNIGHT TRIP !</name><id>14304042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287237600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Photography-Workshops/events/14304042/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/0/global_16934096.jpeg</photo_url></item>