<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Description&lt;br /&gt;SUN, June 27@ 5 PM&lt;br /&gt;Regent Theatre &lt;br /&gt;7 Medford Street&lt;br /&gt;Arlington, MA&lt;br /&gt;781-646-4849&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserved Seats: $17 advance; $20 day of show ($15 for groups of 6 or more)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohamed El Hosseny ((Egyptian superstar dancer)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohamed El Hosseny joined the famous Egyptian Reda Troupe in 1992. During his career as a dancer, he performed all solo parts also with Mahmoud Reda's private dance company. Hosseny's repertoire includes both Egyptian folkloric styles and traditional as well as modern Oriental dance. e masters all commonly known Egyptian folk dances, from Saidi to Alexandrian, Nubian to Fellahi, and naturally Simsimiyya, which is in his blood as he has danced it since his childhood in his hometown Suez. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mohamed El Hosseny--widely recognized as the premiere male dancer in Egypt--joined the famous Egyptian Reda Troupe in 1992. During his career as a dancer, he has also performed all solo parts with Mahmoud Reda's private dance company, among them the male solo in the Rubabikiya Operetta in 1999. Besides Egyptian folk dances, Hosseny also studied ballet and performed with the ballerina Diana Calenti for several years and was featured in many television shows.  Hosseny's repertoire includes both Egyptian folkloric styles and traditional as well as modern Oriental dance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has mastered all commonly known Egyptian folk dances, from Saidi to Alexandrian, Nubian to Fellahi, and naturally Simsimiyya, which is in his blood as he has danced it since his childhood in his hometown Suez. Ballet training of many years has given him power, body control and dancing technique on which he builds his charismatic stage expression. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;El Hosseny currently teaches dance in Helsinki and gives workshops in other locations in Finland as well as other countries throughout the world. He has taught in many festivals, among them Yalla! Festival of Oriental Dance in Helsinki and Ahlan Wa Sahlan Festival in Cairo. Hosseny is the director of El Hosseny Dance Company, founded in 2005. For more information and video clips go to &lt;a href="http://nourhansharif.com/elhosseny.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://nourhansharif....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to the featured concert on the Regent main stage on Sunday, June 27 at 5pm, Hosseny will be teaching workshops throughout the weekend (Friday-Sunday, June 25-27). For details and to register, visit &lt;a href="http://www.za-beth.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.za-beth.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://nourhansharif..." target="_blank"&gt;http://nourhansharif....&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.regenttheatre.com/events/Mohamed_El.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.regentthea...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1277677196000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277069933000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mohamed El Hosseny (Egyptian superstar dancer)</name><id>13857484</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277672400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/13857484/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/f/global_15852959.jpeg</photo_url></item>