<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>TOPIC: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What if consumers were networked as well as business professionals? &lt;br /&gt;What if this could help you be more succesful in your business?&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are going to talk about developing a wealth of information that could help you change the way we consume. There is an easy way to support the health of yourself and your family, and the health of the Earth. Going Green and all the buzz words associated with it have been saturating our lives of recent. Many people find it annoying because it is confusing and because of the media. People are therefore driven away from getting involved, but I want to decode all the talk and explain why it is really important.  I also want to discuss the importance of this movement to your business, and the competitive edge you can develop. We know this is where new business is trending and we need to keep up in the ever changing world, so let's do it! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Networking will be held as usual so bring business cards and any small marketing materials you have for other members. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please email me with any questions, I look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;P.S. I suggest taking the Green Line to our green meeting, get off at the Copley stop. If anyone would like to meet for dinner beforehand please let me know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the lobby</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222383751000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Energy Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-1402</urlname><id>654497</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Green Business Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216671855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>What is the deal with Going Green</name><id>8383517</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219791600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-1402/events/8383517/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/6/global_4875670.jpeg</photo_url></item>