<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351844</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-439-3142 </phone><name>The NonProfit Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>1058586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057489</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10.00 cash at the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you want to raise money to support the causes and organizations you care about?&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for a Skillshare on Fundaising: Getting Past the Fear of Asking March 7th, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which increases our individual capacity for movement building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're very excited that Robbie Samuels, co-founder of Socializing for Justice and &lt;em&gt;Art of the Schmooze &lt;/em&gt;trainer, is returning to facilitate this training.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fundraising: Getting Past the Fear of Asking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This engaging coaching session focuses on getting past the fear of asking and how to avoid some common mistakes. Learn an easy way to sort through contact lists and build a strong prospect list based on the 3 Cs of fundraising: capacity, connection and commitment. Learn specific language for how to make a strong ask, based on the relationship-building tips shared in &lt;em&gt;Art of the Schmooze&lt;/em&gt;, and ten tips that will make your next fundraising plan a success. "If you are afraid to ask for money, kick yourself out of the way and let the cause talk."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - &lt;em&gt;bring your own dinner &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:00 Training  &lt;br /&gt;8:00-8:30 Q &amp;amp; A and more socializing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robbie Samuels&lt;/strong&gt; is a white, queer, feminist, trans man with extensive community organizing, event logistics and fundraising experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In  2006 he co-founded Socializing for Justice  to build a cross-issue  progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the  philosophy of abundance. He is the Special Events Manager at Gay &amp;amp;  Lesbian Advocates &amp;amp; Defenders (GLAD), an adjunct professor at Lesley  College teaching &amp;ldquo;Activism and Change in Communities&amp;rdquo;, and affiliated  with several other organizations. Learn more about his networking and  fundraising trainings at &lt;a href="http://www.robbiesamuels.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.robbiesamuels.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*&lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/strong&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities.   &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this "Movement Moment". Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With over 1600 members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300490428000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>33</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296426049000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Fundraising - Getting Past the Fear of Asking</name><id>16373242</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299538800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/16373242/</event_url></item>