<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A 9.6 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting south of Falls Village, CT off of Rte. 7 at an AT parking area. We will head southbound going briefly along the Housatonic River, then heading up over Sharon Mountain, through portions of the Housatonic State Forest, over Mount Easter, above Housatonic Meadows State Park, and finally over Bread Loaf Mountain and ending on Rte. 4 in Cornwall Bridge, CT. There are 9 lookouts of note in varying directions to look forward to! Not a real lot of altitude gain (about 1,300 ft. altitude at highest spot) but a fair amount of up/down (+/- 400 ft.) for this section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Weather looks great! Low is 49 F to start and gets up to 74 F towards the end of the hike! Partly cloudy with winds up to 9 mph from ESE and 55% humidity (low). Couldn't ask for a better day! ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 8 AM at the parking area on the shoulder of the road on Rte. 7 near the bridge over the Housatonic (just south of bridge). We'll hike the 9.6 miles with a lunch at the Pine Swamp Brook Lean-to for shelter and to replenish our water. Finally, we end by reaching Rte. 4 and walking down a bit to AT parking where one or more shuttle vehicles will be located. I figure we will end the hike at about 2 PM. We'll stop for dinner at a local establishment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If more than 7 people go, we will need an additional vehicle to park at the ending point to shuttle people back to the start. I'd like any volunteers for the task (please call me, see my RSVP for number) to meet at the ending point (parking area off of Rte. 4, Cornwall Bridge... see below) at 7:40 AM at the latest to be shuttled with me back to the starting point.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservitive with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equiped we could come in earlier than I estimated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;br /&gt;* Daypack&lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable, &amp;amp; broken in &lt;br /&gt;* Wool socks&lt;br /&gt;* Hat&lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cold morning &amp;amp; possibly &amp;quot;hot&amp;quot; afternoon, avoid cotton as it stays wet.&lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart water min., 2 quarts suggested max.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail lunch. High energy meal should be planned.&lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, etc.&lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen&lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho/jacket -rain pants optional&lt;br /&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries&lt;br /&gt;* Bug spay -likely need this but may still be too early&lt;br /&gt;* Compass&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kevin S can provide carpooling for up to 6 from the Wal-Mart in E. Windsor **leaving** at a 6 AM for those interested. There will be a blue Dodge Grandcaravan Sport. Return at about 4 PM. It is advised to call Kevin S (number in RSVP) so he knows you plan to carpool. Approximate location/directions for the carpool meetup can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/69+Prospect+Hill+Rd+East+Windsor+CT+06088-3600/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this event is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so all questions should be directed to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the AT hike trailhead, intersection of Rte. 7 (Sharon Canaan Rd.) and Rte. 112 (Lime Rock Rd.) south of Falls Village, CT via MapQuest (Close as I could get w/service, go south on Rte. 7 past intersection a little, dirt parking area on east side of road):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/299+Lime+Rock+Rd+Falls+Village+CT+06031/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the ending location parking area near intersection of Rte. 4 (Cornwall Bridge Rd.) and Rte. 7 (River Rd.) in Cornwall Bridge:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/%5B606-665%5D+Cornwall+Bridge+Rd+Cornwall+Bridge+CT+06754/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the parking area on the shoulder of the road on Rte. 7 near the bridge over the Housatonic (just south of bridge, see event description). I'll be there. Not sure what vehicle I'll be with though. Look for me, 6'2". ;-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208779376000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>It's finally time to start hiking some long hikes! This segment isn't too long and a great opportunity to get a taste of AT hiking. Let's enjoy the woods and trails of CT. :-)</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208389086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from Falls Village to Cornwall Bridge CT</name><id>7753575</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208606400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7753575/</event_url></item>