<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-401-8047</phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>221452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Conspiracy Cafe at 45 Mt. Auburn St. in Harvard Sq. is now open EVERY Sunday from noon to 8:00 pm. It offers a unique setting for 9/11 Truth activists and those curious to learn more about current events through books, DVDs, film screenings and informal discussions, in a casual cafe environment. The Conspiracy Cafe offers a wide selection of books, cds, &amp;amp; other media. So whether your desires are social, intellectual or oriented toward activism, the Conspiracy Cafe has something for everyone. Hope to see you at the next Conspiracy Cafe! So what are you waiting for? Bring a friend, bring yourself, bring an open mind! Come check out what Conspiracy Cafe is all about!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JFK2: The Bush Connection&lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:30&lt;br /&gt;JFK 2 is research at it's best, proves without a doubt George H.W. Bush's complicity in the JFK assassination. This video is the culmination of all the cutting edge research done over the years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zeitgeist&lt;br /&gt;1:30 - 3:30&lt;br /&gt;The movie sums up how the human population is enslaved in three chapters. Religion, Terror and Money. Zeitgeist tells the story of a minor ruling class controlling whole world from the first ages by religion. When we come to near future we see the effect of terror for making people fear and making them easier to rule. Then more important the movie tells how they did take control of money by manipulating markets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Great Global Warming Swindle&lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 4:45&lt;br /&gt;This film by the documentary-maker Martin Durkin presents the arguments of scientists and commentators who don't believe that CO2 produced by human activity is the main cause of climate change. It's a controversial film that was roundly attacked by some scientists and enthusiastically received by others, and the arguments it contains are an important part of the wider debate on the causes of climate change. The film was shortlisted for the Best Documentary award at the 2008 Broadcast Awards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FBI Cointelpro: The FBI's Secret War on Black America&lt;br /&gt;4:45 - 5:35&lt;br /&gt;In early 1971, the FBI's domestic counterintelligence program (code named &amp;quot;COINTELPRO&amp;quot;) was brought to light when a &amp;quot;Citizens Committee to Investigate the FBI&amp;quot; removed secret files from an FBI office in Media, PA and released them to the press. Agents began to resign from the Bureau and blow the whistle on covert operations. That same year, publication of the Pentagon Papers, the Pentagon's top-secret history of the Vietnam War, exposed years of systematic official lies about the war. Soon after, it was discovered that a clandestine squad of White House &amp;quot;plumbers&amp;quot; broke into Daniel Ellsberg's psychiatrist's office in an effort to smear the former Pentagon staffer who leaked the top-secret papers to the press. The same &amp;quot;plumbers&amp;quot; were later caught burglarizing the Watergate offices of the Democratic National Committee. By the mid-1970's Senate and House committees launched formal and lengthy inquiries into government intelligence and covert activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9/11 Martial Law: Rise Of The Police State&lt;br /&gt;5:35 - 8:00&lt;br /&gt;The film documents: What the modern day police state looks like as thousands of peaceful protesters are forcibly detained at a Guantanamo style detention camp called Pier 57 during the 2004 Republican National Convention.   How multitudes of New Yorkers and others are fully aware of the fact that 9/11 was an inside job and are now actively exposing the people behind it.  Why the collapse of Building 7 is potentially the biggest smoking gun indicating government involvement in 9/11. Alex returns to the scene of the crime to physically dissect why the official story can be nothing else but a fraud.  How many of the RNC protesters are actually aiding what they claim to oppose by being deluded into thinking that a re-energization of the left will successfully counteract the Neo-Cons. Communists and socialists are confronted with the truth about the false left-right paradigm and their response only betrays their ignorance. The awful truth about Michael Moore, a man with basic honest intentions but also a man who has been carefully shepherded by the culture creators to pose as the orthodoxy milquetoast of the true story behind 9/11. How Moore stood at the front of the protest for his photo-op and then spent the rest of his time eating tacos.  The occult and satanic underpinnings of the ruling elite families and how their oath to secret societies and each other makes a mockery of their counterfeit pseudo-loyalty to America and what it is supposed to stand for.   Arnold Schwarzenegger's alarming and sordid past and why his intentions should unnerve us all in light of his fated future presidential run. A womanizing, egotistic, power-mad, imperious Nazi whose ideals are diametrically opposed to those represented by the founding fathers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be manning the dvd/cash table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205856667000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We'll be hitting the streets &amp; having a street action as well! People should not be going through Harvard Square without knowing the truth about 9/11! So if you want to come &amp; participate in street actions &amp; see hard hitting films THIS is your spot!</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204328827000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conspiracy Cafe</name><id>7435848</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205683200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7435848/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/5/global_3356197.jpeg</photo_url></item>