<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Turkey Paddle   November 13th, rain date of November 14th!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 1:00 pm for a 1:30 launch. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer: Louise Price    Weezrad@yahoo.com  508-441-7279.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://img.groundspeak.com/waymarking/display/eb4ef3a0-788c-4d57-bb0c-434ed7debef5.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddle on Wallum Lake with dinner after at the waterfront, Lodge Restaurant in Webster MA (148 Gore Road, Webster). Come for the paddle, come for the dinner or both. RSVP required by November 11th  if you are planning on coming to the restaurant.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  at this time of year a wet suit or dry suit is recommended or a change of clothes in a waterproof  dry bag is required.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Changes and cancellations to trips will be posted on the flatwater message board. Please check the board before leaving for any trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wallum Lake in the Douglas State Park, Douglas, Ma., &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wallum Lake is located on the border of  RI and Ma., has  crystal clear water, and an easy paddle.  Any size boat is OK, suitable for all levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GPS coordinates:  N42 01 301      W071 46 073&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: 146 north  exit for Rt 16 to Douglas/Uxbridge&lt;br /&gt; Follow Rt 16 W thru the town of Douglas. You will  come to  an intersection for Rt 16 &amp;amp; 96. GO STRAIGHT. (You will see a sign  for Douglas  State Park/Wallum Lake) This is S. Main St. Follow until you see a sign for  Douglas State Park, take this left. Just down the road take a right  at park entrance. Follow road bearing left down the hill to the put-in.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Also: RT 395 exit 2 for town of Webster. Follow Rt 16 east until you see a  sign on the right for Douglas State Park or Cedar St. Follow Cedar  St to the  end. Go straight across at sign for Douglas State Park. Just down  the road  take a right at park entrance. Follow road bearing left down the  hill to  put-in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our leaders provide directions as a courtesy to paddlers however, you are responsible to refer to a map and familiarize yourself with the trip location.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289769515000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SNEP-1</urlname><id>1360815</id><group_lat>41.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-72.1100006104</group_lon><name>Southern New England Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283976425000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Turkey Paddle  at Wallum Lake Webster MA</name><id>14701415</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289671200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SNEP-1/events/14701415/</event_url></item>