<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Runtime: 1 hrs 30 min. | Rated PG sci-fi action violence throughout, brief language and momentary smoking

Description: Star Wars: The Clone Wars showcases an entirely new look and feel to the galaxy far, far away?combining the expansive scope of the Star Wars Saga with state-of-the-art computer-generated animation. On the front lines of an intergalactic struggle between good and evil, fans young and old will join such favorite characters as Anakin Skywalker, Obi-Wan Kenobi and Padmé Amidala, along with brand-new heroes like Anakin's padawan learner, Ahsoka. Sinister villains?led by Palpatine, Count Dooku and General Grievous?are poised to rule the galaxy. Stakes are high, and the fate of the Star Wars universe rests in the hands of the daring Jedi Knights. Their exploits lead to the action-packed battles and astonishing new revelations that fill Star Wars: The Clone Wars.  

Director: Dave Filoni

Starring: Anthony Daniels, Matthew Wood, etc.

Genre: Science Fiction

Reviews: &lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=11603" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.boston.com/movies/display?display=movie&amp;id=11603&lt;/a&gt;

Trailer: 
&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/zPI48Ti548c&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

for better quality go here:
&lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/wb/starwarstheclonewars/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.apple.com/trailers/wb/starwarstheclonewars/&lt;/a&gt;

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what you are going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix [b]AHEAD[/b] of time! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

How to find me: I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. According to my fandango ticket, it is upstairs (3rd floor) in auditorium 14. I'll be in front of the coffee house next to the windows, near the metal seat+tables. If I find a seat, I'll be sitting down.

The movie begins @7:15PM. I shall be there @6:45PM and plan to get seats by 7PM. Remember that we will also be outside of the auditorium after the movie finishes if you miss us before the movie.

I recommend you buy the tickets in advanced here:
&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/starwars:theclonewars_114457/movietimes?date=8/15/2008" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fandango.com/starwars:theclonewars_114457/movietimes?date=8/15/2008&lt;/a&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green trucker hat w/my screename JediFonger+meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222684060000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214244301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Star Wars: The Clone Wars </name><id>8198067</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218840300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/8198067/</event_url></item>