<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;*** Was rescheduled due to rain ***&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well it's not hiking but it is and event dear to my heart. Come on and join us at Connecticut’s Renaissance Faire! We'll be joining with some members of the Hartford Heights Tall Club (&lt;a href="http://tall.meetup.com/28/calendar/10750189/"&gt;http://tall.meetup.co...&lt;/a&gt; ) where this event is cross-listed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a step back in time and get lost in the revelry and excitement of the Connecticut Renaissance Faire. Be entertained with story telling, musicians, drama, jousting and so much more as you journey into an enchanted 16th century Harvest Festival. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be a part of history, or come as you are and immerse yourself in games, theater and New England’s largest Medieval Marketplace. Experience hours of entertainment and sample a variety of Renaissance foods. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sit back with your Turkey Leg and enjoy a joust. Or, listen to authentic period music while eating a Pirate Pickle. Bring your family and friends and try your hand at games of fortune, or shop among our premium vendors for fine and unique craftsmanship. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whatever your tastes, the Connecticut Renaissance Faire is a unique entertainment experience and a feast for your imagination – for children of all ages. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We'll meet at 10 AM at the ticket booth before we enter.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PRICES and TIMES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open 10am-6pm, September 26 to October 18, 2009 every weekend and Columbus Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*General Admission (13+) $16 &lt;br /&gt;*Youth Admission (5-12)  $8 &lt;br /&gt;*Under 5  FREE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DISCOUNTS - GENERAL &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this opportunity to see what discounts are available.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Military&lt;/b&gt; -Show your military ID and get $2 OFF General Admission. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;NE Rennies &lt;/b&gt; -Show your NE Rennies pin and get $2 Off General Admission. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Seniors ages 60+&lt;/b&gt; -Seniors receive $2 OFF General Admission with a valid ID. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Incredible Opening Weekend Discounts&lt;/b&gt;  -Visit their themed weekend page for details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;E-Newsletter Members&lt;/b&gt;  -Members of their E-newsletter List receive special &amp;quot;Members Only&amp;quot; discounts. Sign up with them and take advantage of these free savings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must present any discounts or coupons to the Faire Box Office BEFORE purchasing your tickets. They are unable to process voids or refunds. Discounts are not applicable with any other discount. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; (Hebron Fairgrounds, 347 Gilead St., Hebron, CT):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Hebron&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=347+Gilead+St"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Textual directions&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctfaire.com/directions_printable.php"&gt;http://www.ctfaire.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional information on the Faire&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctfaire.com/"&gt;http://www.ctfaire.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255357057000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251662630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join in at Connecticut’s Renaissance Faire</name><id>11239714</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255183200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11239714/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/8/global_10476536.jpeg</photo_url></item>