<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Just a guess that the ice cream stand will be open by this date.  If its not, we'll just have to return at a later date!  There is a $2 parking fee. Meet at 10:30 in the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;984 Lowell Rd., &lt;br /&gt;Carlisle, MA 01741&lt;br /&gt;978 369-6312&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/gbfm.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chosen by Yankee Magazine's Travel Guide to New England as Editor's Pick 2000, Great Brook Farm State Park stands as a jewel in northern Massachusetts! Agriculture has been part of Great Brook's history for centuries. Holsteins have been kept here for over 60 years and current farmer Mark Duffy continues the tradition with his black &amp;amp; white ladies. Native Americans used sections of Great Brook Farm as sacred sites. Seventeenth century cellar holes comprise &amp;quot;the city&amp;quot; where early English settlers worked one of numerous mill sites on the 1,000 acre park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barn tours run daily by appointment and public tours are available on Sundays through the month of October. There are over 20 miles of trails available for walkers, hikers, mountain bikers, and horseback riders. During the winter months, cross-country skiing is available and one trail is lantern lit for a &amp;quot;mooon light&amp;quot; experience! The ice cream stand is open through the month of October.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Rt. 128: Take exit 31B. Follow Route 225 West for 8 miles to the Carlisle center rotary, then turn right on Lowell St. (following the sign to Chelmsford.) Fern's Market is on the corner. The Park entrance is 2 miles ahead on the right. The Park Office (984 Lowell St) is just beyond the entrance also on the right. Make right hand turn onto North Road. Parking area is 1/2 mile down on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the ice cream stand is open and sells more than just ice cream, we may have lunch there in the park.  Also if the weather is nice, we could have a pic nic.  We'll see.  If not, we can go for lunch at the restaurant below.  I will update the lunch details closer to the day of the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Garrison's Food &amp;amp; Spirits&lt;br /&gt;303 Boston Road&lt;br /&gt;Billerica, MA 01821&lt;br /&gt;978·670·1202&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178633836000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176755177000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Brook Farm state park &amp; ice cream</name><id>5677133</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178375400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5677133/</event_url></item>