<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>302 n main st</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.312897</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>pizza hut</name><city>rochester</city><id>6300712</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.994293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come hang out with other liberty-lovers in the northern Seacoast region. We meet every month, on the second Saturday of the month at 6 pm, at Pizza Hut Italian Bistro, 302 N Main St, Rochester. The restaurant is conveniently located between Spaulding Turnpike exits 14, Ten Rod Rd, and 15, N Main St / Rte 11 (to Farmington). On the east side of Main St, directly across from the little Main St mall where the Planet Fitness gym is located, the restaurant shares a driveway with the Dunkin' Donuts. The restaurant generally seems to have plenty of room and is quiet and ideal for talking, the reason why we chose this location. We usually get a table in the back seating room, tell the person seating you you're with a small group, Seacoast Liberty (I usually have a little paper sign that says Seacoast Liberty as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is to this point the only weekend meetup for Seacoast Liberty, so I would like to encourage people from other areas to attend. I made it only once a month because it is a bit out of the way for many people, I would also love to have friends come over from the Lakes region, and from Maine, it is only about 30 minutes from Sanford to Rochester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want this event to become something where we discuss our plans and ideas for activism and not just hang out, though that can be fun as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bryce Nielsen</member_name><member_id>24332732</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352599384000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352074262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup in Rochester, at Pizza Hut Bistro</name><id>qgkgqcyqpbnb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352588400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/89968852/</event_url></item>