<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Due to continued interest, I thought we could meet to discuss travel options for the Montreal Film Festival, to be held August 21 to September 1.  I apologize for the late announcement, but some might want to make plans for their trip very soon.  (I know I do.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I thought we could informally meet, share travel info (like hotel, transportation), and meet face-to-face so shared plans could be made (my personal goal for the evening).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because space is an issue, I have to limit it to 15 people, and no Maybes.  Unless you are serious about this trip, please do not RSVP Yes at this point.  (Of course, if there are still openings the day of the event, go ahead and RSVP.)  We'll likely have another Meetup soon, so you'll get another chance.  (Depending on interest, I may make a Wednesday night Meetup about Montreal a standing weekly or bi-weekly event.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ifi you're not 100% but still curious, or if you ARE 100% interested but can't make it next Wednesday, feel free to use the Message Board to connect with others, and keep an eye the Calendar for the next Montreal Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I personally am very serious about this, and I hope there are others who share my view.  I hope to see you next week!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Montreal or Bust!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215211177000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214508069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Montreal Film Festival Redux</name><id>8221818</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215037800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8221818/</event_url></item>