<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>OF COURSE DEPENDING ON THE WEATHER,&lt;br /&gt;If its not raining, i will go anyway just for the practice even if no one else goes so....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow is a prime recreation area for kayaking, hiking, biking, or just plain walking. &lt;br /&gt;If the weather is not good enough for kayaking, the other activities are there too, a quite convienient location. &lt;br /&gt;The water area has 3 rivers feeding in, all of which have explorative properties. There are interesting islands and coves to also checkout. The lake is divided by Bassetts Bridge into a small area and a larger area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;From I-84, south on rte 195 through Storrs to Mansfield ctr &lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. &lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384, follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic. &lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6. &lt;br /&gt;Follow ths highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is acually a parallel to rte6 connector to rte 195, &lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too, &lt;br /&gt;Go north on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, same info from here as above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon with the 2 kayaks on a old sailboat trailer. One kayak has a 55 horsepower engine..No paddle needed for that one...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to go on Kevin's SUNSET hike later that day in Meriden so a few hours of paddling and a short time on the paddle float and roll is gonna be it...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1149279307000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mansfield Hollow in Mansfield</name><id>4961609</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1149438600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/4961609/</event_url></item>