<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10.00 (pay at the door)</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;Ready to make tons of connections at &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/calendar/15722820/" target="_blank"&gt;Connecting for Justice&lt;/a&gt; on 1/27? Need a networking primer to make the most out of this opportunity?&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Join Socializing for Justice for an Art of the Schmooze Skillshare on January 20th, 6:00 - 8:30 PM.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SoJust hosts events that draw progressives of all stripes that share common values but may work on different issues. We create social spaces that allow for the possibility of cross-issue connections and run a Skillshare Series, hosted by The NonProfit Center*, which builds our individual capacity to make a difference in the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;SoJust's Co-Founder, Robbie Samuels, who is well known for his schmoozing skills, is this month's facilitator.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Art of the Schmooze&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forming and cultivating relationships is at the heart of any successful fundraising campaign, volunteer drive, committee effort or community building activity. This workshop will give you the confidence to pursue your personal goals - from the importance of shaking hands and making eye contact, to tips on the best opening line and how to exit a conversation gracefully. An amazing side benefit is that you'll learn how to create a welcoming community space by keeping an eye out for outliers, considering yourself a host instead of a guest and knowing how to compliment someone without &amp;quot;othering&amp;quot; them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCHEDULE&lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 Socializing - bring your own dinner&lt;br /&gt;6:30-8:00 Training&lt;br /&gt;8:00-8:30 Q &amp;amp; A and more socializing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ABOUT OUR PRESENTER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Robbie Samuels&lt;/b&gt; is a white, queer, feminist, trans man with extensive community organizing, event logistics and fundraising experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2006 he co-founded Socializing for Justice  to build a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance. He is the Special Events Manager at Gay &amp;amp; Lesbian Advocates &amp;amp; Defenders (GLAD), an adjunct professor at Lesley College teaching “Activism and Change in Communities”, and affiliated with several other organizations. Learn more about his networking and fundraising trainings at &lt;a href="http://www.robbiesamuels.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.robbiesamuels.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;February 7th Skillshare:&lt;/b&gt; Overcoming Procrastination, Perfectionism, Blocks and Fears presented by Hillary Rettig, author of &amp;quot;The Lifelong Activist: How to Change the World Without Losing Your Way.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*&lt;a href="http://www.nonprofitcenterboston.org/site/c.ddKGIQNuEmG/b.1363373/k.5381/About_Us__Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt; - The NonProfit Center&lt;/b&gt; is located one block from South Station at 89 South Street. The Center is accessible through the main lobby to people who have restricted physical abilities. &lt;br /&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With almost 1600 members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296172987000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292966086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Skillshare: Art of the Schmooze</name><id>15792339</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295564400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/15792339/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/global_20406051.jpeg</photo_url></item>