<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 West St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 587-1011</phone><name>NORTHAMPTON MA_ FORBES LIBRARY </name><city>Northampton </city><id>832342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to Experience Joy and feel like a kid again?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to reduce the negative effects of stress on your body and mind?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to try something fun that will improve your physical, emotional, and spiritual health?   Medical research shows that Laughter will do it!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Sherry will be your laughter guide to an evening of fun and laughter. Meet new friends in a fun easy-going atmosphere. Just bring with you some child-like playfulness and an openness to laugh and connect with other people who also are looking for more fun in their lives!  You'll leave class with a blissful feeling and a glow (both inside and outside) that will last for hours afterwards!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We'll play fun interactive games that will lead to infectious laughter.&lt;/em&gt; The program is based activities developed by Laughter Yoga International (a branch of Yoga developed in India by Dr Madan Kataria), the World Laughter Tour, and original material. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It's very simple and easy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; NO physical yoga postures or poses will be used. You can participate seated for all activities if that's more comfortable for you.  Our direct connection to other forms of Yoga will be deep breathing exercises.  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;And&lt;/em&gt;--just from laughing--we'll even burn a couple of hundred calories as we work out over 350 muscles from our waist up to our heads!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laughter has many proven physical benefits: It boosts the immune system's production of disease-fighting T-cells, releases endorphins that serve as natural pain killers and make us feel good, helps reduce stress, anxiety &amp;amp; blood pressure by lowering the level of the stress hormone cortisol, provides aerobic exercise &amp;amp; promotes muscle tone, increases blood flow thereby bringing more oxygen to body cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are now over 6,000 Laughter fclubs all around the world and that number is growing every day.  &lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;Laughter Yoga has been recommended by Oprah, Dr. Oz, Dr. Andrew Weil, and Dr. Sanjay Gupta.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Donations are gratefully accepted (Suggested donation $3-$6)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be Ready to Laugh-- and be a little Silly!  You'll feel good for hours after the class!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and join us ! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Other people will be joining us who are not coming through Meetup.com so our numbers may be greater than only those signed up here&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Route 91 Exit 18 left turn, slight left at Conz St, left at Main St, left at Route 66 20 yards to Library on left</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Sherry</member_name><member_id>5650811</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364516511000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Partners in Laughter</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup</urlname><id>1384386</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Laughter is the Best Medicine and Fun Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359419114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boatloads of Laughter!</name><id>drrfhfyrfbhc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364252400000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Laughter-is-the-Best-Medicine-and-Fun-Meetup/events/104113062/</event_url></item>