<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Atlantic Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02205</zip><lat>42.353001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Federal Reserve Bank of Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>789278</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054928</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Occupy the Fed Boston starts at noon this Friday. We are working with individuals within the Occupy Boston groups to focus attention on the Federal Reserve. Stewart Rhodes connected me with with Garrett Loporto who has taken on the defacto role as lead facilitator at the Boston site (600 Atlantic Ave- across from the Fed). He is an oathkeeper, Ron Paul supporter, end the fed'er and wants get as many of us as we can to come this Friday and stay as long as you can and keep coming back and staying for as long as you can. Hence occupation. Like to go camping? Sharing common goals? Building strength in unity? For the past five days people have been occupying Dewey Square, under the shadow of the Boston Federal Reserve. The group is made up of all different types of people. Most call themselves socialists. What we call them are allies in the fight to save our republic. Coalition building is essential to any movement. We must seize this moment in time. We don't have to argue about the things we don't agree on. Save that for later. Right now, we must act as one body, one voice. This is the essence of our foundation. This is the revolution. for more info: &lt;a href="http://www.masslpa.org/content/occupy-fed-now-boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masslpa.or...&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=245421228841969" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318006045000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317784121000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Occupy the Fed - Boston</name><id>36192932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318001400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/36192932/</event_url></item>