<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;It's romantic comedy time again &amp;amp; I can't resist the temptation to see the Tina Fey and Paul Rudd combo.. For more information check out the &lt;br /&gt;

movie synopsis below: &lt;br /&gt;

Straight-laced Princeton University admissions officer Portia Nathan lives by the book, both at work and at home. But Portia is caught off-guard when she makes a recruiting visit to an alternative high school overseen by her former college classmate, the free-wheeling John Halsey. Halsey has surmised that Jeremiah, his gifted yet very unconventional student, might well be the son that Portia secretly gave up for adoption many years ago. Soon, Portia finds herself bending the rules for Jeremiah, putting at risk the life she thought she always wanted -- but in the process finding her way to a surprising and exhilarating life and romance she never dreamed of having.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for more information you can go to: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/admission" class="linkified"&gt;http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/admission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I will be wearing a meetup badge. If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator. If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand. I will be there 20 minutes prior to show time &amp;amp; we can go on in 5 min prior to show time. No worries if you run late ----after the movie I will wait outside the movie theatre &amp;amp; anyone that wishes to go for a bite to eat can join. &lt;br /&gt;

Movie: Starts at 4:40pm. I will be there by there by 4:20pm and we will be going into the theatre at 4:35pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers, &lt;br /&gt;

Shannon&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shannon O'Leary</member_name><member_id>12316037</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364081746000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363792599000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Admission"  3/23 @ 4:40pm</name><id>110173292</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364070600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/110173292/</event_url></item>