<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Happy day after New Years Day.  I so wanted to be out on New Years Morning but Mother Nature is not cooperating with the weather.  So lets go out January 2, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soapstone Mountain has been used as a fire tower watch site and used to be the site for the weather radar for many years.  Many of you are familar with the outlook tower that looks north to Westover Air Force base and beyond.  We are going to do a 7 mile loop that will start from the Ellington side, include the tower and get us back where we started. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the plan for those of you with a pension for the tardy.  We are starting on the state forest road off of Kibbe Rd (off of Route 83 in Ellington), we will go up about 2 miles and take a left on to the blue Shenipsit trail, this trail will cross Parker Road with 1.3 miles to the tower.  We will break at the tower to enjoy the view/lunch.  From there we will return to our cars via the dirt forest road, 3 miles.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would like us to be on the trail no later than 10:00 a.m.  Parking will be at the bottom of the road and may require a bit of creativity to keep the road open. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is considered a moderate hike with a 800 ft gain.  It should be do-able for many.  The trail is well traveled and marked.  We will be in the woods with rocks and mud and trees and nature stuff....hiking.  &lt;br /&gt;Please wear appropriate footwear (boots) and bring snacks or lunch and water.  I expect to be on the trail no more than 4 hours.  Considering the season, dress in layers and bring your microspikes.  Not sure if snow shoes are called for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please no dogs or children. &lt;br /&gt;This hike is also posted on the AMC site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Take Rt 84 east to exit 66.  At the end of the ramp take a left, at the stop sign take a left.  At the stop light take a right then your first left onto West Rd by the Vernon police station. &lt;br /&gt; You will pass Garden Barn as you head up hill.  At your second stop light (711, Walgreens, church) go straight onto Rt 83 north into Ellington.  &lt;br /&gt;You will pass Bolles Jeep Eagle, Big y and McDonalds (I suggest bathroom stopping here), Kloter Farms, Rt 140, Elington Airport, TSI Harley Store, and the lot where the buses are parked.&lt;br /&gt;You are looking for Kibbe Rd on your right and it doubles back on itself.  Hoffman Rd will be on the left, if you see that you just drove by your turn.  As soon as you go up the road you will see the forest road on your left.  Make sure to leave the road open as you park on the the edge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you using GPS, use 439 Somers Rd Ellington 06029.  That is the last house on the right before your turn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to start of dirt road we will be hiking (via MapQuest):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Ellington&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=90+Kibbe+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/shenipsitgis.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rough contour map (40') via Google Maps (click Terrain link if no contours show):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=90%2BKibbe%2BRd.,+ellington,+ct&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=30.819956,56.25&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.93868,-72.452345&amp;amp;spn=0.01411,0.027466&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=addr" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263422848000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262130223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking the day after New Years Day, Soapstone Mt, Ellington, CT</name><id>12171740</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262444400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12171740/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>