<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I have 16 passes for 31 members, new friends and guests to see Cadillac Records at the Regal Fenway Theater.  I will try to get 14 more passes more for a extra 28 movie members &amp;amp; guests can come also etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be in the main lobby area aside the arcades. I hope you will be there at 5:15pm on the dot. The movie begins at 7:00pm and the line will start to fill up by 5:15pm and we should be able to enter the line hopefully in the middle by 5:30pm. For those who get out of work after 6pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/sony_pictures/cadillacrecords/" target="_blank"&gt;Cadillac Records Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can call me at my cellphone 6174358177 if your on your way there and curious to find out if we are still standing in line. if you get there by 6 and a few minutes, I'll go get you and bring you to where all of us are waiting to get in but if the line is moving in. I'll see how many last members want to get in and I hope the group can hold our seats + whoever is arriving late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We  will all go in together as one.  I will lead the group to what level of rows are available for us to sit in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, I would like everyone to gather up for a movie meetup group picture after the movie and comment about the movie, maybe go for drinks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be standing aside the ARCADE area</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230918638000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227742351000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CADILLAC RECORDS - Advance Screening</name><id>9236517</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228256100000</time><rsvp_limit>32</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/9236517/</event_url></item>