<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Flash June 11, 2012: A dear friend of mine collapsed at the end of a marathon this weekend. his heart stopped for 50 minutes, He is alive and fighting tonight no doubt because of his good physical condition and his fellow runners helped save his life.  I was listening to a CPR Eduction campaign one morning and it brought me back to my AF Clinic days to where we all had to be qualified in the unit. I feel as active adults, we need to take a minute, review and refresh.You never know when you may need to snap into action, but if if so, you will remember what to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;xiframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ILxjxfB4zNk" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xiframe&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If CPR is started within 4 minutes of collapse and defibrillation provided within 10 minutes a person has a 40% chance of survival.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Take 10 minutes and review the new Hands-only CPR. it's easy, the video is fun, hopefully we never need to use it, but if you have to take action- your training will kick in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our hiking Meetups get our heart pumping, often many times in remote areas. -we may be relying only on our hiking partners for any life saving assistance we might need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being physically active, many of us have had first aid training- but has CPR changed? You ask, what are the rules this year?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to recertify every year in the Guard, and the trainer would always start by reminding us, you cant hurt a dead man. He has a 50% better chance of survival if you try than if you don't.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://youtu.be/ILxjxfB4zNk" class="linkified"&gt;http://youtu.be/ILxjxfB4zNk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the trail, we recommend groups of 4 or more, in case there is an emergency. Call 911 for a rescue, send other hikers for help, but start CPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ILxjxfB4zNk" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/embed/ILxjxfB4zNk&lt;/a&gt;" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPR Facts:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sudden cardiac arrest is the leading cause of death in adults. Most arrests occur in persons with underlying heart disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;CPR doubles a person's chance of survival from sudden cardiac arrest.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;75% of all cardiac arrests happen in people's homes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The typical victim of cardiac arrest is a man in his early 60's and a woman in her late 60's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cardiac arrest occurs twice as frequently in men compared to women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CPR was invented in 1960&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has never been a case of HIV transmitted by mouth-to-mouth CPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In sudden cardiac arrest the heart goes from a normal heartbeat to a quivering rhythm called ventricular fibrillation (VF). This happens in approximately 2/3rds of all cardiac arrests. VF is fatal unless an electric shock, called defibrillation, can be given. CPR does not stop VF but CPR extends the window of time in which defibrillation can be effective.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;CPR provides a trickle of oxygenated blood to the brain and heart and keeps these organs alive until defibrillation can shock the heart into a normal rhythm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twenty-five people take it in turns to perform CPR for 1.5 HOURS to keep man who collapsed after heart attack alive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By &lt;a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/search.html?s=y&amp;amp;authornamef=Daily+Mail+Reporter"&gt;DAILY MAIL REPORTER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Backwater town only has 800 residents and no traffic lights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rescuers gave him no chance of survival or feared brain damage at best&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2011/03/04/article-0-0D779688000005DC-766_233x365.jpg" alt=" Paramedics performing CPR on patient in ambulance" width="233" height="365" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Team effort: Howard Snitzer was saved by dozens of people who performed CPR (posed file pictured)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A man who suffered a massive heart attack was alive and well today after being kept alive for an incredible 1.5 hours by passers-by who took it in turns to perform CPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Howard Snitzer, 54, collapsed in the street when he suffered a potentially fatal cardiac arrest on his way to collect groceries on January 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a population of just 800 people and not a single traffic light in the town, his chances of survival looked bleak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Snitzer was miraculously kept alive by dozens of good Samaritans who pumped his heart as he lay lifeless on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chef has now made an almost full recovery and is relaxing at his home in the back-water town of Goodhue, Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He said: 'I love them. I love those people. What can I say? It's pretty overwhelming to be in a room full of people that are not going to walk away and give up on you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;' And I had nothing to do with it. It's just one of those things. They're all angles as far as I'm concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'I don't remember going (for groceries) , I don't remember getting out of the car and I don't remember blacking out.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Al Lodermeier, who owns the garage just across the street from where Snitzer collapsed, was one of the first people to start CPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He alerted his brother Roy who was joined by another passer-by who witnessed the moment Sitzer collapsed, Candace Koehn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Lodermeier brothers were both veteran first responders with more than three decades of experience on the volunteer Goodhue Fire Department and grabbed the rescue truck for its first aid kit. Koehn had also been trained in CPR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other rescuers joined including police, volunteer fire fighters and rescue squads from the neighbouring towns of Zumbrota and Red Wing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mayo Clinic's emergency helicopter, Mayo One, flew in from Rochester, Minnesota from almost 35 miles away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their teamwork kept blood flowing to Snitzer's brain, making each rescuer a surrogate for his failing heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'I's remarkable. It's a great example of people doing the right thing and having it work out,' Bruce Wilkoff, a Cleveland Clinic heart rhythm specialist, told USA Today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He added: 'The brain survives, at best, five or six minutes when the blood flow stops.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is estimated that across the U.S. only five percent of those who who suffer cardiac arrest on the street are resuscitated and live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even cities with the best records of responding to out-of-hospital cardiac arrests are said to save fewer than half of all victims or just 45 percent at best if the cardiac arrest is witnessed by a bystander.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'I don't think the story's about me,' Snitzer told USA Today. 'It's about the guys in Goodhue and Mayo One.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'My end of this bargain is to honour the guys who did this for me.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the emergency, first responders shocked Snitzer a dozen times to jolt his heart out of its abnormal rhythm, or ventricular fibrillation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paramedics Bruce Goodman and Mary Svoboda also gave Snitzer intravenous drugs to try to restore his heartbeat to normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he didn't respond, he called experts for guidance and they agreed to try a calculated overdose of a heart drug, amiodarone, which worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mayo One helicopter crew landed and  found a line of first responders taking turns pumping on Snitzer's chest. Al Lodermeier was at Snitzer's head, squeezing air into a mask over his mouth using a device called an ambu bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors feared that Snitzer might have suffered a blood clot and suffer brain damage but has now been released from hospital after 10 days and is on course to make a full recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'The number one thing in this case was that someone recognized very quickly that he had arrested and began good, hard, fast CPR,' said Mayo One paramedic Bruce Goodman who arrived shortly after Snitzer collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;'If you'd told me that night that this guy was going to get up and walk out of the hospital I would probably have said, ''I'll bet my house against yours he won't''.'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Read more: &lt;a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1362953/Twenty-people-perform-CPR-1-5-HOURS-heart-attack-man-alive.html#ixzz1oIGgIgeD"&gt;http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1362953/Twenty-people-perform-CPR-1-5-HOURS-heart-attack-man-alive.html#ixzz1oIGgIgeD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The goal is that everyone on our hikes knows CPR. The latest "Hands only" is also the easiest. In an emergency, your training will come back to you.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339699295000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338505282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BYpasser CPR Video Review this entertaining video</name><id>qkzjqcyqjbrb</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339628400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/67176492/</event_url></item>