<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Green Rooster &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Est. 1997   &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;United Congregational Church &lt;br /&gt;6 Institue Road &lt;br /&gt;Worcester, MA 01609 &lt;br /&gt;The GREEN ROOSTER COFFEEHOUSE is in Merriman Hall at the United Congregational Church in Worcester MA. They serve the central Massachusetts folk, country, and bluegrass scenes with occasional forays into classical, blues, jazz, and poetry. The Green Rooster is a family friendly, smoke-free and alcohol-free venue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All shows start at 8:00 &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mar. 1, 2008 / $15 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Duke Levine Band CD Release!&lt;/b&gt;He is described as &amp;quot;Boston's best kept secret&amp;quot;, but we all know he comes from Wista! Easily one of the best guitarist in the country, which can be verified by the names he's toured with (a few weeks after he joined Mary Chapin Carpenter's band, we saw him on the Grammy's!) and by Duke's session work (his name seems to be on every other new folk album). This is his own group, doing his own music, and I'm sure there will be plenty from Duke's new, well-received album, &amp;quot;Beneath the Blue&amp;quot;. &lt;b&gt;Welcome home!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;* NOTE: &lt;b&gt;If you are interested in meeting up earlier, please join me at THE BEAN COUNTER on Highland St. across from THE SOLE at 7:15. Although short notice,, this sounds like a nice enjoyable event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBA: Please check for an update due to weather 
        conditions</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204590038000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Great reviews!!!!Come out and listen to one of the best guitarists in the country at a different type of venue!</why><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204310051000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Duke Levine Band @The Green Rooster Coffeehouse</name><id>7434098</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204416900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/7434098/</event_url></item>