<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Stephanie Borrelli will be offering this workshop from 11 a.m. - 2 p.m. on October 17.  Location is to be announced based on how many people are interested in this workshop.  The location will be somewhere in Middletown, CT.  There is a $50 charge per person if you sign up with Stephanie by October 1.  After that date the charge will be $60 per person.  To sign up you can call Stephanie at 860.301.0204.  You can send a check to Stephanie and write it payable to her.  Please send the check to 836 Brooks Rd., Middletown, CT, 06457.  Please include your phone number, return address and your email with your check so that she can get in contact with you to notify you of the designated location.  Stephanie can also be found on Facebook under &amp;quot;CT PSYCHIC DEVELOPMENT WORKSHOPS&amp;quot; or 'STEPHANIE HEWES BORRELLI.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop will be an extensive, jam packed day.  Materials will be provided for take home to review.  Also, please bring a snack and/or a beverage.  Water will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many hands on exercises that will be utilized with the topics listed below.  This workshop was  created at a base line level.  It is great for new people as well as those who are more advanced to keep one open and clear.  The workshop is created to learn a great deal, have a lot of fun, be interactive with what you are learning and raises one's energy level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The topics that will be covered in the workshop are listed below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Psychics/Mediums, The ways IN which Information is received - Recognizing the signs&lt;br /&gt;*The 4 C's - The Forms of Communication&lt;br /&gt;*Discussion on Aura - the layers - How to see it&lt;br /&gt;*Visualization exercise, holding and enhancing images, bringing in the details and symbols&lt;br /&gt;*What is Meditation - purpose and benefits&lt;br /&gt;*Protection Meditation - exercise Visualization methods to acheive when working with spirit&lt;br /&gt;*Chakra Meditation - What the colors mean - opening the energy, clearing the blockages and   meditation exercise for opening to the energy&lt;br /&gt;*Healing Visualizations - Intent, purpose and release exercise&lt;br /&gt;*Brain Training Discussion&lt;br /&gt;*Connecting to your Guides, who are they, Angels/Guides, meditation exercise&lt;br /&gt;*Ego - Letting go&lt;br /&gt;*Some readings with those in the group&lt;br /&gt;*Shutting Down - why we should and an exercise to do so&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have taken this course and Stephanie is absolutely right when she says that it is a jam packed workshop.  I learned so much, had so much fun and was amazed at what I knew all ready and what skills I was able to ramp up a bit.  Amazingly in such a short amount of time also!  This workshop is well worth the money.  I am still rereading the many handouts that Stephanie provided me with.  She gives you so much information to go over later on that reinforces what she taught &lt;span style="color: white"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;in the class.  Stephanie really knows her stuff and has a charismatic personality in addition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jo-Ann Blanchette-Silverio</member_name><member_id>9921229</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287408461000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284693822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Psychic Development Course Level 1</name><id>14799942</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287327600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/14799942/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/4/6/global_14078886.jpeg</photo_url></item>