<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join me for a tour of an 85-year old house that has been substantially renovated to significantly reduce energy consumption. Very cool stuff!  Afterward, we'll head out for coffee to discuss energy, buildings and sustainable design. (at Starbucks at 112 Trapelo Rd, Belmont, MA 02178)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI: The house looks nothing like the image here. In fact, from the outside, it's indistinguishable from it's neighbors, despite the significant renovations inside and out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;More about this project:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will, Susan and Carolynn Brownsberger will be sponsoring an Open House, in conjunction with National Grid, showcasing the Deep Energy Retrofit of their home in Belmont, MA. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This National Grid Deep Energy Retrofit project was completed in September of 2010 by Byggmeister, a design renovation firm from Newton, and is part of a comprehensive, whole home renovation of this 85-year old two family home. While the footprint of the home has not been altered, the third floor attic has been converted to create additional living space for Will and Carolyn’s family of five.  The super insulated enclosure was substantially enhanced through financial and technical support from National Grid through a technical partnership with Building Science Corporation and Building America.  The Brownsberger residence is the first two family home completed in the pilot. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Gilbert Road home is an example of downsizing from two houses to one, bringing extended family into a one dwelling and expanding that renovation project to capture great energy savings. Those savings would other wise have been lost for many decades to come if the Brownsbergers had not chosen to add deep levels of insulation on the walls and roof while re-siding and remodeling.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here are some of the highlights of the Deep Energy Retrofit of this classic 1925 two family home:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;•  Attic: R-60 (7’ Cellulose, 6” Rigid Polyiso Foam added to exterior)  &lt;br /&gt;•  Walls: R-40 (4” Rigid Polyiso Foam added to exterior)  &lt;br /&gt;•  Windows: R-5 0.2 U Pardigm triple glazed, low E, argon filled &lt;br /&gt;•  Air leakage reduction: &amp;gt; 85%, CFM 50 initial 5700, final less than 700 &lt;br /&gt;•  Heating system: 95% efficient American Standard forced-air &lt;br /&gt;•  Heat Recovery Ventilation: Renewaire EV 130 (ERV)  &lt;br /&gt;•  Lighting: Compact Flourescent or better throughout  &lt;br /&gt;•  Appliances: ENERGY STAR®  &lt;br /&gt;•  Renewables: Solar DHW with electric back-up  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Directions to the open house at 118-120 Gilbert Road, Belmont, MA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By Mass Transit: Take the 73 Bus from Harvard Square and get off at Gilbert Road.  Walk two blocks in on Gilbert to #118-120. &lt;br /&gt;From Route 128: Take Exit 28 in Waltham ( Exit 28 is about 4 miles north of the Mass Pike) to Trapelo Road and travel 5 miles and make left onto Gilbert Rd. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be waiting outside for the group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristen</member_name><member_id>4775682</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290483739000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287424145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deep Energy Retrofit House Tour, plus conversation</name><id>15148206</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290364200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/15148206/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/f/global_18862783.jpeg</photo_url></item>