<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clear Conscience Cafe/Harvest Co-Op Market</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>687911</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Polls speak again and we're off to Mughal with Salman Rushdie  (please note, if you haven't voted -- and less than 30 have, (ahem!!) -- the time to impact our summer reading is nearing!!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio/1-9780679640516-7" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Publisher Comments: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;A tall, yellow-haired, young European traveler calling himself &amp;quot;Mogor dell'Amore,&amp;quot; the Mughal of Love, arrives at the court of the Emperor Akbar, lord of the great Mughal empire, with a tale to tell that begins to obsess the imperial capital, a tale about a mysterious woman, a great beauty believed to possess powers of enchantment and sorcery, and her impossible journey to the far-off city of Florence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;The Enchantress of Florence is the story of a woman attempting to command her own destiny in a man's world. It is the story of two cities, unknown to each other, at the height of their powers — the hedonistic Mughal capital, in which the brilliant Akbar the Great wrestles daily with questions of belief, desire, and the treachery of his sons, and the equally sensual city of Florence during the High Renaissance, where Niccolo Machiavelli takes a starring role as he learns, the hard way, about the true brutality of power.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Vivid, gripping, irreverent, bawdy, profoundly moving, and completely absorbing, The Enchantress of Florence is a dazzling book full of wonders by one of the world's most important living writers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll do the old standby of the Clear Conscious Cafe. Look for me with book in hand, or a groups of us hovering. As ever, if we are crowded out and you see no familiar bookclub faces, you can always try Au Bon Pain across the street (684 Mass Ave:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Am bumping back to the 20 limit for RSVP for our cafe confined months with my apologies, but it's just more practical. Will have a waiting list so &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;PUH-LEEEZ&lt;/span&gt; keep your RSVP accurate to keep someone from missing out if you can't attend. I haven't been an ogre yet, but if folks are being denied attendance due to your inconsiderateness, I may change into the mean version of Shrek (you know, before Eddie Murphy and Cameron Diaz lighten him up). I'm also going to start changing any &amp;quot;maybe's&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; a few days prior to give anyone on the waiting list a chance to join in. So plan to update your RSVPs as your plans become finalized. As ever, will send out my cell number to my yes's the day or so prior. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy reading...maybe we'll be outside for June!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nick</member_name><member_id>10094294</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1275521579000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267214012000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:The Enchantress of Florence by Salman Rushdie</name><id>12718285</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273014000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/12718285/</event_url></item>