<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 University Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.337611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-731-9529</phone><name>Energy Restructuring Institute</name><city>Brookline</city><id>1033723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.131282</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;NOTE: We begin at 6:45 for all new members to become familiar with the concepts.   &lt;br /&gt;COME TO THIS FREE INTRODUCTION TO CHECK IT OUT!  (and for continuing member this is your chance to review.) Continuing members come at 7:15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although there is a lot of understanding about trauma, somehow the complete picture of its affect on us is not quite there.  And you know it because results that you want are not quite there. Understanding energetic displacement and the life-force energy loss incurred through trauma is the missing piece in the puzzle that is your healing journey.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The information I am going to present to you is very empowering. Come and learn that: &lt;br /&gt;1. Your life-force is contained by your energetic boundary which serves as a &amp;quot;cellular membrane&amp;quot; - it surrounds and protects you.&lt;br /&gt;2. The flow of energy in your body is regulated by the four energy gates.  &lt;br /&gt;3.  Trauma and illness cause a neuro-emotional dissociation in the form of upward displacement of your energetic field.&lt;br /&gt;4.  The gates are related to the chakras.  Each chakra stores the record of the traumatic experiences telling us how the gates got locked and what is keeping them locked. &lt;br /&gt;5.  We pay a high price for the energetic misalignment - there is always life-force energy loss. This energy can and must be retrieved before that trauma can be healed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bringing your energy into alignment will bring relief of symptoms; recovery of lost energy will heal your trauma. Makes a lot of sense, doesn't it?  But without the appropriate protocols to assist you in doing that, healing can be difficult to achieve.  Besides, there is a difference between knowing something intellectually and experiencing it.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this meetup you will discover not only how to repair the energetic displacement but also how to recover energy lost to your pain and struggle.  These are crucial steps if you are looking for a lasting healing.&lt;br /&gt;Is lasting healing actually possible? Yes, and if you ask if it is realizable for you, the truth is: it's been done before by many others!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will dive into your personal examples to evaluate the cost of your emotional and physical discomfort in terms of your lost life-force energy.  So, those who participated in our last meetup, either come with your personalized worksheet filled out using the sample protocol given to you last time, or be prepared to work on your worksheet during the meetup.  New participants will be using a sample protocol handout.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Yuliya Cohen</member_name><member_id>6311859</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256445770000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People on a healing journey</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma</urlname><id>1373363</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Freedom from Fear/ Anxiety /Emotional Trauma Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255386969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Four Gates To Recovery: Recovering Your Life-Force Energy Loss</name><id>11611491</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256251500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Freedom-From-Trauma/events/11611491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/f/global_11201455.jpeg</photo_url></item>