<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Providence</address_2><address_1>1060 Hope St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.819347</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>India Restaurant</name><city>Providence</city><id>624279</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.395134</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>I have picked India restaurant on Hope Street for our first Mid-month event.  Indian food seems to be one of this group's favorites, so I figured it was about time to try Indian again.  You can view pictures of their lovely renovated location as well as their menu at their website &lt;a href="http://www.indiarestaurant.com/menu_alacarte.php" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  I booked an outdoor seating, in the hopes of lovely weather.  Should it be too hot or wet, they are more than willing to have us seated inside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that the event will be held at 6PM- instead of our regular time, in order to make sure everyone gets home at a reasonable time to be fresh Monday morning- ugh?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have one bill for food, which will be divided equally among members then a second bill for beverages and alcohol. This way we can order appetizers as a table and everyone can enjoy with minimal confusion and the ones who choose not to indulge in &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; won't have to worry about paying extra when just enjoying non-alcoholic drinks. Please let me know if this is a problem for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed. If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. For everyone who has attended, I only ask that you contribute every other event. This would be such a big help to me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please see my piccy.  I am the one with the red hair ;-).</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216159963000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><why>We're a great group of people who like to try new restaurants.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211940656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RI Dining Out Group Mid-July Meetup- India Restaurant</name><id>8024027</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215986400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/8024027/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/7/global_4274535.jpeg</photo_url></item>