<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.379046</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Chinatown</name><city>Boston</city><id>1346020</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068735</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;August Moon Festival - Boston's Chinatown If you want to meet together, we'll need a way of knowing in advance where and when we gather. I suggest at the Tzu Chi Buddhist professional volunteers pavilion OR at the exhibition area (Chinese dragon, Kung Fu, Karate, dancing, etc.). However, do check out the Tzu Chi Buddhist professional volunteers pavilion and consider volunteering globally IF you have professional skills to volunteer internationally and the money to freight yourself oversees to volunteer with other professional level volunteers who are deeply committed to vegetarianism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familyculture.com/holidays/mooncake.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.familyculture.com/holidays/mooncake.htm&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.chinatownmainstreet.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.chinatownmainstreet.org/&lt;/a&gt; 617-350-6303 is the phone number for Chinatown Main Street, the sponsor of each year's August Moon Festival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Harrison &amp;amp; Beach Street, Chinatown, Boston, MA&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;a href="http://www.bostoncentral.com/events/august_moon_festival/p1041.php"&gt;map&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Take the Orange line to Chinatown or the Green Line to Boylston.&lt;/p&gt;Official Website: 
&lt;a href="http://www.bostoncentral.com/fwd.php?main=events&amp;amp;sub=fair&amp;amp;sub2=1041&amp;amp;pgx=cuc.fgarir%2Fteb.grregfavnzajbgnavup.jjj&amp;amp;backlink=%2Fevents%2Faugust_moon_festival%2Fp1041.php"&gt;August Moon Festival: Chinatown&lt;/a&gt; Location: Harrison &amp;amp; Beach Street, Chinatown, Boston, MA Phone: 
&lt;span&gt;617-542-2574&lt;/span&gt; Dates: Sunday, August 14, 2011&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;Sunday, August 14, 2011 Hours: 11:00am - 5:00pm In/Outdoor: Outdoor Cost: Free 
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://www.bostoncentral.com/images/shim.gif" width="1" height="15" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join the outdoor party in Chinatown to celebrate the end of the harvest season. There will be music, food, activities, storytellers and a dragon parade to celebrate the full moon. Be sure to leave room for mooncakes. Yum!&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;At the Harrison/Beach Street stage, visitors to the festival can watch dancing, musicians, martial artists, and various other performers. You'll find it all happening on Beach and Harrison Streets, in Boston's Chinatown. Rain or shine.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;If you get there early, try grabbing food (better yet - bring your OWN food because it's too busy to waste time) on Tyler &amp;amp; Beach Streets. 10:30 am - 2:30 pm on Sundays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a crowded event, so getting around with a stroller may be difficult. Backpack carriers are your best bet, so tots can be above it all maneuvering the crowds will be a lot easier. Chinatown is a relatively small area so if crowds aren't your thing, best to choose another event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Brief History of the August Moon Festival&lt;/strong&gt;:
 &lt;br /&gt;The August Moon Festival or Mid-Autumn Festival is one of the most celebrated Chinese holidays. It is held on the 15th day of the 8th lunar month. Chinese families celebrate the end of the harvest season with a big feast. Unlike the American Thanksgiving dinner, the Chinese have mooncakes, which are round pastries filled with red bean paste, fruit or jam, instead of grandma' apple pie. Friends and relatives also send mooncakes to each other as a way of giving thanks.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Dragon and lion dances, whose origins also date back to ancient China, are wonderful dances done during festivals, especially exciting are the dragon and lion dances.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://www.bostoncentral.com/events/august_moon_festival/p1041.php</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maynard S. Clark</member_name><member_id>83043</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313386402000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281909851000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August Moon Festival - Harrison &amp; Beach Street, Boston's Chinatown</name><id>14431441</id><headcount>4000</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313334000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/14431441/</event_url></item>