<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hancock seems to be the clear choice (although I still may post WALL-E at a later date.  I'll meet you in the lobby around 7:15.  We can grab a drink after the moive at one of the local places after the movie if you have the time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Hancock:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are heroes... there are superheroes... and then there's Hancock (Will Smith). With great power comes great responsibility -- everyone knows that -- everyone, that is, but Hancock. Edgy, conflicted, sarcastic, and misunderstood, Hancock's well-intentioned heroics might get the job done and save countless lives, but always seem to leave jaw-dropping damage in their wake. The public has finally had enough -- as grateful as they are to have their local hero, the good citizens of Los Angeles are wondering what they ever did to deserve this guy. Hancock isn't the kind of man who cares what other people think -- until the day that he saves the life of PR executive Ray Embrey (Jason Bateman), and the sardonic superhero begins to realize that he may have a vulnerable side after all. Facing that will be Hancock's greatest challenge yet -- and a task that may prove impossible as Ray's wife, Mary (Charlize Theron), insists that he's a lost cause. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hancock-movie.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.hancock-movie.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone needs to reach me, my cell phone number is 203-812-0705.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll meet you in the lobby at 7:15.  Hancock starts at 7:45</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>3461529</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215548183000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215108407000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hancock</name><id>8271543</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215299700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/8271543/</event_url></item>