<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Central Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843232</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-462-7543</phone><name>Capri Seaside Italian Grille &amp; Bar</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>949078</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.817438</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come on out to Salisbury Beach for a nice Italian Dinner, after dinner we will head over to Tupelo and catch the comedy show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE: The reservation is all set and it's under Donna, when you walk in and look around you shouldn't have a problem finding us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: You can park in either the Capri or Tupelo parking lot.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;UPDATE 1/1/10: Janet and I are watching the weather reports closely for the snow that we are expecting tomorrow. Because of this we have not called in the reservation to Capri yet. We will be calling in the reservation tomorrow by 3:30pm. If your plans have changed/you don’t want to be out in the snow please update your RSVP for dinner so we call in the correct amount for the reservation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Capri is a fairly new Italian Grille on Salisbury Beach. They have a dining area, a great bar and an entertainment area, and the food is delicious, check out their menu or get directions &lt;a href="http://www.capriseaside.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.capriseasi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be eating dinner at 5:30pm and then walking right across the street to see the comedy show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please take note of the RSVP deadline and update if your plans change as we must give a final count to the owner so that he can plan the setup of the dinning room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a separate event you can come to dinner and not the show what ever works for you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note snow may cancel this event!  Please check back for updates!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you at this great restaurant! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside the restaurant, look for the meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262644608000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261102061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner at Capri on Salisbury Beach!</name><id>12107414</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262471400000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/12107414/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/c/global_12290876.jpeg</photo_url></item>