<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Seelye Hall - Rm-106</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.330002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Smith College</name><city>Northampton</city><id>271495</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A student from Smith College has confirmed a screening of the film, &amp;quot;Improbable Collapse: The Demolition of our Republic.&amp;quot; This film proposes to provide visual and scientific evidence of a government cover-up and covert actions regarding the horrendous crimes of September 11, 2001, especially on the puzzling collapse of the Twin Towers and WTC Building 7.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, the public is welcome and invited to share different&lt;br /&gt;points of view, to debate the issues, inviting students to join in on the discussions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following is what Zoe, a student, shared by email:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey. . . it's been confirmed! In Seelye 106, on Tuesday, May 1st at 730&lt;br /&gt;pm, and I have the space until 11 (11:15) pm. For the event description,&lt;br /&gt;I wrote: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;A showing of the film 'Improbable Collapse,' a flim discussing the&lt;br /&gt;issues raised by the accepted [official] explanation for the World Trade Center&lt;br /&gt;collapse. Discussion afterwards with members of a local grassroots&lt;br /&gt;organization, including a debate and question and answer session.&lt;br /&gt;Audience skepticism, interest, and engagement of any kind is greatly&lt;br /&gt;encouraged and actively solicited for a topic that rarely receives space&lt;br /&gt;in an academic environment.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would add or change anything, let me know. Also, for a basic&lt;br /&gt;piece of paper advertising this event, what other information would you&lt;br /&gt;like on it? The name of your organization is FlyBy News, no?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I don't know many people who have views on this subject, much less are&lt;br /&gt;prepared to take the opposing side (opposing to you). If you know of&lt;br /&gt;anyone, though, I could contact them myself. It would be nice to have a&lt;br /&gt;real debate. I'll ask around. In any case, get back to me and I'll start&lt;br /&gt;sending emails out to the government, engineering, sociology, film and&lt;br /&gt;physics departments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides this May 1 event, the next meetup will be on may 23rd at the media ed.&lt;br /&gt;foundation community meeting space.. from 6pm..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;also.. there will be a meetup on this at the brattleboro common ground after&lt;br /&gt;community meal .. at 7:30pm, Tuesday May 8. I believe we will be showing a&lt;br /&gt;film at this event.. more info will follow..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;thanks for all your interest.. please confirm if you can make this meetup at smith..&lt;br /&gt;and this will be a good opportunity to see improbable collapse that might have &lt;br /&gt;missed the tour with mike berger. but we got some of his Q&amp;amp;A presentations&lt;br /&gt;that were phenomenal.. recorded.. perhaps we could show this film when edited&lt;br /&gt;at may 23rd meetup? till later,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;jonathan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;i will have information on this event at smith.. also at &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/" target="_blank"&gt;FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178235351000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177679982000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IMPROBABLE COLLAPSE - Smith College - May 1</name><id>5715654</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178062200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/5715654/</event_url></item>