<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm gonna try Thursday nights at least once a month and see how that works for everyone. This meeting will just be a chance for people to get to know each other and hopefully find a game that suits them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in running a campaign, please bring a short description of the campaign, starting level, and maybe a little backstory. Also include something about how much role-playing you'd like out of players and how many players you're willing to take on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're interested in playing a character in a campaign, be prepared to discuss character ideas and ask questions of DMs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been in many situations in my time where players and DMs or players and other players just don't mix well. Remeber, be honest with yourself about what kinds of people you like to game with. Also, be aware that when personalities don't mix, it's best to be honest and up front, but courteous about it. Every first few game sessions are a testing period, for players and DMs so take it slow when getting to know people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll make a sign-up sheet for DMs so they can collect contact info from people who come to the meetup. DM's can contact potential players after the meetup and work out details from there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks everyone and I'll post the location of the event later. It will definitely be somewhere close to the T.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.beantownpub.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beantownpub.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.beantownpu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>D&amp;D Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-DnD</urlname><id>244439</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1147463059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First Boston Dungeons &amp; Dragons Meetup</name><id>4934078</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1147993200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-DnD/events/4934078/</event_url></item>