<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;MEETING POSTPHONED TILL NEXT TUESDAY, FEB 19TH DUE TO IMPENDING WEATHER! COME SAME TIME AND PLACE NEXT TUESDAY AND MAYBE PREP SOME DISCUSSION VOCAB ABOUT YOUR VALENTINE'S DAY!!! ANDREW ALSO ADVISED! ANY QUESTIONS, YOU CAN CALL ME, NIKA. 416-0231!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Priviet!  The next Meetup for the Hartford Russian Language Group will be on Tuesday February 12th at 7:00 and we will continue to meet on the second Tuesday of each month from here on out.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will continue to hold meetings in the back meeting room at the Wood-n-Tap, 99 Sisson Ave, Hartford, CT.  The Wood-n-Tap is a nice, casual place with good food.  As before, I have not arranged for any formal meal, we can simply order off the menu as we please.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our first meetings have been basically informal events.  Most of our last meeting was conducted in Russian, but do not let that discourage you if you are a beginner like me, simply bring along a dictionary and jump right in.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have been growing slowly each month and hope to see some new faces this month! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately I will be out of town for this month's meeting, but it will be led  by Nika.  See you all in March! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS.  My email is anderson06143@yahoo.com and the website for the Wood-n-Tap is www.woodntap.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Anderson</member_name><member_id>1738935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203638916000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Russian Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordrussianmeetup</urlname><id>723352</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Russian Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199841066000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Russian Language February Meetup</name><id>7066777</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203465600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordrussianmeetup/events/7066777/</event_url></item>