<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Davis Square</address_2><address_1>17 Holland St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.776.2004</phone><name>Johnny D's</name><city>Somerville</city><id>669354</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Booty.  Vortex. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Not words one would normally put together ... unless you've been to a Booty Vortex show.  Then you really can't think of one without the other. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 So let's meetup at Johnny D's in Somerville and dance ourselves down to sweaty little nubs while Booty Vortex brings the funk and disco. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Booty Vortex is a 13 piece band that will definitely get you to "shake what yo mama gave ya".  (For more info on the band, see their website: &lt;a href="http://www.bootyvortex.com/"&gt;Booty Vortex&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've always had a &lt;strong&gt;fantastic&lt;/strong&gt; time at Booty shows.  Please join us and you'll have a fantastic time, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The cover charge for this show is $12 cash at the door.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The music starts at around 10:00. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I'll be hanging to the left of the entrance starting at 9:00 p.m. and I'll be there until the music starts.  As you pay your cover charge, look immediately to the left and over the room divider/window behind the door guys -- that's where I'll be. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you come to the show, &lt;strong&gt;please&lt;/strong&gt; text or call me to find me, preferably text. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I look like my profile picture, although I have a shaved head ... and I won't be wearing a knit cap on Satuday.  Once the music starts, I do wander around and look for folks (so it really helps if you posted a good picture of yourself), but texting me is the way to find me once the show starts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 (I'll also email my cell # to all Yes RSVPers on the afternoon of the show.) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you're driving to the show, note that there are street parking spots, but they may be difficult to find. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Johnny D's has a good city parking map &lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/parking/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you're taking the T, the Davis Square Red Line stop is directly across the street from Johnny D's.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here's a link to Johnny D's &lt;a href="http://www.johnnyds.com/"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a joint meeting with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/best-live-music/events/67409132/"&gt;Cambridge-Somerville Live Music&lt;/a&gt; group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my profile picture.  I'll be hanging to the immediate left of the entrance and I'll also email my cell # to all Yes RSVPers on the afternoon of the show.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>paul</member_name><member_id>4738108</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340625836000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338668821000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Booty Vortex @ Johnny D's</name><id>67450302</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340499600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/67450302/</event_url></item>