<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&amp;quot;The Holocaust: Memory and Legacy&amp;quot; to screen Thurs., Dec. 11 at 7 p.m. the &lt;br /&gt;West Newton (Mass.) Cinema, with post-film discussion panel of Holocaust &lt;br /&gt;survivors and others featured in the documentary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is $5; DVDs available for sale, $10. Information: 617-566-7557; Susie_d@yahoo.com, www.IRefusedtoDie.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More film information: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Holocaust: Memory and Legacy,&amp;quot; a new documentary film, is based on Susie Davidson's 2005 book (Ibbetson Street Press, Somerville, Mass.), &amp;quot;I Refused to Die: Stories of Boston-Area Holocaust Survivors and Soldiers who Liberated the Concentration Camps of World War II.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film, narrated by WBZ's Jordan Rich, features interviews with Holocaust survivors and WWII liberating soldiers, and prayers with Rabbi Moshe Waldoks (recently named one of the Top 25 Pulpit Rabbis in America by Newsweek Magazine), as well as music by Glenn Dickson and the Terezin Chamber Music Foundation's Hawthorne String Quartet. Also appearing: &amp;quot;2Gs&amp;quot; (children of Holocaust survivors) Boston City Councilor Michael P. Ross and Atty. Andrew M. Fischer, as well as Holocaust educators Facing History and Ourselves Chief Institutional Advancement Officer Andrew H. Tarsy, Tatyana Macaulay of the Strassler Center at Clark University, and Sonia Weitz of the Holocaust Center, Boston, North, in Peabody. Holocaust survivors include Israel Arbeiter, Samuel Bak, Edgar Krasa, Stephan Ross, Sonia Weitz and Rosian Zerner. The film also features Armenian filmmaker Apo Torosyan and local poets Harris Gardner and Regie Gibson, and children from Lexington, Mass.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ellen</member_name><member_id>4148667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229218771000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston</urlname><id>425314</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Jewish Singles 55+  of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228689769000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"The Holocaust: Memory and Legacy" </name><id>9297962</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229040000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/JewishSingles50-of-GreaterBoston/events/9297962/</event_url></item>