<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>21.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a small restaurant serving &amp;quot;a modern 'cuisine classique' without the limitations of preconceived flavor combination or construct.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The money stuff:&lt;br /&gt;There is a fee of $21 to register for this dinner.  Of that, $20 is a deposit, which will be returned to you at the restaurant (in cash).  &lt;b&gt;If you say that you're coming and then don't, you forfeit the $20. &lt;/b&gt; The remaining $1 is a non-refundable fee.  Part of this goes to Amazon Payments because they charge a transaction fee for the payment, and part of it will go to Meetup to help pay for the group's website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two ways to pay the deposit:&lt;br /&gt;1 – Online via the Euro Meetup website&lt;br /&gt;2 – In cash, by meeting me at a mutually convenient time and place (probably near Harvard Square).  If you want to pay cash, send me an email so that we can arrange a time &amp;amp; place to meet.  The website won't offer cash as an option, it only knows about what happens online.  I'll need to sign you up for the dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I posted this event on the website, I also sent an email to everyone in the group with more details about the restaurant.  If you'd like me to send it to you again, use the link next to &amp;quot;Who's hosting?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our table will take up half the restaurant.  If you need to ask, ask for the Euro group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>A</member_name><member_id>8074607</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282497023000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Europhiles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>euro-76</urlname><id>467296</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Euro Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280861338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Restaurant Week</name><id>14306774</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282437900000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/euro-76/events/14306774/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/d/global_17053757.jpeg</photo_url></item>