<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>224 Anderson Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Resilience Hub</name><city>Portland</city><id>11842732</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256172</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As we cultivate our capacities to become effective change-agents, this webinar will provide an opportunity to explore the relationship between the landscapes within and how we show up in our life and leadership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is a webinar, 8pm - 9:15pm and we are meeting in person to participate together, and to process a bit of our learning together afterward. This will be facilitated event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parties interested in forming a community of practice around this important work will be invited to organize as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More about the webinar:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What becomes possible when we deepen our self-awareness to discover what holds us back? What is the role of deep nature connection, personal practice, and community in cultivating a vibrant and fertile ecology for leadership to emerge and thrive - within us and around us? Who are we being called to become as the future generations call us forward to make a difference? And how can we design a life that feels inspiring AND contributes powerfully to the transformation of our world?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

To explore these questions, James Stark, Christopher Kuntzsch, and Katia Sol will draw upon their experience leading the Ecology of Leadership program at the Regenerative Design Institute in Bolinas, CA. They will provide an introduction to the program's core principles and practices, and share how we can begin to incorporate these into our lives as well as our local transition initiatives. For more information, visit www.TheEcologyofLeadership.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel Lyn</member_name><member_id>4529129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362113101000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362096304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Into the Ecology of Leadership: Leveraging Inner Permaculture 4 Inspired Action</name><id>106956982</id><duration>9000000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362097800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/106956982/</event_url></item>