<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Vassar Street, 4th Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT 32-141 (Stata Center) Room 32-D463</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9957032</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089844</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;With MySQL environments, horizontal scaling, load balancing, caching and firewalling are all achievable but require constant and ongoing modifications to applications.  With the forced 1:1 connection relationship between app servers and MySQL servers, making changes to database architecture (e.g., multi-master or sharding) requires manipulating many moving parts and can involve many people across the organization (e.g., developers, architects, Operations, DBAs, etc.).  In addition, there is a severe lack of real-time instrumentation and real-time Analytics for all SQL queries flowing between the application servers and MySQL database servers, which makes troubleshooting a cumbersome and timely process. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In this talk, you will learn how ScaleArc has developed transparent MySQL Server infrastructure software that achieves instant horizontal scaling, clustering and load balancing, connection multiplexing and connection pooling, transparent query-level caching, wire-speed filtering and higher availability…without requiring any changes or modifications to applications or MySQL databases at any point in time.  In addition, ScaleArc provides real-time tools and Analytics to quickly troubleshoot problem queries, and then allows the user to take action to fix them.  A live demo will &lt;br /&gt;

 be provided, and customer case studies will be discussed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------- Logistics -------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT's map with the building (E32) highlighted: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=32" class="linkified"&gt;http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=32&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT's map with the Kendall square T stop highlighted: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go"&gt;http://whereis.mit.edu/?selection=L5&amp;amp;Landmarks=go&lt;/a&gt; (the stop is in red on that map, and you can see E32 to the left)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT's map with parking lot information: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5&amp;amp;Parking=go"&gt;http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?selection=P5...&lt;/a&gt; There is also plentiful on-street parking (check the meters, some meters go until 8 pm in Cambridge).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that MIT lots are free to park in after 3 pm or so, even if it says "reserved for faculty"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free pizza and soda will be served, so please RSVP accurately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To RSVP anonymously, please login to the Meetup site with the e-mail address "admin at sheeri dot com" and the password "guest". For more information, see: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/calendar/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/calendar/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go up the stairs or the elevator to the 4th floor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sheeri Kritzer Cabral</member_name><member_id>2380684</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352870448000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston-Metro MySQL Users</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mysqlbos</urlname><id>212864</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342666523000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston MySQL Meetup Group Monthly Meetup</name><id>drjskdyqpbqb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352764800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mysqlbos/events/73973832/</event_url></item>