<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Side Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.017940</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Diana's Baths Parking</name><city>North Conway</city><id>553790</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129940</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;NO NEED TO REPLY IF YOU ARE NOT ATTENDING &lt;br /&gt;

 I had scheduled this hike a few weeks back and canceled it but had a couple of folks interested after the fact so here it is again. The Moats line the valley west of Conway and North conway NH. These are not 4000 footers, but the views make up for it as there are extended sections of ridgeline. Please dont confuse this with the Moats traverse that adds in North Moat and considerably more elevation and more difficult trail conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike is great way to get back in shape for summer time hiking. The pace will be moderate suitable for intermediate hikers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail normally has melted out by now athough there are possible wet conditions near the end. The hike is about 8.5 miles with reasonable grades and lots of sun. We will meet at Dianas Baths parking lot off the West side road in North Conway and will then shuttle back to the start of the hike off pasaconaway road. Please meet at Dianas Bath parking ready to hike by 9AM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual the 10 essentials of hiking gear are not optional and given the forecast suncreen and sunglasses should be added to the pack. iF you are not familiar wih the 10 essentials search for hikesafe.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spring gear is a must and just in case traction like microspikes must be carried. Due to the long sunny exposure,2 liters of water is recomended and electrolytes are useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please answer the questions&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dennis P</member_name><member_id>8579894</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368280234000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367432598000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South &amp; Middle Moat plus Red Ridge</name><id>117185682</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367672400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/117185682/</event_url></item>