<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>950 Cummings Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.561001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The American BBQ Restaurant &amp; Catering</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1557517</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.886002</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come on over to The American BBQ in &lt;strong&gt;Beverly&lt;/strong&gt; for a night of food, fun and games!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We  have been to their other location and the food is awesome, let&amp;rsquo;s go to&amp;nbsp;  their Beverly site and check it out.  We will Meetup at 5:00 grab some  dinner, chat and eat and play some games and most of all have some fun!!   There are booths and tables so we can move around as we need to for  the games/the amount of people playing a particular game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the American BBQ!:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re  proud and delighted to serve you our &amp;ldquo;Genuine Wood-Smoked BBQ&amp;rdquo;,  prepared in the true Southern tradition, along with hospitality that&amp;lsquo;ll  make you feel this is your &amp;ldquo;home away from home&amp;rdquo;. First, we dry rub our  premium meats with our own mix of spices and seasonings, then slow cook  them (for 5-16 hours!) in our wood smokers right on the premises. The  meat stays moist, &amp;ldquo;fall off the bone tender&amp;rdquo; and full of natural smokey  flavor. Notice the reddish color near the bone, telling you its really  slow-smoked. They serve beer and wine.  So, pull up a chair, roll up  your sleeves and get ready for the best southern BBQ in the north! Make  no mistake about it, you&amp;rsquo;ll come as a stranger but leave as family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Games!:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Do  you have a favorite non gambling card or board game(s) that you like to  play?  Well bring it/them to this event.   We ask everyone to bring 1  or 2 games or decks of cards that you like to play that you have around  the house even if you don't have a game to bring come along always, we  will have plenty and some one in the group has Apples to Apples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fun!:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Everyone  is open to move around the restaurant and play which ever game(s) you  want, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be stuck playing that one game, you can play as  many or as few as you want.  Also this is an open event so if you are  not able to come at 12:00 then come in anytime grab something to eat and  get in a game or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;American BBQ  &lt;br /&gt;950 Cummings Center Suite 96x  &lt;br /&gt;Beverly, MA 01915  &lt;br /&gt;978.921.1212&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of free parking in the Cummings Center Parking lot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Looking forward to seeing you! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt; &lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif" alt="smile" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk in and you will see us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300070414000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299815039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Food, Fun and Games at The American BBQ!!</name><id>16881005</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299967200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/16881005/</event_url></item>