<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 West St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.316262</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(413) 587-1011</phone><name>NORTHAMPTON MA_ FORBES LIBRARY </name><city>Northampton </city><id>832342</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.636533</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Hi folks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our March selection is Miss American Pie by Margaret Sartor. The Forbes Library has a couple of copies left; just ask at the circulation desk. Hope to see you next month!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Annie&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;A spellbinding and authentic document of American adolescence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set against the backdrop of the deep South in the 1970s, Miss American Pie is the unforgettable account of Margaret Sartor’s life from age twelve to eighteen. A raw document crafted from diaries, notebooks, and letters, this deeply personal yet universally appealing story astonishes with its candor. Young Margaret moves with ease between the seemingly trivial concerns of hairstyles and boys to more profound questions of faith and meaning. By turns funny and poignant, heartbreaking and profound, she tackles all of the decade’s issues—desegregation, drugs, the sexual revolution, the rise of feminism, and the spread of charismatic evangelical Christianity—with humor, frankness, and unexpected insight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miss American Pie reminds us what it feels like to grow up, offering a true and honest look at a teenager grappling with the timeless questions of sex, friendship, God, love, loss, and the meaning of family. The introduction and epilogue, written by Sartor from an older perspective, reflect on those turbulent and life-shaping years, revealing how the girl in the diary turned out after all, and demonstrating that childhood—both its joys and traumas—reverberate deeply in our adult lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs in the Community Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Annie</member_name><member_id>1543974</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1267754243000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paradisecityreaders</urlname><id>1404829</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Paradise City Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265163465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>March Selection: Miss American Pie by Margaret Sartor</name><id>12502803</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267488000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paradisecityreaders/events/12502803/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/1/global_12927089.jpeg</photo_url></item>