<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Temple Pl</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.355240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 542-8111</phone><name>MANTRA</name><city>Boston</city><id>668995</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.062000</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/2/2/6/event_179789222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;GenerationDesi.com and One World Cusine presents the annual Diwali Gala 2012 Night. We are going to make this fun and interactive...it is all about you! Mantra Boston is back!! It is one of the most high end venues for you and you date with good indian food and variety of drinks. Meet &amp;amp; greet! Free bhangra dance classes for all Newbies! Vendor stalls,live dj, delicious food and more! We are adding hookah's in the Hookah Lounge at Mantra for those who might be interested in trying the different flavors!  This Event is not to be missed! &lt;br /&gt;

Right in downtown Boston at the hot and exclusive MANTRA, located at 52 Temple Place, Boston, MA! Plenty of parking available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dooes open at 6:30pm for dinner and live singing and vendor stalls. Dance Party with live DJ and fantastic music ranging from Bollywood, Bhangra to your favorate music. Dance party starts at 9:30pm. Chikni Chameli, Munni Badnam Hui, Sheila Ki Jawaani and much more! Oh..when is it? Saturday, November 17th, 2012. We are keeping the prices so it is enjoyable by your family and friends. Brought to you by MANTRA Boston. &lt;br /&gt;

There are two packages available: &lt;br /&gt;

1. Dinner package: A Diwali special Buffet Dinner, music and entrance to after party included ($15). &lt;br /&gt;

Dinner + Dance Tickets: $35. (Early Bird special price at: $25 only!) Kids tickets start at $20 under 18. (Early Bird special price at: $15 only!) Kids under 3 are free. &lt;br /&gt;

2. Dance Party package: Come for the dance party only - we are expecting a lot of people for this one time event at MANTRA! We have already booked a group of 25 for a birthday party and we are expecting more!! Entrance Tickets at $15. (Early Bird special price for dance party at $10 only!) For birthday parties or VIP tables, starting at $150 per table. Email: Generationdesi@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

For further information/ticketting/rsvp, please see www.GenerationDesi.com and get your tickets now before we sell out!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeet</member_name><member_id>7388670</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353206691000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352789220000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Diwali Gala Night, Hookah's &amp; Fair 2012</name><id>91179162</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353195000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/91179162/</event_url></item>