<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All, &lt;br /&gt; A gentle reminder that the walk to support the MSPCA will be taking place this weekend in addition to our September Meetup. &lt;br /&gt;We will continue to host two locations for the fall season Chi Meetups. &lt;br /&gt;Our next few meetings weather permitting, will be held in two locations (just as we have for the summer). Members can choose to attend the Commons at 11AM and 1PM and we will also continue to hold meetups at 1PM at Doggie Day, Boston (Tremont Street).&lt;br /&gt;Several of our members will be at the Commons first on Sunday as they will be participating in the MSPCA WALK, please see link below for further information. &lt;br /&gt; Parkman Bandstand/Boston Common, 11am Registration, 12pm Walk, &lt;a href="http://www.mspca.org/site/TR?fr_id=1030&amp;amp;pg=entry" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mspca.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those of you who would like to attend the park in the morning then move onto to Doggie day at 1pm are welcome to do so, but PLEASE as always make a note in the rsvp so that we can keep track of the numbers :) If anyone has any further questions regarding this please also post them on the message board thread for the Sunday meetup. &lt;br /&gt;1. Boston Common (near the Boylston T stop/Lowes theater side) 11:00AM and 1:00 PM (leave an rsvp on the message board if you plan to go to the park at 1pm) &lt;br /&gt;2. DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER (Tremont Street, South end, Boston ...our usual location 1:00PM ONLY!!!! &lt;br /&gt;In other news, Doggie Day Playcenter recently had their primetime debut. The store and their services and commitment to all natural organic pet foods were featured on ABC Nightline just a week ago. Bravo! After the recent pet food scare a few months ago we all know this is a topic near and dear to us.  &lt;br /&gt;See link for further info.  See a real-time video &amp;quot;Fido goes Organic&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://abcnews.go.com/Nightline/Story?id=3511922&amp;amp;page=2" target="_blank"&gt;http://abcnews.go.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Key words: Pampering Pets with Organic Food&lt;br /&gt;Nothing but the Best for Some Lucky Cats and Dogs&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190306458000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>64</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186934781000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua September Meetup</name><id>6167283</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189350000000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/6167283/</event_url></item>