<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>address provided on request when you RSVP</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>41.944546</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Jeanne and Wayne's</name><city>Attleboro</city><id>10788692</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.285606</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: $5.00 (if there's a DJ) and a dish to share. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;What will YOU do for a few beads?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;If you don’t know what a second line is, it’s TIME you learned. Mardi Gras is coming to you or at least to North Attleboro. Jeanne &amp;amp; Wayne have a mega-large rumpus room, and they reserved a big chunk of it for Beanstalk dancing. Jeanne promises authentic Mardi Gras 2012 beads for everyone on the dance floor. (Don’t ask what she had to do to get them.) Feel free to wear your own interpretation of Mardi Gras or Carnival attire.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;We’re hoping for a big turnout, to celebrate this holiday in Bourbon Street style and to justify the expense of DJ Dru. Some of you have heard DJ Dru in action -- he’s willing to spin tunes for this party at a reduced fee as a favor to the Beanstalks, but we need a minimum turnout to meet his fixed expenses. If our numbers are smaller, we’ll dance to iPod and Pandora tunes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;You’re welcome to bring non-Beanstalk guests -- just remember that they must be over 21, and you’re accountable for their behavior. You’re also welcome to bring libations, but, if you start acting like a typical Bourbon Street tourist, Jeanne &amp;amp; Wayne will insist that you spend the night on a couch or other flat surface at their place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;The party starts with some food to fortify ourselves. If you’re able, please bring your own potluck contribution -- we suggest that you bring enough for 6-8 tall’uns. Jeanne MIGHT be persuaded to fix her wicked &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;feijoada&lt;/span&gt;, the Brazilian national dish.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Given the right dose of Dixieland jazz and Brazilian samba, maybe we can forget just how cold New England winter is.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;PLEASE TELL Jeanne ASAP whether you (and possibly guests) will join the party on February 9th. So we’ll know whether we have the numbers to cover DJ Dru’s expenses, we want a reasonably accurate count by&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SATURDAY, FEBRUARY 2&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne Smith</member_name><member_id>8341850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360469292000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358308393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mardi Gras Party in Attleboro</name><id>99832992</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360450800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/99832992/</event_url></item>