<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boulder, Colorado&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving&amp;#61666;&lt;br /&gt;Beginners Weekend Seminar presented by Charles Muir, with Leah Alchin&lt;br /&gt;October 24, 25, and 26, 2008 – for Couples and Singles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charles Muir is coming to your area to teach the world-renowned Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving Beginners Weekend Seminar. This is a rare opportunity for you to study directly with the Pioneer of the Tantra Movement in America. You will discover the secrets of sexual intimacy, passion, and spiritual connections in this powerful, fun, and transformative weekend! To create a safe and relaxed environment, there is no nudity in class. However, home play is assigned and is optional for singles. Here is just some of what you will learn to make you a conscious and masterful lover:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Breathing in lovemaking ~ key to ecstasy&lt;br /&gt;* The lost art of kissing ~ five styles of erotic and esoteric kissing&lt;br /&gt;* Six kinds of healing and erotic touch&lt;br /&gt;* The keys to increasing intimacy and spiritual union&lt;br /&gt;* Freeing the female orgasm ~ it’s easy!&lt;br /&gt;* 1,001 methods of exquisite pelvic movement&lt;br /&gt;* Sexual healing and awakening for men, the secret that can &lt;br /&gt;   Quadruple the length and power of your orgasm&lt;br /&gt;* Advanced lovemaking techniques you will use forever&lt;br /&gt;* Female sacred spot massage ritual ~ step-by-step instructions &lt;br /&gt;   to heal, awaken, and release unlimited energy&lt;br /&gt;* Internal muscular exercises for increased energy and pleasure&lt;br /&gt;* And so much more&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Here is what others say:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is a wonderful, powerful training without parallel in the field of transformation.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– Lew Mylar, Clinical and Consulting Psychologist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;I was amazed at how easy it was to become aware of old patterns, then to open to new possibilities in lovemaking.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– Byron Johnson, Engineer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This Tantra workshop is the most significant opportunity available for people looking to bring together spirituality, sexuality, and intimacy. It’s the time for couples of all ages to heal the much neglected individual and collective wound which separates ourselves from the beloved in each of us.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– Daniel Stanberry, Chiropractor and Shanna Stanberry, Licensed Psychologist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;This wonderful course allowed us to explore a new world of energy, sensitivity, intimacy, and appreciation of each other. Lovemaking has taken on a life of its own.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– Richard Tegtmeier, Defense Attorney and Lori Pinello-Tegtmeier, Consultant&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving® Beginners Weekend Seminar&lt;br /&gt;October 24, 25, and 26, 2008 – for Couples and Singles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Times:&lt;/b&gt; Friday night, October 24, 2008 – 6:45 pm to 11 pm, Saturday/Sunday – 10 am to 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location:&lt;/b&gt; Radisson Hotel, 1900 Ken Pratt Boulevard, Longmont, CO 80501 (directions mailed upon registration)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt; $450 per person, $900 per couple. Receive $55 per person discount for fully paid registration prior to September 24, 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hotel Accommodations:&lt;/b&gt; Radisson Hotel, seminars discount $89 per night if reserved 3 weeks prior. Refer to Source Tantra Seminar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REGISTRATION&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coordinator: JUDITH SHIVANI DAVIS   Register by phone, at our website&lt;br /&gt;Phone (Judith Shivani Davis): 303.449.6096   Email: &lt;u&gt;judithad@comcast.net&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="color: navy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;u&gt;www.sourcetantra.com&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: If you are registering as a Single person, the registration deadline is Friday, October 10, 2008&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ex: I'll be the guy in the back with a Meetup t-shir</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah Alchin, ACTE</member_name><member_id>7260814</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226807383000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Tantric Practitioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>tantrausa</urlname><id>1157501</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Tantra USA</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222746206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra: The Art of Conscious Loving Seminar in Boulder, CO Oct. 24, 25, 26, 2008</name><id>8861865</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-25200000</utc_offset><time>1224900000000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tantrausa/events/8861865/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/3/9/global_5699689.jpeg</photo_url></item>