<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01247</zip><lat>53.959106</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Your home or work</name><city>Your city</city><id>1192498</id><country>us</country><lon>-1.079194</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>95.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>As part of the &lt;b&gt;Authentic Masculine Magnetism Program&lt;/b&gt;, this 4 week TeleSeminar will provide you with &lt;b&gt;concrete techniques, exercises and action steps&lt;/b&gt; to &lt;b&gt;boost your sense of confidence and self worth.&lt;/b&gt; This in turn lays the groundwork for you to magnetize women who are interested in YOU.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Derek Ebrecht and I are joining forces to bring you a &lt;b&gt;synthesis of some of the most effective tools and techniques out there&lt;/b&gt;. We will introduce a series of concrete exercises/techniques, as well as additional awareness and action practices for HW between calls. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mondays, 8-9:30pm, Oct 11, 18, 25, Nov 1. Listen live and/or download the recordings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$95 if paid by Oct 10, $120 thereafter. Register ONCE for whole series.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This Tele-Seminar is for men who:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Are consistently falling into the “friends” category with women&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Find it challenging to initiate connection with women they are attracted to&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Aren’t sure how or when to escalate a connection and generate sexual interest&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Struggle with the dichotomy of nice guy/bad boy archetypes&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Are ready to turn knowledge into action&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;You will:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Hear what women want&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Learn a series of concrete techniques to boost your confidence &lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Have HW assignments between calls&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Receive mid-week check in emails with responses and guidance to your individual questions&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Have the external accountability to the group to get you into action&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830;    Receive supportive feedback on how to integrate the insights and practices into your life&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Have access to download audio recordings of all sessions and guided exercises&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefits You Will Receive:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Greater confidence and self worth&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Increased ease in approaching women and generating sexual interest&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Increased integrity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will get the most benefit from this series if you commit to practicing the techniques daily over the four weeks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brynn Bishop&lt;/b&gt; is a Tantra Educator, and Empowerment and Pleasure Coach, with over twenty years experience in the fields of body-mind integration and conscious relating. Through a unique synthesis of diverse modalities, Brynn assists individuals and couples in developing personal empowerment, relational skills and expanded pleasure. She is passionate about helping others increase their capacity for connection and fulfillment, and access their full aliveness and passion!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a NLP Master Practitioner &lt;b&gt;Derek Ebrecht&lt;/b&gt; helps individuals and couples attract the life, passion and vitality they desire. His passion for building relationships and maintaining them through time has been a focus of his for 10 years. Let him guide you to finding relationships that last.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Confirmed registrants will be emailed teleconference number</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Derek Ebrecht</member_name><member_id>4695117</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286845652000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286185676000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boost Your Confidence: A Four Week TeleSeminar for "Nice Guys"</name><id>qgkqpynnbpb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286841600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/14992235/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/b/global_18422827.jpeg</photo_url></item>