<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey Incubators!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This great opportunity to take hang out with your fellow incubators outside our usual improv/dinner date environment.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now with that said, all the details are below.  Be sure to thank Giovanni for offering it up to us.  Also, if you RSVP make sure you can def make it as to not waste a spot of fun for another incubator.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join me, the one and only Giovanni at the Museum of Science for Member Appreciation Night on Sunday, Sept, 14 at 6 p.m. This is a &lt;b&gt;free&lt;/b&gt; event for members who are allowed to bring in extra people on this one special night. My membership allows me to bring in &lt;b&gt;seven people&lt;/b&gt; so sign up early.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Parking is free at the museum for this one night. In addition to going through the exhibit halls, admission includes a free showing at the 3-D digital theatre and free admittance to the indoor butterfly garden. There will be special presentations, activities and a raffle. In addition, this year's theme is Robots. The staff will be on hand to demonstrate various uses of robot technology. You can meet Tinker, a virtual museum guide who can respond to your questions, and AIBO, a robot dog with artificial intelligence. Program a robot (without any experience!) at the tangible interface exhibit, explore the &amp;quot;Mars Yard&amp;quot; with a Personal Exploration Rover, and control a real MARCBOT, the same model being used in Iraq for investigating suspicious packages. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the main lobby of the Museum of Science around 5:45 p.m. because we have to sign in together. If you have any questions, email Giovanni.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will look like a Giovanni</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221781417000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220477497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Incubator Science Social Night brought to you by the one and only Giovanni!!!</name><id>8681884</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221428700000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/8681884/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>