<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.309551</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617- 524-3158</phone><name>The Loring-Greenough House</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>449325</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, April 12, notloB Folk Concerts will be pleased to present, at the historic Loring-Greenough House in Jamaica Plain, Darol Anger and Emy Phelps, with very special guest Sharon Gilchrist. Having jammed with Rushad Eggleston at his third notloB concert, this will be Darol's first feature notloB performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DAROL ANGER AND EMY PHELPS &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.darolanger.com/concerts/emy_phelps_and_darol_anger" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.darolanger.com/concerts/emy_phelps_and_darol_anger&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/Emy-Phelps-and-Darol-Anger/169326649792175" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Emy-Phelps-and-Darol-Anger/169326649792175&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Exceptional among modern fiddlers for his versatility and depth, Darol Anger has helped drive the evolution of the contemporary string band through his involvement with numerous pathbreaking ensembles such as his Republic Of Strings, the Turtle Island String Quartet, the David Grisman Quintet, Montreux, the Duo and other ensembles. Today Darol can be heard on NPR's "Car Talk" theme every week, along with Earl Scruggs, David Grisman and Tony Rice. He has recorded and produced scores of important recordings since 1977, is a MacDowell and UCross Fellow, and has received numerous composers' residencies and grants. He is a featured soloist on dozens of recordings and motion picture soundtracks. Virtuoso fiddler and multi-string master Darol Anger here focuses his talents in service of the singer-songwriter's art. Emy Phelps is a standout artist in a large field, a prolific songwriter with a riveting voice which plumbs the deepest emotions. A musician of note in the Pacific Northwest, she has made a 30 year music career while raising 3 sons and one daughter, achieving degrees in Theatre Arts and Special Education, and touring for 7 years with Brian Ransom's Ceramic Ensemble. In combination, these 2 musicians bring out each other's special ability to convey deep emotional resonance and spark low-key fireworks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHARON GILCHRIST &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.sharon-gilchrist.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.sharon-gilchrist.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Sharon Gilchrist originally hails from Southlake, Texas. She has performed with a long list of artists - the Peter Rowan and Tony Rice Quartet, Uncle Earl, The Santa Fe All-Stars, the Bill Hearne Trio and Mary &amp;amp; Mars, to name a few. She is currently based out of Santa Fe, New Mexico where she teaches private mandolin lessons at Santa Fe String Studios and is on staff as a mandolin teacher at the College of Santa Fe. Sharon received a Bachelor's Degree in Mandolin Performance from Belmont University in Nashville, Tennessee. While in Nashville, she spent time playing upright bass with several singer-songwriters in the indie-rock scene such as Josh Rouse, Rebecca Stout and Jennifer Niceley. She also served as musical director and composer for the modern art collective, DddD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested donation $20 at the door; $15 for Loring-Greenough museum members. Plus $1 preservation fee. &lt;br /&gt;

Doors 7:30, Concert 8:00 &lt;br /&gt;

Room capacity is 40, reservations are required, notlobreservations at gmail dot com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pastries from Fiore's &lt;br /&gt;

Coffee from JP Licks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info - &lt;a href="https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/" class="linkified"&gt;https://sites.google.com/site/notlobmusic/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Join the mailing list - &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic" class="linkified"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/notlobmusic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;notloB Folk Concerts has produced close to 100 not-for-profit concerts in the greater Boston area since 2007. The series is volunteer-run; 100% of the donations go to the musicians and production expenses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334280175000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332801391000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Darol Anger and Emy Phelps, with very special guest Sharon Gilchrist</name><id>57974072</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334275200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/57974072/</event_url></item>