<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;COST:  $40 pp - MUST PAY CASH WHEN WE MEET&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RAIN DATE SCHEDULED FOR AUGUST 15TH - SAME TIME &amp;amp; PLACE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum 15 members renting to book&lt;br /&gt;Entire Trip = noon - 4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Everyone - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for another Kayaking Adventure!  This will prove to be a great experience.  We've teamed up with Eastern Mountain Sports to plan a guided kayaking tour out of Hingham Harbor.  We'll begin with a brief lesson and then begin our exploration of the inner Boston Harbor Islands and its National Park Lands on one of Eastern Mountain Sports most popular paddles.  Our guide will discuss various history, water foul and point out notes of interest throughout our paddle.  We'll take a break and stretch our legs on one of the many islands and have a snack as we talk about the extensive preservation work that has allowed this area to become a vital resource for all of its visitors. Come be a part of this fun paddle around Hingham Harbor!  Great for all experience levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need a &lt;u&gt;minimum of 15 members&lt;/u&gt; renting to book!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring: &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;water shoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;a snack/lunch and beverage &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;plenty of water &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;a hat &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;No alcohol &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;a smile for a good time&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bringing your own boat:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;No cost&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;need your own PFD, paddle and whistle&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;WEATHER:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to check your email either Friday night or Saturday morning for cancellation notice from me.  &lt;b&gt;RAIN DATE SCHEDULED FOR NEXT DAY OR AUGUST 15TH - SAME TIME!!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*SSFMG and its organizers are not responsible for any injuries to participants or damage to kayaks and/or kayak equipment. Personal flotation devices (PFDs) are required for all participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hingham Harbor&lt;br /&gt; - From Route 3, take Exit 14 (Rockland, Nantasket) to Route 228 North&lt;br /&gt; - Follow Route 228 North to Route 3A North&lt;br /&gt; - At the set of lights, go left, onto Route 3A&lt;br /&gt; - Follow 3A for about a mile, until the Hingham rotary&lt;br /&gt; - Take the second right out of the rotary&lt;br /&gt; - The launch site is located at Hingham Harbor Beach/Park on Rt. 3A in Hingham&lt;br /&gt; - up the road from the rotary, straight at lights (Stars on the corner)&lt;br /&gt; - Will be just on your right beyond 1st light&lt;br /&gt; - We'll launch at the beach area between the boat ramp and the marked swimming area&lt;br /&gt; - Look for the trailer with the kayaks&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in Parking Lot at boat ramp - look for Kayak Trailer</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>8338847</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282099392000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277308586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking - Hingham Harbor Guided Tour</name><id>13887168</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281800700000</time><rsvp_limit>31</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/13887168/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/5/c/global_7576956.jpeg</photo_url></item>