<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 Main St #14</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01752</zip><lat>42.346626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Earthsong Yoga</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>1510084</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.549316</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April&amp;rsquo;s FREE Community Evenings, our gift to you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : large"&gt;New Possibilities for Feeling Good!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;nbsp;(this event will also be available on April 11th, at Roots and Wings in Natick; see calendar)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you like a mini-retreat focused fully on feeling good? Who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t?!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Then join us, and let Ann guide you through three transformative, relaxing, feeling-good meditations. We&amp;rsquo;ll deeply relax. We&amp;rsquo;ll dream and create. We&amp;rsquo;ll remember happy times. We&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate. And we&amp;rsquo;ll connect to expanding love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our intention is to help you deeply relax, let go of your tension and stress, and to leave feeling soaked up with love, appreciation, and good thoughts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Sound good? If so, join us, and invite your friends and family to join us, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px ; text-align : left"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ann was wonderful! I came into the room after the rush of the day and was immediately at peace. Her calm, focused and patient nature was so welcoming. I am still using the techniques taught at this gathering. They have helped me react with purpose. I'm very grateful to Ann for sharing her time and knowledge.&amp;rdquo; Linda M.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;So treat yourself to this wonderful free event for you. Please invite others to sign up and join you. Share this with your friends, family and groups. The class is appropriate for everyone, and all are welcome! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Space is limited, so registration is required. Registration for this event fills up VERY quickly!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We usually have a waiting list, so if your plans change, please, please be considerate and let us know as soon as possible so someone else can take your place.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Please plan on arriving around 7:25 to get settled. No need to bring anything, unless you want to.&amp;nbsp; Chairs, yoga mats, pillows and yoga blankets are available there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope you'll join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Ann&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., spiritual life coach with www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;This public event is co-sponsored by Earthsong Yoga and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Thank you to Earthsong Yoga for co-sponsoring these public service events with us! Check out all the programs and healing practitioners they offer for your health and well-being! We love them!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;www.EarthsongYoga.com&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On second floor of old large building; look for signboard on sidewalk</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333760849000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332452941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Possibilities for Feeling Good! Free community evening of guided meditations</name><id>57463302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333755000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/57463302/</event_url></item>