<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; on the PHONE &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Note: This is a long distance call; not toll-free. &lt;br /&gt;** Phone # will be sent to you after you RSVP : YES&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Chime in&amp;quot; from 9 - 10 pm ...mastermind with Linda Marks.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as well as join in &lt;br /&gt;- with your questions &lt;br /&gt;- to get support and suggestions &lt;br /&gt;- to share your LOA experiences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Linda Marks, BostonLOA member and heart-centered therapist and coach&lt;/b&gt;, presenter at June’s meetup, is on the call to answer any questions &amp;amp; help you understand further how to &lt;b&gt;reclaim the power of your heart. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even when times are tough (e.g. our current economic climate, challenges in relationships, juggling multiple responsibilities in daily life), coming from a heart space will help you move through the challenges with creativity and power. No matter what happens externally, coming from heart space will help you stay empowered. And living in coherence strengthens your creative force, so your actions are strengthened with full heart power. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;i&gt;The body is an electromagnetic energy field and &lt;br /&gt;the heart is the strongest generator of electromagnetic energy in the body. &lt;br /&gt;The electrical field generated by the heart is 60 times that of the brain. &lt;br /&gt;The magnetic field generated by the heart is 5,000 times that of the brain. &lt;br /&gt;If we learn to connect with the power of our hearts, &lt;br /&gt;and bring this power into our daily lives, &lt;br /&gt;we empower our visions and actions.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Comments from some of our members:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Linda is vibrant and energetic; she knows her material well. She is so intensely committed to the &amp;quot;heart&amp;quot; concept that you got to see life (hers) through a completely different lens - a beating heart. “ - &lt;i&gt;Nancy Conrad&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Very Transformative - Learning how to harness the power of the heart to heal the mind. Also helpful in developing heart focus for manifesting.” - &lt;i&gt;Geoffrey&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go here to read all the wonderful comments: &lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/calendar/10350159/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245373478000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244844846000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BostonLOA TELE-Meetup: LOA Masterminding with Linda Marks</name><id>10640091</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245200400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/10640091/</event_url></item>