<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>62 Dunham Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.574697</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 232-7200</phone><name>North Shore Music Theater</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1296765</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.868823</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>They are holding 20 tickets for our group for the performance on Friday night, May 30th, at 8:00 pm at $30.00 per ticket, usually $60.00&lt;br /&gt;Interested people can call the Group Sales ticket office at 978-232-7202 and reference my name (Jill) and the Merrimack Group.  They will hold these seats until Friday, May 24th.  People can call and pay directly at the group sales number...&lt;br /&gt;The production runs 2 hours 50 mins. Suggestions are welcome for a place to go after if anyone is interested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NSMT is thrilled to produce the New England Regional Theatre Premiere of Mel Brooks' THE PRODUCERS, winner of 12 Tony® Awards including Best Musical. That is more Tony® Awards than any other show in Broadway history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on the hit 1968 film, this Mel Brooks masterpiece is the story of a washed-up Broadway producer and his timid accountant who hatch a scheme to get rich quick by producing a sure-fire flop. It's a comic tour-de-force that spoofs the big, old-fashioned Broadway musical while paying tribute to it at the same time. The Producers, originally directed and choreographed by Susan Stroman, will leave you laughing out loud!&lt;br /&gt;Book by Mel Brooks &amp;amp; Thomas Meehan.&lt;br /&gt;Music &amp;amp; Lyrics by Mel Brooks.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;North Shore Music Theatre - HOME&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jill and Chuck our organizers will meet you in the lobby. A block of seats are being held.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212363651000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>Fun people and discounted seats..thanks Jill!!</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211139446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Producers at North Shore Music Theater</name><id>7962820</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212190200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/7962820/</event_url></item>