<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 2nd Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.483320</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7815057865</phone><name>Boston Affilaite Marketing Networking Group @ iBasis in Burlington, MA</name><city>Burlington</city><id>191888</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.222290</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>----- Local Boston Affiliate Webmaster Publishers &amp;amp; Affiliate Marketing Managers Wanted! ------ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Affiliate Marketing Roundtable is a group of Boston affiliate managers and affiliates that meet in a monthly open round table discussion to share tips, strategies and develop long term partnership with in the local Boston affiliate marketing community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;175+ Members and Growing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Average 20+ affiliate marketers attend this Boston affiliate marketing event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually meet the 3rd Thursday of the month at 2:30pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However will push this one out an extra Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Hosted at iBasis / Pingo.com in Burlington, MA with a fridge full of drinks and snacks provided. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda:  This Meeting is for Merchant / Affiliate Marketing Manager Topics Only &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:15 to 2:30pm Open Networking &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:30 to 3:30pm Affiliate Marketing Roundtable Discussion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* 2-3 Min Merchant Intro: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Share Your Affiliate Program's Product or Service&lt;br /&gt;- Explain you?re (USP) Unique Selling Proposition: How do you stand up to your competing affiliate programs&lt;br /&gt;- Details on your payouts, average order size and conversion rates &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What type of online publishers are you looking for?  Share who is your target affiliate? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally Funny Short Story Time: Today Meeting Theme is Family: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Share an interesting story about your family or in laws. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:30 to 3:40pm  &lt;a href="http://www.squidoo.com/AffiliateMarketingPartnerships/" target="_blank"&gt;Merchant to Merchant Cross Promotional Strategies. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Networking for merchant partner referrals that compliment your affiliate program. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:40 to 4:15pm  Affiliate Recruiting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All Attendees MUST bring a list of potential affiliate referrals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You cant take from the group, unless youre willing to give&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring: &lt;br /&gt; List of Your Top 20 General Category Affiliate Partners&lt;br /&gt; List of targeted specific referrals to give to an attending merchant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* This is why its important to mention your program in the RSVP to be sure to receive and give potential referrals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OPEN TOPIC &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(If Time) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  Share Affiliate Incentives &amp;amp; Promotions&lt;br /&gt;  Affiliate Manager Newsletter Communication Tips&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:15 to 4:30pm Flexible one on one time to set up individual networking opportunities with affiliate managers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Each attendee will be given a slot of time to share tips and find support from fellow members. &lt;br /&gt;* The group also provides a monthly team check up of support to your monthly tasks and goals &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some attendees may want to arrange one on ones to meet up for lunch prior or coffee after or just go shopping at the Burlington Mall! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Group organization &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brian Hawkins &lt;br /&gt;Affiliate Marketing Manager &lt;br /&gt;Pingo &lt;a href="http://www.Pingo.com/affiliate.do" target="_blank"&gt;Phone Card Affiliate Program &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.SuperAffililiateBluePrint.com" target="_blank"&gt;Phone Card Marketing Tips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;affiliate /at/ pingo.com &lt;br /&gt;781-505-7865 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s. dont worry, will get you all out before traffic piles up on 95, so that you can get home early as an extra perk for attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DONT FORGET TO POST A LINK WITH YOUR RSVP TO YOUR AFFILITE PROGRAM &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Matson</member_name><member_id>1490252</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541333000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in SEO/SEM</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSEO</urlname><id>219718</id><group_lat>42.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Search Engine Optimization Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177441883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New England To Boston Affiliate Marketing Networking group</name><id>5704478</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180031400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSEO/events/5704478/</event_url></item>