<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>52.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Update:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hi,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;In addition to the fun weekend we have planned, Cranmore is offering the following:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.cranmore.com/winter/adult_lessons" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cranmore&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Dates:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;January 21-22, 2012&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Who can participate:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;New skiers &amp;amp; snowboarders, &amp;amp; their skiing/snowboarding friend!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Bring a Friend to Learn to Ski or Ride! The new skier or snowboarder purchases a Getting Started package (two hour group lesson, rental equipment &amp;amp; beginner lift ticket) for the special price of $60, and the skier or snowboarder who brings the new skier or snowboarder receives a free lift ticket for him/herself to enjoy the same day.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Make your reservation by Monday, January 16 as we only have 6 spots remaining for the January 20 - January, 22 weekend.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Darlene, me and the rest of the Wedeln crew from Friday, January 20 through Sunday January 22 up at the most beautiful Ski Club in the Mount Washington Valley! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spend the weekend with us either:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Downhill skiing with us at Wildcat, Attitash, Cranmore, Bretton Woods, or Sunday River.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cross-Country Ski with us at Jackson X-C in the classic New England town of Jackson, NH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Snowshoeing out our back door or take a winter hike!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Enjoy the apres-ski event held by one of our sister clubs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Have dinner with the Wedelns - Meal details to be sent out closer to the event. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- After dinner, we will be having our social event!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you need to know!:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Guest Fees are $25 per night plus $2 Amazon Payment fee. This must be paid online &amp;nbsp;in advance. (&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;total guest fees = &amp;nbsp;$52 via Meetup using Amazon Payments - NO REFUNDS GIVEN FOR ANY REASON)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Meals are TBD but are likely $25 - $30 for the weekend to be paid when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Social events are $12 each. Payable when you arrive. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you arrive, you will be given a tour of the house and assigned to a room and bed. Rooms are separated by gender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are required to please bring your own:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bedding: (sleeping bag, pillow, or twin sheets, blanket, pillow)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Toiletries (towel, flip flops for shower, soap, shampoo, hair dryer etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Skis / Snowboards / Snowshoes / X-C skis can be brought up as well or rented easily from local shops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You are required to keep your room clean. To keep our guest fees low and since we are a private club, you may be asked to perform some light duties around our club like help vacuum a hallway, clean a bathroom, or mop a floor. We love when guests volunteer to help out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please Note - Space is extremely limited - so sign up today. You must reserve by Martin Luther King Day - Monday, January 16. Reservations will be closed after that date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All guests must be 21 years of age or older and be able to provide an acceptable proof of age and identification upon arrival (State issued Driver's License or Government Issued Passport are acceptable forms of age and identification). As a private entity, the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors club reserves the right to remove guests from the premises for any&amp;nbsp;reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any questions? Feel free to e-mail me and ask me questions or post it on the message board. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jonathan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions to be sent to YES RSVPs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327324495000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325598684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun Snowsports Weekend!</name><id>46422152</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327111200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/46422152/</event_url></item>