<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They really do paddle faster if they hear Banjos and see PITCH FORKS...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looks like there has been a lot of rain for a good river flow conditions for the racers and for us to watch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch these kayakers and Canoeists either make the rapids Expertly or be torn to pieces loosing all of their cargo and many body parts&lt;br /&gt;Blooding up the finish line drawing sharks all the way up the river from the DEEP ocean to have us scream in delight&lt;br /&gt;at the feeding frenzy.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LETS CHEER ON THE RACERS, THIS IS A GOOD EVENT TO WATCH AND THE POT LUCK EVENT AFTER IS A GOOD SOCIAL EVENT TILL ITS WARM ENOUGH FOR US TO KAYAK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be many walk/hike events with &amp;quot;Features&amp;quot; untill its warm enough to kayak so you are not missing anything if you need to walk, besides i have a walk/hike event on Sunday if your Azz is ugly and fat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Race only happens once per year and i think its worth our participation, besides it interesting..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;_Prediction as of Monday:    Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 47. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pot luck will most likely be &amp;quot;inside&amp;quot; and in Wethersfield, we may burn some wood in the burn barrel. &lt;br /&gt;More details closer to the event day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a spectator event for us and pot luck Barbie-q event afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: additional Parking and shuttle bus info at bottom of this link: ~~&amp;gt;    &lt;a href="http://www.scanticspringsplash.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.scanticspr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*New*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCANTIC SPRING SPLASH&lt;br /&gt;SPECTATOR SHUTTLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE spectator parking will be available at the staff parking lot of Fermi High School (corner of North Maple Street and Moody Road).  The free shuttle bus will provide spectators a worry free trip to and from the Powder Mill Barn on race day.  The bus will run from 11:30 am until about one half hour after the end of the race.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and enjoy the race, and don’t worry about finding a parking space at Powder Hollow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring a food item to help fill our canoe for the Enfield Food Shelf.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will most likely park here and use the supplied bus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 19th ANNUAL SCANTIC SPRING SPLASH CANOE AND KAYAK RACE March 27th, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a Location that is prime for so many things, last summer it was a place for us to play in the water, tubing,  and have a barbie -q a few times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time of year only the brave will go in the water, and we are only just going to watch them and cheer the racers on... They will go in the water for us and give us a great show.&lt;br /&gt;Scantic River Water Temp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 15th - 43.2 deg  as of 3:15 Monday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The actual race starts about 11:30 to 12:00 pm and it takes a while to go the 5 miles, but with a good current and their paddle speed, its not long before some start to finish, while waiting its good to check out the area and just converse..so i will get there about 12 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So closer to the date the event will be updated on weather, water conditions and if the event is canceled by the promoters. etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pot Luck Location: too soon to choose MOST LIKELY IN WETHERSFIELD. but not confirmed yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.scanticspringsplash.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.scanticspr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FINDING US at the Site:&lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt; WE will be UPSTREAM from the Road Bridge BY TAKING THE PATH DOWN TO THE RAPIDS (apx 300 feet from the bridge) at THE WATERS EDGE, LOOK FOR THE ORANGE 6 FOOT POLE AND ORANGE HUNTING HAT.&lt;br /&gt;Here is a pick of me and the group from last year and the vantage point..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://journalinquirer.mycapture.com/mycapture/enlarge.asp?image=22972559&amp;amp;event=720481&amp;amp;CategoryID=45476" target="_blank"&gt;http://journalinquire...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The river racers will be paddling &lt;br /&gt; 5 Miles with 1 mandatory Portage from Somersville, CT to Powder Hollow Barn in Hazardville. 3 Class II Rapids, including the popular finish area. Lots of spectators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THAT WILL BE SOME OF US... SPECTATORS &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving and parking directions DIRECTIONS i used for the last 3 years (but now i see they have shuttle busses also..Fermi Highschool check scantic splash for those details):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 91 to Parking lot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 47 East. Go eastbound 2.7 miles on RT-190 (Hazard Avenue) from Enfield to Hazardville.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At intersection of RT-190 and North/South Maple Street (RT 192)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~&amp;gt; turn right (South) onto South Maple Street. (but if going to Fremi High sckool for the shuttle bus, take a left and go north on North Maple.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look For the 6 foot Orange Pole and Orange Hunting Hat by the actual rapids waterside.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269878952000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264108278000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> *KAYAK RACERS*  on the Scantic RiverEvent &amp; Group Barbie-Q Nearby </name><id>12385561</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269705600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/12385561/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/8/7/global_4907255.jpeg</photo_url></item>