<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.989895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hazard Grille</name><city>Enfield</city><id>950610</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/1/2/event_78717362.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The Man in the Rockefeller Suit by Mark Seal &lt;br /&gt;

 The story of Clark Rockefeller is a stranger-than-fiction twist on the classic American success story of the self-made man-because Clark Rockefeller was totally made up. The career con man who convincingly passed himself off as Rockefeller was born in a small village in Germany. At seventeen, obsessed with getting to America, he flew into the country on dubious student visa documents and his journey of deception began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next thirty years, boldly assuming a series of false identities, he moved up the social ladder through exclusive enclaves on both coasts-culminating in a stunning twelve-year marriage to a rising star businesswoman with a Harvard MBA who believed she'd wed a Rockefeller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The imposter charmed his way into exclusive clubs and financial institutions-working on Wall Street, showing off an extraordinary art collection-until his marriage ended and he was arrested for kidnapping his daughter, which exposed his past of astounding deceptions as well as a connection to the bizarre disappearance of a California couple in the mid-1980s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story of The Man in the Rockefeller Suit is a probing and cinematic exploration of an audacious imposer-and a man determined to live the American dream by any means necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: Abdul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Angel Makers by Jessica Gregson&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 When the men of a remote Hungarian village go off to war in 1916, the women left behind realize their lives are much better without them. Suddenly, they are not being beaten; they have time for friendships; they even find romance with the injured Italian soldiers staying just outside of town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Sari, an intelligent girl who's always been an outcast (her fellow villagers suspect her of being a witch because of her medical knowledge), it's the first time in her life she's had friends. When the men return at war's end, the freedom Sari and the others have enjoyed is suddenly snatched from them, and they realize they need to do whatever it takes to hold onto it. Sari puts her medical knowledge to use to off her husband. Then she helps one of her friends. And another. When the word spreads, she realizes her problems are only beginning. This creeping and hugely readable first novel is based on a true story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chosen By:&amp;nbsp; Cat P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine A Powell</member_name><member_id>13299731</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330562145000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323640558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>February's Discussion: The Man in the Rockefeller Suit &amp; Angel Makers</name><id>44131502</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330471800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/44131502/</event_url></item>