<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Hazard Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06082</zip><lat>41.989895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hazard Grille</name><city>Enfield</city><id>950610</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.579881</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/0/1/c/event_146616892.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Let the Great World Spin by Colum McCan &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 In the dawning light of a late-summer morning, the people of lower Manhattan stand hushed, staring up in disbelief at the Twin Towers. It is August 1974, and a mysterious tightrope walker is running, dancing, leaping between the towers, suspended a quarter mile above the ground. In the streets below, a slew of ordinary lives become extraordinary in bestselling novelist Colum McCann’s stunningly intricate portrait of a city and its people. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Let the Great World Spin is the critically acclaimed author’s most ambitious novel yet: a dazzlingly rich vision of the pain, loveliness, mystery, and promise of New York City in the 1970s. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Corrigan, a radical young Irish monk, struggles with his own demons as he lives among the prostitutes in the middle of the burning Bronx. A group of mothers gather in a Park Avenue apartment to mourn their sons who died in Vietnam, only to discover just how much divides them even in grief. A young artist finds herself at the scene of a hit-and-run that sends her own life careening sideways. Tillie, a thirty-eight-year-old grandmother, turns tricks alongside her teenage daughter, determined not only to take care of her family but to prove her own worth. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Elegantly weaving together these and other seemingly disparate lives, McCann’s powerful allegory comes alive in the unforgettable voices of the city’s people, unexpectedly drawn together by hope, beauty, and the “artistic crime of the century.” A sweeping and radical social novel, Let the Great World Spin captures the spirit of America in a time of transition, extraordinary promise, and, in hindsight, heartbreaking innocence. Hailed as a “fiercely original talent” (San Francisco Chronicle), award-winning novelist McCann has delivered a triumphantly American masterpiece that awakens in us a sense of what the novel can achieve, confront, and even heal. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Chosen by Catherine&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Quiet The power of introverts in a World....by Susan Cain&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 At least one-third of the people we know are introverts. They are the ones who prefer listening to speaking, reading to partying; who innovate and create but dislike self-promotion; who favor working on their own over brainstorming in teams. Although they are often labeled "quiet," it is to introverts that we owe many of the great contributions to society--from van Gogh’s sunflowers to the invention of the personal computer. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Passionately argued, impressively researched, and filled with indelible stories of real people, Quiet shows how dramatically we undervalue introverts, and how much we lose in doing so. Taking the reader on a journey from Dale Carnegie’s birthplace to Harvard Business School, from a Tony Robbins &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 seminar to an evangelical megachurch, Susan Cain charts the rise of the Extrovert Ideal in the twentieth century and explores its far-reaching effects. She talks to Asian-American students who feel alienated from the brash, backslapping atmosphere of American schools. She questions the dominant values of American business culture, where forced collaboration can stand in the way of innovation, and where the leadership potential of introverts is often overlooked. And she draws on cutting-edge research in psychology and neuroscience to reveal the surprising differences between extroverts and introverts. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Perhaps most inspiring, she introduces us to successful introverts--from a witty, high-octane public speaker who recharges in solitude after his talks, to a record-breaking salesman who quietly taps into the power of questions. Finally, she offers invaluable advice on everything from how to better negotiate differences in introvert-extrovert relationships to how to empower an introverted child to when it makes sense to be a "pretend extrovert." &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This extraordinary book has the power to permanently change how we see introverts and, equally important, how introverts see themselves. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Chosen by: ???&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine</member_name><member_id>12990945</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346709440000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341182471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>August's Discussion</name><id>71564482</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346193000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/71564482/</event_url></item>