<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364744</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 661-1580</phone><name>Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1019999</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We may have neglected the gloomy Scandinavian literature for far too long. That's about to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Tove Jansson&amp;rsquo;s most unnerving and unpredictable novel, deception&amp;mdash;the lies we tell ourselves and the lies we tell others&amp;mdash;comes into focus.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Snow has been falling on the village all winter long. It covers windows and piles up in front of doors. The sun rises late and sets early, and even during the day there is little to do but trade tales. This year everybody&amp;rsquo;s talking about Katri Kling and Anna Aemelin. Katri is a yellow-eyed outcast who lives with her simpleminded brother and a dog she refuses to name. She has no use for the white lies that smooth social intercourse. Anna, an elderly children&amp;rsquo;s book illustrator, appears to be on the other end of the scale: a respected member of the village, if an aloof one. Anna lives in a large empty house, venturing out in the spring to paint exquisitely detailed forest scenes. But Anna has something Katri wants, and to get it Katri will&amp;nbsp;insinuate herself in Anna&amp;rsquo;s life.&amp;nbsp;A strident battle of wills ensues&amp;nbsp;before we get anywhere near&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;proverbial (and literal) thaw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I loved this book...understated yet exciting, and with a tension that keeps you reading. I felt transported to that remote region of Sweden and when I finished it I read it all over again. The characters still haunt me." &amp;mdash; Ruth Rendell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Here the setting is winter, and the almost Highsmithian subject concerns a woman who inveigles herself in the life of a famous, and rich, writer. Jansson's writing is, as always, understated yet acute and thrilling." &amp;mdash; &lt;em&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arlinda S.</member_name><member_id>4452084</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335826072000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Club Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>classicbooks</urlname><id>518343</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Classic Books: Book Club for Die-hard Readers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333987741000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tove Jansson: The True Deceiver</name><id>59833532</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335736800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/classicbooks/events/59833532/</event_url></item>