<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The word namaste is an expression of deep gratitude and recognition. It is a word that acknowledges the divine beauty within ourselves, then looking outward to see it in one another.&lt;br /&gt;Every year at Thanksgiving, many families offer gratitude among themselves. Sitting around a plump turkey, relatives give thanks for comfort, for joy, and for each other. &lt;br /&gt;Gratitude and yoga go hand-in-hand, and both are essential to well-being. In all other forms of exercise, gratitude takes the form of relief. Yoga teaches us to be grateful for the present moment, not only for the promise of future reward. It allows us to appreciate the full spectrum of life, from pleasure to pain and joy to sorrow. Through the practice of yoga, we learn that life is a chiaroscuro; the darker moments allow the lighter times to glow ever more brightly. Therefore, we become grateful for every moment of life.&lt;br /&gt;Join us for this special two-hour yoga class on Thanksgiving morning 9:00am-11:00am. We will practice asana (postures) to relax and renew the spirit, stretch and strengthen the body, open the heart, and stimulate digestion.&lt;br /&gt;This class is the perfect way to start the traditional day of feasting and family, using yoga to celebrate the gifts and blessings of this life! Yoga: A Practice of Thanksgiving is by donation, no one turned away for lack of funds. Cultivate a spirit of gratitude both on Thanksgiving day and the rest of the &lt;br /&gt;Visit the Alchemy Cafe next to the Co-Op after class to participate/ learn more about Juicefeasting-day of fasting. Juices will be available for purchase for those interested in Thanksgiving fasting . See www.juicefeasting.com for more info.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://bhavanajagat.files.wordpress.com/2009/07/1199986046-hr-297.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>zoraida</member_name><member_id>9306539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259417327000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256312705000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yoga: A Practice of Thanksgiving</name><id>11694154</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259244000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11694154/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/6/global_11365894.jpeg</photo_url></item>