<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Updated Sept. 11: The Kendall has the start time as 4, but it's one of only 2 screenings that day because of the Boston Film Festival.  Therefore it's possible that the show will be crowded, so I recommend that you get your tickets early, just in case of sell-out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope this isn't too &amp;quot;last minute&amp;quot; for you to attend -- it looks like a real fun film.  I tend to get tired of WWII films, but the satirical nature of this looks very intriguing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About I Served the King of England:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forty years after the international success of Closely Watched Trains, writer/director Jirí Menzel returns with an epic black comedy, adapted from a novel by the same author, Bohumil Hrabal. Jan (Ivan Barnev) is short in height but high in ambition. The social-climbing, opportunistic, irrepressible waiter/everyman dreams of becoming a millionaire. Always striving to please (and get ahead), he leaves his job at a pub for a luxury brothel, and then graduates to the most beautiful hotel in Prague. Along the way he enjoys lots of beautiful women and luscious food (often combined). In 1938 Hitler annexes Czechoslovakia; Jan falls madly in love with Líza (Julia Jentsch, Sophie Scholl), a German-speaking Czech who hero-worships Hitler. After Jan passes an Aryan test, they wed—but the war separates them. The story is told in flashback by a sadder and wiser Jan, just released from a stretch in a communist jail, reflecting on the turbulent times he has survived and on his luck (&amp;quot;always bad&amp;quot;). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;87% on the Rotten Tomatoes Tomatometer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Menzel tweaks the essential character of his homeland through the escapades of an Everyman waiter in the sexy, deadpan, 2008 foreign-language Oscar entry I Served the King of England. And what's news is how enduringly charming the Menzel touch remains, and how potent the existential rue that lingers after the ostensibly lighthearted parable has ended.&amp;quot; -- Lisa Schwarzbaum, Entertainment Weekly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[S]cenes of marathon gourmandizing offer some of the most pungently satirical observations of unfettered gluttony ever filmed... There is hardly a moment in this film in which you are not aware that its absurdist view of the human condition was shaped by traumatic 20th-century events. — Stephen Holden, The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you next week!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be at the front of the theater holding a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220838693000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>I Served the King of England</name><id>8711138</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221422400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8711138/</event_url></item>