<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>see map at end of announcement</address_2><address_1>182 Memorial Drive (Rear)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building 4, Room 370</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>624507</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TITLE: &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Discovering Fallen Angels, a Value Approach, by Charles Silk of C. Silk &amp;amp; Sons Financial Services&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DESCRIPTION:  We love the insights of veteran stockpickers such as Charlie Silk. An individual investor in the 1960s, he became a professional investor with a successful record in his chosen method - Fallen Angels. Peter Lynch once wrote about Charlie Silk &amp;quot;My favorite candidate for the world's greatest amateur investor is Charles Silk.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlie will talk about &amp;quot;Fallen Angels&amp;quot;, his strategy to discover stocks that have minimum downside risk with significant potential future profits.  The number of &amp;quot;Fallen Angels&amp;quot; rises in markets that have a down-side bias.  Hence, the equity market since July 2007 has provided a huge number of &amp;quot;Fallen Angels&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this talk Charlie will:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Describe his and his associates' extensive filtering process to determine whether candidate stocks should be rejected from further consideration or accepted for further research.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explain how they investigate the company to see if a decline was temporary and if the security exhibits potential for a near term turnaround.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go through the ten points he considers in determining whether the stock should be evaluated further.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explain the technical patterns he uses to determine an attractive entry price point. This helps provide Silk clients with confidence in their selections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide perspective on current market conditions through a look back at ten significant market retractions dating back to 1972. These periods had provided numerous &amp;quot;Fallen Angel&amp;quot; candidates. Of these ten pullbacks, three very large retractions were:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;li&gt;1972-1974 This period had sharp declines in equity values.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;1999-2001 The Dot com bubble imploded causing the NASDAQ Composite peak in March 2000 to bottom in October 2002 at 1,108. During this time the index lost 1800 listings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;June 2007 to present: The source of this decline is the credit crisis coupled with low interest rates.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the 1994 Worth Magazine article by Peter Lynch - &amp;quot;Charlie Silk's 150-Bagger&amp;quot;: &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/81154/Charlie%20Silk%27s%20150-Bagger%20by%20Peter%20Lynch.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bio: Charles Silk's interest in the stock market has thrived for 60 years, beginning in his teens. He studied accounting and finance at the University of Michigan, receiving a Bachelor and Masters Degree in Business Administration. After college he served as a Naval Officer in the Korean War, went to Arthur Andersen, IBM and in 1962 he opened a computer service bureau. His interest in the stock market continued and his fallen angel theory came together. In 1987 he became a full time investor, instilling the knowledge he gained to his children. He has had three guest appearances on CNBC. At nearly 70 years of age he passed the Series 7 exam and opened the doors along with his sons Marc and Stephen, to C. Silk &amp;amp; Sons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Securities offered through Delta Equity Services Corporation, Bolton, MA. Member FINRA, SIPC (978) 779-5361. Advisory services offered through Delta Global Asset Management, a registered investment advisor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;IBD Group Rate for Upcoming Level 2 Seminar!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a effort to help members get started on their own journey learning the IBD (TM) Method, we have secured a special offer from IBD for 33% off on the August 16 seminar in Boston! &lt;b&gt;To learn more, go to this link:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/81154/L2_WorkshopflyerBoston.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Market Talk led by Doug Roberts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doug has delivered his Market Talk ever since we moved to MIT. The banter in our group of bulls versus bears has become vigorous as the market alternately rallies and tumbles. Join this discussion as Doug gives his perspective on fundamentals, technicals and sentiment. Doug is one of the leaders of the group and is a full-time trader.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets starting at 5:30 PM. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The agenda:&lt;br /&gt;6:00 - 6:50 Pre-Meeting with Boston Tigers, led by Bob Podd &lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Doug&lt;br /&gt;        Market Talk led by Doug&lt;br /&gt;        Stockpicks led by Chris&lt;br /&gt;        Discovering Fallen Angels, a Value Approach, by Charles Silk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to DouglasWRoberts@gmail.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join in our virtual trading, go to this link for instructions and signup links:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your own decisions about investing your money. Investment ideas and recommendations made in our meetings and our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217632390000</updated><rating><average>3.91000008583</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>81</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214302431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Investor's Business Daily Wednesday Meeting</name><id>8203405</id><headcount>105</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217458800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/8203405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>