<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kancamagus Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03251</zip><lat>44.052308</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lincoln Woods Trail</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>942675</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.572339</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Franconia Falls is located at the end of one of the flattest long-distance strolls in the White Mountains.&lt;/b&gt; In just over 3 miles you will gain a mere 300 feet of altitude, with no ups and downs to speak of. For comparison, consider nearby Beaver Brook Falls, which gains 1,200 feet of altitude in only 1 mile, or the Falling Waters Trail, which gains 1,000 feet in just over 1.4 miles. This lack of elevation gain is the big reason why this waterfall is a favorite hike for families. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Who should come: Anyone that wants to get out and hike a low elevation trail in a beautiful setting. &lt;br /&gt;Perfect for recovering injuries, new hikers, and testing out your hiking gear. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why:  Smoother trails and a swimming hole! A modest elevation gain and plenty of miles to cover makes this an ideal location for you to participate at your own pace and to meetup with other members at a casual pace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Saturday overnight group will be joining in (pheew!) after their overnight camp out so we plan on a good time. &lt;br /&gt;Hike on this flat trail as long as you wish, just watch your time. Bring a picnic lunch, or test out that camp stove. No open fires.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Falls and swimming area is an easy walk up the old railroad grade on the Lincoln Woods Trail/Wilderness Trail to just beyond a bridge crossing Franconia Brook.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Type: cascades and slides&lt;br /&gt;Height: 30-foot total drop&lt;br /&gt;Source: Franconia Brook&lt;br /&gt;Trail Length: 3.2 miles one way&lt;br /&gt;Trail Difficulty: easy&lt;br /&gt;Altitude Gain: plus 300 feet&lt;br /&gt;Hiking Time: 90 minutes&lt;br /&gt;Alt. Names: n/a&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Very similar to Diana's Baths in the town of Conway, Franconia Falls lacks waterfalls of striking natural elegence or style. Both make up for this deficiency with their sunny slabs of rock, swimming pools that widely vary in size, depth, and current, and opportunities for roving around the falls for hours of refreshing pleasure. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best waterslide in the house is near the base of the falls, very close to the trail that parallels the brook. Roughly 20 feet long, but not continuous, this slide will propel you into a 5-foot-deep pool. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Franconica Falls  hike Distance 6.74 mi round trip&lt;br /&gt;Time 3 hr 52 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +681 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Woods Facilities: portable bathrooms and fee parking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trailhead:&lt;/b&gt; Lincoln Woods visitor information center, off NH Route 112 just E of bridge over East Branch of the Pemigewasset River, elevation about 1180 feet&lt;br /&gt;44.0638°N, 71.5884°W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;WMNF fee site&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 Exit 32 at Lincoln and go E on NH Route 112 (Kancamagus Highway) about 5.7 miles to sign and parking lot on L&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: We are limited to groups of 10 for this wilderness area hike. For us, 3 member rsvp's create a meetup group.  We will split our meetup into groups, stagger our times so we can abide by the WMNP rules.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Lets have a red bandana day! Meet groups at the trailhead and waterfall</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247922046000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245002684000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Franconia Falls: Hike and Swim</name><id>10649792</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247407200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10649792/</event_url></item>