<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>120 Highland Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02492</zip><lat>42.305237</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 453-4005</phone><name>Panera Bread</name><city>Needham</city><id>336450</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.218510</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;IBD Levels Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are forming an IBD Levels focused group that will keep people together who are currently working their way up the IBD Levels. This group will meet for the first time on July 2nd at Panera Bread in Needham, at 7:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Who:&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Only those seeking to move up the Levels, now, should attend.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You don't need to commit to going up to Level 4, but our overall goal will be to develop as many Level 4 candidates as possible. Mike Kinkead, Doug Roberts and Jeff Orrik will be there on July 2. Since this is 4 days after the Level 1 seminar on June 28 (see the ½ price flyer at: &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/81154/Boston%20IBD%20Meetup%20Special%20Offer%20-%20Level%201%2C%2028Jun08.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; ) then &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;come only if you have completed Level 1 at some point&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What:&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Although we will adapt to the group that shows up, our activities will be two-fold:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;     &lt;li&gt;We will review the material, the concepts, that underlie the IBD Methodology in order to develop the Level expertise for each person who comes.&lt;br /&gt;     &lt;li&gt;We will build, as a group, a system for identifying stocks at buy points. We will start with Mike Kinkead's beachhead and figure out what we can do to systemize it using the people at hand. We will share our leads and system with the larger IBD group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;When:&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; First meeting is Wednesday, 7:00-9:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Where:&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Panera Bread at 120 Highland Avenue in Needham 02494. It is very close to Route 128 / I 95. Here's a mapquest link: &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/120+Highland+Avenue+Needham+ma+02494/"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; When you arrive at Panera Bread, we have the private room. They expect us, individually, to buy food and drink. Yes, we can eat at this meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why:&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; We need, as a group, to develop steeples of expertise in various skill sets. Why not start with the method that IBD pioneered? Other expertises will come if we can get a solid start in this one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This first meeting will be our moment to figure out who we are as a group, review some Level 1 concepts, review the Levels program, plus poll everyone to find what skills and tools we have to accomplish our goals. We would like 12-20 at a minimum, but less will work. If we get materially more then we will figure out what to do at the first meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please, please, please. If you are coming please RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215230935000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213335407000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>IBD Levels Group - First Meeting</name><id>8135085</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215039600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/8135085/</event_url></item>