<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Cambridge Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.362583</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft's facility on Main St.</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9453872</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for an evening of free movies with Boston SciFi &amp;amp; Fantasy fans! In October, we'll be watching Halloween themed movies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Cabin in the Woods (95 min, R) &lt;br /&gt;

 Five friends go for a break at a remote cabin in the woods, where they get more than they bargained for. Together, they must discover the truth behind the cabin in the woods. &lt;br /&gt;

 Director: Drew Goddard &lt;br /&gt;

 Writers: Joss Whedon, Drew Goddard &lt;br /&gt;

 Stars:Kristen Connolly, Chris Hemsworth and Anna Hutchison&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tim Burton's The Nightmare Before Christmas (75 min, PG) &lt;br /&gt;

 Jack Skellington, king of Halloweentown, discovers Christmas Town, but doesn't quite understand the concept. &lt;br /&gt;

 Director: Henry Selick &lt;br /&gt;

 Writers: Tim Burton (story), Michael McDowell (adaptation) &lt;br /&gt;

 Stars:Danny Elfman, Chris Sarandon and Catherine O'Hara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a new meetup event for our group, so we're going to start small, and if there is interest in it, we can try to grow it. Jax Adele has graciously volunteered to let us use some conference space at Microsoft in Cambridge (right off the Kendall Red Line T Stop), and the room we have reserved has a maximum of 40 seats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logistics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You must RSVP to the meetup in order to attend this event. Microsoft will have a list of attendees and check them in to the event. Remember, there is a limit of 40 people for this event. If you are not on the list at Security, you will be turned away (sorry!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* If you are bringing a guest, be sure you indicate that when you RSVP and provide their name so we can check them in at Security! &lt;br /&gt;

 * The event is free! &lt;br /&gt;

 * Microsoft has some free sodas and fruit juices available, but you are welcome to bring your own drinks (non-alcoholic, please). &lt;br /&gt;

 * Jax is providing some air-popped popcorn for us to enjoy (and some butter/salt for those who like it), but that is the only food we will have on site. You are welcome to bring your own outside food, and there is a microwave available for our use. &lt;br /&gt;

 * Schedule: &lt;br /&gt;

 5:00 PM - Doors open &lt;br /&gt;

 5:30 PM - Cabin in the Woods &lt;br /&gt;

 7:15 PM - The Nightmare Before Christmas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must be out of the Microsoft offices by 10 PM!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* This event is happening in the brand new Microsoft office at 1 Cambridge Center (NOTE: This is not the N.E.R.D building). It is right next to the Kendall Red Line T Stop. You will need to enter through the door directly across the street from Cosi. Security should direct you to our event on the 4th floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;****** &lt;br /&gt;

 We hope to make this a regular monthly event, so please let us know what you'd like to see in the future! If there are interested people above and beyond the 40 seat limit we have currently, we might be able to use a bigger space at Microsoft, so please let us know in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351477476000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349902930000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October Movie Social Meetup</name><id>86415102</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>18000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350594000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/86415102/</event_url></item>