<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Innovators, &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We  wanted to give you advance notice of a special speaker for the June  Meeting - Warren Tuttle, President of the United Inventors Association,  will be speaking at our June 1, 2011 meeting! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Warren has worked  behind the scenes on some very successful kitchenware products, such as  the Smart Spin (8 million units sold) and the MISTO gourmet olive-oil  sprayer (4 million units sold). As a marketing expert, he consults for  large corporations, helping them become more innovative. He also speaks  at national events, such as the International Home &amp;amp; Housewares Show  - we are truly lucky to snag him for our meeting......please get the  word out to your friends and associates! Remember, the public is now  invited FREE to these open meetings. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We are also starting to  record audio from our open meetings - and have started a Podcast series,  which you can find on itunes at the following link: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/innovation-invention-speakers/id433329307" target="_blank"&gt;http://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/innovation-invention-speakers/id433329307&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;or, on the web at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://hearth.com/podcast/irn/podcast.xml" target="_blank"&gt;http://hearth.com/podcast/irn/podcast.xml&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In order to keep our members up to date with links, annoucements and other such news - we have started a facebook page at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;hhttp://www.facebook.com/pages/Holyoke-Massachusetts/Innovato&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;rs-Resource-Network/210705578957971&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/67kd75w" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/67kd75w&lt;/a&gt; (shortened version) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please  "like" us on facebook - we need to get a certain amount of people who  check in to reap the benefits. You can also add your own comments and  links, so we can have a continual exchange of links and upcoming events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advance Notice of Next Public Meeting - Special Speaker, etc. &lt;br /&gt; Please friend us on Facebook to stay up to date on links, happenings, etc. &lt;br /&gt; Podcasts of Public Meetings now available&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Blanchard</member_name><member_id>9728219</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307210638000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305070459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June Public Meeting with a special presentation from Warren Tuttle, UIA</name><id>17915011</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306967400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/17915011/</event_url></item>