<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org/exhibits_shows/imax&amp;amp;d=255"&gt;http://www.mos.org/exhibits_shows/imax&amp;amp;d=255&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine swimming alongside some of the most graceful and extraordinary creatures on Earth &amp;mdash; wild dolphins. Dive in with two scientists studying these elusive animals in the crystalline waters of the Bahamas and wind-swept seas of Patagonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also included, Back for a Limited Time: Celebrate the 25th anniversary of the Mugar Omni Theater with a revival of New England Time Capsule, the beloved pre-show film produced for the theater's 1987 opening. Take a trip back in time to 1980s Boston &amp;mdash; fly over the skyline, stare down a Roger Clemens curveball, and take a pulse-pounding ride down Storrow Drive. Shown exclusively at the Museum of Science, this short travelogue about history and life in New England is narrated by Leonard Nimoy and features a soundtrack composed by John Williams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Per the Museum:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tickets must be picked up in person at the Box Office on a first come first serve basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tickets cannot be ordered online, nor can they be used for any other day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Once the Omni theater is full, there will be no more admittance during that time slot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Per me:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Shows have been selling out by mid afternoon. I'm going to go early and get 20 tickets. If anyone else can go in the morning and pick up 20, please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tickets can be picked up at the Box Office starting at 9:00 am that day&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- We can meet in the front lobby between 6:15 and 6:30 near the Membership Booth after you have your tickets&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>8776856</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332650525000</updated><rating><average>4.42000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>93</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330876242000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Dolphins" IMAX Film Free Showing at the Omni Theater (show starts at 7:00)</name><id>54906262</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332540900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/54906262/</event_url></item>