<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1515 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377920</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Law School, Ames Courtroom, Austin Hall</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669109</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120070</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The FCC is holding a public hearing in Boston about the future of the Internet. Make your voice heard: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attend the Hearing in Boston &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T and Verzion have given us a glimpse of a world without Net Neutrality, and it's a chilling sight. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In recent months, these cable and phone companies have repeatedly been caught blocking, filtering and spying on your Internet activities. If we let them get away with this, these powerful companies will continue to roll back our freedoms whenever we go online. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now the Federal Communications Commission is coming to Boston to investigate. Will you attend this important event? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT: A Public Hearing on the Future of the Internet&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Monday, Feb 25, 2008 &lt;br /&gt;TIME: 11:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Harvard Law School, Ames Courtroom, Austin Hall&lt;br /&gt;1515 Massachusetts Avenue, Cambridge, MA 02138&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;a href="http://www.law.harvard.edu/about/contact/directions.php/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.law.harvar...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information: www.savetheinternet.com/=boston &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The question before us is simple: Will we have a closed Internet controlled by a small handful of giant corporations, or an open Internet controlled by the people who use it? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With so much at stake, it's encouraging that the FCC's first move is to come to Boston for public feedback about the importance of a free-flowing Internet. Let's hope this important hearing in Massachusetts is just the beginning of a national conversation that spreads to every town and city across the country.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204128539000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203639595000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Public Hearing on the Future of the Internet</name><id>7381676</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203955200000</time><rsvp_limit>999</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7381676/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>