<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;SATURDAY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; appears to be the preferred choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;ALSO, NEW DETAILS FOR YOU:&lt;/b&gt;  A&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;fter Dim Sum/Dian Xin, or Lunch, we have options for any of you with a little more free time - I have some friends that may be planning to go to the &amp;quot;Jin Men Chao Shi&amp;quot; in Quincy, shopping, snacking and I've been told there is some interest for karaoke there as well Saturday afternoon.  This is very much &amp;quot;on the fly&amp;quot; and spontaneous, but whatever your plans or your feelings on Saturday, we can find convenient ways to get around if desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO GET THERE&lt;/b&gt; - PLEASE NOTE THESE AS TAKING THE WRONG TRAIN WILL ADD 30/45 MINUTES TO YOUR TRIP ON A WEEKEND:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Take the &amp;quot;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Braintree Line&lt;/span&gt;&amp;quot; Red Line T (Ashmont Line does &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; go to North Quincy) to North Quincy Station - exit the cars and immediately walk &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;right&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  - go up the stairs, immediately go &lt;b&gt;l&lt;u&gt;eft&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - exit the station - I shall be there to await from 11:00 a.m. until we have most or all of you there - I shall send my phone# to &amp;quot;YES&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;MAYBE&amp;quot; respondents some time on Friday - use this to call me if you think you will be more than 15 minutes late*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;CURRENT WEATHER FORECASTS:[/&lt;/span&gt;b]  Saturday and Sunday both declare to be 70/75 degrees and partly sunny.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;******************&lt;br /&gt;NORTH QUINCY, MASSACHUSETTS&lt;br /&gt;I am blessed to live in a community that now boasts about 8,000 citizens that arrived from several prominent provinces and cities in China, all speaking dialects which include plenty of Mandarin.   This is of a total population for the City of Quincy that is somewhere around 80,000.  If you are unfamiliar with North Quincy, you will discover quite quickly, especially on a Saturday or Sunday morning, that the red line sings with dialects and you could quite fall asleep to the music and still know when to get off the train from the sudden rush of bodies upon arrival at North Quincy's station, conveniently situated towards finding some good eats.  If you think I am kidding, I can tell you- my job sometimes leaves me sleepy and I've more than once sensed the musical sounds of Cantonese, Taisonese, Mandarin, or some other &amp;quot;ben di hua&amp;quot; along with movement to know it is time for me to snap out of my sleepiness - I've arrived home!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Cambridge's Central Square red line station, one would need perhaps 20 minutes before arriving in North Quincy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would be honored and gratified to share this community with any of you that would find the time and intention to enjoy a nice lunch or Dim Sum/Dian Xin at one of the restaurants that can be found within earshot of the MBTA's red line station at North Quincy.  There would plenty of opportunity to practice and engage in Mandarin, and I'm confident you'll find the authenticity of the cooking at any of the restaurants worthy of merit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the meal, the day is yours - if you would do the me the honor, I would be further gratified to lead you to a few folks that operate businesses nearby (most are present on Saturdays, some on Sundays), or even venture a bit down the road to  Wollaston where there are further restaurants and bakeries, before you head back home.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SO:&lt;/b&gt;  I'll pay attention to responses, see what day/time people prefer, and also what kind of meal is preferred - I'm quite receptive to either Dim Sum or Lunch as I have had experience with both menus, though I of course can not vouch for how these rate compared with your hometown.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you so much for your consideration of this Meetup.  I will check the board between now and Friday and if I see sufficient response, I shall email my phone# to &amp;quot;maybes&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to ensure you have means of communicating with me after Friday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"Braintree Line", Red Line, to North Quincy Station  - See Below...</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245432631000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston Mandarin Meetup Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>chinese-35</urlname><id>33097</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Mandarin Chinese Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244644866000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NORTH QUINCY - Dim Sum or Lunch, then.....</name><id>10620958</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244905200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chinese-35/events/10620958/</event_url></item>