<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will continue with Plato's Meno. This text is available on the internet:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://classics.mit.edu/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://classics.mit.e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://classics.mit.edu/Plato/meno.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://classics.mit.e...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since it is estimated about 20 pages in printed form, we also would like to cover some part of Locke's work at our next meeting. An Essay On Human Understanding is made up of 4 books, the first is about 50 pages so that would be appropriate in addition to Meno.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we want to cover the entire essay then we will spend 5 to 6 meetings on Locke. In order not to loose sight of our plan here are the works that we have planned, talked about for the near future: Leibniz: New Essays on Human Understanding (a commentary on Locke), Hume: An Enquiry Concerning Human Understanding, enlightenment (de La Mettrie's name came up), philosophical aspects of colonial-revolutionary America (maybe the Federalist Papers)......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last time Rendang was closed (looked like being under renovation) so for next time we will meet in the Bombay Club and probably will discuss our options to have at least two good places where we can meet anytime.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for us(philosophy meetup group) from the staff.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206492696000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200174433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plato: Meno (In anticipation of Locke's An Essay On Human Understanding)</name><id>7098973</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201219200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/7098973/</event_url></item>