<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 College Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.397586</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Somerville Community Baptist Church</name><city>Somerville</city><id>893421</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121642</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>After the grand ol' Ras na hEireann 5K, come eat pancakes!!!!!  ALL YOU CAN EAT!  This marvelous event is open to the public, from 11-2pm, with a special invitation to all the 5K runners who will be in Davis Square that morning...yes, that means YOU!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND...don't be surprised to be served up some green cakes in honor of well, Ireland;)  Yum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fellow TMIRCE runner, Dave Keeney, and I are hosting this Pancake Brunch in support of my upcoming &lt;a href="http://www.paveyourlane.com" target="_blank"&gt;Run Across America &lt;/a&gt;(see info below) and the charity &lt;a href="http://www.girlsontherun.org" target="_blank"&gt;Girls on the Run&lt;/a&gt;, the beneficiary of my run.  It is a fundraiser, and for a suggested donation of $10 at the door, you get to eat tons of hot cakes.  What could be better, seriously?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This fundraiser invites the Boston-area community to unite around (what I hope to be) a revolutionary event benefitting a worthy cause, while enjoying a hot brunch and the warm company of friends and neighbors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spread the word!  Invite family, friends, running buddies, facebook peeps, the people who will cheer for you at the race...  yeah, dawg.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, VOLUNTEERS NEEDED!  Do you like to mix batter?  Can you flip cakes like no other?  Do you want to greet people?  Do you like to handle cash?  Do you like holding up signs that say, &amp;quot;Pancake Bruch, this way,&amp;quot; and cheering?  Do you have a plug-in pancake griddle?  Want to make an ingredient donation?  Ha ha, contact me at Katie.Visco@gmail.com!  Could use your help on the Cakes Squad:)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;Toodles,&lt;br /&gt;Katie and Dave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       INFO ABOUT MY RUN ACROSS AMERICA:&lt;br /&gt;On Sunday, March 29th, I will depart on a historic 3,200 mile run from Boston to San Diego. As the youngest female ever to start a solo run across America, I am running to inspire and empower people to follow their passions, and give back to the world by doing so. Along the way, I will stop to speak at schools and with groups about the importance of living a passion-driven life and utilizing a passion to do good in the world.  Major locations along the route include Boston, Providence, New Haven, New York City, Allentown, Cleveland, Toledo, Gary, Chicago, Iowa City, Kansas City, Topeka, Albuquerque, Flagstaff, Phoenix and San Diego.  For more information and to get involved please visit &lt;a href="http://www.paveyourlane.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.paveyourlane.com&lt;/a&gt;.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      &lt;a href="http://www.girlsontherun.org" target="_blank"&gt;Girls on the Run&lt;/a&gt;® is a not-for-profit prevention program that encourages preteen girls to develop self-respect and healthy lifestyles through running. Their curricula address all aspects of girls' development - their physical, emotional, mental, social and spiritual well-being.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The church is just steps up College Ave. from the heart of Davis Square.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237585166000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236114208000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HUGE Pancake Brunch (after the Ras na hEireann  5K) in Davis Square!</name><id>9872405</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237129200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/9872405/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/0/global_7541744.jpeg</photo_url></item>