<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Hancock St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02171</zip><lat>42.278568</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 328 5473</phone><name>Panera Bread </name><city>Quincy </city><id>820990</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.030876</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
  &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Madonnas of Echo Park by Brando Skyhorse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/6/6/7/event_48069831.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skyhorse maps in his vivid debut the spirit of L.A.'s Echo Park, where Mexican-Americans define themselves either in alignment with or in opposition to their barrio. Each story-like chapter tells the tale of a character who has grown up in, moved to, or fled Echo Park, such as an itinerant construction worker hired to dispose of a murder weapon, a woman who converses with the Virgin Mary, and a hustler who swears he's going to stay out of prison this time. These lives coalesce around a random shooting that claims the life of a young girl. Family epics also emerge, notably the story of Aurora Esperanza, whose absent father narrates the opening story and whose mother was at the center of a tragedy. Aurora herself closes out the book, drawing together threads of homecoming that weave throughout the novel. Though a few of the narrators' voices aren't distinct enough, Skyhorse excels at building a vibrant community and presenting several perspectives on what it means to be Mexican in America, from those who wonder how can you lose something that never belonged to you? to those who miraculously find it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Let's meet in front of The Clam Box, and we'll find a more picturesque spot on the beach from there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;If it rains, our backup location is Panera in Quincy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;South Shore meetups will alternate between Sunday afternoons
 &lt;br /&gt;and Wednesday/Thursday evenings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Please read the book if you plan to come.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Be &amp;nbsp;a participant, not a spectator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;The next few books will be chosen by:
 &lt;br /&gt;Tiff - September
 &lt;br /&gt;Kuljit - October&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Shirley</member_name><member_id>8579308</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317786626000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310095944000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Shore: Madonnas of Echo Park</name><id>24986681</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316041200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/24986681/</event_url></item>