<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Books for October are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blink: The Power of Thinking Without Thinking - By Malcolm Gladwell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon.com Review&lt;br /&gt;Blink is about the first two seconds of looking--the decisive glance that knows in an instant. Gladwell, the best-selling author of The Tipping Point, campaigns for snap judgments and mind reading with a gift for translating research into splendid storytelling. Building his case with scenes from a marriage, heart attack triage, speed dating, choking on the golf course, selling cars, and military maneuvers, he persuades readers to think small and focus on the meaning of &amp;quot;thin slices&amp;quot; of behavior. The key is to rely on our &amp;quot;adaptive unconscious&amp;quot;--a 24/7 mental valet--that provides us with instant and sophisticated information to warn of danger, read a stranger, or react to a new idea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gladwell includes caveats about leaping to conclusions: marketers can manipulate our first impressions, high arousal moments make us &amp;quot;mind blind,&amp;quot; focusing on the wrong cue leaves us vulnerable to &amp;quot;the Warren Harding Effect&amp;quot; (i.e., voting for a handsome but hapless president). In a provocative chapter that exposes the &amp;quot;dark side of blink,&amp;quot; he illuminates the failure of rapid cognition in the tragic stakeout and murder of Amadou Diallo in the Bronx. He underlines studies about autism, facial reading and cardio uptick to urge training that enhances high-stakes decision-making. In this brilliant, cage-rattling book, one can only wish for a thicker slice of Gladwell's ideas about what Blink Camp might look like. --Barbara Mackoff &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Twilight - by Stephenie Meyer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon.com Review&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Softly he brushed my cheek, then held my face between his marble hands. 'Be very still,' he whispered, as if I wasn't already frozen. Slowly, never moving his eyes from mine, he leaned toward me. Then abruptly, but very gently, he rested his cold cheek against the hollow at the base of my throat.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Shakespeare knew, love burns high when thwarted by obstacles. In Twilight, an exquisite fantasy by Stephenie Meyer, readers discover a pair of lovers who are supremely star-crossed. Bella adores beautiful Edward, and he returns her love. But Edward is having a hard time controlling the blood lust she arouses in him, because--he's a vampire. At any moment, the intensity of their passion could drive him to kill her, and he agonizes over the danger. But, Bella would rather be dead than part from Edward, so she risks her life to stay near him, and the novel burns with the erotic tension of their dangerous and necessarily chaste relationship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meyer has achieved quite a feat by making this scenario completely human and believable. She begins with a familiar YA premise (the new kid in school), and lulls us into thinking this will be just another realistic young adult novel. Bella has come to the small town of Forks on the gloomy Olympic Peninsula to be with her father. At school, she wonders about a group of five remarkably beautiful teens, who sit together in the cafeteria but never eat. As she grows to know, and then love, Edward, she learns their secret. They are all rescued vampires, part of a family headed by saintly Carlisle, who has inspired them to renounce human prey. For Edward's sake they welcome Bella, but when a roving group of tracker vampires fixates on her, the family is drawn into a desperate pursuit to protect the fragile human in their midst. The precision and delicacy of Meyer's writing lifts this wonderful novel beyond the limitations of the horror genre to a place among the best of YA fiction. (Ages 12 and up) --Patty Campbell&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258389736000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254701010000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>October's Book Discussion.</name><id>11546842</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256767200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/11546842/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/8/e/global_11054958.jpeg</photo_url></item>