<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1080 Chapel Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.308068</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-432-2800</phone><name>Yale Center ForThe British Arts</name><city>New Haven</city><id>869091</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.930590</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/d/e/event_73954782.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Yale Center for British Arts has two shows running that involve Johan Zoffany (1733-1810), one of his paintings in England of people from all sectors of society, the other of the British colonization of India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at 12:30 and take the 1:00 tour:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://calendar.yale.edu:80/cal/ycba/week/20111203/All/CAL-2c9cb3cd-31b9b3e1-0131-cdd68290-00006986bedework@yale.edu/"&gt;"Johan Zoffany RA: Society Observed"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;We can look at the other exhibit,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://britishart.yale.edu/exhibitions/adapting-eye-archive-british-india-1770-1830"&gt;Adapting the Eye: An Archive of the British in India, 1770&amp;ndash;1830&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;after the tour. If people are interested, we can meet at an area coffee shop to hang out and talk afterward. The museum is also running the film Taj Mahal from 1963 at 2 PM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is some more information on the Zoffany exhibit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of all the major artists working in eighteenth-century England, none explored more inventively the complexities of Georgian society and British imperial rule than Johan Zoffany (1733&amp;ndash;1810). Born near Frankfurt, Zoffany trained as an artist in Germany and Italy. In 1760 he moved to London, where he adapted brilliantly to the indigenous art culture and patterns of patronage, creating virtuoso portraits and subject pictures that proved to be highly desirable to a wide range of patrons. Zoffany&amp;rsquo;s work provides an invaluable and distinctive appraisal of key British institutions and edifices: the art academy, the Court, the theatre, the families of the aristocracy and bourgeoisie, and the burgeoning empire. Despite achieving considerable success in England, Zoffany remained in many ways an outsider, scrutinizing British society and its customs and mores. Restless and drawn to a peripatetic existence, he traveled for extended periods in his native Germany, Austria, Italy, and India. After his death there was no move to situate Zoffany as one of the key figures in the burgeoning British school of art; this exhibition aims to correct that oversight and will demonstrate his central importance to the artistic culture of eighteenth-century Britain and Europe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Johan Zoffany RA: Society Observed&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;features some seventy oil paintings and a selection of drawings and prints, many of which have been rarely or never exhibited, from public and private collections around the world, including Britain, France, Germany, Italy, Australia, India, and the United States. Incorporating revelatory new research carried out over the past decade, the exhibition&amp;mdash;the first devoted to Zoffany ever to be held in the United States and the first in Britain since 1977&amp;mdash;constitutes a timely and radical reevaluation of the extraordinary life and career of this brilliant and enigmatic artist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet inside near the information booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Merrill</member_name><member_id>7492092</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323031368000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321810246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Yale Center For British Art</name><id>41826782</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322933400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/41826782/</event_url></item>