<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the November meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, a reminder: we start the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we will jump into the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event: Understanding your decision criteria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why do you make the decisions you do?  From choosing a restaurant to choosing a spouse, we are making large and small decisions every day.  But how do we make them?  What do we consider when we make these decisions?  We call these considerations “decision criteria”.  For most of us, these criteria are unconscious.  However, wouldn’t it be useful if we were conscious of the criteria we were applying to decisions, and be able to change them if needed?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this month’s meetup, we will use a simple and effective process tool to help you elicit your decision criteria.  This is a tool you will also be able to use with others to help them understand &lt;i&gt;their&lt;/i&gt; decision criteria.  We will also look at the criteria for making decisions in different aspects of our lives (sometimes it varies, sometimes it doesn’t).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to work on specific issues you are having that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;We meet on the first floor of Sturtevant Hall, 197 Herrick Road, which is near the library on the central quad of Andover Newton. &lt;br /&gt;Andover Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.  I'll probably be the one talking.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1229643596000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224200124000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP November Meetup - What are your Decision Criteria?</name><id>8976014</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227223800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/8976014/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/7/a/global_6332938.jpeg</photo_url></item>