<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*LAST SECOND CHANGE TO MEETING SPOT*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Sorry about the late notice, but I got in touch with Excelsior and they are NOT open to the public this Saturday night.  We will instead meet at Sweetwater Cafe, which is a bar located in The Alley, at 5 Boylston Place, right next to The Estate.  The plan remains the same, only the meeting location has changed - meet at Sweetwater around 8pm (front of the bar), and move go to Estate around 9:45pm.**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Just received an email that says LADIES get in FREE before 10pm at The Estate!** Meet up at Sweetwater and don't be late!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The holiday season is quickly approaching, so this will be one of our last events of the year.  It has been a while since we have had a night life event, and it would be great to see new and current members come out to party this Saturday night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will start at Sweetwater Cafe, a laid back bar located in the Alley.  This is a great place to meet members in a low key and intimate setting, before heading out to one of the near-by clubs in the area.  This is a great event to meet new people and to get your groove on!  All members welcome, and feel free to bring a friend or two!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 8pm in the front bar area at Sweetwater Cafe.  If you don't find us in the front, we will definitely be on the first floor, so please look for me to find the group.  We will head over to one of the local clubs (to be determined - but most likely the Estate) around 9:30 or 10pm to beat the lines.  Please meet us at Sweetwater Cafe, and get there early as to have time to meet folks and beat the lines later.  Cover:  None for Sweetwater, but there will be a cover for the club, which I expect to be $20.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please dress appropriately as these are upscale venues.  If traveling by T, Boylston the closest T stop on the green line.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!  Charlie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>8</waitlist_count><updated>1232154945000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228200390000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW LOCATION! Downtown Boston Nightlife Mixer and Dancing This Saturday, Dec 6!</name><id>9263517</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228611600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/9263517/</event_url></item>