<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Somerset Pkwy</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03063</zip><lat>42.786247</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603 886-1200</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Nashua</name><city>Nashua</city><id>671445</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.509540</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Mark Basile will make a presentation to the &lt;a href="http://AltExpo.org" target="_blank"&gt;Alternatives Exposition&lt;/a&gt; that details his independent scientific examination of the World Trade Center dust. Mark's work confirms work done independently by several other scientists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In Mark's slide show, you'll see the actual electron microscope images, the spectrometer traces, the videos of the ignition of particles of the unexploded nano-thermite that were found in the World Trade Center dust. If you are a skeptic, you should examine the scientific evidence, question the scientist who has done the research, see if you can come up with any other explanations for what you see on these slides...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark's talk will be at the Alternatives Expo (AltExpo) who will hold forth in a suite on the 2nd Floor (Rm. 204) of the Crowne Plaza Hotel in Nashua - 2 Somerset Parkway. The &lt;a href="http://freestateproject.org/libertyforum" target="_blank"&gt;New Hampshire Liberty Forum&lt;/a&gt; is being held on the first floor and might be of interest to you as well. The Liberty Forum is put on by the &lt;a href="http://freestateproject.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Free State Project&lt;/a&gt;, who are encouraging people from around the country to move to New Hampshire to help make it a freer place to be.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don't have to register for the Liberty Forum to attend the AltExpo events, and there is no charge for the talk, but a reasonable donation of $5 would be appreciated to help diffray costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Room 204 - AltExpo suite</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269205511000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268844714000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dust PROVES it! 9/11 Was an Inside Job!</name><id>12901603</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269032400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/12901603/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/d/global_4705149.jpeg</photo_url></item>