<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This park has lots of lakefront campsites! NH campground reservations for the entire season begin Wed Feb 6th at 9am. Book now and get one of the better sites! &lt;br /&gt;I am going for a site on Horse Island, check out the campground map at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/library/pdf/campgrounds/PawtuckawayMap06.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last year I rented a canoe for the weekend and launched right from my campsite, it was great! I am going to take Friday off and make it a 4 day weekend - but join us however long you can. We will go canoeing/kayayaking and will improvise on some hikes.  Bring your own food and be prepared to cook and feed yourself. We can see about sharing when we are up there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, please indicate in your rsvp comment if you have made a reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Park description:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Less than 40 minutes to the coastal beaches to the east and to Manchester to the west, Pawtuckaway State Park Campground is well located for easy access to a variety of attractions and activities. All sites are wooded and many provide views of the lake. Each of the campsites has an open fireplace, picnic table, flat area for a tent, and a parking space. Although there are no hook-ups, recreational vehicles are welcome in sites where they fit. Running water, flush toilet facilities, a camp store, boat launch, and canoe and paddle boat rentals are available. Coin-operated showers are accessible 24 hours a day. Please remember that pets are not permitted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pawtuckaway State Park offers a variety of landscapes, with something to do and see for everyone. There are many opportunities for hiking, with trails leading to many special points of interest, including a mountaintop fire tower; an extensive marsh where beavers, deer, and great blue herons may be seen, and a geologically unique field where large boulders called glacial erratics were deposited when glacial ice melted near the end of the Ice Age. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The campground sites line the shore of beautiful Pawtuckaway Lake. The park includes a large family beach on the lake with a bathhouse, a group picnic area, a playground, park store, and a group shelter with a ball field available by reservation only. Other activities in the park include biking, fishing, snowmobiling, and cross-country skiing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pawtuckaway State Park&lt;br /&gt;128 Mountain Road&lt;br /&gt;Nottingham, NH 03290&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reservations:&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The opening day for the New Hampshire State Parks camping season is right around the corner!  We have been working with ReserveAmerica to get everything up and running for February 6th, when the call center will open and online reservations will be accepted.  Both methods of making a reservation will be available beginning at 9:00 am.  From there, online reservations can be made 24 hours a day, and the Call Center hours are as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 6 through April 14:&lt;br /&gt; Weekdays:  9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m. EST&lt;br /&gt; Weekends:  10:00 a.m. - 3:00 p.m. EST&lt;br /&gt;April 15 through Labor Day:&lt;br /&gt; Weekdays:  8:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m EST&lt;br /&gt; Weekends:  9:00 a.m. - 3:00 p.m. EST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beginning on February 6, 2008 at 9:00 am, the dedicated toll-free number to call to make a reservation through the ReserveAmerica Call Center is 1-877-nhparks (1-877-647-2757).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The complete list of new policies, as well as 2008 campground rates, will be posted on the ReserveAmerica site.  A link to that information will be posted here before the reservation season begins on February 6. New Hampshire State Parks will be listed on the ReserveAmerica website beginning on February 6th. &lt;br /&gt;From I-93:&lt;br /&gt;Take Route 101 east to Exit 5 and follow signs to Pawtuckaway State Park. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/state-parks/alphabetical-order/pawtuckaway-state-park/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nhstatepar...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220360738000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202012929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camping Weekend</name><id>7251969</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219960800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7251969/</event_url></item>