<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>CONSCIOUS MOVIES AND MEANINGFUL CONVERSATION - Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;All are Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;@ The Center of Light - 7PM FREE&lt;br /&gt;97 Perkins Street in Jamaica Plain &lt;br /&gt;call 617-852-2822 for information or to register&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;November 3rd, 7PM: THE SECRET&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Fast forward to the 21st Century and the innovation of cinematography, computer graphics and incredible writers deliver a multi-media tour de force for those looking to break free. For the first time in history, The Secret will be revealed that utterly transformed the lives of every person who ever knew it... Plato, Newton, Carnegie, Beethoven, Shakespeare, Einstein. &lt;br /&gt;Some of today's greatest teachers will be presented in The Secret and will impart this special wisdom that has been known by so few. They include some of the world's leaders in the fields of business, economics, medicine, psychology, history, theology and science. Each of these teachers is living proof of The Secret?each of them a walking marvel of achievement and success. &lt;br /&gt;The Secret also reveals amazing real life stories and testimonials of regular people who have changed their lives in profound ways. By applying The Secret they present instances of eradicating disease, acquiring massive wealth, overcoming obstacles and achieving what many would regard as impossible. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*This ground-breaking, feature length movie presentation reveals how to apply this powerful knowledge to your life in every area from health to wealth, to success and relationships. &lt;br /&gt;This is The Secret to everything - the secret to unlimited joy, health, money, relationships, love, youth: everything you have ever wanted. Presented in wide screen, high quality, video with stereo sound sit back and enjoy the first of many viewings over the coming weeks. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540694000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Consciousness movie members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>consciousness-65</urlname><id>355065</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Conscious Movie Meetup!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1162602336000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Meetup! December Meetup</name><id>5242760</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1165017600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/consciousness-65/events/5242760/</event_url></item>