<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Opposite Sears entrance at Galleria Ma</address_2><address_1>59 First Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.368895</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>VFW</name><city>East Cambridge</city><id>1276287</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.077357</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Live Music, Singles Networking, Cheap Drinks, Pool table.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Party with Free Live Music in East Cambridge near the Galleria Mall.  The venue has very cheap drinks, a relaxed atmosphere, pool table, and free live music with great musicians and an open mike.  Here is the ad - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attention Party goers,  Musicians, Singles &amp;amp; Singers!!  Come join the party at the Wed Night Open mike! Everyone Welcome. No cover charge - Play pool or music solo or with backing band. All instruments and styles welcome.  Originals, covers, blues, jazz, classic rock, R&amp;amp;B, Motown, folk, etc.   Back up band with drums, bass, guitar, and Songlist for singers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity to further your music experience and career, jam with other musicians, play solo, play originals, and network.  The goal is to have everyone play as much as possible.  &lt;u&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please come to check this out, have a drink and support this for your Music Guild even if you don't play tonight.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Crystal Bar VFW across from the Sears Entrance of the Galleria Mall near Lechmere. 59 1st St., Cambridge. Weekly open mike Wednesday night - starts at 7PM. Bring your friends for the party, network, play pool, and meet, interesting people &amp;amp; singles. Inexpensive drinks. (bottle beer $2.75 import $3.75 wine $3!!!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to rehearse the songs with the group RSVP for and come to the &lt;b&gt;jam/rehearsal meetup the Sunday prior to the Open MIke&lt;/b&gt;.  If you can bring song sheets for your songs on one page that will facilitate playing.  If you are playing at semi-professional level and are playing solo or don't need to rehearse, just come to the open mike.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to be play with acconpanying bass /lead/harmony try to come early at 7PM and bring about 4 copies of 2 or 3 songs you want to play on 1 sheet per song if possible, so we can all play it.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm Bill, 6'4"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>9500592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279218717000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Musicians &amp; Songwriters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild</urlname><id>1420875</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>The NEW England Singer Songwriter Musician Guild</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278602950000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Music Open Mike, Singles Networking, Cheap Drinks, Pool table.</name><id>jwnxnynkbsb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279148400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-NEW-England-Singer-Songwriter-Musician-Guild/events/14040242/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/a/global_11501162.jpeg</photo_url></item>