<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Boylston Street at 180 Lamartine Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.317017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Southwest Corridor Park</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>317277</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.104340</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover group expenses.</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Recess for Justice is going down at the Stony Brook court right off Lamartine Street in JP. (Exit Stony Brook T station on the Orange line, walk directly across the street to the park - we'll be on the field and in the courts right in front of you.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can't wait for sunny days of summer! Like this:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://lh4.google.com/send2robbie/Ru4Eo_3q5JI/AAAAAAAAACQ/3BobgVu34fY/Birthday07%20003.jpg?imgmax=512" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your favorite outdoor game or check out the assortment of fun we'll have on hand: Frisbees, kickball &amp;amp; chalk (for 4-square!), basketball, softball (bring a glove) and whatever other randomness we can think of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it's hot we can run through the fountain sprinkler to cool off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around 3pm we'll start to figure out what to do next.  We'll likely go to Ula Cafe for coffee, smoothies, snacks and board games (bring 'em!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the photos from previous Recess for Justice events in &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/photos/382694/"&gt;08&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/?photoAlbumId=226090&amp;amp;photoId=2233731"&gt;09&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/a/3/event_2233731.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns while perfecting your Frisbee forehand, you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want to connect outside of SoJust events?&lt;/b&gt; Members can view and post events, job &amp;amp; volunteer announcements, roommate searches, etc. on the website - just click '&lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/"&gt;Messages&lt;/a&gt;'.  The &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/calendar"&gt;SoJust Calendar&lt;/a&gt; is packed with social justice-related events held throughout Greater Boston.  Help us keep it filled - tell us about events you hear about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From our FAQs:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;It's not very easy for me to meet new people and I'm not really one for small talk.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hear you. That's why at SoJust events, in addition to traditional name tags, we have &amp;quot;Ask Me About&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Looking For&amp;quot; tags. That way you can slap whatever you're into lately up on your shirt and wait for fellow SoJusters to approach you. These seem to do the trick of moving past the basic &amp;quot;what do you do for work? where do you live?&amp;quot; questions to conversations that lead to more substantial connections.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What actually happens at events?&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll always be greeted by friendly folks who can help get you socializing, introduce you to people, and chat with you about questions or wishes. It's likely a few people will be there promoting their campaigns and issues (&lt;i&gt;yes, SoJust welcomes that sort of behavior&lt;/i&gt;). At our bigger events, there's always a literature table to toss down flyers, postcards, and other paraphenalia about events around town. Most importantly, we can pretty much guarantee there will be someone there you've never met before. As one of our members said, &amp;quot;You are bringing together people who might never get together otherwise - if that ain't a step towards justice I don't know what is.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt;  and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;Event Photos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250285688000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245898063000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Recess for Justice</name><id>10730883</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248022800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/10730883/</event_url></item>