<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Chale Ipanema has been under new management since early 2007. The atmosphere is clean and simple. Two rooms adjoin each other with a bar in back.The restaurant serves Colombian, Peruvian, Brazilian and Portugese food. Portions are large, the food is fresh and well plated and there’s an extensive selection of meat, seafood and poultry dishes. It has an “upscale menu”, the food is served with passion, and the prices are very affordable. We started with an appetizer of Colombian spinach and cheese empanadas for $1 each. To be truthful, they were so good that at this point I thought I’d come back for four of these and a Sangria and I’d walk out a happy woman. The empanadas are filled with your choice of vegetables, beef, chicken or spinach and cheese. They were hot and gooey with a crispy fried pastry. Other interesting appetizers are the Papa a La Huancaina ( potatoes in a cream sauce with egg, olive and red pepper) for $8.00, Ceviche De Pescado (served with fish in lemon juice, sweet potatoes, yucca and corn on the cob) for $8.00, Ceviche Mixto (fish, octopus, muscles, calamari, shrimp cooked in lemon juice with cilantro) for $11.00 and Camarones Apanados Con Coco (Coconut shrimp served with a passion fruit mayonnaise) for $11.00.Some interesting salads included:&lt;br /&gt;Ensalada De Espinaca Tropical - fresh Spinach Salad served with cheese, almonds, apples and mango with a dressing of mango, strawberries and vinegar for $7.00,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Salada De Palmito Arugula - hearts of palm and arugala in honey and balsamic dressing for $8.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now comes the main course. Expect to spend a lot of time trying to decide on what you want from all the yummy offerings. Just to whet your appetite, some of your choices include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carnes (Meat)&lt;br /&gt;Sides include plantains (crispy or sweet,) yucca, french fries, sausage, beans and salad.Rib eye steak $17.00&lt;br /&gt;Grilled pork chops $11.00&lt;br /&gt;Grilled pork loin $11.00&lt;br /&gt;Steak with onions&lt;br /&gt;Steak, pork belly served with rice, fried egg, plantain, arepa, avocado and Spanish sausage $12.00&lt;br /&gt;Chicken with rice $11.00&lt;br /&gt;Filet mignon with shrimp and mushroom sauce $21.00&lt;br /&gt;Beef tenderloin and shrimp in a piri piri sauce $24.00&lt;br /&gt;BBQ combo of beef, pork, sausage, roasted pepper onion and tomato in chimichurri sauce $19.00&lt;br /&gt;Chicken scallopini in lemon and caper sauce $18.00&lt;br /&gt;Grilled chicken breast and chorizo $12.00&lt;br /&gt;Beef, pork and chicken kebab served over special house rice $19.00&lt;br /&gt;Roast duck with marron glace sauce, sweet potato and Brazil nuts $21.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seafood&lt;br /&gt;Sides include plantains (crispy or sweet,) yucca, french fries, sausage, beans and salad.Calamari, shrimp, octopus, clams, mussels sauteed with coconut milk and heavy cream served over rice and french fries $16.00&lt;br /&gt;Filet of salmon with shrimps, sauteed in white wine butter, Parmesan cheese and heavy cream with rice and salad $21.00&lt;br /&gt;Filet of tilapia served with calamari, shrimps, octopus, slams, mussels, sauteed in seafood sauces and rice $21.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;…and yet much more…..grilled scallops, grilled lobster, jumbo shrimp, paella for two, etc.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be the table having fun</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5096147</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217890958000</updated><rating><average>4.38000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216981555000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chale Ipanema</name><id>8409188</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217718000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/8409188/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/c/global_2456236.jpeg</photo_url></item>