<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gee Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.640365</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dogtown</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>1247897</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.669149</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/8/1/event_39794721.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Since many of you are coming to Gloucester from 'off the island' it makes sense to meet as a group at the Friendly's parking lot right off the first rotary after the bridge.  We will carpool to the starting point.  Let's meet there NO LATER than 9:30 so we can get a headcount and proceed.   If you need specific directions to get to that point let me know early.  Basically, you take 128 north until you get to the rotary. We will leave for the trail at or BEFORE 9:40 so don't be late or  you'll miss  us.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our walk will be led by native guides, Gret Webster &amp;amp; Michael O'Leary.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Men are  welcome to come on this walk with us. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several trails in Dogtown.  We will follow trail #4 to locate as many boulders as possible.  During the Great Depression, Roger Babson commissioned 36 unemployed Finnish quarry workers to carve the mottos on the boulders.   They are now known as the Babson Boulders.  You will learn more about the Babsons and the history of the settlement during the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 IMPORTANT INFORMATION FOR HIKING!!  Although this would be considered an 'easy to moderate' hike for serious hikers, be advised that portions of the 'walk' may be taxing if you have any health issues.  Please let me know if you need anything.  Guidelines for safe hiking... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will walk at the pace of the slowest hiker. &lt;br /&gt;

 We will stay together at all times.  There are many trails in Dogtown and it is easy to get lost if you don't have a map. &lt;br /&gt;

 Bring water! &lt;br /&gt;

 Be sensible about your footwear.  No sandals please, unless they are made for safety while hiking. &lt;br /&gt;

 A walking stick could come in handy. &lt;br /&gt;

 Sunscreen/insect repellent would be smart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We LOVE this hike and this is our 3rd reprise! We usually eat at LobstaLand aftwerward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Besides learning some history and seeing the boulders, I love Dogtown because of the peace I feel there and the sense that time somehow is standing still.!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Gret&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Friendly's in Gloucester at the first rotary just over the bridge.  We'll carpool from there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mia</member_name><member_id>3507274</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gret Webster</member_name><member_id>12467902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340800949000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Women Supporting Women</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Women-Social-Network-Group</urlname><id>1379831</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Women Supporting Women Through Life's Incredible Journeys</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339688221000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Walk the Words / Dogtown (and lunch)</name><id>69159972</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340544600000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Women-Social-Network-Group/events/69159972/</event_url></item>