<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 117/Bus #70 or #170</address_2><address_1>1056 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.376331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-891-7677</phone><name>Cafe Angelinos</name><city>Waltham</city><id>931399</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.254417</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;Welcome back Daniella and to newbie Barbara   :)  Hope you enjoyed cribbage with us and will be returning again and again and again - Even when you are NOT new I still love skunking y'all    :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND a hearty CONGRATs to Joe who now has a job and can stay with us   :) AND who just got initiated by Capt'n Bette to reverse cribbage and who was laughing (LOL) about it as it is a fun game especially when you have to unlearn everything you know about Cribbage   :)  as did Karen as well as Emad, who forgot to show up last night  :( and was missed by ALL.  I don't think we even noticed that Gabe wasn't there as he had SKUNK  FLU ! ! !  and of course Susan is still away in Maine...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry, David and I had some G*R*E*A*T games, I beat them both twice I am sure   :)  even tho they were trying to gang up on me and Larry was WAY WAY ahead and blanks out on fourth street (yuck yuck).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Debbie skunked me :( :(  boo hoo and then proceeded to beat me up on the second game too  :(  :(&lt;br /&gt;BUT, she had a great F*U*N 'card Yankee Swap' that we will be doing on January 5th to start the New Year off with a BANG!!!!  AND it will be only 1 day after my 69th birthday   :)  SO YOU ALL BETTER BE ATTENDING as I will be baking my own birthday cake to celebrate along with the 'card Yankee Swap' for this F*U*N  Festive Occasion   :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Next meet up will be December 15th and I will be away on a cruise to the Caribbean (oh poor me) and we will also be playing on December 29, and will pick up the NEW YEAR on January 5, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Turkey Day to Y'ALL ! !   and you too Vegan Joe ! !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ME      :) :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back room with our Cribbage Boards out for ALL to find   :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Micki E</member_name><member_id>4468648</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259881489000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cribbage Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WalthamCribbage</urlname><id>378600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Waltham Cribbage!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258558131000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltham Cribbage Meet Up - Welcome to December 2009</name><id>11903329</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259708400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WalthamCribbage/events/11903329/</event_url></item>