<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 City Hall Plaza</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.360399</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-635-3911</phone><name>Boston City Hall Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>759013</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057982</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many of you are attending the 2nd Annual Japanese Spring Festival. Would you like to attend as a group? If you would like to join me and attend as part of a Group-- please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will make a point of stopping at the Japanese Flower Arranging booth. There will be an Ikenobo Ikebana booth at the Festival. Teachers of the Ikenobo style of Japanese Flower Arranging will be on hand to demonstrate the art of Ikenobo and to answer any questions about this style of Japanese Flower Arranging. Essentially this style of Japanese Flower Arranging is very important, as all Ikebana originated from this style. It began in Kyoto, Japan as a Buddhist floral offering. This will be a great opportunity for you to acquaint yourself with this style of Japanese Flower Arranging and an opportunity for you to find future classes if you so desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this Festival has much MORE!! There will be about 34 Food Booths and about 80 non-food booths PLUS stage performances. Last year over 13,000 people showed up. They are expecting more this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Stage will include: Chorus performing Japanese traditional songs/Kid's dances/traditional Japanese dances/Japanese Pop music. Food booths include: traditional Japanese food: Yakisoba/Okonomiyaki/Ramune and tea/Udon/Ukon spice drink/Beef bowl with rice/green tea ice cream/rice balls/ramen/curry rice/grilled squid/mochi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus many booths selling and promoting Japanese Culture and Arts &amp;amp; Crafts. For example: origami/ kimono/ calligraphy/ martial arts/ Buddhism/ anime and manga/Japanese healing arts/etc... Please see &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.JapanFestivalBoston.org"&gt;http://www.JapanFestivalBoston.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be there to guide us. Please meet me at 10:30am at the Starbucks with the steaming kettle at 63 Court Street (next to Government MBTA station). This is the Starbucks with the giant golden steaming kettle hung over the entrance. (see &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.CelebrateBoston.com/strange/giant-tea-kettle.htm"&gt;http://www.CelebrateBoston.com/strange/giant-tea-kettle.htm&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's enjoy a leisurely Sunday together immersed in Japanese culture! Stay as long as you like. I will be there from 10:30am until closing at 6pm. If you can not meet me at 10:30am I could rendezvous with a later group at 1pm. Please remember to RSVP!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can contact me at: &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/events/119288212"&gt;http://www.Meetup.com/Japanese-Flower-Arranging/events/119288212&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>10:30am--- Meet me in front of Starbucks with the giant golden steaming tea kettle next to Government MBTA Station  http://www.celebrateBoston.com/strange/giant-tea-kettle.htm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim</member_name><member_id>88605612</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369006923000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368512405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enjoy Japanese Flower Arranging at the Boston Japanese Spring Festival and MORE!</name><id>119292932</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368973800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/119292932/</event_url></item>