<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's meet at Zaftig's at 5:00 for dinner and talk before the film.&amp;nbsp; Zaftig's does not take reservations on the weekend, but I just spoke to Lara and she said that around 5:00 we should be able to be seated with very little wait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Note: On Sunday nights after 6:00 pm, Cinematographer Coolidge Members receive free admission.)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomato Meter 92% Fresh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMDB 7.9 out of 8.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From The Coolidge Corner Theater website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the best reviewed films of the year, director &lt;strong&gt;Mike Leigh&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rsquo;s (&lt;em&gt;Secrets and Lies, Topsy Turvy&lt;/em&gt;) latest film follows a blissfully married couple (Ruth Sheen and Jim Broadbent) and their increasingly strained relationship with a fragile and needy friend (Lesley Manville). Drawing Oscar-worthy performances from his three leads, Leigh has once again created a wholly original and unpredictable film&amp;mdash;a story about families and friendships that is equal parts heartbreaking and hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From A.O. Scott, The New York Times:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like &amp;ldquo;Happy-Go-Lucky,&amp;rdquo; though on a somewhat larger scale, &amp;ldquo;Another Year&amp;rdquo; is about the unequal distribution of happiness. Why do some people &amp;mdash; like Tom and Gerri, the post-&amp;rsquo;60s 60-something couple at the center of this episodic story &amp;mdash; seem to have an inexhaustible, even superabundant supply, while others seem unable to acquire even the smallest portion? Can happiness be borrowed, stolen or inherited? Is it earned by meritorious works or granted by the obscure operations of grace?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These may sound like silly, abstract questions, but they could hardly be more serious or more relevant. Here in America, after all, the pursuit of happiness has the status of a foundational right, coincident, but not quite identical, with material prosperity. In Britain, where dourness can seem to be as much a part of the stereotypical national character as bad food, foul weather and precise distinctions of status, the assertion of a right to be happy can seem almost revolutionary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;latimes.com/entertainment/news/la-et-another-year-20101229,0,4823299.story&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;latimes.com Movie review: 'Another Year'&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Kenneth Turan, Los Angeles Times Film Critic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 29, 2010&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Another Year" is about the turning wheel of life, an examination of the pleasures and jealousies, disappointments and insecurities, destroyed dreams and rekindled hopes that make up our daily existence. It may sound commonplace, but in the hands of master filmmaker Mike Leigh, the everyday becomes extraordinary. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The film is also further proof &amp;mdash; if proof is necessary after six Oscar nominations for writing and directing, a Palme d'Or and a best director award from Cannes, and a Golden Lion from Venice &amp;mdash; that Leigh's explorations of human psychology are on a level of their own. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Using a particular method of working with actors that thoroughly involves them in creating characters from the ground up, Leigh goes deeper into individuals than one would have thought possible. The people he and his cast create in this joint venture combine depth and complexity with a kind of unstudied naturalism, so much the better to make audiences complicit in their lives. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The three actors who are the focus of "Another Year" &amp;mdash; Jim Broadbent, Ruth Sheen and an indescribable Lesley Manville &amp;mdash; are all veterans of multiple Leigh ventures, and it's a special pleasure to see them finding their places in this new situation, to watch as Leigh slowly but with impeccable sureness adds character and incident to the mix. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If Leigh's last film, " Happy-Go-Lucky," focused on youthful concerns, "Another Year" shows us life through the lens of people who are older but still trying to connect with one another, still trying to figure out the elusive answer to the human equation. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After a stunning opening vignette featuring Imelda Staunton, "Another Year" introduces its central figures of Tom (Broadbent) and Gerri (Sheen in an especially subtle performance). They are as sane and stable a longtime married couple as Leigh's films have ever offered. He is a geologist, she a mental health counselor, and together they form an island of steadiness and dependability, underlined by their passion for gardening, that everyone they know clings to and admires. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;No one depends more on these two than Mary (Manville), a coworker of Gerri's who's been a family friend for close to 20 years. Mary is a little frantic from the first moments we see her, a flighty, live-wire individual who seems to have too much energy for her own good. We notice this but, like Tom and Gerri, we let it go because, well, that's just the way she is. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;"Another Year" is broken up into four sections, each named after a season. Though Tom, Gerri and Mary appear in all of them, each season has its own particular narrative line, kind of like a short story within a themed collection. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The film starts with spring, which provides an intense look at Mary when she comes to Tom and Gerri's for dinner. Within the context of a single evening, Manville's superlative acting unself-consciously peels Mary like an onion, revealing her as someone alternately in denial and despair about the unhappiness in her life, uncomfortable in her own skin but unwilling or unable to do anything about it but drink too much too often. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Summer brings a visit from Ken ( Peter Wight), an old childhood friend of Tom's. Though the motto on Ken's T-shirt ("less thinking, more drinking") indicates a possibly dissonant lifestyle choice, the two remain close enough for a wonderful impromptu moment in which Tom jumps on his pal's shoulders. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Against all reason (isn't that always the way?), Ken finds himself attracted to Mary, with unsettling results. Even more against reason, autumn brings an intensification of what had seemed a harmless romantic crush on Mary's part, with even more unsettling results. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The mood darkens in winter, when a funeral brings Tom and Gerri to Tom's childhood home, where his brother Ronnie (a marvelous David Bradley in his first Leigh film) is coping with his wife's death and the emotional assaults of his disaffected son, Carl (Martin Savage). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;It's inevitable that some of these individuals have more screen time than others, but Leigh's methods ensure that everyone brings the same level of intensity and commitment to what he or she does. As "Another Year" and its memorable people prove one more time, there are no small parts in these films. When Leigh says, as he did in Cannes, that "I practice a craft that can't be copied," this is what he's talking about. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Zaftig's at 5:00 for dinner. Coolidge upstairs lobby circa 6:30 for film.  I'll have  Red Meetup Sign in hand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297702268000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Another Year by Mike Leigh has gotten rave reviews from critics and friends.  It's coming to The Coolidge this weekend.

Zaftig's
335 Havard Street
Brookline, MA 02446
617-975-0075</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297383405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Another Year - February 13, 2011  6:30 pm  Zaftig's 5:00 for dinner.</name><id>16523003</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297639800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/16523003/</event_url></item>