<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06101</zip><lat>41.778392</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860)521-5362 extension 21.</phone><name>North Cemetery on North Main Street </name><city>Hartford</city><id>783509</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.676224</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WEST HARTFORD HAUNTINGS RISES AGAIN; Noah Webster House Hosts Nighttime Cemetery Tours &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This October, West Hartford Hauntings will return for its fourth year of frightful cemetery tours! The Noah Webster House &amp;amp; West Hartford Historical Society brings the residents of West Hartford’s North Cemetery back to life in this spooky theatrical show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Friday, Saturday, and Sunday nights, October 24-26, several of these past residents will rise to tell their stories.  A milkman who froze to death tells his chilling tale, the first wife of a local minister shares her past, and a decapitated man speaks of being struck by a trolley. Not only do these and other ghosts tell their tales, specters, spooks, and phantoms also prowl the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each evening, 12 tours will begin at the North Cemetery on North Main Street in West Hartford. There, tour goers will meet their guide- also a “past resident” of West Hartford. Tours depart every 15 minutes between 6 and 8:45 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are on sale now!  Ticket prices are $9 for children 17 and under and $15 for adults.  They are available through the museum by calling (860)521-5362 extension 21.  For information on the availability of an American Sign Language interpreter, (available for certain tours) call ext 21 or email comments@noahwebsterhouse.org. West Hartford Hauntings is made possible by a grant from the Connecticut Humanities Council.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call and Get Your tickets I will  send my # to Yeses the Day Before.  Maybe have Hot mulled  cider  up the hill if its available&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225117357000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223421450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WEST HARTFORD HAUNTINGS RISES AGAIN; Noah Webster House Hosts Nighttime Cemetery</name><id>8918148</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224891000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8918148/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/e/2/global_2940738.jpeg</photo_url></item>