<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Please join us this Tuesday to enjoy a beautiful night of spring frisbee.  We'll be meeting at 8PM at the Cambridge Common baseball diamond which is located a couple blocks north of Harvard Square. We generally play from 8-10PM and then go out for food and drinks. Before attending our events, please review our &lt;a href="http://fitness.meetup.com/350/about/"&gt;About Us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd recommend you bring a light-colored shirt for visibility's sake and a change of clothes. We supply all of the equipment necessary so there's really nothing else you need to bring besides your smiling face. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/laughing.gif' border='0' alt='laughing' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Organizers pay out of pocket for the frisbees, lanyards, glowsticks, field cones and first aid kits. Please consider bringing a couple bucks or visiting our &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/IRMLHWE8OGKZ"&gt;Amazon Wishlist&lt;/a&gt; to support our equipment costs. Our group is free and will always be that way but your optional donations are certainly appreciated! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=10+garden+st+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;amp;sspn=33.626896,81.738281&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.376807,-71.119566&amp;amp;spn=0.007656,0.019956&amp;amp;z=16"&gt;Cambridge Commons Map&lt;/a&gt;. Parking at Cambridge Common's is tricky and we highly recommend you take the &lt;a href="http://www.mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; to Harvard Square. If you have any questions about our group, please don't hesitate to contact our Organizers!  Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Chea</member_name><member_id>4415505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207872194000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We've created an awesome community of fun people who go out of their way to ensure that everyone feels welcomed and included. We also have fantastic games of Ultimate!</why><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207532216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Beautiful Night for Illuminated Frisbee (Cambridge Commons)</name><id>7688214</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207699200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7688214/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/c/global_3460060.jpeg</photo_url></item>