<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>to cover the room rental</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>By popular demand, it's another practice for the Boston/Cambridge Salsa Meet-up Group!  The Dance Complex is closed for summer vacation, so we thought we'd try a new studio--and this time one that has air conditioning ;-)  Thanks to the many enthusiastic responses about our last practice, we have increased the length of time to 1.5 hours, but you are still welcome to come for just part of the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be a terrific opportunity to practice with other dancers, improve your skills, and help others do the same.   We'll look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be going out for dinner at 8:30 pm, for whoever wishes to come.  Based on a few people letting me know they'd like Middle Eastern food, I found this restaurant in Watertown Square:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Demos Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;64 Mount Auburn Street, Watertown, MA 02472&lt;br /&gt;(617) 924-9660&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to join us there, whether you attend the practice or not.  See you soon!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring your dance shoes, your smile, and some ideas of what you would like to work on!  Music is always welcome too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The studio is easily accessible by car and there is plenty of parking in the back.  It is also easy to come by bus from Cambridge and other locations (#71, #70, #70A).  I just went to MBTA.com, and entered &amp;quot;the intersection of Parker and Garnet Streets,&amp;quot; and it gave me several choices.  If anyone would like to try to carpool or ride the bus together, please feel free to post it in your response.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>22</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1154990679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa Meet-up Practice</name><id>5065952</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156806000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/5065952/</event_url></item>