<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>google it</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.266743</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>north brookfield town common</name><city>north brookfield </city><id>11202552</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.082848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;HEAR YE… HEAR YE…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tired of the government running rough shod over your rights?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Believe in the Constitution and the Bill of Rights?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel it is time to join others who feel the same way?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like the idea that if you want to own a particular firearm, you can, because this is America?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then stop moaning about it, stop tweeting how ticked off you are and stop Facebooking your disappointment, and come do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are holding the “LET FREEDOM RING” rally on January27th, at the North Brookfield town common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have speakers from the Libertarian party, the Tea Party, Red Pill Politics, and the Gun Owners Action League.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our voice cannot and will not be heard one at a time. We need a show of force that we will not sit idly by while our rights and freedoms are trampled upon by our self serving government and the puppet masters at the United Nations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tell all who feel the same way. Make this a happening. Don’t sit at home because it’s the easy thing to do, be a part of taking back what is ours to begin with. WE THE PEOPLE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few hundred people doesn’t even make the papers...A few thousand will be seen all over the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a sticker proclaiming your freedoms and place it on the WALL OF FREEDOM. LET’S BE HEARD…. BE STRONG…. BE LOUD…. BE AMERICAN&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rain or shine event starting at 1:00 pm, January 27th, 2013, North Brookfield Town Common Would you like an opportunity to speak, or have an organization that you would like represented? Contact us at redzonetactics@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359320730000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1358375143000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Freedom Rally</name><id>99951602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359309600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/99951602/</event_url></item>