<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We hope you're willing to make the drive through Witch City for some game play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should you have a favorite game please bring it; otherwise, you know we're well stocked. You are also welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who have never attended a traditional game night, these events are social, but we are serious about game playing. We usually split up in different rooms or areas to play smaller games of players' choice and then come together for a larger game or two at the end of the night. However, sometimes we just play large party games for the majority of the evening. It depends on the mood of the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats, but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a 3 year old, who will be headed to bed as people arrive. We also have a baby, who isn't much of a game player, but he will eventually go to bed as well. Expect to see him awake while you are here, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319511626000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318442459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Traditional Game Night</name><id>37140332</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319328000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/37140332/</event_url></item>