<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am listing this member-run event on our site because a couple of our long-time members are organizing it and wanted to open it up to fellow randomites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;==========&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't have plans for the Memorial Day holiday weekend and would like to get away and hike in the White Mountains you might want to consider going with the Wedelns. &amp;nbsp;While they are primarily a ski group, they also do other outdoor activities and for the long weekend they are looking to organize intermediate and advanced hikes on Saturday and Sunday - followed each night by barbecues and bonfires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a great intro-weekend to the Wedeln Ski &amp;amp; Outdoor Club. &amp;nbsp;If you have never been to their house then this is an ideal weekend to make your first visit. &amp;nbsp;The house is tucked away half way up Hurricane Mountain in N. Conway and has hiking and biking trails right out the back side of the house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accommodations are only $20 per night, bring your own bedding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the link to their event description - if you plan to go please RSVP on their page so they can keep track of who is going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/17414438/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/17414438/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>George Fraley</member_name><member_id>10925592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306761363000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306720312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Memorial Day Weekend Hiking in the Whites with the Wedelns (Monday)</name><id>20194881</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306756800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/20194881/</event_url></item>