<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>THIS IS THE SECOND OF A TWO-PART SERIES!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; How to Celebrate a Joyous Holiday Season in Uncertain Times&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me as we retool Christmas (or Hanukkah or Kwanza, or Santa’s visit); changing it from a months-long orgy of conspicuous consumption to what it was intended to be – a peaceful celebration of joy, hope and love - so critical in today's financially challenging times. I'm using the framework of the Christian Advent and Christmas timeframes, but they can be easily adapted. So whether you celebrate Christmas, Hanukkah, Kwanzaa or some combination, you'll be able to use the information presented.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the first session, we learned how to use the four weeks before Christmas (Advent) as a time of preparation. This part focuses on &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Twelve Days of Christmas. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; If you don't celebrate Christmas, these tips transfer well to planning winter activities woth your family and friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know?&lt;br /&gt;* It is possible to actually enjoy the holiday season at a relaxed pace and without massive consumption &lt;br /&gt;* You can celebrate in any way that is meaningful to you. Martha Stewart feasts are optional; so are mega-watt animatronic displays on your front lawn, adorable matching sweaters for your family, and themed decorations throughout the house&lt;br /&gt;* Christmas does not start before Halloween or even the day after Thanksgiving. Nope. Christmas begins on December 25 and lasts until Twelfth Night (January 6th; also called Epiphany)&lt;br /&gt;* You don’t have to squeeze visits with birth families, in-laws, blended families and friends into Christmas Eve and Christmas Day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop focuses on identifying and prioritizing the activities that give you joy, and scheduling creative, low (or no-) cost, fun events over a series of days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll cut through the forest of “have-tos” and get down to “want-tos”, and we’ll learn simple ways to ramp up the joy while keeping down costs.&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Best,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marilyn&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228575317000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224354185000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Celebrate a Joyous Holiday Season in Uncertain Times - Part 2</name><id>8985759</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228262400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/8985759/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/d/global_5119229.jpeg</photo_url></item>