<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>deposit</description><amount>250.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This course is recommended for home-owners and renters, gardeners, landscape professionals, planners, architects, engineers, tradespeople, community activists and anyone interested in changing &amp;quot;how we organize ourselves&amp;quot; in the landscape. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Expected Outcomes:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Gain a thorough understanding of permaculture origins, ethics, principles and methodologies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Enhance your ability to build soil, capture water, reduce energy consumption, generate energy, grow and store food, read the landscape and create edible perennial ecosystems. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Become a resource for your family and neighborhood, building resilience at the personal, household and community levels. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Learn how to transform even challenging properties into healthy, hi-yielding, low energy systems of abundance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Be able to approach any property and apply a permaculture design methodolgy and set of applied techniques to achieve increased resilience and true sustainability.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Past students are recommending the Permaculture Design Certificate Course course because... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Everyone should familiarize themselves with permaculture principles &amp;amp; techniques given the local &amp;amp; global changes that are underway.”   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It's what we have to do! We all need to enter this scary future more prepared than we are and this course will steer you in the direction of sustainability... and it's fun.” (Russ Van Deursen) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It is tremendous and life altering and revolutionarily simple in it's brilliance and because you discover the tools within you to create the change that you know must happen in this great big beautiful injured world.”  (Sarah Bostick) &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;“It will change your outlook on life. And once you've been awakened, there's no desire to go back to the way things were.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It will change how you see yourself in the world. It is a necessary class for anyone looking to &amp;quot;rebuild our communities&amp;quot; (self, family, towns, earth) in a healthy manner.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Many of us seek to improve our World but few of us have the practical skills needed to manifest the desired outcome. Taking the Permaculture Design Course I learned not only specific skill sets but had the amazing experience of working with other people from all walks of life who share this common goal. Charles, Julia, and Lisa were inspirational expert instructors who took the time to ensure each student's progress while providing the very best course material.”  (Kiarna Boyd) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Overall, to say this permaculture class was great falls vastly short. It's like the language we have can't contain my feelings regarding the class. It was a paradigm-shifting spiritual type of event. This class on permaculture landscape design gave my life positive new meaning and direction. A positive solution-oriented Path to follow that looks at the destruction we have wrought on this planet full in the face, and doesn't shy away from the immensity of it, but like aikido, uses the same forces that create destruction to heal and recreate balance, beauty, health, community. This class was the perfect mix of people who magically came together at the right time. It was the stuff legends are made of when you reflect back on your life when you're near the end.&amp;quot;  (Jesse Watson)&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Permaculture Design Certificate Course Details&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The course will be based in midcoast Maine and will include such sites as Newforest Institute, Humustacia Permaculture Gardens, Avena Botanicals and other sites relevant to permaculture.  It will consist of the traditional 72-hour PDC course + 20 to 30  additional hours to ensure we cover regional examples and timely developments.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;July 6 - July 18, 2010.  This will start just two days after the &lt;a href="http://northeastconvergence.wordpress.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Northeast Permaculture Convergence&lt;/a&gt; in Unity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;:  $1,200 which includes course and certification, camping, all meals, coffee, tea + am/pm break refreshments, handouts, course materials on a CD, field trips and guest speakers.  &lt;b&gt;$250 Deposit&lt;/b&gt; holds your spot in this course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, (available to any student) reduce the cost of your course tuition by helping get more people trained.  For every enrolled student that you refer, receive $50 off your total tuition for this course. &lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Class Size&lt;/b&gt;:  15-18 students  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;:  This course is comprised of lecture, hands-on exercises, guest speakers, field trips, readings/homework, video, discussion and student design projects.  There will be pre-work before the course and some required reading between course weekends.  Students must attend all sessions and complete the group design project in order to receive their certificates. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Course Flyer:  &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/215138/2010_PDC_Flyer.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mail-In Registration Form: &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/215138/2010%20PDC_Registration.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or register online and make a deposit &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/calendar/12640424/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preliminary Syllabus&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part One:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Big Picture / Permaculture in Context &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Permaculture Ethics &amp;amp; Principles &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Patterns in Nature &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reading the Landscape &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intro to Site Assessment &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soils &amp;amp; Soil Health &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composting &amp;amp; Worm Bins &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sheet Mulching &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building Your Permaculture Toolkit &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Synergistic Garden&amp;quot; &amp;amp; Masanobu Fukuoka &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zones &amp;amp; Sectors &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Viewing a Permaculture Property &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Season Extension / Hoop Houses &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part Two&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating a Food Forest &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keyline and Swales &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Animals in the Landscape &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plant Pathology &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intro to Green Building with Field Trips/Examples &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Begin Visioning Process &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Water in the Landscape (Water Collection, Ponds, Flowforms, Greywater, etc.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Biodynamics &amp;amp; Planting Strategies &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Herb Spiral and Pond Building &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part Three&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Renewable Energy &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Green Remodeling Options/Examples &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Affordable Green Building/Examples &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lawns vs. Food + Field Trip &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Permaculture &amp;amp; Community &amp;quot;Invisible Structures&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Local Currency, CSA, Open Source, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Broadacre&amp;quot; Permaculture Lessons &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;More Design Considerations + Review &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slow Food &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;International Permaculture Connections &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design Practicum + Presentations &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Carrying Permaculture Forward &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Instructors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Charles &amp;amp; Julia Yelton&lt;/b&gt;, of Humastacia Permaculture Gardens in Whitefield, Maine are international permaculture designers and teachers.  They have traveled and lectured on permaculture topics throughout the world.  Formerly of Crystal Waters permaculture village in Queensland Australia, they have gone on to practice and teach for over 17 years in Asia, Europe and North America, most recently designing and implementing comprehensive permaculture gardens in Cyprus.  They were the founding Co-Directors of The Permaculture Center at Newforest Institute in Brooks, Maine and have been named 2008 Still Water Fellows by the University of Maine, Orono.  They split their time between Whitefield, Maine and their permaculture property in Sicily. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lisa Fernandes&lt;/b&gt; is the organizer and founding member of the Portland Maine Permaculture and has been a student of permaculture and green design since 1992. She is a certified team trainer and group facilitator and owned a training &amp;amp; consulting business for several years. She studied political science (undergraduate) and environmental history (graduate) before designing &amp;amp; implementing municipal waste reduction &amp;amp; recycling programs (with a focus on organic waste recycling). Lisa is also a gardener, certified Master Composter and has studied medicinal plants for nearly twenty years. She has worked in the public, private and non-profit sectors and currently brings her varied experience to developing &amp;amp; delivering permaculture training events and permaculture designs for local clients. She currently serves on the Cape Farm Alliance and is active in the Eat Local Foods Coalition. She is a principal in Resilient Homes, an ecological design and solar hot water company and was founding director of The Pattern Factory design studio at Newforest Institute. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279804971000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266524176000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 Maine Permaculture Design Certification Course</name><id>12640424</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278421200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/12640424/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/d/e/global_8486014.jpeg</photo_url></item>