<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>IRN Speaker for December Public Meeting - Wed., Dec 1 - 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Mihalek - Inventor and Developer of the Traveler-ER™ and Marketer Extraordinaire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are pleased to welcome Thomas Mihalek, a dynamic marketer, inventor and speaker, to present to IRN members and the general public at our Dec. 1 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas is the inventor of a device named Traveler-ER™ which allows an individual to carry their personal medical records and history on their person at all times.  As with many innovations, the “aha” moment occurred during a real-life situation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas and his wife, a Registered Nurse, were at a trade event in Las Vegas, enjoying a dinner with a number of other attendees. Suddenly, a man sitting nearby collapsed on the floor! Thomas and his wife, among others, attended to the man while EMS and other help were called via 911. In the meanwhile, since Thomas and his wife did not know the man, they asked those sitting around him if they knew anything about his medical conditions, etc. and the answer they received was simply “That’s Bob, from the Purchasing Dept.”  It turns out that no one had a clue as to what Bob’s medical history was, and therefore it was difficult for both the EMS and the medical pros in the dinner theater to help. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And so was born the idea for the Traveler-ER™ (Web site: &lt;a href="http://traveler-er.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://traveler-er.co...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas will be sharing his experiences as well as his collected wisdom from 20+ years in marketing, sales and business development. His other firm, TRM (Tactical Results Marketing) perform consulting for companies ranging from startups to the Fortune 500. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas is a local here in Western Ma, having earned various degrees at Westfield State and Umass/Amherst. We hope you can join us in learning more about his views on innovation and marketing.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Down the stairs on the right from the entrance lobby for Scibelli Enterprise Center. Right corridor, door on the right.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Kat.</member_name><member_id>8999115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Blanchard</member_name><member_id>9728219</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291412422000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290046570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Meeting</name><id>15484386</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291246200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/15484386/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/c/b/global_19419787.jpeg</photo_url></item>