<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>South End</address_2><address_1>1357 Washington St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02118</zip><lat>42.341510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-423-0555</phone><name>Union Bar &amp; Grille</name><city>Boston</city><id>344464</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Winner of Best of Boston for 2009 - This is a special place. The food is some of the very best I have had in Boston. This is priced right and a must place to experience. Food, setting and service all 5 plus stars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$9.95 All Inclusive Brunch  Special&lt;br /&gt;Offer good from 10:00 AM to 11:00 AM Sunday&lt;br /&gt;and 10am to 3pm Saturday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cinnamon Swirl Sour Cream Coffee Cake &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Choice of:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chef’s Special Omelet&lt;br /&gt;Served with Homefries &amp;amp; Choice of Toast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smoked Salmon Scramble&lt;br /&gt;House Cured Salmon, Crème Fraiche, Scallions, Homefries &amp;amp; Choice of Toast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;B-52 French Toast&lt;br /&gt;Orange Marmalade, Maple Syrup and Smoked Bacon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Served with:&lt;br /&gt;Fresh Squeezed Orange or Grapefruit Juice&lt;br /&gt;House Coffee and Tea&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to the above brunch selections they have an extensive Brunch Menu:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.unionrestaurant.com/menu/brunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.unionresta...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More About Union Bar and Grille:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Union Bar and Grille is The Aquitaine Group's newest venue. Located in the newly revitalized SoWa area of the South End, Union Bar and Grille is at 1357 Washington Street and Union Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The team that makes up Union Bar and Grille includes Executive Chef/Partner Seth Woods, General Manager/Partner Jeffrey Gates and Partner Matthew Burns. Working alongside Woods is Chef de Cuisine Stephen Sherman. Sherman has been cooking with Woods since January 2002 at Aquitaine - Bar a Vin Bistrot and later at Aquitaine Bis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Union, according to Webster's Dictionary is &amp;quot;a hall or gathering place where people of all neighborhoods and backgrounds can come together to exchange ideas, philosophies and general conversation. Union, according to the Aquitaine Group, is &amp;quot;what going out to dinner used to be -- not a culinary education, just good food that you want to eat.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Union Bar and Grille offers a full bar and an all-American wine list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Restaurant Designer Peter Niemitz and the Niemitz Design Group alongside The Aquitaine Group created a balance between simplicity and sophistication in this renovated warehouse space on historic Washington Street. As one enters through the yellow tinted glass vestibule, eyes are immediately drawn to the innovative use of texture, materials, and neutral color. The space is a blend of design elements from historic and current themes. Rough sawn beams and Heart Pine plank floors contrast with clean architectural millwork. Texture and transparency are the major design elements. A steel and glass wall separates the bar from the dining room and the interior surfaces transition from smooth to highly textural. The firm designed the unique historically inspired chandeliers and all of the furniture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Aquitaine Group is owned and operated by Executive Chef/Partner Seth Woods, Partner Matthew Burns, and General Manager/Partner Jeffery Gates. Among The Aquitaine Group's stable of award winning and respected restaurants include: Metropolis Cafe, Aquitaine- Bar a Vin Bistrot, and its latest restaurant, Union Bar and Grille in the South End neighborhood of Boston, Aquitaine Bis in Chestnut Hill, and Armani Cafe on Newbury Street in Boston's Back Bay.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257790853000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257439444000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>$9.95 All Inclusive Brunch @ Union Bar - Winner of Best of Boston for 2009</name><id>11803234</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257616800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11803234/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/c/global_6726124.jpeg</photo_url></item>