<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This walk was originally the Neponset River walk, but that was too close to the interstate so I changed it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 10 in the parking lot at Pleasure Bay, the map link points to an apartment building across the street from it.  If you need a ride please ask for one in your rsvp, saying what neighborhood you are in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Castle Island / Pleasure Bay&lt;br /&gt;Owned and operated by the Department of Conservation and Recreation, this area provides an abundance of recreation and historical learning opportunities for the visitor. Accessible from downtown, the HarborWalk extends along Pleasure Bay, with a detour to Castle Island. Pleasure Bay is a calm, enclosed lagoon with a sandy beach for swimming. Pleasure Bay is one of the most popular swimming and sunning beaches in the City. Foot showers and water fountains are located on-site. Because the bay is fully enclosed by the man-made Head Island Causeway, water and sediment quality are consistently high. The causeway located behind the beach provides a great walk way for strolling around Pleasure Bay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Originally freestanding, Castle Island has been connected to the mainland since the 1930s, when streetcars brought bathers to Pleasure Bay. Fort Independence, located on Castle Island, is a five pointed granite structure. The current structure is the eighth fort to occupy this site and contains over 172,687 linear feet of hammered stone and was constructed under the direction of Colonel Sylvanus Thayer between 1834 and 1851. The fort is open during the summer months, and visitors can explore independently or take a free tour. The fort and the island are on the State and National Registers of Historic Places, and Fort Independence is a National Historic Landmark. There are views to Logan Airport and the Harbor Islands, and visitors can observe boating activity in the Harbor. The area is excellent for jogging, walking, picnicking and hiking, and there is a fishing pier and swimming area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonharborwalk.com/placestogo/location.php?nid=6&amp;amp;sid=44" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonharb...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Parking: &lt;br /&gt;Free public parking is available.&lt;br /&gt;Bus: &lt;br /&gt;Take MBTA Route 5, 7, 9, 10, or 11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at Fish Pier Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;667 East Broadway&lt;br /&gt;617-269-2111&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175006151000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173586122000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pleasure Bay walk</name><id>5557831</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174833000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5557831/</event_url></item>