<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Middlesex Canal Park Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.496334</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Showcase Cinemas</name><city>Woburn</city><id>3990132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.157211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of us will be watching the movie MoneyBall at the Woburn Cinema.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase your ticket and meet inside at the entrance to the MoneyBall Theatre at 12:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start time is 12:40pm. Run time is approximately 2 hours or much shorter than your average Sox game.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MoneyBall is NOT about how the 2011 Red Sox&amp;nbsp;suffered&amp;nbsp;the worst September collapse in the history of Baseball with a $165 Million Dollar payroll while players fattened up on fried chicken and beer in the club house during games. This movie will be out in about 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MoneyBall is a movie starring Brad Pitt based on the best selling book by Michael&amp;nbsp;Lewis, "MoneyBall - The Art of Winning an Unfair Game" about the Oakland Athletics baseball team and its general manager Billy Beane.&amp;nbsp;It focuses on the teams modernized, analytical, sabermetric approach to assembling a competitive baseball team, despite Oakland's disadvantaged revenue situation.&amp;nbsp; By re-evaluating the strategies that produce wins on the field, the 2002 Athletics, with approximately $41 Million in payroll,&amp;nbsp;were competitive with larger market teams such as the New York Yankees which spent $125 Million&amp;nbsp;in payroll that same year.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will head over to ScoreBoard next door&amp;nbsp;for a bite, to watch the Pats game or a playoff game.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Movie starts at 12:40pm, Meet at 12:30pm at the Entrance to the MoneyBall Theatre</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318857083000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318628093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watch The Movie MoneyBall at Woburn Showcase Cinema &amp; Lunch at  Scoreboard</name><id>37428792</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318782600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/37428792/</event_url></item>