<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Mass Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366693</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1403775</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105443</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time&lt;/em&gt; by Mark Haddon is unlike any other book I have read. That's because the narrator, Christopher John Francis Boone, is unlike anyone I have ever met. He is a teenager with an developmental disability who is a mathematical genius but cannot understand human emotions. The novel is written as if Christopher is writing it for a class assignment. He numbers the chapters in prime numbers because that is what he likes. In fact, you hear a lot about what Christopher likes and does not like in the pages of this mystery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story begins when Christopher finds a dead dog on the neighbor's lawn. As he works to figure out who killed the dog, you learn a lot about Christopher's family, past and neighbors. It soon becomes clear that the dog's murder is not the only mystery worth solving in Christopher's life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story will draw you in, make you laugh and cause you to see the world through different eyes. The novel entertains, but it also provides an avenue for empathizing with people with developmental disabilities. I highly recommend it for book clubs (see &lt;a href="http://bestsellers.about.com/od/bookclubquestions/a/curious_q.htm"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time&lt;/em&gt; book club discussion questions&lt;/a&gt;) and individuals who are looking for a good read.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paras Hezar</member_name><member_id>12400154</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306452320000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time by Mark Haddon</why><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303787535000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:  Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time</name><id>17434076</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306365300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/17434076/</event_url></item>