<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>695 Hillside St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02186</zip><lat>42.213120</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Hills - Houghton Pond</name><city>Milton</city><id>5099502</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094185</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE!!!!! You DO NOT have to RSVP that you are not attending. This only fills up my mailbox. Thanks &lt;br /&gt;

 Fast paced hike with elevation. We will hike to Elliott Tower,  continue on the Blue Skyline Trail to Rte 138 and back. We averaged 2.5 to 3 hours. This hike does have a lot of elevation. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you have not hiked before, have a medical condition, or cannot keep pace at 3 mph or more, you may not want to consider this event. Please bring a map of the Hills with in the event you fall behind. &lt;br /&gt;

 By signing up to his hike you agree to the liability waiver below. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 LOCATION: Houghton's Pond Recreation Center, Milton, Ma parking area (I will be parked here). The one with the construction site and playground. Look for a Silver late model Volvo. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 RECOMMENDED GEAR: Water, snacks, food, gloves, proper shoes for hiking, proper clothing for weather conditions. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Debra's Cell # - 508-237-4454; use email address, dlh161@gmail.com. I cannot respond to the meetup email from my smartphone. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 DIRECTIONS: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Address – Houghton’s Pond Recreation Center, 695 Hillside St, Milton, MA 02186 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Take Route 93 to Exit 3, Houghton's Pond. Turn right at the stop sign onto Hillside Street. Houghton's &lt;br /&gt;

 Pond is located approximately 1/4 miles on the right; continue onto the Houghton Pond entrance on the &lt;br /&gt;

 right. Or you can take Exit 5 MA 28 Randolph Milton, keep on Randolph St. until you get to set of lights, &lt;br /&gt;

 take left at lights onto Chickatawabut Rd, then left onto Hillside St near the State Police, continue onto &lt;br /&gt;

 the Houghton Pond Recreation Center entrance on the left. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Peaks: Great Blue Hill (635 feet). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Difficulty Level: Fast and Strenuous. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: We have averaged about 2.5 to 3 hours. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Weather Forecast: &lt;a href="http://www.weather.com/weather/today/USMA0260:1:US%3Cbr%20/%3E"&gt;http://www.weather.com/weather/today/USMA0260:1:US &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 CANCELLATION POLICY: Inclement weather (mainly Rain) may cancel the hike. If cancelled, it will be &lt;br /&gt;

 rescheduled a few weeks later. I will not have the time to call everyone, so you'll need access to your &lt;br /&gt;

 email to see if the hike is canceled. I will try to post it 4 hours before the hike. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CODE OF CONDUCT AND LIABILITY WAIVER: As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 * Weather can change quickly. Weather conditions which normally do not appear problematic can be when the body is stressed by hard exercise. You can develop hypothermia or hyperthermia very easily at any outside temperature.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Houghton's Pond Recreation Center, Milton, Ma parking area (I will be parked here). The one with the construction site and playground. Look for a Silver late model Volvo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debra </member_name><member_id>12483780</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348423116000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347978198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Blue Hills - Skyline Trail</name><id>82939052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348411500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/82939052/</event_url></item>