<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Rolling it to 1pm, we'll have a chance to say hi and get settled and probably start the film around 1:30ish... I'll have some popcorn and possibly some other snacks, maybe some hot apple cider, and lots of delicious Bolton well water! Feel free to bring something to share (this is a vegetarian house, please no meat). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've placed a limit of 15 people, with the understanding that some of us will be lounging on the carpet, so if you get here on time, you can place dibs on the couch and chairs! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I do have 2 cats, who will disappear the minute they see anyone they don't know, but their presence will still be noticeable in the den. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Really excited that this filled up so quickly! Going to be a great discussion. I'll send my cell phone and address to 'yes' RSVPs when we're closer to The Date. &lt;br /&gt;************************** &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[John said:] I went to see Memento last nite with Nerd Fun.  It's one of those movies that gets better every time you see it.  I think it'd be interesting to discuss memory, how it's fallible and malleable, whether an objective reality of the past matters if you can't mentally access it, how you can tell if someone knows something if they want you to think they don't, etc.  Perhaps we could watch the movie independently, or as a group somehow (too bad I found out about the showing at the Harvard Archive too late).  Or just delve into the whole topic of epistemology and its relationship to reality. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Memento_(film" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be run by Karen. More info to come....&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen</member_name><member_id>1755369</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1295286374000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Inquisitive Minds</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>InquisitiveMinds</urlname><id>1441172</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Inquisitive Minds</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292899574000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Knowledge and Memory</name><id>15786295</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295200800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/InquisitiveMinds/events/15786295/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/5/global_20394549.jpeg</photo_url></item>