<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Oliver Stone’s new documentary SOUTH OF THE BORDER&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$7.75 - mantinee&lt;br /&gt;$9.75 - after 5:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your tickets here: &lt;a href="https://www.vendini.com/ticket-software.html?e=7ee5df95d98a7e38435077a1321fd902&amp;amp;t=tix" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.vendini.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Opens Friday October 1st in BOSTON, MA!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BRATTLE THEATRE&lt;br /&gt;40 BRATTLE STREET, CAMBRIDGE, MA 02138  |  617.876.6837&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DON’T MISS THE GREAT Q&amp;amp;A MODERATED BY THE NATIONAL LAWYERS GUILD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WITH:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iris Gomez (moderator) - Boston Immigration Attorney; Member of the National Lawyers Guild, Massachusetts Chapter&lt;br /&gt;Yana Garcia - 3rd Year Law Student at Northeastern University School of Law&lt;br /&gt;Mark Weisbrot - Co-Writer of &amp;quot;South of the Border&amp;quot; (with Tariq Ali), Economist, Scholar&lt;br /&gt;Gregory Wilpert - Consultant on &amp;quot;South of the Border,&amp;quot; Scholar, Writer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Synopsis: There’s a revolution underway in South America, but most of the world doesn’t know it. Oliver Stone sets out on a road trip across five countries to explore the social and political movements as well as the mainstream media’s misperception of South America while interviewing seven of its elected presidents.  In casual conversations with Presidents Hugo Chávez (Venezuela), Evo Morales (Bolivia), Lula da Silva (Brazil), Cristina Kirchner  (Argentina), as well as her husband and ex-President N&amp;#279;stor Kirchner, Fernando Lugo  (Paraguay), Rafael Correa (Ecuador), and Raúl Castro  (Cuba), Stone gains unprecedented access and sheds new light upon the exciting transformations in the region.&lt;br /&gt; ••••••••••••&lt;br /&gt;Since hitting the big screen, SOUTH OF THE BORDER has been generating some heat!&lt;br /&gt;·  FAIR's Peter Hart weighs in on right-wing journalists and their coverage of the film and in particular the Larry Rohter of The New York Times.&lt;br /&gt;·  David Corn in Mother Jones, 'Why the director's controversial new documentary, South of the Border, is generating so much heat.'&lt;br /&gt;·  FOX &amp;amp; Friends lashed out and attacked “South of the Border,” spreading outrageous ignorance in the guise of news.&lt;br /&gt;·  Activists in Los Angeles mobilized to counter a protest of the film organized by the Venezuelan opposition -  Anne Thompson/Indiewire and Steve Pond/The Wrap report.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distributed by:&lt;br /&gt;Cinema Libre Studio&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285980344000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285353380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oliver Stone’s new documentary SOUTH OF THE BORDER</name><id>14884234</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285975800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/14884234/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/3/8/global_18196152.jpeg</photo_url></item>