<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>301 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.342918</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Pops Symphony Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>2060881</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085686</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.artsboston.org/sites/artsboston.org/images/event/51911/keithlockhart_holidayx95_medium.jpg" alt=" " width="95" height="95" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for a festive Holiday Pops Concert featuring the Boston Pops. We have excellent first balcony, 2nd row&amp;nbsp;seats for a Sunday afternoon performance of the traditional seasonal concert series. The detailed program is not yet available, but it always features a combination of seasonal music, holiday sing alongs, and, of course, a visit from Santa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll gather before hand for brunch at &lt;strong&gt;Pho Basil, 177 Mass Ave (near Berkley College) at 1:00&lt;/strong&gt;. The restaurant has a moderately priced&amp;nbsp;menu with very good food (recently reviewed in Boston Globe). Each patron is responsible for thier own tab; Paypal &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; accepted for this event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symphony Hall is a ten minute walk from the restaurant. The concert starts at 3:00 pm. Concert tickets will be handed out at the brunch. Based on past experiences, we cannot hand out tickets at Symphony Hall. Contact Mark Carrig if you cannot come to the brunch. We have only a limited number of tickets so plan ahead and register early. This event will sell out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket cost: $80.00.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Payments must be received by&amp;nbsp;Dec. 15th&amp;nbsp;or while tickets are still available. Your payment is your reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symphony Hall is located at the intersection of Massachestts and Huntington Avenues in Boston. Brasserie Jo is in the Colonade Hotel, 120 Huntington Ave., about 2 blocks away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearest T stops are Prudential (for the restaurant) and Symphony (for the concert) on the Green Line, "E" branch only. Nearest parking is at the Prudential Center Garage, which offers a discount if you show your concert ticket when leaving.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Brassarie Jo's for brunch prior tro the show</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324323817000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323540282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Start the Season with a visit to the Boston Pops!</name><id>44035532</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324231200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/44035532/</event_url></item>