<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hi All, seems a lot of us wanted to attend this AOPA/ASF Seminar in Bedford. This is the night of our usual meeting, but we have changed it to accommodate this event. I expect there will be 200 or so pilots at this meeting. They usually have some good door prizes also :-) (Is Murphy going???? ) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maybe we can meet at the Terminal and drive down to Bedford together. A Drive-Out! Let's see how this will work. Maybe have a late dinner there. It's about 45 minutes from KFIT ( to drive aarrgghh) and the meeting is at 6:00. If we plan on meeting around 4:30 or so, we should be fine. A head count might be good so we don't leave without anyone.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wrecks in the City &lt;br /&gt;Wrecks in the City When an aircraft goes down in a city or neighborhood, the community interest is often considerable. The media- and in some cases local politicians-get involved. In short, accidents in populated areas have repercussions well beyond the safety of the pilot. Thought about what you'd do in an emergency? We'll look at:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The challenges of urban flight  &lt;br /&gt;In-depth case studies, including ATC tapes  &lt;br /&gt;This seminar is being held at the CRASH COURSE 2009 Event in Bedford, MA only. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Safety Seminars  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pilots are interested in safety. Safe pilots attend the AOPA Air Safety Foundation's more than 200 free safety seminars it offers every year throughout the United States. Everybody's welcome!&lt;br /&gt;Wings Program... Registration is not required. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;March 10, 2009                    &lt;a href="http://www.aopa.org/asf/seminars/seminar.cfm?FA=SS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aopa.org/a...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Time: 6:00-8:30pm &lt;br /&gt;Wrecks in the City  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bedford, MA   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DOUBLETREE HOTEL BOSTON/BEDFORD GLEN &lt;br /&gt;44 MIDDLESEX TURNPIKE &lt;br /&gt;BEDFORD, MA 01730&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>charley valera</member_name><member_id>4792795</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Louise Anderson</member_name><member_id>6714056</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237328210000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Pilots and Co-Pilots</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>FitchburgPilots</urlname><id>1060828</id><group_lat>42.5800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Fitchburg Pilots Association/EAA Chapter 1454 Meetup Site</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235310889000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AOPA Air Safety Foundation Meeting in Bedford (not KBED)</name><id>9795070</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1236717000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FitchburgPilots/events/9795070/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/5/9/global_4880393.jpeg</photo_url></item>