<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Prepare for this day and the next (Sunday, Feb. 3) by signing up as 'Precinct Leader' at ronpaul2008.com under the 'Grassroots Program'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't done much till now for the Paul campaign, or you have done a lot, the precinct work is the most important single task you can do before the primary. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And it's easy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once you register on the site, there is a lot of information and videos. Read through and watch them if you have time. But don't get caught up or be put off by them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only information you really need is the list of voters in your precinct all within walking distance of your home. Download the 'Precinct Walking List' and print it out and use it to find, first, the Republicans and, secondly, the independent voters who live near you. Then take a walk around to leave literature at their homes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need literature post a request on the email list to find someone nearby with extras or download literature from the official campaign site and make photocopies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure the literature says the most important thing. 'Vote Ron Paul for President, Tuesday, February 5' . Attach an extra page if you have to. This is a good leaflet to use: &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.c.." target="_blank"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's all there is to it. And it is the most important work you can do for the Ron Paul campaign in Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And you only really need to do it one weekend on the weekend of Feb. 2 and 3, either on one day or two. That's it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sign up at www.ronpaul2008.com under the 'Grassroots' logo.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ureneck</member_name><member_id>4211251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1202140896000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201353077000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Precinct Canvassing for Primary Day</name><id>7198828</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201968000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/7198828/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/7/global_1551159.jpeg</photo_url></item>