<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>493 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01510</zip><lat>42.417632</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>My cell: 978-270-2319</phone><name>Dunkin Donuts</name><city>Clinton</city><id>1225852</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.688822</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us to investigate an interesting site in Clinton MA: an abandoned train tunnel that has many reports of paranormal activity. The line that included the tunnel and trestle was built in 1903 by the Boston &amp;amp; Maine Railroad as part of a four-mile extension from West Berlin. Passenger and freight was hauled on this line for a while. Freight traffic dwindled in the 1930s and the passenger service was stopped in 1958 and the track was abandoned. At one time, it was the second longest tunnel in Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out this article about the tunnel in the Telegraph:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.telegram.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20060807/NEWS/608070345/1101" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.telegram.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many paranormal teams have captured evidence of paranormal activity: strange lights, EVPs, disembodied voices.  If you are interested in investigating outdoor sites, I recommend this one as good practice for separating natural from paranormal activity. Because of the length and shape of the tunnel, every sound echos, making it hard to determine the source. The tunnel constantly drips water, making sounds that can further distort what you are hearing. It's definitely atmospheric.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've investigated twice. The first time I didn't experience much at all--one K2 hit as I was leaving, plus the usual battery drain I always seem to get. The second time was quite different. I heard a disembodied voice, and another investigator's equipment bag was dragged several inches. From this, and from reports by other teams, activity seems to be sporadic, but when it's hot it's hot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm placing a cap of 15 people on the investigation because the site isn't conducive to large groups investigating (noise pollution). However, if enough people are interested, I'd be happy to schedule a second night there. If the first meetup is filled, just sign up on the waiting list and you'll be part of a second night's investigation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Well meet at Dunkin Donuts, 493 Main Street, Clinton MA.&lt;br /&gt;Get directions from Google Maps: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=493+Main+St,+Clinton,+MA+01510&amp;amp;sll=42.414649,-71.688151&amp;amp;sspn=0.013814,0.037122&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=493+Main+St,+Clinton,+Worcester,+Massachusetts+01510&amp;amp;z=16" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We need to consolidate into as few cars as possible because of parking restrictions at the site.&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: There's a short but fairly steep climb from the street to the tunnel entrance. Be prepared for a bit of a climb.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: We'll meet at 7:30 in the Dunkin Donuts parking lot. The investigation will begin by 8pm and last approximately 90 minutes (longer if we're experiencing good activity).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: Flashlight (it's dark in there), waterproof shoes (it's wet in there), your equipment, and extra batteries.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272238501000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269372927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clinton Abandoned Train Tunnel</name><id>12970528</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272065400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/12970528/</event_url></item>