<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-990-7411</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213795</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join Us for this month's conscious movie when we will be featuring Nuclear Tipping Point. This film is a conversation with four men intimately involved in American diplomacy and national security over the last four decades.  &lt;br /&gt;Former Secretary of State George Schultz, former Secretary of State Henry Kissinger, former Secretary of Defense Bill Perry and former Senator Sam Nunn share the personal experiences that led them to support a world free of nuclear weapons and the steps needed to get there. Their efforts reframed the global debate on nuclear issues and, according to the New York Times, "Sent waves through the global policy establishment."  &lt;br /&gt;Our January Conscious Movie supports the Nuclear Security Project to raise awareness about nuclear threats and to help build support for the urgent actions needed to reduce nuclear dangers.  &lt;br /&gt;If you have ever walked out of a movie theater affected by a powerful film, movie nights at the Center of Light are for you! These events provide a way for people to talk about inspiring movies on a deeper level and how they affect our lives, our attitudes, our perceptions. It&amp;rsquo;s also a great opportunity to meet like-minded people!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296349850000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294330274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conscious Movie Meetup for January - Nuclear Tipping Point</name><id>15943532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296345600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/15943532/</event_url></item>