<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>393 Charles St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02904</zip><lat>41.845051</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401 331 3000</phone><name>Pearl Restaurant</name><city>Providence</city><id>699190</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.418757</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was just informed TODAY about an amazing little thing called &amp;quot;Providence Restaurant Week&amp;quot;. It is a 2 week long event where restaurants offer a 3 course pre-fixe menu's for the awesome price of $29.95 per person. You can find out more here for menu's, locations and other sorts of interesting bits about Providence Restaurant Week. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because I thought this would be a fabulous way to try some of the &amp;quot;pricier&amp;quot; Rhode Island hot spots, I made a bunch of reservations all over for 4 people per sitting. Also, it will be a great way to try and find new places to visit as a group. I am going to try and attend most events, but should you want to go, and not see my name on an event, just let the host know the reservation is under Abigail. All events are on a first come, first serve basis, and all restaurants will have separate event postings. Because it is so close to the event dates, and the events are soooo small, no contact no shows prior to the event are not allowed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't worry about the dollar meetup fee I usually charge. Because these events are in addition to the regular schedule, I don't think it's fair to you to have to pay it.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216508787000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214887346000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence Restaurant Week- Pearl- CONFIRMED reservation</name><id>8251605</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216335600000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/8251605/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/e/global_4646382.jpeg</photo_url></item>