<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 Woodland St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.202816</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Art Studio 360</name><city>Holliston </city><id>1014146</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.422827</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;ATC JAM SESSION:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us for an afternoon of artistic &amp;quot;jamming&amp;quot;! We'll spend the afternoon exploring these special ATCs that are created by multiple artists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Saturday, April 24th 1pm to ??? - really, we'll stay as late as anyone wants to stay. :) Arrive and leave when you like. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AGENDA:&lt;/b&gt; Fairly free-form; grab a set of ATCs, work on them, and pass them. Much like the Jam Jar available at most of our regular meetups, we'll have sets of matching backgrounds that each person adds a small touch to assembly-line style, with the result being a set of matching or identical ATCs, one for each artist to keep. We'll have sets of 3 as usually found in the Jam Jar, and we'll experiment with doing sets of 4 and 5 and see how they come out when more artists play. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Around 2:00 I'll do a quick demo of how to make backgrounds, and how to get 10 ATCs out of an 8.5&amp;quot; x 11&amp;quot; piece of cardstock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom. Take-out or sit-down food and beverages nearby. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $10 per person, regardless of how long you stay. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt; Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups and their guests (18+ only, please). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;---Whatever supplies you'd like you use, but space is limited so try to keep it to what will fit in one plastic grocery bag. (Plus I've found that jams work best with a relatively limited selection of tools and toys.) And remember; speed is part of the fun of jams, so slow-drying paints or inks may not be best.&lt;br /&gt;---A few sets of &amp;quot;starter backgrounds&amp;quot;, so that we can dive right in. (Not required, but recommended.) &lt;br /&gt;---Snacks and or beverages to share (optional)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;A few basic supplies--scissors, glue, tape, etc. -- are available for loan.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/b&gt; You must RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. You must RSVP for your guests as well. If your plans (or your guests’ plans) change, PLEASE update your RSVP accordingly so that someone can take your place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If we need to cancel due to weather or for any other reason, we'll post a message here AND e-mail anyone who's RSVP'd as far in advance as possible. For your own protection, we suggest that you check the Web site before leaving the house. Looking forward to seeing you!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>signs will be posted... but just follow the sound of art being made!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsi</member_name><member_id>5074581</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272301712000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271302445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Special Day of ATC Jams!</name><id>13188082</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272128400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/13188082/</event_url></item>