<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>339 Breakfast Hill Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.011097</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Breakfast Hill Golf Club</name><city>Greenland</city><id>2630111</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.817207</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Update 8/30/2012:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi guys,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can't add a third tee time here until much later in the day, so I'm keeping this one to just the two tee times. If anyone needs to cancel, please try to do so 24 hours in advance in order to give someone on the Waiting List enough notice to join. Thanks! - Michelle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone is not attending/volunteering at the Deutsche Bank or otherwise going out of town this Labor Day weekend, I have two tee times (11:51am and 12:00pm) at Breakfast Hill in Greenland, NH.  18 holes with cart only $52.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We played here last year and had a great time. It's Rated one of the Best Places to Play by Golf Digest. Great 19th hole as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Course description from their website:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Breakfast Hill Golf Club sits on a piece of land which has been family owned for over two centuries. In 1997, plans were made to build an upscale, public golf course. Once serving as working New Hampshire farmland until 1956, a long-lived dream became a reality when a championship 18-hole layout was completed on June 30, 2000.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Quaintly nestled under our trademark soaring pines sits an upscale public golf course still premature in age yet in its prime amongst the area’s best layouts. Breakfast Hill Golf Club invites you to experience a true New England golf experience unlike any other. Designed by renowned golf course architect Brian Silva, Breakfast Hill rests on 170 acres of family owned land dating back over 250 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;Our championship par 71 layout has consistently been ranked a top five course by Golf Week magazine as one of America’s best daily fee facilities. As recently as 2008, Golf Digest awarded Breakfast Hill four stars as one of their Best Places to Play.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;The practice facility is one of the most all-inclusive in the area. Every aspect of one’s precision can be tested and enhanced. The driving range includes four target greens with varying distances. Included in our practice facilities, a sprawling 10,000 square foot putting green, a favorite destination for practice or play, can boost one’s short game to perfection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333333"&gt;&lt;a href="http://breakfasthill.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3987cb"&gt;http://breakfasthill.com/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>12663379</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1346526002000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Golfers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>golf-260</urlname><id>1127024</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2200012207</group_lon><name>The Boston and Beyond Golf Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346252180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast Hill Golf Club</name><id>79900462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346514300000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/golf-260/events/79900462/</event_url></item>