<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Tuttle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01880</zip><lat>42.502338</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Laurie's 909</name><city>Wakefield</city><id>10253922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/d/2/event_196279922.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/5/6/event_205767222.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Update your RSVPs. Chuck Korb, the Founder and Co-Organizer of the Sabermetrics, Scouting &amp;amp; Science of Baseball Conference for the Jimmy Fund will be joining us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join the Red Sox Natives and other invited groups on the first day of Spring for "Talking Baseball - 2013 Season Preview" along with a live performance by Howie Newman on  the Third Wednesday After Work  at Laurie's 9:09 Steakhouse and Raw Bar in Wakefield on Wednesday, March 20 at 6:00pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Talking Baseball - The 2013 Season Preview" will be hosted by Bob from Laurie's 909 and multiple members of the Red Sox Natives.  All are invited to participate in this informal and fun gathering topped off by entertainment from Howie Newman at approximately 7:30pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Newman is a sportswriter, baseball color analyst, singer and song writer viewed as one of the most engaging performers on the New England folk circuit combining music, comedy, and audience participation to provide a unique entertainment experience. He has released 2 CDs of Baseball songs including (Why Did You Go, Johnny Damon?), (Wait Til Next Year),  (Astro Turf), (Utility Infielder Blues), (Mendoza Line), (It's The End of The Curse and We Know It), (Doug Mientkiewicz), (Traded) and (Blasted In The Bleachers). For more information please visit &lt;a href="http://www.howienewman.com"&gt;http://www.howienewman.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What will our invited guests talk about?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Terry Francona's Book " Francona - The Red Sox Years" led by Natives Author Steve Masse&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Baseball Player Development led by Native Coach Henry Munevar of Henry's Baseball Club&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Baseball Operations led by our own Native Mike who has worked for a minor league team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Who are the new 2013 Red Sox and what can we expect from them led by Jon and Frank&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Avascular Necrosis (the Mike Napoli Hip Injury) as explained by Native who has it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. 2013 Predictions??? As we watch a NESN replay of the Red Sox/Yankees afternoon Spring Training game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for additional Baseball people to join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no cover!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be occupying both the Penny Lane and Trackside Raw Bars at Laurie's so invite other Sports Fans and your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for appetizers (the fried chicken and beer special), dinner, a cocktail or two or three, socializing and more. $1.00 Oysters are available from 5-7pm while they last. If you have a group of people that want a table reservation for dinner please call Laurie's at 781-246-1909 and make a reservation. For information on Laurie's 909 and the menu go to http://&lt;a href="http://www.lauries.com/"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get there when you can and stay as long as you are able. You are more than welcome to show up for all or just part of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Invited Groups include:1. Red Sox Natives (Frank &amp;amp; Jon), 2. Boston Happy Hour (Tonya), 3. North Shore Womens Group (Maria), 4. North Shore Separated &amp;amp; Divorced Group (Maria), 5. Social Fun (Biaggio) and 6. Wakefield Weeknights &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this will be your first time meeting the Red Sox Natives Crew and the other groups check out the photos of those who RSVP Yes so you can find the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to maintain your own tab or pay as you order and tip your servers. However, if you sit at a group table a group bill may be provided so please communicate with your server when ordering. Credit Cards will be held by the servers at Laurie's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie's 909 Steakhouse and Raw Bar is Wakefield's newest restaurant and Bar with live entertainment several nights per week and Tuesday night Trivia with Morgan White Jr. from WBZ Radio. Laurie's is located at the Wakefield Commuter Rail Train Station in Wakefield. The Reading and Haverhill Commuter Rail trains stop at Laurie's. Trains leave North Station Boston at 5:15, 5:35, 5:55, 6:20 and 7:20pm. It's a 20 minute ride to the Wakefield stop in front of Laurie's. Trains depart from Wakefield to Boston at 8:05, 9:09, 10:19 and 10:59pm. Laurie's is easily accessible within 10 minutes from Routes 128, 93, 28 and 1. Free parking is available in two lots on Tuttle Street, in the Church parking lot if there are no activities there, and on street after 5:30pm. Check out the MBTA or Hop Stop for additional public transit options including the less reliable/frequent 136 and 137 bus lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the "Penny Lane" Bar, the 9:09 and Beatles references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information at http://&lt;a href="http://www.lauries909.com"&gt;www.lauries909.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be occupying both bars!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363888791000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Socializing</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>wakefieldweeknights</urlname><id>1270802</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Wakefield Weeknights and More!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361116708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Talking Baseball - 2013 Season Preview" with Live Performance by Howie Newman</name><id>105006912</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363816800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/wakefieldweeknights/events/105006912/</event_url></item>