<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Near above Address</address_2><address_1>298 Carlisle Rd. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01730</zip><lat>42.498428</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Carlisle Rd. Boat Launch</name><city>Bedford</city><id>772864</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.306763</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Level 1 - Open to all kayak types as well as canoes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a leisurely foliage paddle on the Concord River from Bedford MA to Concord.  The Concord River is ideal for small boats, and the Bedford boat launch at the Carlisle Road bridge is a popular launching spot for canoes, rowboats &amp;amp; kayaks. The Concord River is a placid river with a light breeze; it swings around corners spreading out to submerge the bottoms of trees. On the sides, there are trees and bushes growing up out of the water, and if you are watching, you'll see turtles, beavers, and many different kinds of birds. There is a wildlife refuge on both sides with posted signs... great for nature watching. Paddling up river, we will eventually reach the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/mima/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Minute Man National Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. We can beach the boats at the North Bridge where the spark of the American Revolution ignited a war, walk around or sit on a bench and have lunch. There are Historians around the park that will tell you all about it, as well as the start of literary revolution with a new Western philosophy called Transcendentalism. Ralph Waldo Emerson, Henry David Thoreau, and a few others lived in Concord.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This paddle will last approx. 5 hrs with a round trip distance of 9 miles.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for kayakers - parking is limited</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Neil Sheehan</member_name><member_id>7739813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255360295000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>NE Seacoast Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastPaddlers</urlname><id>1238731</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Paddlers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250858727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Concord River Paddle</name><id>11164674</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255186800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastPaddlers/events/11164674/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/7/global_5643399.jpeg</photo_url></item>