<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 and 224 Anderson Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670235</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station / The Resilience Hub</name><city>Portland</city><id>11570052</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256172</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the May 2013 Transition Challenge, the facilitation workgroup of Transition Startups in Portland is hosting a series of Thursday evening events!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This night we are watching &lt;strong&gt;First Earth&lt;/strong&gt;. Housing and Shelter, Building and Supply are sometimes more about set in their ways industry and political systems then about design consideration or for resilience. This film turns a lot of your run of the mill construction and neighborhood assumptions sideways. What fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We hope to hold a conversation this night about these infrastructure pieces as means for informing future transition work in Portland.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Knee deep in conventional construction? Hope to see you builders, designers and&lt;/span&gt; architects &lt;span&gt;here!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Sitting on a marine clay deposit? We have someone for you to meet!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Health conscious concerned about building materials? We want to talk with you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Does your urban or suburban neighborhood need some community and&lt;/span&gt; artistic &lt;span&gt;pizzaz? Lets collaborate!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/d/0/event_233932432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here is some more about this film: "This is a documentary about the movement towards a massive paradigm shift for shelter -- building healthy houses in the old ways, out of the very earth itself, and living together like in the old days, by recreating villages. It is a sprawling film, shot on location from the West Coast to West Africa. An audiovisual manifesto filmed over the course of 4 years and 4 continents, FIRST EARTH makes the case that earthen homes are the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/6/6/event_233932582.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; healthiest housing in the world; and that since it still takes a village to raise a healthy child, it is incumbent upon us to transform our suburban sprawl into eco-villages, a new North American dream."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;6:30 We gather 7:00 announcements and film. Facilitated discussion to follow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;$3 donation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is coordinated and facilitated by the facilitation workgroup of the new Transition Start ups in Portland Meet up Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please join that meet up too at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Transition-Towns-Start-ups-in-Portland/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Transition-Towns-Start-ups-in-Portland/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel Lyn</member_name><member_id>4529129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368150555000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368027015000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taking the Transition Challenge: Movie Night Featuring First Earth</name><id>118367472</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368138600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/118367472/</event_url></item>