<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From Negaholic to The King or Queen of Positivity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Life is a journey, not a destination. Choose to get off the dirt path and onto the yellow brick road.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Debby Hoffman Adair&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Audience participation highlights this phenomenal program as Debby brings to life what it truly means to be POSITIVE. For the past 23 years, Debby has been on a personal journey to leave negativity behind, find joy in a sometimes not so positive world and empower herself to lead the life she was destined to have. What she has come to know about the balance between positive and negative behavior will inspire you to take responsibility for your own attitude and become your true, positive self. Thought provoking, fun and filled with information, participants will be able to: understand the dynamics of attitudes, what to do about the &amp;quot;negative&amp;quot; people in their lives, learn new easy-to-do ways toward positive communication and how to remain positive in the fact of life's difficulties. True empowerment comes to those who know the secrets of positivity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;President Elect of the New England Chapter of National Speakers Association, Debby Hoffman Adair is known as “a different perspective” when it comes to sharing ideas to create a positive impact.  A professional speaker and author for over 17 years, Debby is a solutionist, helping individuals, businesses and organizations transforming problems into opportunities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A serial entrepreneur with experience ranging from advertising to membership development, she is the owner of Positive Results Seminars, In the Presence of Positive Women, a membership based organization dedicated to helping women empower themselves, founding member of Jigsaw Consulting (committed to helping you change your world, one piece at a time) and her new company, created with her husband Rick Adair called Beginner’s Mind – Speaking – Consulting – Coaching.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suzanne Larocque</member_name><member_id>9376325</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297206770000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294200577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>January Breakfast Meeting- From Negaholic to The King or Queen of Positivity</name><id>15924475</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295527500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/15924475/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/b/global_20619451.jpeg</photo_url></item>