<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 N Plains Hwy</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06492</zip><lat>41.470514</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 888) 855-4716</phone><name>Trail of Terror</name><city>Wallingford</city><id>1077001</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.818379</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

$10.00 entrance fee... first come, first serve basis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When does the Trail open? &lt;br /&gt;

The Trail opens at approximately 7pm on September 29th, October 5, 6, 7 | 12, 13, 14 | 19, 20, 21 | 26, 27, 28 &amp;amp; 30th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How late is the Trail open until? &lt;br /&gt;

The Trail is open until 11pm Fridays and Saturdays and until 10pm on Sundays. However the Trail may sell out of tickets for the night and close the gates earlier than the times posted. All guests who are present before we close the line off to new guests or arrive with online speed pass tickets will enter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does the Trail donate all their proceeds and are all the staff volunteers? &lt;br /&gt;

It is true, the outrageous staff of the Trail of Terror is made up entirely of volunteers. Our staff are also as dedicated to community charities as they are to maniacal merrymaking. Over the years, the Trail donated $500,000 to the Wallingford, CT chapter of the Red Cross. The Trail now benefits the Wallingford Emergency Shelter, works closely with C.R.E.W. (Community Revitalization Efforts of Wallingford) to support students who provide humanitarian aid in areas where it is most needed as well as donating to other various local charities in need. See our Donations website for a complete list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens during unfavorable weather? &lt;br /&gt;

The Trail of Terror is an outdoor event, unfavorable weather conditions such as rain, high winds or thunderstorms can cause unsafe conditions for both you our guests and the creatures of the Trail. In event of a weather closing an announcement will be posted on trailofterror.com, Facebook and Twitter by 5pm of that night. Prepaid tickets for canceled nights can be transferred to another night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are costumes, masks or makeup allowed? &lt;br /&gt;

No, any guest that enters the Trail of Terror wearing a costume, mask or makeup will be asked to remove these items. If they are unable to comply to that request they will not be allowed to enter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can I send someone to save a place in line for my group if we are arriving late? &lt;br /&gt;

No, the sending of a small group to hold places in line for a larger group is strictly prohibited. The line to enter the Trail is formed in a first come first served basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What should I wear? &lt;br /&gt;

The Trail is an outdoor event that takes place during the month of October. We recommend clothing that you will be comfortable in for a few hours outside. You will be walking in the woods so comfortable footwear is highly recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have condition X, Y or Z should I come to the Trail? &lt;br /&gt;

You should not enter the Trail of Terror if you suffer from any physical or mental ailments such as asthma, heart condition, vertigo, seizures, respiratory condition, or any type of intense phobia or if you are pregnant. Please see our list of posted warnings for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Trail is an outdoor event that uses special effects, theatrical smoke, strobing lights, loud music/sound effects, unsteady/uneven ground, etc. If you believe that any of these will cause you undo physical or mental harm please do not come to the Trail. If you have specific questions don't hesitate to contact us with them at info@trailofterror.com. Please allow for an up to one week reply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trail of Terror guests please respect the neighborhood. &lt;br /&gt;

 **** Please notice parking notifications. Cars will be towed at owners expense ****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be advised that the PNA park is now charging $5 per car to park on their grounds, this fee is not affiliated with the Trail of Terror.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>simone</member_name><member_id>7013797</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350604055000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346979683000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Venture through the TRAIL OF TERROR!!!</name><id>81233622</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350252000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/81233622/</event_url></item>