<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Online</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>Online</city><id>4355392</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Worcester Alliance of Photographers: Call To Photographers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Signs of Life"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A Call for Photographs: The Worcester Alliance of Photographers is sending out a call to all Photographers for our 4th The City Hall Gallery Show. Theme for this call is: Signs of Worcester&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are many, many signs around Worcester that are interesting and unique to our little piece of the world. So we are issuing a call to photographers to submit images that show off Worcester's interesting signage or unique type styles or any "writing" you may find around Worcester County. Look for the endangered species of signage; the hand painted, the monumental, the pre -fab vinyl lettering, the plastic, the neon or bulbous, or computer- generated signage. Look for anything with amazing type, lettering, or simplicity. We urge you to notice and document the signs you see. Submit your images to the Worcester Alliance of Photographers Call to Artists on our web site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The theme for this exhibit will be Signs of Worcester County.&lt;/span&gt; Submitted photographs must have something to do with signs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Submissions for judging will be due on or before 6/27/12 at noon.&lt;/span&gt; Images must be in JPG format (sRGB) and sized to be approximately 5 by 7 at 300ppi. Please keep physical file sizes at/under 1MB. Upload your image submissions directly to our online gallery:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/8465902/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/photos/8465902/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image file names should be in the format: LastName_FirstName_ImageTitle.jpg (e.g., Smith_John_ThePerfectPicture.jpg). This is how we identify who's image is who's.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Selected images will appear in our gallery on 7/11/12.&lt;/span&gt; It is up to you to check the online gallery to see if your image has been chosen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our frames are 16x24 in size. This means- All accepted photographs must be matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions - we will accept white mats only. You must come to the framing party on August 4th at the Worcester Library to frame your own matted pieces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are responsible for labeling the artwork on display with artist name, title and price (if your image is being offered for sale). So you need to supply this information at the framing party.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rules:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Each artist may submit up to 3 images via website gallery for judging (no fee).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All artwork submitted for hanging must be matted (white) to 16x24 mats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Indicate whether artwork is being offered for sale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Purchases will be handled by WAP and Worcester Windows.&lt;/span&gt; WW will collect a 20% commission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sold work must remain on display for the duration of the exhibit.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Insurance for artwork is provided.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Schedule summary:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;6/27/2012 (noon) Image submission deadline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;7/15/2012 Gallery updated with selected images.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;8/4/2012 Framing party at libray artwork due.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;8/13 or 8/20/2012 (5 PM) Opening reception.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;8/13/12 to 11/1/2012 Show is open to the public.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For more information about Worcester Alliance of Photographers, please visit our website: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/photo-22" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/photo-22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Online http://www.meetup.com/photo-22</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340824262000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337965258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>City Hall Gallery Call: Signs of Worcester</name><id>66327862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340812800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/66327862/</event_url></item>