<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Wachusett Mountain is about an hour's drive from Boston.   September is a wonderful time to visit since the hawk migration is in full force.  We will meet at the visitor center at 10:45am.  Please note the walk to the top is not especially difficult but could be more challenging than other walks.  My plan is too walk/hike for about 2.5 hours so please bring some snacks and plenty of water.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LUNCH: my mom who lives nearby has offered to have a cookout at her house.  She will have drinks, salad, hamburgers, veggie burgers, and hot dogs. Please bring a dish to share. If you have a cooler, please bring it on the walk and say so in your rsvp.  Also, there is a grocery store within 5 mintues of my mom's house if you prefer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3,000-acre Wachusett Mountain State Reservation surrounds the summit and offers a wealth of natural and recreational resources. The Reservation's natural resources include forests, alpine meadows, ponds, streams, fields, and even a perched bog. Recreational opportunities abound at the reservation including hiking, nature study, hawk watching, picnicking, and skiing. The Reservation offers 17 miles of hiking and walking trails, including 3.9 miles of the Midstate Trail, which runs from Ashburnham to the Rhode Island border. Mountain Road stretches to the John Hitchcock Visitor's Center at the summit, a short distance from the Wachusett Mountain Ski Area, which is the largest in eastern Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/wach.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch:  TBA &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1190731536000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1189021732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wachusett Mountain state reservation - advanced walk/hike</name><id>6303810</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1190558700000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6303810/</event_url></item>