<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Hike Description #1: Ascend via Blueberry Ledge Trail/Rollins Trail to&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Mt Whiteface&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;, descend via McCrillis Trail/Flat Mountain Pond &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Difficulty/hike rating: strenuous &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Mileage: 9.4m RT &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Elevation gain: 3,050 ft &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;AMC Booktime: 6:15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Hike Description #2: ascend via Blueberry Ledge Trail/Rollins Trail to&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Mt Whiteface&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;, Rollins Trail/Dicey's Mill Trail to Mt Passaconaway, descend via Dicey's Mill &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Difficulty/hike rating: strenuous &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Mileage: 11.9m RT &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Elevation gain: 3,800 ft &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;AMC Booktime: 7:50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on feedback from the participants, I've decided to expand the plan to be flexible enough to tag both summits if conditions are good, and the group feels like we can do it, or to descend from Whiteface w/o going down the Blueberry Ledge Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will spot a car (or 2) at the Flat Mountain Pond Trailhead on the way to Ferncroft. If we do just Whiteface, it'll be waiting for us. If we do both peaks, we just retrieve the car after returning to Ferncroft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tend to hike slower than booktime, and stop frequently on ascents. I have no clue what the trail conditions will be like, and will be checking conditions all week. This hike might be barebooted, might need crampons, or snowshoes. Participants should plan to bring all of the above, at least in the car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mt Whiteface is my primary goal, with Mt Passaconaway as an added bonus. Last time I was on Passaconaway I really didn't get to appreciate the summit, because it was 10 degrees and blowing hard. I'm expecting this weekend will be better than that. If there is significant snow on the Rollins Trail on the ridge between the summits, that 8 hour estimate will turn into 10+ easily, making this a no-go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RSVP questions are NOT optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting time is flexible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Our goal is to start together as a group, hike together and finish together as a group. A group can be as small as 3-4 people, but no one should hike alone. Adhere to the HikeSafe guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE. We rely of the RSVP's to get a true headcount and the hikers rely on the leaders to communicate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;You are responsible for yourself, so be prepared:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;1. With knowledge and gear. Become self reliant by learning about the terrain, conditions, local weather and your equipment before you start.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;2. To leave your plans. Tell someone where you are going, the trails you are hiking, when you will return and your emergency plans.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;3. To stay together. When you start as a group, hike as a group, end as a group. Pace your hike to the slowest person.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;4. To turn back. Weather changes quickly in the mountains. Fatigue and unexpected conditions can also affect your hike. Know your limitations and when to postpone your hike. The mountains will be there another day.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;5. For emergencies. Even if you are headed out for just an hour, an injury, severe weather or a wrong turn could become life threatening. Don’t assume you will be rescued; know how to rescue yourself&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;# Be knowledgeable of what to prepare for.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;# Contact the event organizer about any concerns and event challenges.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;# Every participant needs to come fully prepared.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;# Disclose any medical conditions before the event.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;# pack to survive the event and for "what if".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with our Disclaimer. Participation in an event is certifying that you are fit and able to accomplish an event. All hikers will hike at their own pace. By attending events, you and your guests agree to the terms above. Any unqualified participant can be denied participation in the group.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Junky blue Toyota Corolla w/MA plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>JCarter</member_name><member_id>11575712</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335195104000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334365086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Whiteface (and maybe Passaconaway)</name><id>60504952</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335013200000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/60504952/</event_url></item>