<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>796 Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.330025</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Samadhi Integral</name><city>Newton Centre</city><id>1236125</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.194648</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Most of us are familiar with the 2-D Wilber-Combs matrix.  States along a horizontal axis (gross, subtle, causal, witness, and nondual) and structures along a vertical access (premodern, modern, postmodern, integral).  As Ken Wilber and Allen Combs first made clear with their model -- &lt;b&gt;one can have a state experience at any structure of development.  One will then interpret the experience through the lens of developmental complexity.&lt;/b&gt;  However, there's a small problem....&amp;quot;Witness&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Nondual&amp;quot; are not states.  They are new vantage points of awareness -- a subjective shift of where awareness is &amp;quot;coming from&amp;quot;.  One can be in a personal vantage point, a witness vantage point, or a nondual vantage point, and simultaneously have a state experience of gross, subtle, or causal.  This talk will articulate the very latest in integral thinking.  A 3-D Wilber combs matrix will emerge -- States, Structures, Vantage Points; adding more depth and clarity to the integral model of spiritual unfolding.  Please join us for this provocative discussion led by Dustin DiPerna on some new ways of considering spiritual experience and development. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dustin DiPerna currently serves as the Director of Integral Affairs at the World Council of Religious Leaders. He is passionate about the ways in which religion might be used as a positive force in the world for social good and collective change. In particular, Dustin uses a tool called &amp;quot;religious diplomacy&amp;quot; to promote cultural and religious understanding around the globe. In addition to his work at the World Council of Religious Leaders, Dustin is also pursuing a Masters of Liberal Arts degree in Religion at Harvard University. He recently completed writing his first book entitled Developmental Religious Pluralism: A Brief Introduction to Integral Religious Studies, to be released in publication later this year.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ted</member_name><member_id>1467536</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1260188131000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>kenwilber-88</urlname><id>91062</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Integral Commons (Ken Wilber group)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256221330000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Understanding Spiritual Development: States, Structures, Vantage Points</name><id>11685804</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259885700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/kenwilber-88/events/11685804/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/5/f/global_7098607.jpeg</photo_url></item>