<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>749 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.415901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 389-8615</phone><name>Oliveira's Restaurant</name><city>Everett</city><id>966479</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.047577</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're returning to Oliveira's for another affordable night of Brazilian dining with friendly, warm folks. Once again we've been offered &lt;a href="http://www.oliveirasrestaurant.com/menu.html" target="_blank"&gt;rodizio&lt;/a&gt;, an all you can eat barbecue for $13.95. Servers will bring swords of meat to our tables in addition to an abundant selection of delicious fare from a self serve &lt;a href="http://www.oliveirasrestaurant.com/buffet.html" target="_blank"&gt;buffet bar&lt;/a&gt;. Drinks and &lt;a href="http://www.oliveirasrestaurant.com/gallery/sobremesas/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;dessert&lt;/a&gt; are NOT included.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're more than welcome to order from the &lt;a href="http://www.oliveirasrestaurant.com/traditional.html" target="_blank"&gt;a la carte menu &lt;/a&gt; or pay for your meal by weight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tables of six will be arranged so conversations are manageable and bill paying easy. You're welcome and encouraged to table hop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;center&gt;PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE YOU &lt;u&gt;MUST&lt;/u&gt; ANSWER THE QUESTIONS WHICH APPEAR AFTER YOU RSVP YES.&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU RSVP NO YOU DO NOT NEED TO ANSWER THE QUESTIONS&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;Oliveira's is clean, the food fresh, and the prices very reasonable.&lt;br /&gt;We have been promised attentive, helpful and prompt service with adequate wait staff. &lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lovely music of Receita de Samba begins at 7:30 PM in the main dining room. I always enjoy Anna's and Bill's shows and I'm sure you will as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/receitadesamba" target="_blank"&gt;Listen to the music of Receita de Samba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Transit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line subway to Sullivan Station then&lt;br /&gt;Bus 109 Linden Sq Via Broadway then&lt;br /&gt;get off at Broadway &amp;amp; Gladstone Terrace&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl" target="_blank"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to arrange your driving directions  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Available on Broadway and behind Oliveira's Restaurant as well as the shopping center (Family Dollar and Walgreens are the main stores) which is behind the gas station.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members of the &lt;a href="http://portuguese.meetup.com/316/calendar/10956896/"&gt;Portuguese speakers&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonOnyxbirds/calendar/10956977/"&gt;Onyxbirds&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://travel.meetup.com/461/calendar/11032435/"&gt;WorldTrekkers&lt;/a&gt; Meetup groups will also be joining us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Before I list the Reservation Rules, please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I want to assure you I do understand if you've RSVPd YES and you have a sudden change of plans because you're lost, you don't feel well, you have transportation issues, you don't have the money, or you just don't want to be around people. My only request is for you to let me know as soon as possible so we don't worry about you and our reservation is adjusted. As long as you contact me you will not be considered a NO-SHOW.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rules for Events with &lt;u&gt;Reservations&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you MUST call or text me at (617) 445-7549.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVPs are on a first come, first served basis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If dinner is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will automatically be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the dinner and you have not attended, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If I change you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update dinner confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW each will count as if you've NO-SHOWED.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the dinner, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events with reservations you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/suggestion/"&gt;Tonya&lt;/a&gt; about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will arrive at 6:45 PM to confirm seating and welcome you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Tonya/Meetup reservation or call/text my cell (617) 445 7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254067204000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248556672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oliveira's Restaurant - Dinner - Saturday August 15th  - 7 PM</name><id>10956907</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250377200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/10956907/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/8/c/global_8855004.jpeg</photo_url></item>