<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>116 Poole Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03452</zip><lat>42.845470</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Monadnock State Park    Phone # 603-532-8862</name><city>Jaffrey</city><id>7040212</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.088676</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's hike Mount Monadnock!  Mount Monadnock is the most climbed mountain in North America.  100,000+ people hike Mount Monadnock each year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The summit of Mount Monadnock is 3,165 feet above sea level.  With the summit exposed at the top, the mountain gives a feeling similar to those thousands of feet higher.  At the summit,  on a clear day you can see parts of all 6 New England states and 100 miles in every direction.  The panorama takes in the Prudential Tower in Boston, Newburyport harbor, Mount Washington in the north, Stratton and the Green Mountains to the west, and parts of the Berkshires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us if you're able to occasionally use your hands to pull yourself up granite rocks.  On the way down the mountain, you will occasionally need to sit and slide a few feet down granite rocks.  This is a hands-on hike, with impressive views at the summit.  The elevation gain for this hike is 1,800 feet, and the hike is approximately 4.5 miles round-trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most popular &amp;amp; shortest trails are the White Dot and White Cross Trails.  We're going to skip the White Dot Trail.  We'll go up and down the White Cross Trail because the White Cross Trail is easier than the White Dot Trail. The White Dot and White Cross trails on Mount Monadnock are large and wide, largely due to the volume of hikers on them.  The White Cross trail is fun to hike, with a steady steep climb and some nice scrambles up the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;"The White Cross Trail is a slightly less popular route then the White Dot Trail. Like the White Dot Trail, the White Cross Trail has a # of small scrambles but these scramble are less intense then the White Dot Trail. The White Cross Trail is also much easier then the White Dot Trail for descent down the mountain."      &lt;a href="http://www.summitpost.org/white-cross-trail/167816"&gt;www.summitpost.org/white-cross-trail/167816&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The upper 300 feet of the mountain is above tree-line and is very exposed to the weather, so please bring a jacket and layers of clothing.  The weather conditions on top of Monadnock average about 10 degrees cooler than the valleys below.  Please wear hiking boots and carry 2 quarts of water per person.  Make sure not to overload your backpack, which is a mistake new hikers make on this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people underestimate Mount Monadnock and anybody hiking should use care. Accidents, injuries, and rescues are quite frequent on Mount Monadnock. The trails are very rough and rocky. There are areas of smooth slick ledge.  Lichen-covered rock may be slick. We will use care and take our time hiking Monadnock.  We will allow at least 4 hours to hike directly up and down the mountain. Please note: most accidents occur on the way down the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Dogs are not allowed on Mount Monadnock.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;APPROACH VIA THE MONADNOCK STATE PARK TRAILHEAD: Head west from the town of Jaffery. Two miles on your right you will see a sign pointing to Monadnock State Park. Head up two miles to the to the toll gate ($3.00 per person).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monadnock is said to be the world's third most climbed mountain, following Japan's Mount Fuji and China's Mount Tai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hikers can call Monadnock directly for the most up-to-date trail information or other inquires: 603-532-8862&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Packing and planning tips can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;For more information:  &lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/explore/state-parks/monadnock-state-park.aspx"&gt;www.nhstateparks.org/explore/state-parks/monadnock-state-park.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>GPS:  42.86130°N / 72.1083°W     driving directions:   http://monadnocktrails.com/Directions.php</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338140663000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336159942000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's hike Mount Monadnock, N. America's most climbed mountain, 4.5 miles total</name><id>63446202</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338129000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/63446202/</event_url></item>