<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers, I have been asked by so many people when I will be putting on our next Scavenger Hunt, well I propose trying it again for the 28st of June, hopefully it won't rain. I really need help with running this event, so please contact me if you are a professional scavenger or just want to help out! So mark your calendars for this fun event. After the scavenger hunt we will meet for dinner to discuss our bounty at a local restaurant which will be decided by a group majority. Also bring your digital camera or photo digital phone if you have one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What is a scavenger hunt you ask? Well a scavenger hunt is an active and enjoyable team activity that is based on a list of questions to be answered and objects to be collected or an action to be performed by the group or a person in the group (like kissing a complete stranger on the lips or getting kicked out of a store). Some answers and objects can be collected at specific locations, others can be collected at numerous locations. The questions are in random order, challenging teams to determine their optimal route and to prioritize the tasks that they will try to accomplish in the allotted time. Each team selects a unique route which means that teams don't follow each other around, however they frequently see each other along the way, adding to the competitive nature of the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting in the center of the downtown Portsmouth at a cafe called &amp;quot;Breaking New Grounds&amp;quot; it a coffee shop. Again if anyone wants to help me with this event I would really appreciate it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions don't hesitate to write or call me. My number is 603-509-2907 &lt;br /&gt;Thanks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy in the white "Trailblazers" shirt on.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214935723000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>We had so much fun at the last Scavenger Hunt, and remember to bring your digital camera to record that special momemt</why><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212058003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scavenger Hunt</name><id>8034004</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214668800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8034004/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/2/global_4282114.jpeg</photo_url></item>