<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for a potluck. We will be gathering in the skyroom of 100 Memorial Drive Apartments for a potluck at noon. This is the top most floor of a 13 story building overlooking the Charles river and the Boston skyline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a relaxed and chill opportunity to come out and meet fellow atheists. Bring your favourite dish, and enjoy a view of Boston on the first day of spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $5 pp. The room costs $75 from noon-6pm. Any additional contribution that people can help me with will be appreciated. I have paid for the reservation out of my own pocket, and $5.00 a person will help offset that cost. This is an excellent venue, however, and I am willing to pay out of my pocket to get it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS from Subway: Take the redline and get off at Kendall/MIT. Walk south from the station toward the water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By car: Use google maps, and when driving on memorial going east/west turn left/right on wadsworth, then make an immediate left on Amherst. Park anywhere on the street here at Amherst. The building will be on the left, just after the MIT SLOAN business school. There should be plenty of parking on a sunday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Apartment building is pretty hard to miss. Go in through the entrance on Amherst street. If the Concierge asks, tell him you are going to the skyroom (it's the "S" button on the elevator). Reservations will be made under Boston Atheists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;QUESTIONS: Call me at 702.280.3583&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are on the top floor of 100 Memorial Drive Apartments.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Evan</member_name><member_id>4427039</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessie</member_name><member_id>13884412</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300759105000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><why>It's the first day of spring</why><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1298218997000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>First day of Spring potluck</name><id>16633509</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300636800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/16633509/</event_url></item>