<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte 112/Kancamagus Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>44.008961</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Oliverian Brook Trail Head</name><city>Albany</city><id>5157542</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.269997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Karine &amp;amp; Spruce &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire&amp;nbsp;description&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;before you RSVP and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;answer all questions&amp;nbsp;that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;One of our favorite hikes - we'll be traversing 7 mountains on this &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;challenging 17 mile&amp;nbsp;hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; - including 4 official 4K peaks and 1 New England 100 highest peak. We will be hiking North Tripyramid (4,180 feet - #32&amp;nbsp; on NH4K), Middle Tripyramid (4,140 feet - #35 on NH4K), East Sleeper (3,840 feet - #84 on NE100),&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mt. Whiteface (4,020 feet - #45 on the NH4K),&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Passaconaway (4,043 feet - #42 on the NH4K). We will also climb South Tripyramid and West Sleeper, though they don't officially count for any major lists. These mountains are located in the Southeastern part of the White Mountain National Forest in the Sandwich Range Wilderness. They have beautiful scenic wooded trails, a few steep climbs, and a handful of beautiful vistas from a few viewpoints along the way. We'll travel on the following trails: Pine Bend, Mount Tripyramid, Kate Sleeper, Rollins, Square Ledge, Passaconaway cut-off, and Oliverian Brook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This hike is &lt;strong&gt;challenging&lt;/strong&gt; - while the official 4K peaks are frequently visited in winter, the Sleepers are not, which means we'll likely have to break trail through deep snow on this 3 mile section of the Kate Sleeper trail which will slow us down on an already long and difficult hike. *Everyone* will get to take a turn up front breaking trail. :) Due to the length of the hike and the uncertainty of trail conditions, it is very likely we will finish in the dark. &lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;em&gt;In order to sign up, you should be an experienced winter hiker who has recently completed trips of 12-15 miles and who is comfortable breaking trail in deep snow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Also, there is a *slight* chance we'll have to reschedule the hike to Sunday, February 19th. We'll keep you posted as the hike date nears.*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&amp;nbsp;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are discouraged&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike, unless they have experience with long, challenging hikes in winter. Please email us to discuss if you'd like to bring your dog. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~ 2 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; semi-loop hike (our start and end points are 3 miles apart on the Kanc Highway - hence the car spot), we&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;follow Pine Bend trail to the Mount Tripyramid trail and summit the 3 Tripyramids. Then we'll partially descend the South Slide to get to the intersection with the Kate Sleeper Trail. We'll follow the Kate Sleeper trail across to the Sleepers to Rollins Trail and follow that trail up and over Whiteface and over to Passaconaway. From there, we'll descend the Square Ledge Trail to the Passaconaway cutoff to the Oliverian Brook trail and back to our cars. We'll meet to spot our cars at the Oliverian Brook trailhead at 6:30am, before going to the Pine Bend trailhead and starting our hike at 7am. We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about 17 miles&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb nearly 6,000 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;While it should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 12 hours 45 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip we may actually move slower because of winter conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED/EXTREME&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, elevation gain and winter conditions. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We have traveled these trails several times before and we also did research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click below&amp;nbsp;for more information:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6996"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6996"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for North Tripyramid (peakbagger.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6997"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6997"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for Middle Tripyramid (peakbagger.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=7001"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for East Sleeper (peakbagger.com) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=7002"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for Whiteface (peakbagger.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6999"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for Passaconaway (peakbagger.com)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for trail conditions from TrailsNH.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&amp;nbsp;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for current weather conditions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. Mountaineering snowshoes with aggressive teeth for traction while climbing. Mountaineering crampons with 10-12 teeth are required for this trip - Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable as back-up only. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly draws heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket. Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants. Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens.&amp;nbsp;Goggles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead of a hydration bladder since the mouthpiece/tube can freeze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket which packs small and weighs just ounces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries - lithium work best in colder temperatures. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We'll meet at 6:30am at the Oliverian Brook trailhead along the Rte 112/Kancamagus Highway near Albany, NH.&amp;nbsp; According to Google Maps this spot is about 150 miles from Boston and it should take about 2 hours 50 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=NH-112+E%2FKancamagus+Hwy&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=43.9909,-71.335387&amp;amp;spn=0.024422,0.035706&amp;amp;sll=43.9909,-71.335387&amp;amp;sspn=0.024422,0.035706&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFSBSnwId1Gu_-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=dme&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=15&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for the driving directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1328629329000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326470380000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Tripyramids, Sleepers, Whiteface &amp; Passaconaway (ADVANCED/EXTREME)</name><id>47955332</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328441400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/47955332/</event_url></item>