<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Please come join the holiday fun this evening or maybe catch this on your own at another time......&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;My track phone number is 413.559.0192 but cannot view the site once I leave home at 5:30pm.Hoping to meet in the lobby if that is practical. Never been to this location.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Weekend &lt;br /&gt;

 Tom McCabe's PaintBox Theatre &lt;br /&gt;

 presents &lt;br /&gt;

 A Christmas Carol&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CC LogoOver the shoulder terror over the glasses Scrooge sneer &lt;br /&gt;

 Paintbox Website!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit our Facebook! &lt;br /&gt;

 About Us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PaintBox Theatre is a theatre of improvisation and imagination for the whole family. Audiences young and old have called it unique, wild, zany, and even educational. Audience members range in age from 1 to 100 and include parents, seniors and other adults. &lt;br /&gt;

 To bring a classic tale to life the Paintbox way- start with the story, fold in art and literacy, stir. Voila! Out pops a funny, fanciful show that appeals to young and old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Start with a children's classic. Add three actors. Add a theatre, the Paintbox stage &amp;amp; a screen. Add artwork (by kids). Add lots of audience participation &amp;amp; improvisation. Stir well. There you go: Paintbox! &lt;br /&gt;

 Tom McCabe, &lt;br /&gt;

 Founder &lt;br /&gt;

 His Website &lt;br /&gt;

 The Surfing Storyteller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We opened last weekend and had a blast. Here's a link to an article that appeared - The Advocate &lt;br /&gt;

 and a comment on Facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jessica wrote: "my girls and I saw your Sat. show and thank you so much for giving me a chance to share a happy Christmas memory at a time when every second with our kids is precious. the show was terrific of course, as always:)"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 We will be doing shows this Friday at 7:00 and Saturday at 10:30 and 1:00. Please Pass the Word!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PaintBox Theatre has adapted Christmas Carol as a child-friendly romp featuring lots of audience participation and holiday cheer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll sing carols, participate in not one but two snowball fights with invisible snowballs and everyone will learn how to waltz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than 50 children artists drawing pictures based on characters and locations from this Dickens classic. The pictures will be projected above the stage throughout the performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There'll be a carol sing in the lobby during intermission and pre-show several members of the audience will be offered parts in the show as the Cratchit children. Yes, even Tiny Tim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To Order Tickets Online Click Here &lt;br /&gt;

 Tickets and Seating&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;General Seating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Single Tickets: $7.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Groups (14 or more) $5.00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets will be available at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fri., Dec. 14 - 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sat., Dec. 15 - 10:30 AM &amp;amp; 1:00 PM Fri., Dec. 21 - 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sat., Dec. 22 10:30 AM &amp;amp; 1:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Northampton High School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;380 Elm Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Northampton, MA 01060&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CONTACT INFO:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom McCabe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom@TomMcCabe.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;413-210-1898&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PaintBoxTheatre.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356148089000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355854373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>This Weekend Tom McCabe's  PaintBox Theatre  presents  A  Christmas Carol</name><id>95797602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356134400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/95797602/</event_url></item>