<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-536-5400</phone><name>Boston Public Library/ Rabb Lecture Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>401397</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Istanbul, Mumbai, Bangkok and Tokyo are among the destinations that drew Oregon's Ryan Yaden in his recent exploration of architectural heritage in light of the pressures facing modern Asian mega-cities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yaden recounts his travels on May 28 as the guest speaker in &amp;quot;Exploring Design,&amp;quot; the BSA lecture series at the Boston Public Library. He focuses on &amp;quot;eight instances of history lost and found, from the lost Hippodrome of Istanbul to the contemporary ghost-skyscrapers of Bangkok.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yaden was the 2005 recipient of the BSA-administered Rotch Travelling Scholarship, a $35,000 award that enabled him to undertake his trip. He earned his undergraduate degree in architecture at the University of Oregon and his master's degree at Harvard's Graduate School of Design in 2003. Yaden worked for Boston architecture firm--including Ann Beha Architects and designLA--and, after his Asian journey, returned to Oregon and the firm of Works Partnership Architecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This presentation is cosponsored by the Rotch Travelling Scholarship program (&lt;a href="http://www.rotchscholarship.org/competition)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rotchschol...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All &amp;quot;Exploring Design&amp;quot; lectures are free and open to everyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's chat and mix and mingle afterwards, too. For those of you interested, meet up by the entrance after the lecture is over. We are going to take a short evening walk to the banQ, the new bar/restaurant on Washington Street. Designed by Office dA, banQ is an adaptive reuse of the old Penny Savings Bank building. If you don't make the lecture, please feel free to join us there around 8!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To subscribe to YPNet's monthly e-newsletter, which provides a wide range of architecture and design competitions, exhibits, mixers and opportunities around Boston, click &lt;a href="http://www.architects.org/subscribe" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alyson</member_name><member_id>5616452</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Moser-Booth</member_name><member_id>6447986</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212184986000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209140667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Heritage and adaptive re-use in Asia</name><id>7810918</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212012000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/7810918/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/f/global_3912783.jpeg</photo_url></item>