<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join Stevie from the &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup Group&lt;/span&gt; on &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;March 31 at 6.45 pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; for &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Un baiser s'il vous plait&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, the 6th (final!) film of the &lt;b&gt;Salve Regina French Film Festival held in Newport RI&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All films are being shown to the public for no charge thanks to the support of the French American Cultural Exchange (FACE), the Cultural Services of the French Embassy and the French Ministry of Culture (CNC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An RSVP limit of 15 will ensure we have enough seats in the theater given its freely available to all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the film&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Salve Regina French Film Festival website shows the following details for the screening of this film:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;Un baiser s'il vous plait/Shall We Kiss?&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;•Date &amp;amp; Time: &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;Date &amp;amp; Time: 7 p.m. Thursday, April 2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;•Location: &lt;b&gt;Bazarsky Lecture Hall, O'Hare Academic Center&lt;/b&gt; (Salve Regina, Ochre Point Rd, Newport RI)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt; A funny, oddly sexy and quintessentially French romantic comedy.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-----------&lt;br /&gt;Further details about the film (taken from the website of Music Box Films at &lt;a href="http://www.musicboxfilms.com/shallwekiss/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.musicboxfilms.com/shallwekiss/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.musicboxfi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;directed by Emmanuel Mouret&lt;br /&gt;starring Virginie Ledoyen, Emmanuel Mouret, Julie Gayet, Michaël Cohen, Frédérique Bel, Stefano Accorsi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While traveling to Nantes for one evening, Emilie meets Gabriel. Equally seduced by one another, but both otherwise committed, they know they will probably never see each other again. He would like to kiss her. She as well, but a story prevents her from doing so: that of a married woman and of her best friend who were surprised by the effects of a kiss. Of a kiss that should have born no consequences&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Technical Information&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Production Year - 2007 &lt;br /&gt;Country of Production - France &lt;br /&gt;Language - French with English subtitles &lt;br /&gt;Running Time - 102 min &lt;br /&gt;Screen Ratio - 1.85:1 &lt;br /&gt;Sound - Dolby digital &lt;br /&gt;Rating - unrated &lt;br /&gt;___________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being organised by Stevie Worthington as part of a &lt;b&gt;6 part Meetup event&lt;/b&gt; for the &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Providence French Language Meetup group&lt;/span&gt; held in &lt;span style="color: skyblue"&gt;NEWPORT RI&lt;/span&gt;. If you can't make this night, hopefully you can make it to at least one of the other films in the Film festival on either &lt;b&gt;22 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;24 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;26 Mar&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;29 Mar&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;31 Mar&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;Any questions, send Stevie an email - merci! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be inside the lobby from 6.30pm wearing a pink jacket holding a meetup sign</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238884630000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237298845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film Festival in Newport - Film 6 "Un baiser s'il vous plait/Shall We Kiss?"</name><id>9972350</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238711400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/9972350/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/5/global_7716501.jpeg</photo_url></item>