<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01550</zip><lat>42.077618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Vienna Restaurant &amp; Historic Inn</name><city>Southbridge</city><id>3199121</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.038712</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Halli Hallo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Weather forecast is for a beautiful autumn day, as we planned!&amp;nbsp; Walk is at Westville Recreation area meeting at the large parking area on Wallace Rd, a continuation of Breakneck Rd which is off of South St. Want to carpool? Let us know!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wir haben endlich entschieden etwas besonderes zu machen. A regional Treffen!&amp;nbsp; I hope that many of you will be able to join the fun. We have invited German speakers from CT,MA and RI. The afternoon will begin with an optional Spaziergang along a river trail followed by happy hour/dinner at the gourmet, quaint Vienna Restaurant, all while enjoying German conversation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The restaurant should be lovely.&amp;nbsp; It's in an elegant old inn with fireplaces etc.&amp;nbsp; This will be a change from the East Side or Student Prince.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Spaziergang starts at 1:30 along what was intended to be an extension of the Grand Trunk Railroad.&amp;nbsp; The train never came, but the land, river and trail are there for us to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then a gem&amp;uuml;tlich&amp;nbsp;happy hour/dinner by the fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sound nice? Please do try to join us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the restaurant &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The original, more humble dwelling was built in 1812, then later, our Italianate Revival home which you see as Vienna Restaurant and Historic Inn.&amp;nbsp; The Mansion of 26 (8 bathrooms) rooms sits atop upper Main Street and is on the National Register of Historic Places.&amp;nbsp; Vienna's Inn has a 3-story mansard roof with meandering hallways and ceilings high enough to touch the heavens! While dining in our restaurant - don't forget to look up and see the gorgeous meticulously restored friezes on the ceilings, each of the 2 rooms has a different style.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We serve each meal with villeroy and boch bone china, cotton table linen, real candle light and antique wood-burning fireplaces...~most important, real food &amp;amp; geniune hospitality! Be our guest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We&lt;/span&gt; offer several intimate dining rooms for upscale fine dining.&amp;nbsp; All dining rooms are equipped with working fireplaces for warmth, tranquil, romantic atmosphere in all areas of the restaurant.&amp;nbsp; Vienna houses an extensive wine cellar featuring the wines of the world from Austria, France, Germany and South Africa to Austrialia with hundreds of labels to choose from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The restaurant is quite proud to offer an accomplished staff with out the attitude.&amp;nbsp; Our guests should relax and experience warmth &amp;amp; hospitality beyond expectations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specializing in Austrian and German cuisines as well as Hungarian, Polish, French and Swiss.&amp;nbsp; Even your dining companions who prefer a great juicy steak or seafood additions of the day- Our dishes are sure to please every palate. Vegan dishes available by advance request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Treffpunkt for the walk at Westville Recreation Area, Wallace Rd</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318810357000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Deutsch speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>german-425</urlname><id>438488</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford German Kaffeeklatsch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314288815000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>German Meetup Extravaganza</name><id>30893911</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318786200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/german-425/events/30893911/</event_url></item>