<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come along for a nice snowshoe up one of the nicest trails in the whites.  We will be starting from the Sabbaday Falls Picnic Area off of NH-112 (Kancamagus Highway) and snowshoeing the 5 miles of Sabbaday Brook Trail.  From  the end of sabbaday it is a short hike in each direction to the two official peaks of the tripyramids.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Total Distance: 11.4 miles&lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain: 2800 feet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are parts of the trail that are steep, but most of it is fairly flat and easy to follow.  There are a number of stream crossings in summer, but they should all be well-frozen this time of year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snowshoes are a requirement for this trail as it is not as frequently used as the trails from waterville valley.  As always while winter hiking, please bring a headlamp and spare batteries as it is very likely we will be hiking down in the dark.  Insufficient or improper equipment may result in your removal from the trip.  If you are unsure what to bring please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter hiking, while more fun than summer hiking, is also more strenuous.  If you are not in reasonably good shape do not attempt this hike.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be driving a silver mazda wagon</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263777266000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262640058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tripyramids from the Kanc</name><id>12220074</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263562200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12220074/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/d/global_12503517.jpeg</photo_url></item>