<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.240830</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.571910</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Paddle through coves (look for mink, muskrat and beaver!), boggy areas (look for pitcher plants!) and along the shoreline of beautiful Whitehall State Park in Hopkinton, MA. Plan to arrive in time to be ready to paddle at 3:00 PM and spend 2-3 hours on the water. The free parking area is on Route 135 between Westborough and Hopkinton Centers @ 42.24166 North - 71.57316 West.  There's a fishing tournament there that ends around 1:00 PM, so we should have plenty of parking available by the time we arrive. If parking is sparse, we will double up in the spots (they are plenty long enough for 2 cars).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've set a limit on attendance, but there are bound to be cancellations, so if the meetup is full and you would like to join us, put your name on the waiting list.  There's a good chance you'll get a spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The water temperature at Whitehall is 64 F&lt;/strong&gt; as of Friday, April 20 .  It has warmed up nicely.  It is supposed to be a bit windy on Saturday afternoon, but once we get across the lake to the big island we can stay in more sheltered areas.  Be prepared to paddle hard against the wind in the beginning of the trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335186391000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332194195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddle at Whitehall</name><id>57019862</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335034800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/57019862/</event_url></item>