<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Do you have &amp;quot;extra&amp;quot; photo gear laying about taking up space? or Maybe you are looking for a new bit of new gear? We have the event for you! Yes, It's time to sell or swap your extra photography gear at the CIPNE Photo Bazaar and Swap Fest. At this free event we will have tables set up where you'll be able to show what you have to swap/sell. Swapping is a great win-win situation, so bring a list of what you want to get and what you have to give/swap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Items available will range from inexpensive filters (a few dollars) all the way up to expensive studio lights and camera bodies + lenses ($1000+).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sellers: Research beforehand fair market prices for your gear so they will be more likely to be sold. Consider bringing a friend to help you sell if you want to walk around and buy. In the spirit of cooperation, fairness, and goodwill, be forthcoming in indicating the true condition of gear, and any defects, when asked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buyers: Research beforehand fair market prices for gear that you want to buy. Bringing cash and checks are a good idea. Show a list of gear that you want to buy; maybe someone will know where it is available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Check the lists of items for sale or wanted, and add your own items here **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Disclaimer: The CIPNE Photo Bazaar and Swapfest is organized and run under the spirit of cooperation and fairness. CIPNE and anyone associated with CIPNE is not liable for any swapping or selling transactions that result in any problems or issues. Participation in this event is under the doctrine of &amp;quot;buyer beware&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lensprotogo.com" target="_blank"&gt;Lens Pro to Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lensprotogo.com/index.php?pr=Directions" target="_blank"&gt;Link to directions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;152 Commonwealth Ave.,&lt;br /&gt;Unit M-1, C,&lt;br /&gt;Concord, MA 01742&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Set up: 12:00–12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Trading time: 12:30–3:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Break down: 3:30–4:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: FREE event! Tell your friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP so we know how many tables to set up for this event!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266502315000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265396733000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CIPNE Photo Bazaar</name><id>12529116</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266080400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12529116/</event_url></item>