<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone!&lt;br /&gt;   We are beginning our first series of classes for this year. As you can see from the title of the series, we are going to be exploring topics related to the practice of mysticism. What is mysticism? A mystic is someone who is not satisfied with merely believing something about God, and usually is dissatisfied with dogma and rules that are often associated with traditional religion. A mystic wants to experience God and the spiritual world for themselves, so that they can truly &lt;i&gt;know.&lt;/i&gt; Meditation, which is more than just learning how to relax, is the workbench of mystical practice, and with practice, can enable you to have profound experiences of God inside yourself. As such, each of these classes begins with a guided meditation, followed by a lecture/discussion on a topic related to mysticism. There are mystics in all major religions, and this class is open to everyone, regardless of your religious or spiritual background. If this sounds like something you would like to find out more about, I invite you to join us for these classes. It is a powerful series, and when you complete this introductory series, you will be invited to attend more advanced classes if you wish. &lt;br /&gt;   This class is offered free of charge, but pre-registration is required.&lt;br /&gt;   I look forward to seeing you all in this vibrant, interactive, and spiritually deepening class.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Topic for week 1: &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Introduction to Mysticism - An Overview&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265934870000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265161055000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meditation and Mysticism: Experiencing God Inside Yourself - class series</name><id>12502396</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265761800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/12502396/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/f/global_1078639.jpeg</photo_url></item>