<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1500 West St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01002</zip><lat>42.305320</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413-253-2883</phone><name>Notch Visitor’s Center, Mt. Holyoke State Park.</name><city>Amherst</city><id>902685</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.528889</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Rising roughly 1,000 feet in elevation, the Mt. Holyoke Range runs east to west offering fine views of the Connecticut River and the Pioneer Valley. We'll meet at the Notch Visitor’s Center on Rte. 116 in Amherst, Mass. Our day begins with a steep ascent to the summit of Bare Mountain. We’ll follow the Monadnock-Metacomet Trail along a ridge line crossing the “Seven Sisters”, a series of small peaks. After approximately 5 miles, we arrive at the summit of Mt. Holyoke where we’ll enjoy spectacular views from the historic Summit House. We’ll retrace our steps to the Notch Visitor’s Center return along the Monadnock-Metacomet Trail.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t let the relatively low elevation of the Mt. Holyoke range fool you. This hike contains many short steep climbs and descents. The length and rugged terrain make this a strenuous hike. Please be prepared with appropriate clothing (NO COTTON), boots, food and water.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS: Take the Massachusetts Turnpike (I-90) to exit 5, Rte. 33 north to Rte. 116 North to the Notch Visitors Center.  Driving time is a little under 2 hours West of Boston.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: 10 miles R/T   &lt;br /&gt;Duration: 7 hours  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be driving a 2003 Gold honda Accord MA plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter G</member_name><member_id>2906700</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272412748000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269103033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Holyoke Range  - A good tune up hike</name><id>12940703</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272200400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12940703/</event_url></item>