<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>NEW ROUTE&lt;br /&gt;Glen Boulder, Boot Spur, Mt. Washington and Tuckerman Ravine &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ravine of the Castles to Jefferson, challenging small group hike&lt;br /&gt;Sunday's weather looks great for a last minute adventure exploring scenic Castle Ravine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMC Totals:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance        10.25 mi&lt;br /&gt;Book Time  9 hr 22 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain        +4284 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss       -4284 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Challenging&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trails Used:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Castle Ravine Trail, ascent&lt;br /&gt;leads through wild &amp;amp; beautiful Castle Ravine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Castle Trail, descent&lt;br /&gt;follows the narrow, serrated ridge that runs northwest from Jefferson, providing magnificent views &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please refer to AMC's White Mountain Guide for more detailed information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: due to the rugged terrain, this is not a dog friendly hike.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283087554000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282874764000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NEW ROUTE: Glen Boulder, Boot Spur, Mt. Washington and Tuckerman Ravine </name><id>14557561</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283083200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14557561/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/global_17520233.jpeg</photo_url></item>