<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Timberline Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03860</zip><lat>44.042778</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><city>Bartlett</city><id>761180</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.107178</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>PLEASE RSVP BY WEDNESDAY 8PM IF YOU PLAN TO GO, THIS EVENT WILL BE CLOSED TO NEW RSVPs AT THAT TIME.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Wedeln Ski House is my favorite place to stay up north, located in the heart of the White Mountains just north of North Conway. Cost is only $20 per night for guests but the best part is meeting other riders and skiers.  The Club often works with local mountains to get discount tickets.  This weekend the Wedeln Ski Club will participate in a ski and snowboard race at Wildcat Mountain, that means anyone staying at the club gets a special discount ticket on Saturday, only $39!!!  No you do not have to race to get the discount.    Window price is $70 so staying at the Wedeln's ski house pays for itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should have about 40 people of all abilities going to Wildcat on Saturday so you will have no problem finding people to ski with.  Hit the green trails with other beginners, Wildcat's famous Polecat trail is the longest green trail in NH OR challenge yourself with the experts as we rip up some of the best tree-skiing in the east.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I encourage you to come up on Friday night and stay through Sunday.  The rooms at Wedeln are 2 bunk-beds per room (mostly), segregated by gender.  Guest bring their own, towels, sheets, blanket and pillows.  Every weekend there is a mix of new guests and veteran members - it is always a fun and welcoming atmosphere.  Most weekend we will do some apres ski fun and head out for to local bars or other ski clubs for night events.  Of course you can always hang out by the cozy fire place if that is more your pace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get the $39 lift ticket on Saturday you must:&lt;br /&gt;1. stay at the ski house, you will get a guest card.&lt;br /&gt;2. present the guest card to the special table on the top floor of the wildcat base lodge.&lt;br /&gt;3. pay in cash.&lt;br /&gt;4. buy me a beer at the bar (just joking on 4).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please on RSVP is you know you can make it. &lt;br /&gt;21 + pnly&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom and Darlene will be at the house by 8pm on Friday night</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Darlene</member_name><member_id>7362850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296263909000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295576989000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend at The Wedeln Ski Club - $39 Wildcat discount</name><id>16127379</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296259200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/16127379/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/7/global_6256599.jpeg</photo_url></item>