<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Chestnut St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.249938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.471.4363</phone><name>Fat Cat</name><city>Quincy</city><id>884104</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.001294</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join fellow Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun Thursday&amp;nbsp; Night Dinner @ Fat Cat&amp;nbsp; in Qunicy.&amp;nbsp; Yelp states the approximate cost for one meal including drink, tax and tip is approximately $11-$30.&amp;nbsp; The Fat Cat is a small restaurant located in Quincy Center which has received great reviews from practically everyone who has dined there.&amp;nbsp;As this restaurant is small and does not accept reservations, this will be&amp;nbsp;an "intimate" meetup and seating will be limited to members only.&amp;nbsp; The Fat Cat does not seat incomplete parties so if you don't mind arriving on time,&amp;nbsp;waiting a few minutes (or up to 1/2 hr) to be seated, and meeting up with just a few members, this is the perfect event for you as we&amp;nbsp;go to our 102nd "unique" restaurant.&amp;nbsp; ("Unique" meaning we have not eaten there before as&amp;nbsp;a Group.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet and get to know each other, as well as talk about different foods, restaurants, and meals we enjoy. This will also be a great time to plan our next Dining Out event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner @ Fat Cat Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, February 24th, 2011 @ 5:30pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;24 Chestnut Street, Quincy, MA 02169&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-471-4363&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.fatcatrestaurant.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting Location: &lt;em&gt;Outside the front door if it's nice out. We will then go in together as a Group.&lt;/em&gt; Otherwise, inside the Lobby. If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under "Jeanne."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizer(s): Jeanne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Min/Max: Min of 6 people 48 hours in advance. Max of 8 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests: None.&amp;nbsp; This is a Members-Only event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fees: 2011 Annual Members - FREE, Group Members - $2; You may become a 2011 Annual Member for $12 at this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Deadline: 6:00PM on Wednesday, February 23rd. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page. (It's not&amp;nbsp; OK to be late as all of the party must be there to be seated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Directions will be posted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking: You will have to either park out side the restaurant if available.&amp;nbsp; Otherwise you will have to park in the community parking lot which is past the restaurant second right.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>714439</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1300554653000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Members have been asking to go to the Fat Cat Restaurant for awhile now and it's a great restaurant for a small group outing, which some members have asked for recently.</why><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282426700000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thursday Evening Small Group Dinner  at the Fat Cat</name><id>14496694</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298586600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/14496694/</event_url></item>