<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>182 Western Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.362930</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stone Hearth Pizza Co.</name><city>Allston</city><id>7070002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129494</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for dinner at Stone Hearth Pizza (this well priced restaurant has awesome pizza and a variety of other menu items). We will also be participating in World Book Night- an event which encourages people to read more. World Book Night partners with authors and publishers to give away one million specially printed books to encourage and celebrate reading. Each guest at dinner will receive a complimentary copy of the national bestseller, Zeitoun.This true story will be released as a Jonathan Demme film in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each guest pays for their own dinner/drinks. Please only sign up if you can definitely attend. Please do not sign up just to hold your spot. If your plans change, please update your RSVP as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zeitoun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, is the true story of Abdulrahman Zeitoun, the Syrian-American owner of a painting and contracting company in &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Orleans"&gt;New Orleans&lt;/a&gt; who chose to ride out &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hurricane_Katrina"&gt;Hurricane Katrina&lt;/a&gt; in his home. After the storm he traveled the flooded city in a secondhand canoe rescuing neighbors, caring for abandoned pets and distributing fresh water. Soon after the storm, Zeitoun was arrested without reason or explanation at one of his rental houses. He was not immediately charged with a crime but was imprisoned for 23 days without having stood trial. During that time he was accused of terrorist activity presumably because of his ethnicity, was treated inhumanely, and was refused medical attention and the use of a phone to alert his family.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) at our tables. Please call/text Catherine at 774 232 0000 if you have trouble finding us.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337993102000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336360338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and World Book Night</name><id>63721122</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1337814000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/63721122/</event_url></item>