<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We're adding some extra fun time to our meetup this month by beginning with a&lt;b&gt; potluck BBQ dinner&lt;/b&gt;.  We'll provide the paper goods, drinks, and some grilled chicken.  Please contribute either a healthy side dish (veggies are greatly appreciated!) or a dessert.  We can be outdoors or in, depending on the weather.  For our evening's topic, we'll be inside.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How connected do you feel to your emotional guidance system?  Your emotions are your connection to your inner wisdom/inner being/Source.   We'll do an exercise to learn your own unique signals and to really get in touch with this means of communication; and talk about how to use this valuable form of guidance.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our intention is to also begin by activating a feeling good, Source-full state; and to close with time for group coaching and support on any issue you like.  Bring your questions!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is very important to all of us that &lt;b&gt;if you RSVP &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot;, to please show up&lt;/b&gt;.  If you need to change your plans, please let us know.  It really helps us with our planning and in being able to start on time.  Thank you for cooperating with this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can't wait to co-create with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Click on meeting location for directions.  We're down a long driveway, so look for mailbox at end.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251331892000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248221110000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer BBQ and Using Your Emotional Guidance System</name><id>10928054</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250632800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/10928054/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/global_7566145.jpeg</photo_url></item>