<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.212359</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 749-7160</phone><name>Wompatuck State Park</name><city>Hingham</city><id>726971</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.859782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Burn some calories, stretch your legs, enjoy nature and chat with like minded folks while walking  4-5 miles at Wompatuck State Park. The walk should take about 2 hours depending on our pace (we'll base that on the group's fitness and comfort level.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Please arrive by 6:20pm. Due to limited day light hours, we are leaving promptly at 6:30pm for the walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located just a 35-minute drive from downtown Boston, Wompatuck State Park offers 262 wooded campsites (140 of them with electricity), 12 miles of paved bicycle trails, and many miles of wooded bridle paths and hiking trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most notable features of the Park is Mt. Blue Spring which is a popular source of fresh drinking water. Visitors can help themselves for free. The park is named for an Indian chief the local colonists knew as Josiah Wompatuck. In 1665, Chief Wompatuck deeded the park and the surrounding land to the English settlers. During WWII the park was used as an ammunition depot by the US military. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recommended: &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Snacks (fruit/granola bars, etc.)  &lt;br /&gt;Water/sports drink  &lt;br /&gt;Sturdy shoes (although terrain will be flat) &lt;br /&gt;Bug spray &lt;br /&gt;Flashlight (just incase)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out the website at &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/d.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;. for more information about the park.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer: Elaine (AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fees: $2 pp for non-annual members &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum/maximum attendance: Minimum of 4 people (incl. organizers) by 6pm on Wed. July 29th. Less than 4 people RSVP'd yes by then, will cancel. Maximum amount: 25 members (incl. organizers).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: Wed., July 29th 6pm. After that time please email or contact an organizer directly.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wompatuck State Park is located near Hingham on Boston's South Shore.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South and Cape Cod: Rte 3 North to Exit 14 and the interscetion with Rte. 228. Follow Rte. 228 North approximately 5 miles to Free Street on the right. Turn right onto Free St. one mile to the park entrance on the right. Continue straight through the park and you will see the &lt;b&gt;visitor center&lt;/b&gt; on the right. Park in parking lot there.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: Follow Rte. 3 South to exit 14 and and the intersection with Rte. 228. Follow Rte. 228 North approximately 5 miles to the intersection with Free St. on the right. Turn right onto Free St. and follow it one mile to the Park entrance on the right. Continue straight through the park and you will see the &lt;b&gt;visitor center&lt;/b&gt; on the right. Park in parking lot there.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the parking lot at the Visitor's Center</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249516395000</updated><rating><average>4.28999996185</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246230579000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening Walk at Wompatuck State Park</name><id>10755366</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248993000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10755366/</event_url></item>