<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boston ATP &amp;amp; WLP User's Group:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Boston Fidelity ATP &amp;amp; WLP Users...we are now 57 members strong!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We meet at MIT Bldg E51 Rm 345 (note room change) or an empty room near it! Here's the map &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?mapterms=e51" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Our mtg format is always Open Discussion to &amp;quot;MAXIMIZE LEARNING&amp;quot; while staying on topic &amp;amp; off war stories! All Fidelity User's are encouraged to offer demonstrations of their Fidelity &amp;quot;Styles, Tricks &amp;amp; Tips&amp;quot; to the Group. Simply email me in advance so we can plan the meeting accordingly?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This Month's flexible &amp;amp; fun Agenda&lt;/b&gt; is (arrive when you can):&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5:00pm Eric demonstrates LIVE extended hours trading&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;6:00pm Learning to use Fidelity software w/General Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;7:00pm Jeff &amp;amp; Robert facilitate two WLP learning sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;7:55pm we will take a short break.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;8:05pm Eric facilitates ATP learning sessions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;9:00pm Detailed Q&amp;amp;A on content of above 2 Learning Sessions&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;9:30-10pm Approx End (you can leave whenever you want)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The focus of the meeting will be:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use Fidelity Wealth Lab Pro for &amp;quot;Creating &amp;amp; Backtesting Trading Strategies&amp;quot;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to use Fidelity Active Trader Pro to &amp;quot;Optimize Swing Trading &amp;amp; Day Trading&amp;quot;!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please always have the NEWEST versions of ATP &amp;amp; WLP downloaded, installed &amp;amp; fully usable as we will not have time to help you with this. If you need help call Fidelity 800 Support or go into a Fidelity Office TODAY and get it done asap so you are comfortable!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If possible bring your laptops w/power &amp;amp; extension cords to do both of the above LIVE with us or come prepared to take very detailed notes. If you have never connected to MIT's wireless then arrive early &amp;amp; we'll HELP you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Anyone is WELCOME, not just Fidelity customers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;About Our Group and Fidelity Tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fidelity's Active Trader Pro (ATP) and Wealth Lab Pro (WLP) are powerful programs. We are meeting to collaborate on improving our skills &amp;amp; developing usable strategies for Active Trader Pro &amp;amp; Wealth Lab Pro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group is for those interested in learning Active Trader Pro and Wealth Lab Pro. We will exchange ideas, research strategies for trading including back testing, buying and selling stocks and options using automated alerts and auto-execution with both Active Trader Pro and Wealth Lab Pro. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the first floor lobby of MIT Building E-51 adjacent to the parking lot entrance. We will begin by discussing how to set up and navigate in these programs. We will also brainstorm possible profitable strategies that can be tested. Please familiarize yourself with the programs and bring ideas about which strategies you would like to test.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our Group's Fidelity Vice President is Mahlon Williams who attends our meetings.&lt;br /&gt;Our Group's Fidelity contact is Mike Saniuk in Cambridge MA office=1-800-273-0130 x54460&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239225188000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238424082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston ATP &amp; WLP Users Group</name><id>10069434</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239051600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/10069434/</event_url></item>