<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Mirror&lt;/b&gt; by Andrei Tarkovsky (1974, 108 min.) &lt;b&gt;Actual screening time at the MFA is 8 pm.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the late start-time, I thought it would be best for us to meet before the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Alas, Symphony Hall opens this week and all the local restuarants will be packed and so we will be meeting at The Atrium at Northeastern. For those unfamiliar with the Atrium, there are a number of tables inside the building directly behind Au Bon Pain. Boloca and Q'Doba are both in the vicinity as well. I'll be there with a bright red Meetup Sign, so you should have no problem spotting us. This is right on Huntington Ave down about 100 yards from where the E-line stops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrei Tarkovsky,  working under the constraints of the Soviet regime only directed 7 films, yet these films are  considered  to be some of the most poetic and influential of all  20th century filmakers . &lt;b&gt;The Mirror&lt;/b&gt; is his most personal .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For many, &lt;b&gt;The Mirror&lt;/b&gt; is simply Tarkovsky's masterpiece—his most ambitious and most emotionally wrenching film. The plot concerns a dying man who reflects back on his childhood during World War II, the postwar transformation of Russian society, and his difficult relations with his wife and his mother. Yet, the film is concerned less with the facts of the memories than the memory's textures: the precise feelings experienced at these moments. A collage of imagery—including dramatic sequences, personal memories, newsreels, dreams, and purely abstract passages—the film also liberally quotes from the poetry of Tarkovsky's father, Arseny. In a double role as both the narrator's estranged wife and his mother, Margareta Terekova is simply amazing.   MFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Here's a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.filmref.com/directors/dirpages/tarkovsky.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.filmref.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone will be  updated  with where and when we'll meet by Sept. 15th,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Tom will be at a table with a Big Red Meetup Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221950007000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219710958000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tarkovsky's The Mirror</name><id>8620462</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221777000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8620462/</event_url></item>