<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Westbound-behind Chuck E. Cheese)</address_2><address_1>3 Vision Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.300643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney Place Assisted Living</name><city>Natick</city><id>766030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The decision to reenter the workforce after a family hiatus can seem daunting: &amp;ldquo;Do I want to return to my prior profession, or try something new?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;What am I qualified to do after years at home?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;How can I strike the right balance between work and family?&amp;rdquo; "When is the right time to go back?" Many women discover that their professional dreams and motivations have changed. Most women feel their skills are rusty, their network is weak, and/or they have failed to keep abreast of industry trends. In this presentation you will learn how to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Know when the time is right to go back to work&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Identify your marketable skills and interests&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Evaluate your work+life objectives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Discover the work that&amp;rsquo;s right for you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Reenter the workforce with confidence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Revive your resume&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Leverage traditional and social networks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presented by Mary Kaye, founder of Comeback Moms, which guides women to find the work that&amp;rsquo;s right for them. She has over 20 years of experience, as a Navy pilot, corporate director, mother and career coach, helping individuals and professionals perform beyond their expectations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This discussion is open to all who wish to attend, including visitors!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by the MetroWest Boston chapter of Mothers &amp;amp; More. With over 200 members from Framingham, Natick and surrounding areas, Mothers &amp;amp; More provides information, support, and fun for both working and stay-at-home moms, with children of all ages. Non-mobile infants welcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327542419000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326616151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Going Back To Work: Tackling the Big Questions - When? How? and What?</name><id>48156592</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327537800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/48156592/</event_url></item>