<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey Guys,&lt;br /&gt;  Straight from the polls, we're planning our next read.  We're really mixing it up this summer, and throwing a Thursday into the mix.  We'll plan on heading back to the yard unless the weather tells us otherwise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Black Swan by Thomas Mann&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://search.barnesandnoble.com/The-Black-Swan/Thomas-Mann/e/9780520070080" target="_blank"&gt;http://search.barnesa...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Mann's bold and disturbing novella, written in 1952, is the feminine counterpart of his masterpiece Death in Venice. Written from the point of view of a woman in what we might now call mid-life crisis, The Black Swan evinces Mann's mastery of psychological analysis and his compelling interest in the intersection of the physical and the spiritual in human behavior. It is startlingly relevant to current discussions of the politics of the body, male inscriptions of the feminine, and discourse about and of women. The new introduction places this dramatic novella in the context of contemporary feminist and literary concerns, bringing it to the attention of a new generation of readers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, plan on hitting Harvard Yard (meet on the stairwell to the right of John Harvard's statue if you're facing him).  I'll have a blue bag and backpack in tow, and we'll be sitting on a large blue beach towel.  If it's actively raining between 6:30-7, plan on braving the fans and heading to Au Bon Pain in Harvard Square.  Otherwise, we'll take a group vote as to where we place our tushes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251050370000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247436959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers: The Black Swan by Thomas Mann</name><id>10860267</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250204400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/10860267/</event_url></item>