<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>420 Totten Pond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-0100</phone><name>Hilton Garden Inn Hotel</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669398</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.254820</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.bostonareia.com/meetings.php" target="_blank"&gt;For More Info Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://BostonAREIA.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Hilton Garden Inn, 420 Totten Pond Rd., Waltham, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;November 15, 2007 - Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mik Collins of Rehablist&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:30 PM - Networking and Meet the Vendors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 PM - New Member/Visitors Orientation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How your local business, especially real estate investors, can quickly dominate internet&lt;br /&gt;lead generation directly to your business in your town beating your competition with just the click of a mouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you'd like to easily obtain a steady stream of hot real estate deals or customers for your local real estate investing business, boost your advertising response and track every penny you spend on ads, then this might be the most important meeting you ever attend on Internet marketing......&lt;br /&gt;The problem with all this Internet marketing stuff is that it's so darn complicated and time consuming. You need a simple way to get the results you need, leveraging the huge power of the Internet, without the long learning curve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - You don't know where to start? How would you even know if you did it right? &lt;br /&gt; - Does this language sound like Greek to you? Click through rates, Pay for Inclusion, PPC (pay per click), Landing pages, Relevancy rate, Search Engine Optimization, Organic vs. paid listings, SEO (search engine optimization)... .... &lt;br /&gt; - Which search engines should you start with? You know you want to be found on the Internet, to use the Internet to bring in more business, but where do you stab? I guarantee that this program will cut months off your learning curve. You won't have to waste thousands of dollars just to ''figure it out.? &lt;br /&gt;Hi, for those of you I haven't met yet my name is Mike Collins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you'll learn:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - What makes a good buying or lead generation website &lt;br /&gt; - How to participate even if you don?t have a website yet. Yes with just and email address you may be able to do as well as the guys who spend thousands on websites . &lt;br /&gt; -Why personal real estate wholesale ?selling? sites are a waste of money. &lt;br /&gt; -How to drive hot prospects to your buying sites &lt;br /&gt; -How to get free listings on major search engines &lt;br /&gt; -Exactly how to sell your houses on the net &lt;br /&gt; -Learn how you can literally ?own? the Internet lead generation for hot deals in your marketplace. &lt;br /&gt; -Why some sites are a waste of money and time &lt;br /&gt; -What?s the difference between free listing and paid listings? &lt;br /&gt; -Which sites are better and which is brings more leads? &lt;br /&gt; -How to register your sites for free on the major search engines. &lt;br /&gt; -How to vault directly to the top of the search engines ? and stay there. &lt;br /&gt; -What's the deal with these national website that you can belong to like IBuyHouses.com and WeBuyHouses.com? How can you profit by working with them? Or can you? I unlock the secrets. &lt;br /&gt; -How to own your part of the valuable ?online real estate? that makes this all possible &lt;br /&gt; -How the pay per click wars going on in every industry (including real estate) can be used to your benefit. We'll also be doing a review of &amp;quot;The Big Boys&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;Ever wonder what the deal is with all those house buying sites that seem to dominate the first few &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bernadette</member_name><member_id>4477491</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195339209000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192746775000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Make a fortune with Internet Bandit Signs!</name><id>6575679</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195165800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/6575679/</event_url></item>