<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>AL-r' s kayak rental</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per kayak rented</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Paddle Mansfield Hollow Lake! With the AMC and / or AL-r...if there is a extra kyak..or i just swim...&lt;br /&gt;some can play around in the areas and switch yaks....dont matter to me...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK YOU CAN PADDLE WITH THE AMC Or seperate with anyone else for a more social discovery..or if you want to paddle closer to someone. to a more secluded area......social discovery...hmm a new line..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think its easier for everyone if i just stay parked in the boat launch area till its picanick time....at least you can find me...LOOK FOR THE ORANGE CONES...im going to get close to the water as i can...dont like carrieing them yaks..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;when its over..food tiem in the other area, ...&lt;br /&gt;Ok i see a bit cooler..a bit windy..but should be pretty good...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK if any new persons are comming go to the boat launch area...first and fins us...might as well use that as our &amp;quot;PLACE&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Oh forgot  THA SHABOO thing is in willymantic starting about 5..maybe a plan for that...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The following is from the AMC website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activity: Paddling  &lt;br /&gt;Status: OPEN  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Mellow 4-hour paddle on peaceful lake. Excellent for beginners. You must provide your own boat, no loaners available and leader has no info on where to rent. Lifejacket required. Bring food and water. Paddlers under 18 must be with parent/guardian. Contact leader for more info. Meet at 10 am. Directions: I-84 Exit 68 to Rte. 195 South for 11 miles. Go 0.5 miles past Rte. 89, left on Bassett Bridge Rd. Go 1.4 miles to boat launch on the left.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Related Website(s):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct-amc.org/flatwater/index.shtm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct-amc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/cwp/view.asp?A=2716&amp;amp;Q=325236" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Date(s): August 18, 2007 (Sat)  &lt;br /&gt;Location: Mansfield,  Connecticut, East of River,  CT  &lt;br /&gt;Sponsoring Chapter: Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;Leader: Tom Ebersold &lt;br /&gt;bikehikekayak123@sbcglobal.net  &lt;br /&gt;Registration is not required for this trip. However, you may wish to contact us if you have any questions. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If the group with the AMC is too big for Tom, i will take our group for a matching or crossing trip in the same areas...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RAIN CANCELS THE EVENT.. I will update as the event draws closer..and as usual my part of the trip dosent end when the thers go home...&lt;br /&gt;its usually cook dinner and have a fire pit going later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I only have 4 yaks available to rent out now....so you better know which one you fit in..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Hollow Boat Launch: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-84, south on rte 195 (exit 68) through Storrs to Mansfield ctr (about 11 miles from 84)&lt;br /&gt;Go 0.5 mile past rte 89 junction and turn left onto Bassset Bridge rd at the stoplight, should see Mansfield Hollow Park sign. (licquer store at the intersection too)&lt;br /&gt;Will see a picknick area on left go a bit further apx 0.5 miles to the access right before the bridge on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-384, follow rte 6 to toward Willimantic. &lt;br /&gt;6 and 66 will intersect at a light. Take a left on to 6. &lt;br /&gt;Follow ths highway to the second exit, go straight (=rte633 or s. frontage rd.) it is acually a parallel to rte6 connector to rte 195, &lt;br /&gt;Signs for UCONN should be there somewhere too, &lt;br /&gt;Go north on rte 195 toward UCONN for about 2 miles then turn right at the onto Basset Bridge Rd, same info from here as above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have the blue Toyota Avalon with the kayaks on a old sailboat trailer. maybe even one kayak with a 55 horsepower motor on it and a torpedo prop... &lt;br /&gt;The RedNeck Jet....runs on pure moonshine...&lt;br /&gt;That will get that mother in law over the dam in no time...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For users of GPS or Mapquest..&lt;br /&gt;use 300 Bassetts Bridge Road, Mansfield Center, CT&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1188861434000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186400378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>UPDATE:Paddle at Mansfield Hollow/Dam Area With the AMC</name><id>6132467</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187445600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6132467/</event_url></item>