<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Rock Climbing Parents/uncles/Aunts - let the kids in on the fun too! I'm hosting a Kid's climbing event at MetroRock. It's a joint event with my Parent's Meetup and Hope Fellowship Church in Cambridge. Cost is $11 per child.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A couple of BELAYERS are needed - FREE (same-day) day pass if you can help out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good, healthy fun for you and the kid(s) in your life. SO ditch the Saturday morning cartoons and join us for some climbing. What could be better than that? We'll bring in some apres-climb pizzas for lunch too if there's interest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metrorock is hard to find for first time visitors. So if you find yourself going in circles here are some hints - From the traffic circle near Wellington Station take Santili Highway towards Best Buy and Mellon: &lt;br /&gt;If Best Buy is on your right and the Mellon building is on your left as you are going away from the circle, you are on the correct road. Then, take a left when you see a sign that says MetroRock. This sign is very very easy to miss as it is quite dark at night. Also, the road is full of potholes so drive slowly. Then take the next left to MetroRock. &lt;br /&gt;Or, see &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock...." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.metrorock....&lt;/a&gt;. for directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The gym also has a shuttle to the gym from the T - Orange Line @ Wellington Station if you don't have a car.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wait at the picnic table for a while.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin</member_name><member_id>4202767</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246320202000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244846774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>KID'S Rock Climbing at MetroRock!</name><id>10640250</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246113000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/10640250/</event_url></item>