<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Faneuil Hall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>417-496-1973</phone><name>Faneuil Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>821340</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055740</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What happens when you mix a Bar Crawl, a Booze Cruise and Pirates?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You get the Crawl In Boston Pirate Crawl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Saturday June 9th, we'll be bringing you the 4th edition of the finest themed bar crawls that Boston has to offer. It's time to kick off the summer with the return of the Pirate Crawl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the stops will take us onto a boat for a scenic trip of the Boston Harbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing can beat the feeling of going out on the water aboard the Provincetown II, Boston Harbor's largest cruise ship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the views of Boston's glorious skyline and the beautiful harbor islands from the ship's immaculately maintained and expansive open decks. In the grand tradition of coastal steamers, the Provincetown II will provide you with unequaled spaciousness and simple elegance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ship is outfitted with table seating, perimeter seating, a fully enclosed deck, semi enclosed deck, and the enormous top deck. Along with the ship's fully stocked bars, the Provincetown II's large dance areas will ensure a wonderful time on the water, in all weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the ship, we'll be navigating around Boston to the best bars the city has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limited Tickets Available!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much more info including tickets and pictures from the past 3 years at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://crawlinboston.com/pirate" class="linkified"&gt;http://crawlinboston.com/pirate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339272722000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Lifers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonnights</urlname><id>860845</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Nights</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334843970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pirate Pub Crawl / Booze Cruise</name><id>61243992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339261200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonnights/events/61243992/</event_url></item>