<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bay State Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.349949</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bay State Underground at BU</name><city>Boston</city><id>777983</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095289</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This week, we'll hit a reading before we gather round the table at a local watering hole -- Uno's? -- for a discussion of our recent writing. Bring manuscripts as usual if you plan to join us afterwards for this pubbery. If you get lost or find yourself in a moment of literary panic, don't hesitate to call me: 617-935-4951.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The reading: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Bay State Underground&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by Boston University and AGNI Magazine&lt;br /&gt;In the basement of 236 Bay State Road (BU East T-stop, Green Line)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The readers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom Yuill: Tom's work has appeared or is forthcoming in Newsday, Agni, A Public Space, The New Journal, Slate, Visions and Coelecanth, among others. He has read or taught poetry at the University of Pennsylvania, Harvard University, Old Dominion University, the University of Iowa and the Massachusetts College of Art. he currently teaches at Boston University, and is an Associate Professor at the New England Institute of Art.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Swann Li: Swann Li was born in the 1970's China. Having lived at different levels of China's social strata, she writes on China's rapid changes, growing gaps in Chinese society, and Chinese expatriates' and emigrants' life in America. She is currently pursuing an M.F.A. in Creative Writing (Fiction) in Boston University.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hank Backer: Hank hails from Northern Kentucky, where he studied poetry at Thomas More College, a small liberal arts college. He now attends Boston University's Poetry program.  He's been previously published in The Rectangle and Words, Thomas More's literary magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 7:00, reading starts at 7:30. The Underground is BYOB this year so don’t forget to bring your beverage of choice.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228695167000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228404983000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bay State Underground, and Poets' Pub following</name><id>9279719</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228521600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/9279719/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/e/5/global_187765.jpeg</photo_url></item>