<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Fosters Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01002</zip><lat>42.510390</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 355-2853</phone><name>UMass</name><city>Amherst</city><id>791625</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.543185</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;NECCC 65th Annual Photographic Conference&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To be held at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst, MA&lt;br /&gt;July 16, 17 &amp;amp; 18, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Come join us for a wonderful weekend of learning, sharing, and camaraderie. There will be&lt;br /&gt;programs of interest for all levels of photographers. Back by popular demand, David Middleton&lt;br /&gt;will present a program ‘On Becoming a Pro’. David is a Nikon ‘Legends Behind the Lens’ speaker.&lt;br /&gt;The popular commercial photographer, Jack Reznicki, a ‘Canon Explorer of Light’, will present ‘A&lt;br /&gt;Photographer’s Life’. The talented Nature photographer, Robert O’Toole, will present a program on&lt;br /&gt;Nature Photography sponsored by Sigma Corporation of America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Our feature presentation will be ‘Special Moments and Special Places’ presented&lt;br /&gt;by Darrell Gulin of Sammamish, WA. Darrell is a ‘Canon Explorer of Light’. Darrell&lt;br /&gt;has been photographing for over 25 years, marketing his work for the last 23&lt;br /&gt;years and has been a full time Nature/Travel Photographer for the last 17 years.&lt;br /&gt;He is the past President of the North American Nature Photography Association&lt;br /&gt;(NANPA). He has been their keynote speaker and leads their pros’ meeting. His&lt;br /&gt;photographs have been published in: Outdoor Photographer, Newsweek, National Geographic,&lt;br /&gt;Audubon, National Wildlife, Birder's World, Sunset, Nature Conservancy, Popular Photography, Natures&lt;br /&gt;Best, and many more. He is an accomplished speaker/teacher whose credits are too numerous to&lt;br /&gt;mention. He travels around the world capturing special moments photographically.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more information and Registration Form:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.neccc.org/NECCC%202010%20Preview.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;NECCC_2010_Preview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The conferacne will include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speakers for our Camera College include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Hassell Take Photos; Give Life Sponsored by Hunt’s Photo and Video&lt;br /&gt;Joe LeFevre Panoramic Possibilities Sponsored by PrintMakers&lt;br /&gt;Ron Magill A Walk on the Wild Side Sponsored by Nikon&lt;br /&gt;David Middleton On Becoming a Pro Sponsored by Nikon&lt;br /&gt;Charles Needle Impressionistic Photography Sponsored by Lensbaby&lt;br /&gt;Robert O’Toole Alaskan Safari Sponsored by Sigma Corporation of America&lt;br /&gt;Wendell Phillips Passage to the Global Community&lt;br /&gt;Jack Reznicki A Photographer’s Life Sponsored by Canon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loaner Equipment – Canon and Nikon representatives will have top of the line equipment for attendees to borrow&lt;br /&gt;by the hour for use during the weekend. Flash programs for Nikon and Canon will be held.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-Conference 3 hour workshops - Additional fee - Must Register (for one or the other).&lt;br /&gt;Photoshop (Basic &amp;amp; Intermediate) Space limited, laptop necessary. Tom and Lisa Cuchara, instructors.&lt;br /&gt;Photoshop Lightroom Space limited, laptop necessary. Fred Drury, instructor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-Conference Portfolio Review by top New England Photographers.&lt;br /&gt;Forty-five minutes per person, maximum 10 images - Space limited. Additional Fee - Must Register&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Beginner class for first time digital camera users&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Hands-on class for Digital SLR&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Camera College classes with practical application in Hi-Jinx: High Speed Flash and Macro photography. Bring your&lt;br /&gt;cameras.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Vendors&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Competitions (print and digital)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Models&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Hi-Jinx&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Free camera testing&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Door prizes&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9679; Air Conditioned dorms available&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Harding</member_name><member_id>9811788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279505537000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266933766000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>65th ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF THE NEW ENGLAND CAMERA CLUB COUNCIL</name><id>12683043</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279288800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/12683043/</event_url></item>