<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 876-0999</phone><name>Casablanca</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669159</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121340</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.casablanca-restaurant.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://www.casablanca-restaurant.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.casablanca...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-four hours from the event and you are not able to attend, you MUST call or text Tonya at (617) 445-7549. An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The holiday bustle is over, and now it's time to sit back and relax. If you've already blown your New Year's diet, well, then, come on out and blow it some more! Kick off 2008 with a sumptuous Mediterranean-themed brunch spent with old friends and new at this charming Harvard Square bistro.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A bit of background about the establishment: Yes, that Casablanca.The classic movie starring Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman was the original inspiration for this Harvard Square restaurant, right down to the 25-foot murals by David Omar White. When it first opened in 1955, it fast became a beloved, if culinary unambitious, American joint. After falling victim to urban renewal in 1990, it was resurrected by a team of investors led by Sari Abul-Jubein in 1991, this time with a menu including North African influences. Since then, the food has taken center stage at Casablanca, with award-winning presentations of sophisticated Mediterranean fare. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RULES OF ENGAGEMENT:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow foodies' time by arriving promptly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES afterward and you have not attended, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours, without an explanation, it will count as a NO-SHOW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, to those on the wait list,&lt;br /&gt;to the organizer, as well as the restaurant whose staff size is based on our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're removed and have extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so rate the event by completing the survey afterward.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barring a blizzard, we'll meet outside. The restaurant is housed in the same building as the famous Brattle Theatre,  and is located beneath Cafe Algiers. (It has its own separate entrance outside and downstairs.)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199972363000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196359001000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Post-holiday frenzy brunch at Casablanca</name><id>6825516</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199637000000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6825516/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/6/global_2870214.jpeg</photo_url></item>