<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1></address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03842</zip><lat>42.939126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hampton Beach</name><city>Hampton</city><id>760062</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.828385</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;If you are not planning on attending the Whale Watch then come spend the day at the beach....&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets go out for a day at the beach and watch the sculptures take shape.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sand Sculpture Competition is a yearly event at Hampton and is spectacular to see. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Here is a little history&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It all began in 2000 with twenty-five cents. One quarter. The New Hampshire Quarter to be precise.&lt;br /&gt;Local artist and master sand sculptor Greg Grady was commissioned by the U.S. Mint to create a larger than life replica of the new tail side edition New Hampshire quarter out of ten tons of sand during the Hampton Beach Childrens Festival. At the time, it was just a part if the statewide celebration held for the release of that coin. It was something Hampton Beach had never seen the likes of before!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following year, the first annual Hampton Beach Master Sand Sculpture Competition was held. When 220 tons of imported sand was trucked into the beach with Greg Grady and his 'bunch' laboring for five days on the sponsor site followed by a three day competition of ten world class masters creating their own unique sculpture, a new era was born and sand sculpture had arrived to the northeast. Over the course of the event nothing but sand, water, and a bit of their own creativity is used to create astonishing works of art out of shapeless heaps of sand. When completed they are sprayed with windscreen (a solution of school glue and water) to protect them from the elements and remain standing for viewing for weeks creating a free museum of master pieces on the beach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our Event Plan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Seashell Stage at 11:00am, enjoy a day at the beach and watch the sand sculptures take shape.  So grab your beach chair, your towel, your Sun block and your cooler and come on down to the beach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because this is a crowd drawing event, I will be getting to the beach by 10am to reserve a spot for the group, if anyone would like to arrive early and assist me it would greatly be appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind that Rain will cancel this event, please check back prior to departing for this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is interesting in carpooling from the Newburyport Park N Ride, I will be leaving from the lot about 9:15am, please let me know if you are planning on carpooling.  If anyone is interested in organizing a later carpool, please let Donna or Janet know and we can post it on the site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children are welcome at this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the beach.  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Restrooms by the Seashell Stage</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245078354000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243821693000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hampton Beach Sand Sculpture Competition</name><id>10540016</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244905200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/10540016/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>