<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>89 South Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351844</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-439-3142 </phone><name>The NonProfit Center </name><city>Boston</city><id>1058586</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.057489</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice is co-sponsoring this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be the Media! helps participants understand the link between strategic communications and organizing strategies as well as learn essential communications tools and techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year's theme is &lt;strong&gt;supporting civic engagement:&lt;/strong&gt; effective communications tools and strategies to mobilize your constituency and stakeholders. Workshop topics will include: mobile phone blogging; an introduction to media basics, messaging through creative action, communicating across differences and conducting a website audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Date: Thursday, December 6, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 9am - 5:30pm (lunch provided)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Third Sector New England's NonProfit Center, 89 South Street in Boston (close to South Station)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $40, includes lunch; scholarships available; all are invited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href="http://bethemediaevent.org/cat/workshops-2012/"&gt;Workshops&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://bethemediaevent.org/cat/presenters-2012/"&gt;Presenters&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://bethemediaevent.org/cat/allies-sponsors/"&gt;Sponsors&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bethemediaevent.org/register/"&gt;Click here to register.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details are on the website: &lt;a href="http://www.bethemediaevent.org"&gt;www.bethemediaevent.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also sponsored by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.resistinc.org/"&gt;Resist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resist is a progressive foundation that supports grassroots organizing for peace, economic, social and environmental justice, and provides political education for social change activism. For 40 years, RESIST has funded groups that challenge reactionary government policies, corporate arrogance, and right-wing fanaticism through organizing, education and action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a nonprofit organization itself, RESIST relies on contributors with a strong commitment to social, economic and environmental justice, and a firm belief in the need to build grassroots movements and capacity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://progressivecommunicators.net"&gt;The Progressive Communicators Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Progressive Communicators Network  is a project of &lt;a href="http://www.spiritinaction.net/"&gt;Spirit in Action&lt;/a&gt;. We’re a national network of people who work as communications professionals or organizers who are focused on racial or economic justice, and who use communications tools and strategy. We teach each other, we support each other, and we help each other navigate the tough world of social justice communications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the heart of PCN’s work are deep personal and political relationships based on trust, integrity, and accountability that bridge identities, communities, organizations, issues, movements and ideologies. Learn more about us at &lt;a href="http://progressivecommunicators.net"&gt;www.progressivecommunicators.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.presspasstv.org"&gt;Press Pass TV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press Pass TV is an award-winning organization that uses the power of media arts to provide meaningful education and employment for youth living in underserved neighborhoods. We offer creative outlets as an alternative to violence, teach life-sustaining skills and empower communities to find shared solutions and envision a better world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://eyeoftheday.org"&gt;MataHari: Eye of the Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MataHari: Eye of the Day is a Greater Boston organization of women of color, immigrant women and families who organize as sisters, workers, and survivors for personal and societal transformation, justice and human rights. We organize domestic workers, provide case management and survivor services, and fight for immigrant and women’s rights including those who suffer domestic, workplace and/or systemic violence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.communitychangeinc.org"&gt;Community Change, Inc. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Community Change was born out of the Civil Rights Movement and in response to the Kerner Commission which named racism as “a white problem.” CCI has done what few organizations are willing to do: shine a spotlight on the roots of racism in white culture with the intention of dealing with racism at its source, as well as with its impact on communities of color.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jessica Critcher</member_name><member_id>46812122</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354833661000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354211369000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>7th annual Be the Media! Mini-Conference</name><id>93350052</id><duration>30600000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354802400000</time><rsvp_limit>1</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/93350052/</event_url></item>