<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We'll be joining in from 9 AM to about Noon on the trail projects that the Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) has organized to clear blowdowns on the Mohawk Trail. We'll meet at the hiker parking lot on Rt. 4 on the east side of Cornwall Bridge (details below). Tools will be provided. Be dressed for outdoor work. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NATIONAL TRAILS DAY PROJECTS ON THE MOHAWK TRAIL&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;*** Weather update (6/5/09): Prediction is excellent! Sunny, 0% for rain, starts out at 60 F then to 70 F by Noon. Same and 70's all the way to sundown! ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CONTEXT...&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;American Hiking Society's National Trails Day&lt;/b&gt;® (NTD), is held the first Saturday of every June and with more than 1000 events hosted by trail and community groups, public agencies, and businesses from coast to coast, is America's largest celebration of trails and the outdoors.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.americanhiking.org/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.americanhi...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Mohawk Trail&lt;/b&gt; was established as a Blue-Blazed Hiking Trail May 8, 1988 and is maintained by the &lt;b&gt;Connecticut Forest and Park Association&lt;/b&gt;. It follows the former eastern or traditional route of the Appalachian Trail, which was relocated when a new AT footpath was opened west of the Housatonic River. At 23.4 miles, the trail crosses more than a half dozen summits 1,200 feet or higher in the Litchfield Hills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctwoodlands.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctwoodland...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC)&lt;/b&gt; was Founded in 1876, the Appalachian Mountain Club is America's oldest nonprofit conservation and recreation organization. They promote the protection, enjoyment, and wise use of the mountains, rivers, and trails of the Appalachian region. They believe that the mountains and rivers have an intrinsic worth and also provide recreational opportunity, spiritual renewal, and ecological and economic health for the region. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/about/mission.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PROJECT DETAILS...&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To clear blowdowns - fallen trees and branches blocking the trail. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO EXPERIENCE NECESSARY!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tools and training will be provided by CROTON POINT PARK.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Optional tools to bring&lt;/b&gt; (put your name on them just in case): &lt;br /&gt;* Loppers &lt;br /&gt;* Hand Shears &lt;br /&gt;* Bow Saws &lt;br /&gt;* Chain Saws (and all related safety equipment, must be able to lug over trail to working sites) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required items:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* MUST wear Boots &lt;br /&gt;* MUST wear Work/Gardening Gloves (If you have extra Gloves it would be great if you could bring them) &lt;br /&gt;* BUG SPRAY (headnet may be helpful) &lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;* Plenty of water (at least 2-3 LITERS) &lt;br /&gt;* Lunch and snacks &lt;br /&gt;* Hat or bandanna is recommended &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests are allowed. No dogs. Kids over 14 are welcome who WANT to be there and can (and will) work!  &lt;br /&gt;We will work for 3 hours - until approx 12:00 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AFTER THE WORK IS DONE...&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It would be great if we could do a pot-luck BBQ at a nearby facility. Please post comments on the event as to desires to stay together for this and details. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GETTING THERE...&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please meet at 9:00 AM, at hiker parking lot on Rt. 4 (Furnace Brook Rd.) on the east side of Cornwall Bridge. Parking for 10 or more vehicles. Unpaved parking lot marked with &amp;quot;Hiker Parking&amp;quot; sign. Located immediately northeast of triangle at junction of Rt. 4 and Rt. 7. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMC Contact:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Henry Edmonds &lt;br /&gt;(203) 426-6459 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/b&gt; for meetup location via MapQuest (Furnace Brook Rd./Rt. 4, Cornwall Bridge, CT):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Cornwall+Bridge&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=%5B300-360%5D+Furnace+Brook+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06754&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.81875&amp;amp;longitude=-73.36775&amp;amp;geocode=STREET" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;(Lat=41.81875, Long=-73.36775) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark green Dodge Caravan, CT plates. Meet at event location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244466485000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243663940000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Trail Days Project on Mohawk Trail CT</name><id>10528265</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244293200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10528265/</event_url></item>