<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Boston Weblogger Meetup happens on the third Thursday of every month in conjunction with the weekly blog meeting at the Berkman Center for Internet &amp;amp; Society at Harvard. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: At this particular meeting on December 15th, the group will be meeting for dinner but there will *NOT* be a meeting at the Berkman Center.  If you would like to walk to the restaurant with part of the group, please meet at the Berkman Center at 7PM. Otherwise, everyone is meeting up at Grendel's Den in Harvard Square on Winthrop Street at 7:30 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is encouraged to RSVP but even if you do not see a lot of RSVPs here, there are usually at least 10 people at the meetup since it's held in conjunction with the Berkman group's meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Berkman Center for Internet &amp;amp; Society is located at 1587 Mass Avenue in Cambridge, MA in the Baker House at Harvard Law School. It's about a ten minute walk from both Harvard Square and Porter Square. You can also take the #77 bus between Harvard Square and Arlington Heights and ask for the stop at Harvard Law School. If you're driving you might be able to find parking along Mass Ave or you can park in one of the garages in Harvard Square and walk down Mass Ave to the Berkman Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/thursdaymeetings" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/thursdaymeetings" target="_blank"&gt;http://blogs.law.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emma</member_name><member_id>2161382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273539993000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Bloggers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>bloggers</urlname><id>21458</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston Area Weblogger Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1132488150000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Weblogger December Meetup</name><id>4804042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1134693000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bloggers/events/4804042/</event_url></item>