<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>591 Donald Lynch Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01503</zip><lat>42.353519</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Regal Solomon Pond Stadium 15</name><city>Marlborough</city><id>5001132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.615440</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: The movie starts at 8 pm. We will meet at 7:30 in the lobby BEFORE the ticket booths and to the right. If you need to change your RSVP to no after 5 pm or if you have trouble finding us at the theater, call 978-857-3734. Everyone is responsible for their own tickets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE THE DIFFERENT THEATER!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am experimenting with a different theater. If you RSVP no and the reason is the different theater (as opposed to not wanting to see the movie or it being a bad day or just not feeling like it), please say that in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual, time will be updated a few days before the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Andrew (Dane DeHaan) is a socially awkward, introverted teen whose main form of escape and expression is a video camera. But things begin to change when Andrew, his cousin Matt (Alex Russell) and popular classmate Steve (Michael B. Jordan) discover a&lt;/span&gt; mysterious substance that leaves them with incredible powers. As their abilities become more powerful, the teens' lives spin out of control when their darker sides begin to emerge. Andrew's camera captures the unfolding events.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the lobby to the right of the ticket booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle</member_name><member_id>2132838</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329972836000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328583029000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chronicle</name><id>51333752</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1329784200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/51333752/</event_url></item>