<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Market Talk by Jerry Zukowski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jerry Zukowski will be delivering our market talk this month.  He is a former mutual fund manager.&lt;br /&gt;This is our regular forum for market discussion. The talk starts with a market prediction by the speaker. The speaker then makes a short case for the prediction - about 10 minutes. The audience participation of this 30 minute talk should be 20 minutes. The discussion is lively; insights come from around the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Stock Picks by Chris Jones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your tickers - the group will analyze them on the fly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Feature Talk: The Chapman Wave, Stocks and the Market by Basil Chapman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Basil Capman returns with a feature length talk on his Chapman wave and what its telling us about stocks and the market.  He will be analyzing several charts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Feature Talk: A Simple Trading Strategy by Rondeau Flynn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investor/Trader Rondeau Flynn will discuss the ease and simplicity of trading just  one price pattern that can be found in any market, and any time frame.  He will outline the basis for a risk adjusted return that correlates with volatility, and show a unique way in how profits targets can be measured.  New and experienced traders  alike should benefit from a defined edge that this one sole price pattern presents. Working on his 4th trading manual due out next year, Rondeau Flynn will show how sometimes, simple really is better.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The agenda: &lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;7:10 Market Talk by Jerry Zukowski &lt;br /&gt;7:40 Stock Picks&lt;br /&gt;8:00 Break &lt;br /&gt;8:10 Feature Talk: The Chapman Wave, Stocks and the Market by Basil Chapman&lt;br /&gt;9:00 Feature Talk: A Simple Trading Strategy by Rondeau Flynn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING Announcement:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets during the hour from 5:30 PM to 6:50 PM. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to identify people who evidence expertise in particular interests we have virtual trading. &lt;br /&gt;To join in our virtual trading, go to this link for instructions and signup links:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd/browse_thread/thread/ff5e030eb15a6c7c" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food or drinks are not allowed in any MIT meeting room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254957345000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>65</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253025484000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Group September Meetup</name><id>11377532</id><headcount>67</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253746800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/11377532/</event_url></item>