<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Berkshires</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06757</zip><lat>41.679958</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Club Getaway</name><city>Kent</city><id>684911</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.490791</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us Oct 2nd -4th for an Amazing Fall Sports &amp;amp; FUN Weekend/ EARLY HALLOWEEN PARTY!!! &lt;br /&gt;Getaway at its most beautiful. The weather is perfect for NFL Coed Fantasy Football, hiking, biking, hay rides, pumpkin carving, apple pie baking , and the Halloween Fantasy Ball!! (Bring your costume) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://FunMeetupGetaway.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://FunMeetupGetaw...&lt;/a&gt; , click book now on the right , or call 917-868-4268 &lt;br /&gt;Join us this Weekend for a Fun weekend, Save $50 when mentioning FunMeetup by phone or typing FUN Meetup in the comment box when signing up online for the upcoming Weekend!! (plus the free drink booklet if you call and text 917-868-4268 friday night at the welcome party @the boathouse!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://HalloweenWeekendGetaway.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://HalloweenWeeke...&lt;/a&gt; or http call Greg @ 917-868-4268 if any questions! &lt;br /&gt;A Vacation in a Weekend! &lt;br /&gt;Vacation! The word alone makes you happy. At Getaway you can get everything you want in a vacation in one amazing, affordable weekend. &lt;br /&gt;On a Getaway Vacation you'll do more in a weekend than most do all summer. Enjoy your favorite sports, activities and adventures…try something new…kick back and socialize…celebrate with great food and parties…relax and rediscover yourself. And become part of a fun-loving, adventure-seeking community. &lt;br /&gt;Everything you love to do is right here waiting for you and it’s all included in one low price. Just grab a friend, a loved one or come by yourself (and meet our group, NYMeetup, JMeetup or Fun Meetup /call Greg @ 917-868-4268 to meetup the first night @ the welcome party) and make new friends everywhere you go. And it’s all right here in the beautiful Berkshire Mountains of Kent, Connecticut, only 3 hours from Boston by car &lt;br /&gt;It’s the vacation you deserve, just when you need it most. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fall Sports and Fun Oct 2-4 &lt;br /&gt;Club Getaway is the perfect place to be this fall. The countryside is ablaze with color. The air is cool and crisp. It's the best time of year to enjoy your favorite sports and adventures. Hiking and biking in the Berkshires. Teaming up for touch football and volleyball. Swinging out on the tennis court and dance floor. Flying through the air on the trapeze or zip line. Plus all the other Getaway activities. &lt;br /&gt;In addition to all the cool Getaway stuff, our Fall Weekend is packed with special events. &lt;br /&gt;The Halloween Fantasy Ball &lt;br /&gt;Without a doubt, the best party of the year. We spend weeks decorating for this one. Think about your custome now. THere will be lots of prizes and surprises. &lt;br /&gt;The Haunted House &lt;br /&gt;Walk through the spookiest Haunted House you've ever been through...if you dare! &lt;br /&gt;Autumn Hikes &lt;br /&gt;The perfect time of year for hiking in New England. With hikes at all levels, you'll enjoy the countryside at its best. &lt;br /&gt;Watson Scavenger Hunt &lt;br /&gt;Join a team. Hunt for clues. Be the first to discover the booty! Watson Adventures brings its nationally reowned scavenger hunt to Club Getaway. &lt;br /&gt;Apple Pie Baking &lt;br /&gt;Our cooking class goes seasonal! Bake a beautiful apple pie to bring home to mom. &lt;br /&gt;Football &lt;br /&gt;What would fall be without football? Join in our co-ed touch football and let the excitement begin. &lt;br /&gt;Hayrides &lt;br /&gt;There's nothing quite like a hayride through the fall foilage. We've got the strumming guitars and hot apple cider. &lt;br /&gt;Pumpkin Carving &lt;br /&gt;This is anything but the pumpkin carving of your childhood. We've got all the pumpkins and all the tools for you to create a masterpiece! &lt;br /&gt;Fall Biking &lt;br /&gt;Theres nothing more beautiful than biking the Berkshires on a beautiful Autumn day. Rides for all levels. &lt;br /&gt;Al Hanneman's Volleyball Clinic &amp;amp; Tournament &lt;br /&gt;Bump, set and spike with Getaway's favorite team sports. Great clinics, tournaments and play. &lt;br /&gt;Sample Schedule/ From last time / Subject to Change... &lt;br /&gt;Friday Night &lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 9:00 pm Welcome Arrivals Begin! &lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 9:00 pm Join us for Welcome Drinks and Hors D'oeurves on the Lake Side Deck &lt;br /&gt;8:00 - 9:00 pm Meet the Staff and Weekend Campers &lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 10:30 pm Family Style Welcome Dinner with Free Flowing Wine in the Mountain House Dining Room &lt;br /&gt;10:30 pm Join us in The Boat House Lounge for Opening Party, Champagne and Dancing with DJ Craig Cruise. Or Play Volleyball &amp;amp; Basketball under the Lights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Morning &lt;br /&gt;8:00 am Early Risers! Morning Coffee and Continental Breakfast &lt;br /&gt;8:00 - 9:00 am Early Morning Mountain Hike &lt;br /&gt;8:30 - 10:00 am Sumptous Buffet Breakfast &lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 10:00 am Yoga with NYC's OM Yoga &lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 10:00 am Advanced Tennis Lessons with Pro Ken &lt;br /&gt;9:00 am - 7:00 pm Lounge by the Lake, Relax and Socialize on the Deck &lt;br /&gt;9:30 - 10:00 am Morning Stretch &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Basketball Clinic with Former NY Knicks Hollis Copeland &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Fly on the 350' Aerial Zip Line &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Cardio Kickboxing with Jen Fitness &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Intermediate Tennis Lessons with Pro Ken &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Mountain Bike on Single Track Trails for Beginners &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Rock Climb - Rappel Down a Rock Ledge &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Volleyball Clinic - Bump, Set &amp;amp; Spike &lt;br /&gt;10:30 am - 12:00 pm Road Biking - Easy Ride on 21 Speed Specialized Bikes &lt;br /&gt;10:30 am - 12:30 pm Hike Along the Appalachian Trail &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:00 pm Learn to Fly on the Trapeze &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:00 pm Pilates with Jen Fitness &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:00 pm Challenge the Climbing Wall &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 12:30 pm Arts &amp;amp; Crafts &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 12:30 pm Archery Class &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 12:30 pm Golf Lessons with Silo Ridge Pro &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm Bike Trip to Town of Kent &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm Mountain Hike to Scenic Overlook &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm Co-ed Volleyball - Open Play &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm 3 on 3 Basketball with Hollis Copeland &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm Beginner Tennis Lessons with Pro Ken &lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:00 pm Cooking Class with Connecticut Culinary Institute &lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:00 pm Trapeze &lt;br /&gt;1:00 - 2:00 pm International Lunch Buffet under the Tent &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Afternoon/Night &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:00 pm Tennis Tournament &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Basketball Clinic with Hollis Copeland &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Rock Climbing &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Intermidiate Road Biking - 10 miles &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Mountain Bike II - Single Track Trails Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Archery Class &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Co-ed Volleyball Tournament &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Latin and Swing Dance Class with Lucky &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:30 pm Walk to Kent for Shopping or Ice Cream &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 4:00 pm Advanced Trapeze &lt;br /&gt;2:30 - 4:30 pm Mountain Bike II - Single Track Trails Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;2:30 - 4:30 pm Arts &amp;amp; Crafts &lt;br /&gt;3:00 - 4:30 pm Fly on the Bungee Trampoline &lt;br /&gt;3:00 - 5:00 pm Scuba Class &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Advanced Road Bike &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Swing Dancing with Lucky &lt;br /&gt;3:30 - 5:00 pm Wine Tasting with Wine Expert Horst &lt;br /&gt;4:00 - 5:30 pm Co-ed Keg Softball &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Bike Trip to Town for Ice Cream &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Yoga with NYC's OM Yoga &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 5:30 pm Collage Art Class &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 7:00 pm Lakeside Happy Hour: Live Music, Complemantary BBQ Grill and Drink Specials &lt;br /&gt;4:30 - 6:00 pm Texas Hold'em Poker &lt;br /&gt;8:00 - 9:30 pm Restauratore Italiano under the Tent followed by Live Music &lt;br /&gt;9:30 pm Party at the Boat House Lounge with DJ . Dancing till the wee hours. &lt;br /&gt;12:00 am Midnight Campfire with Live Music and S'mores &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday &lt;br /&gt;8:30 am Early Morning Coffee and Continental Breakfast &lt;br /&gt;9:00 - 10:30 am Sumptous Buffet Breakfast &lt;br /&gt;9:00 am - 2:00 pm Lounge by the Lake, Relax and Socialize on the Deck &lt;br /&gt;9:30 - 10:00 am Early Morning Stretch &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Intermediate Tennis Lessons with Pro Ken &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Yoga with NYC's OM Yoga &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:00 am Volleyball Clinic - Bump, Set &amp;amp; Spike &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Bike to Town of Kent &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Single Track Trails for Beginners &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Golf Lesson with Silo Ridge Pro &lt;br /&gt;10:00 - 11:30 am Rock Climb - Rappel Down a Rock Ledge &lt;br /&gt;10:00 am - 12:30 pm Walk to Town &lt;br /&gt;10:30 am - 12:30 pm Arts &amp;amp; Crafts &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:00 pm Fly on the 350' Aerial Zip Line &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:00 pm Pilates with Jen Fitness &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:30 pm Archery Class &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:30 pm Mountain Hike to Scenic Overlook &lt;br /&gt;11:00 am - 12:30 pm Latin and Swing Dance Class with Lucky &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 12:30 pm Mountain Bike II - Single Track Trails Intermediate &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 12:30 pm Beginner Tennis Lessons with Pro Ken &lt;br /&gt;11:30 am - 1:00 pm Intermidiate Road Biking - 10 miles &lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:00 pm Dodgeball Team Challenge &lt;br /&gt;12:00 - 1:00 pm Kick Boxing with Jen Fitness &lt;br /&gt;12:30 - 2:00 pm Challenge the Climbing Wall &lt;br /&gt;12:30 - 2:00 pm 6 Mile Scenic Bike Trip &lt;br /&gt;1:00 - 2:00 pm Lakeside Live Reggae Band &lt;br /&gt;1:00 - 2:00 pm Fly on the Bungee Trampoline &lt;br /&gt;2:00 - 3:00 pm International BBQ Buffet Lunch &lt;br /&gt;2:30 pm Awards Presentation with CG Staff &lt;br /&gt;4:00 pm Hugs &amp;amp; Goodbyes Car and Bus Departure &lt;br /&gt;Any questions, Call Greg @ 917-868-4268 ! &lt;br /&gt;After signing up in advance (most weekends sell out weeks in advance) call and text Greg @ 917-868-4268 to meetup at the Welcome Party Friday Night! &lt;br /&gt;any questions, call Greg @ 917-868-4268, book now at &lt;a href="http://HalloweenWeekendGetaway.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://HalloweenWeeke...&lt;/a&gt; (Oct. 2nd/ OUR FINALE Getaway Weekend FOR THE YEAR / if you can't make this weekend), Remember to call and text greg @ 917-868-4268 Friday Night at the welcome party/boathouse to get your FREE DRINK TICKETS (in addition to the savings you get when you book by phone/ mention FUN MEETUP or type fun meetup in the comment box if signing up online! &lt;br /&gt;Join us this fall/ OCT 2nd. for an amazing weekend :) &lt;br /&gt;Sports, parties, friends, laughing, dancing, and everything else, Join us for an incredible getaway!!!! &lt;br /&gt;, It's a weekend you can't miss as we celebrate the end of the season!! &lt;br /&gt;Any questions, call me @ 917-868-4268 ! &lt;br /&gt;type Fun Meetup in the comment box to save $50 or call me @ 917-868-4268 if any questions, Don't Miss the water skiing, campfire, zip line, socializing, great music, lakeside live and all the fun ! &lt;br /&gt;Join us Oct 2nd -4th for Fall Sports &amp;amp; FUN Weekend/ EARLY HALLOWEEN PARTY!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://FunMeetupGetaway.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://FunMeetupGetaw...&lt;/a&gt; click book now on the right , or call 917-868-4268&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>call &amp; text Greg @ 917-868-4268 Friday Night @the boathouse welcome party for your free drink book (after typing or mentioning FunMeetup or Boston Meetup when booking) , meet us at the welcome party friday night at the boathouse</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>8121708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256250057000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonMeetup</urlname><id>1477254</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0400009155</group_lon><name>#1 Meetup - BOSTON MEETUP,  Travel&amp; Events, BOSTONMEETUP.org</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>100</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253217089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Sports&amp;Fun Weekend, EARLY HALLOWEEN PARTY,Relaxation,Socializing/Adventure!</name><id>11398936</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254517200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonMeetup/events/11398936/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/9/global_9285353.jpeg</photo_url></item>