<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rte 133</address_2><address_1>36 Essex Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.665812</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bruni’s Market</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>1028047</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.835214</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>2009 Castle Hill Summer Picnic Concerts presents Entrain is a Rock funk jam band!!  Spend an unforgettable evening of picnicking, dancing, and music at Castle Hill overlooking magnificent Crane Beach it’s an outing everyone will love!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting up: Seeing it is a work night and everyone may not be able to get there early let’s meetup at 7:00 in Bruni’s parking lot, plenty of free parking there and a safe place to leave your car.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking at Bruni’s Market Place, please park on the side away from the market and restaurant that way they shouldn't bother us if we leave cars there.&lt;br /&gt;Entrance into Crane Hill: If you want and if it works out when we are ready to head out we can then pile up to 4-5 people in the cars and head out from there.  &lt;br /&gt;However may people are in the car and there is no member then we will all split the $25.00 admission fee, &lt;b&gt;please bring enough money to pay your way into the gate.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOOD: While we are at Bruni’s Market they also have great sandwiches, etc. if anyone wants to pick up dinner, a snack or wine/beer also.  Check out their site: www.brunismarket.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entrain starts at 7:00.  Please note we will only wait 15 minutes past the meetup time before we all head out to Castle Hill.  If you already know ahead of time that you are coming and that you will not be able to make it to the Bruni’s by 7:15 at the latest, please email Janet and I and we can tell you where we are at so you can find us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other food idea's: Castle Hill offers the following picnic concert vendors for your convenience: Pizza by Sal’s Pizza at White Farms Ice Cream. Pre-order at 978.412.4138 and have your dinner delivered to Castle Hill. Ice cream by White Farms Ice Cream. Popcorn, nuts, candy, and soda by Q’s Nuts.  Sandwiches, chowder, and other picnic fare from Ipswich Shellfish Fish Market. Pre-order over the phone at 978.356.6941 Tuesday thru Thursday up until 3PM.  Pick up your order at the Ipswich store or have it delivered to Castle Hill. View the take-out menu at &lt;a href="http://www.ipswichfishmarket.com/picnic.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ipswichfis...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please help us keep Castle Hill clean by carrying out what you carry in, I will bring a trash bag so we can help keep Castle Hill clean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember to bring a chair or blanket to sit on, and don’t forget the bug spray.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the side away from the market and restaurant.  In front of my car.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251587496000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249348202000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go see Entrain @ Castle Hill!</name><id>11028159</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251414000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11028159/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>