<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.361290</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Microsoft  NERD New England Research &amp; Development Center </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1626763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081192</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“If you're designing and building websites and web applications, then you need to care about Usability. These days, Usability and User Experience are very crucial to success, and can mean the difference between making it or breaking it.”&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Usability Speed Dating Night is back! After the success of our last &lt;a href="http://www.bostonphp.org/events/15797436/" target="_blank"&gt;Usability Testing Night&lt;/a&gt; in March 2011, we are holding another event on January 16, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Usability?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Usability is a measure of the quality of a person’s experience when interacting with content or services. If you're designing and building websites and web applications, then you need to care about Usability. These days, Usability and User Experience are very crucial to success, and can mean the difference between making it or breaking it. I've seen so many sites that fail, only because they did not focus on Usability. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you’re still not sure what a usability test is, then watch this &lt;a href="http://www.peachpit.com/promotions/promotion.aspx?promo=137602" target="_blank"&gt;Demo Usability Test&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;How it will work:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will test 10 member sites for usability. The sites to be tested will be coordinated in advance. There are three roles defined for this event: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Site Owner: The owner of the site being tested. The site owner will facilitate the tests of their site. &lt;br /&gt;

 Test Participant: The person sitting at the computer and testing a site; the user. &lt;br /&gt;

 Observer: The person who is watching the usability test. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Attendees will act as either a Test Participant and/or Test Observer for these sites. Each Site Owner will have their own station for testing, with a laptop and chairs. Attendees will cycle through each test station for 10-15 minutes and may evaluate and partake in as many tests as possible. At the end of the evening, we will hold a debriefing of a few sites, highlighting what usability issues were found. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This will be a fun-filled and invaluable experience for those wanting to learn more about usability and testing. Steve Krug will join us, and we will provide "High Quality Snacks" for all testers and participants. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00-6:15 : Doors open, socializing 6:15-6:30 : Introductions 6:30-7:15 : Test Demo by Steve Krug &lt;br /&gt;

7:15-8:45 : Let the Testing Begin &lt;br /&gt;

8:45-9:00 : Highlights, "Now What?", Wrap Up &lt;br /&gt;

9:00 - ? : Beers somewhere?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 To make this an effective learning event, we will need to limit the number of attendees to avoid the stations becoming too crowded. Likewise, we must ensure that those who RSVP actually attend the event. For these reasons, we must charge attendees $7 for attending. The money will be used to offer refreshments at the event. If you RSVP, there is no refund for changing your RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;****If you have a site that you would like to test during this event, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:heather@bostonphp.org" target="_blank"&gt;Heather O’Neill&lt;/a&gt; (heather@bostonphp.org) by Wednesday November 21, 2012.&lt;/strong&gt; We will contact the Site Owners by end of day Wednesday, November 28, 2012 about testing their site.  Otherwise, those who are registered are welcome to be a participant or observer or both.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matt Murphy</member_name><member_id>4790321</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Bourque</member_name><member_id>5046031</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marli</member_name><member_id>6594007</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Krug</member_name><member_id>12248696</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather O'Neill</member_name><member_id>12680969</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>21</waitlist_count><updated>1360206299000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonphp</urlname><id>120818</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston PHP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>75</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351896708000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Usability Speed Dating with Steve Krug!</name><id>89706192</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358377200000</time><rsvp_limit>75</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonphp/events/89706192/</event_url></item>