<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>68 Jackson Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.395514</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-794-8208</phone><name>Rev.Christine's Home</name><city>North-Cambridge</city><id>729576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.135557</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>You are welcome to join us for the second session of the 6 class series on Wednesdays at 7 pm. (You can join us even if you miss last Wednesday.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This series is designed to help you to understand the laws of the universe, start or deepen your meditation practice and explore the foundations of Mysticism. Even if some of the Teachings are based on the Christian Mystical Tradition, this is open to all. There is no restriction on faith and spiritual background. You only have to believe that there is most likely a power and intelligence that is higher than human intelligence.&lt;br /&gt;In each class we explore three areas:&lt;br /&gt;• Spiritual exercises designed to help you develop skills needed for inner work and meditation&lt;br /&gt;• Understanding the cosmos, the Laws and Beings that govern it, and our roles as living, conscious humans in that cosmos&lt;br /&gt;• Hands-on experiences, through which you can learn to see, hear, and feel the spiritual world&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These classes have been taught for many years to many people. Take this opportunity for yourself. If Wednesdays doesn't work with your schedule, there are some other dates and times in different locations like Jamaica Plain (near Stony Brook orange line) on Sundays at 12:30 pm and Newton (near Mass Pike) on Fridays at 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Contact me if any questions via e-mail or phone. I will be glad to answers them.&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Christine 617-794-8208&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come inside the porch and ring the bell</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christine Doucet</member_name><member_id>3401828</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265075356000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-684</urlname><id>1246909</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Meditation Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264380145000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>second session on the series on Meditation and Mysticism class</name><id>12411576</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264636800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-684/events/12411576/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/7/global_5061495.jpeg</photo_url></item>