<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>289 Knight Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02909</zip><lat>41.818195</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>E &amp; O Tap</name><city>Providence</city><id>3681892</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427437</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday Night Meetup series! This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different restaurant and bar scenes in Providence.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Third time is a charm!!&amp;nbsp; We will meet at E &amp;amp; O Tap at 6, walk to The Avery at 7:30, and as 9 approaches we will call Julian's and ask them to hold a table for the number of people we have at that point. Julian's has food, quite good food, in case you're starting to feel peckish by then.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At E &amp;amp; O we will probably be in the booth near the door.&amp;nbsp; At the Avery we may try to take the tables at the back.&amp;nbsp; If you plan to meet us at Julian's and you don't let us know you're doing that, please consider sitting in someone's lap. They do tend to be busy that late.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's the beginning of Providence Craft Beer Week!&amp;nbsp; These bars are advertising this as the "Return of the Beermuda Triangle" at the Julian's website.&amp;nbsp; The Avery and Julian's will be having beer promotions this night. The Avery will be showcasing Wachusett from 7 to 9 and Julian's will have Stone.&amp;nbsp; Yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park once and walk with us.&amp;nbsp; We will make sure everyone gets back to their cars afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. Ever.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bruce is hosting this one as only he can! Take a look at his picture</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bruce B</member_name><member_id>11410054</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317848547000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316985465000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Beermuda Triangle III, the Return</name><id>34917622</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317679200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/34917622/</event_url></item>