<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>18 Raymond Street - Apt. 1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.361900</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 901-8871</phone><name>Jason's House</name><city>Allston</city><id>1376656</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134400</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let me ask you a few questions..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you ever gone out with a man that you were initially attracted to, but you quickly lost both your respect and attraction for him because he kept looking to you to see if it was "okay" to engage you physically?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you get stuck in logical, boring small talk with the men you meet, and wish that he would take it to the next level, but for some reason he never pulls the trigger and you don't understand why?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Would you like the men you meet to see you as &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;desirable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and not just a platonic friend or a buddy to chat with?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you said yes to any of these questions, then this is just what you've been waiting for. &amp;nbsp;In this special workshop, I'm going to reveal some of my most powerful techniques and strategies for making any man desire you, helping him feel more comfortable with you, and making him excited about the possibility of getting physically intimate with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three words that changed my life forever, and how you can use them to immediately to become more desirable to the kind of men you really want to meet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have you ever felt discouraged because a man kept looking to you to lead the date, and wouldn't take any steps to physically connect with you even though you could tell that he was into you? It could have been because you ignored one simple rule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a man seems to be rushing things, I'll show you &lt;strong&gt;how to gently deflect his advances while still keeping him interested in you&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;This one secret alone is worth the price of admission, because most women completely screw this up and cause the man to think she's not interested in him (which makes him lose interest as well).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple "backwards leading" trick that compels men to make a move on you, even if they were nervous or hesitant before. &amp;nbsp;If he's having trouble taking the next step, this will solve the problem immediately, and he will be grateful for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A huge mistake&lt;/strong&gt; women make on dates that bore men to tears and make them lose interest. &amp;nbsp;And the worst part? &amp;nbsp;He will never tell you if you're making this mistake. &amp;nbsp;He'll just disappear and move onto another woman who doesn't do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The three kinds of touch&lt;/strong&gt; that are only taught to professional massage therapists, and how to use them to create an instant physical response that makes him want to get closer to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to &lt;strong&gt;'texturize your touch'&lt;/strong&gt;, and make him crave your hands all over his body.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to effortlessly compel him to make that all important first kiss without seeming pushy or overly eager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple secret I learned from a female mall employee that instantly makes your hugs and kisses more stimulating and memorable. &amp;nbsp;Want to leave a strong impression? &amp;nbsp;Make this one small change to what you're already doing and watch how he responds!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*************************************************&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 HOW TO GET INVOLVED&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This event is going to be at my home in Lower Allston, right near Harvard Business School. It's very easy to get to both by car and public transportation, and there's plenty of on-street parking. Directions will be emailed to you. We will start the event promptly at 7:00pm and run until 9:00pm. Please plan on arriving by 6:45 so you have time to settle in and meet the other guests. You never know who you'll meet that can become a new friend and add a lot of value to your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Cheap. &amp;nbsp;If you took a class like this through an adult education center, you'd easily pay more than $50 to attend, and&amp;nbsp;that's assuming there even&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;a class that could offer you this kind of knowledge, which there isn't. &amp;nbsp;This is the R-Rated stuff that most dating teachers would be scared to teach you, but I am committed to helping you improve your dating life, and this is a very important piece to get handled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So how much?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Because I want to help as many women as I can, I've decided to keep the price very affordable so that anyone who wants to come will be able to. &amp;nbsp;The cost for this event is only $25, which is very low considering the quality of training that you'll be getting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about it...&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;that's 83 cents a day for a month&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;What else do you spend 83 cents on every day that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever? I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How big is the class?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Because this is class is being held at my house and not a large seminar room, I have to limit the size to only 10 students. &amp;nbsp;There are over 800 other people seeing this message, so be&amp;nbsp;sure to put in your RSVP right now in order to lock in your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$25 cash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go ahead and put in your RSVP right now in order to secure your spot. &amp;nbsp;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warmly,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email you directions.  My house is easy to find.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320012167000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318862635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*FOR WOMEN ONLY* - How To Become More Desirable On A Date</name><id>37673282</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319583600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/37673282/</event_url></item>