<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.000555</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Odiorne Point Boat Ramp</name><city>Rye</city><id>992188</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.753951</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Host: Claire P. cell @ 603-247-0897 &lt;br /&gt;

RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather permitting, I think it would be fun to go for a bike ride from the Odiorne State Park to downtown Portsmouth for Market Square Day. This event is meant more to have fun than to get a workout. I thought that we would bike with many breaks/stops along the way. We will spend a couple of hours, including lunch , then head back to Ordione after we feel well rested. If time allows, and people feel up to it, we can then ride in the park, which has amazing views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 9:00 am at the second park entrance, coming from the south, which is on Route 1A in Rye NH. Any types of bikes can be used for this event. If interested in car pooling, please post a comment, when you sign up, and we’ll try to arrange something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring your sunscreen, insect repellent and plenty of fluids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is at no cost. I hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carpooling options. Because this event is so far out of our area, it may be a good idea if some of us car pool, and offer to bring others’ bike, if we can. I have room for one bike on my bike rack, first call first served. If you want to offer to bring someone’s bike, all you have to do is enter a comment to that effect along with your cell phone number. This way you can be contacted for arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP or call my cell @ 603-247-0897. If you do not plan on coming, do not RSVP no.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Odiorne State Park(second entrance if coming from the south)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339258882000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339190387000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike ride from Odiorne Park</name><id>68364312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339246800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/68364312/</event_url></item>