<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 wallace street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.304236</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Peter house</name><city>rochester</city><id>900638</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.972141</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/9/4/event_170781652.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;HI CRAZY DANCE PARTY FRIENDS! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

PLAY WITH US AND TAKE HOME A COLORFUL ONE-OF-A-KIND SHIRT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At this special Human Canvas event we will be providing 100's of CRAYOLA FABRIC MARKERS.&lt;/strong&gt; These markers let you create permanent designs on fabric without being toxic to your skin. Crayola Fabric Markers wash off of skin and hair with just soap and water. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Crayola Fabric Markers are permanent on clothing if you place them in a hot dryer before washing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a part of the Human Canvas Evolution! The next generation of Paint Dancing. The Human Canvas Dance is destined to become the next international rage of fun Paint Dancing events!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a fabulous event for singles meeting Singles! Please bring your friends :)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

HERE'S HOW THE HUMAN CANVAS EVENTS WORK!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Put on a white shirt or t-shirt or visit the local thrift store and buy one. It can be any kind of white shirt. Toss it on, come to the warehouse and let EVERYONE at the party use you as a Human Canvas and draw on your shirt with Crayola fabric markers while we group dance and hang out! If you are really feeling adventurous, add white pants, hats, gloves, shoes, accessories, you name it. Feel free to wear as much white you like! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TAKE HOME A UNIQUE WORK OF ART CLOTHING!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are excited about using fabric markers instead of washable markers! It will be thrilling to see permanent works of art going home with everyone! :) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;CHOCOLATE AND WINE FROM AROUND THE WORLD!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Please consider bringing some chocolate or wine.&lt;/strong&gt; Imagine all the fun we will have with a unique selection of chocolate and wine from around the world. If everyone brings just a little something, this will be a wonderful feast! Please bring anything you like. Every little bit helps, but what we really want, is your smile!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;We will be having a potluck before the event so bring something to share!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will be pumping up the sound and playing some awesome Music!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are several groups promoting this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The count will likely hit 150 or so! This event is guaranteed to become the photo opportunity of a lifetime! Don't worry if you can't find the right outfit in time. Just grab a white T-shirt or anything white and join-in on all the crazy fun of the Human Canvas White Shirt &amp;amp; Magic Marker Paint Dance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LOCATION:&lt;/strong&gt; The warehouse is located accross from the "Windjamers Restaurant" and Next door to "Blue Seals Feeds". The address is 8 Wallace Street, Rochester. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Saturday, November 10, 2012 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Peter's Home, 8 Wallace Street, Rochester, NH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can always get in touch with me through "Trailblazers" on Meetup or calling me at: 603-312-6735&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A donation of $5 would be appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;If anyone want's to help me setup and take down I would appreciated it. Let me know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352603546000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350736096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>PAINT DANCING PARTY</name><id>87797532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352592000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/87797532/</event_url></item>