<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Room 424</address_2><address_1>771 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.350477</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mugar Library</name><city>Boston</city><id>1321281</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.109632</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The third session (of five) of the first literary seminar sponsored by the Boston Poetry Union for the summer 2010 season, &amp;quot;A Brief and Incomplete Introduction to Spanish and Latin American Literature,&amp;quot; will be held this Tuesday evening, tomorrow, July 27th, from 6:00 to 8:00 in room 424 of the Mugar Memorial Library at Boston University at 771 Commonwealth Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this session, we will be discussing the Peruvian poet César Vallejo and that poetic titan from Chile, Pablo Neruda, both via Robert Bly's notable translations published in the 1960s. I'll also be handing out the prose readings, short prose pieces by the Argentines Jorge Luis Borges and Julio Cortázar, for anyone who would like to prepare for session four ahead of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More generally, the seminar will cover almost five hundred years of poetry and prose from the sixteenth century to the present day, with authors representing six countries covered in this order in the five sessions: Quevedo and Góngora (Spain); Machado and Lorca (Spain); Borges and Cortázar (Argentina); Vallejo (Peru) and Neruda (Chile); and Paz (Mexico) and García Marquez (Colombia).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The third session costs $5.00 payable in cash or check to &amp;quot;Boston Poetry Union,&amp;quot; as will each of the remaining sessions, totaling $15.00, which you can pay tonight if you plan on attending the remaining three.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As has been customary for these postings, I'll copy the blurb I wrote for the BPU's blog:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;I do my best to formulate difficult and intriguing questions about texts that readers have deemed the best works produced in these various national traditions. Why has history been kinder to Quevedo than to Góngora? How do their respective writings represent very old breeds of impulse that we’re still struggling with? What made Machado return to the fields of Castilla? What did Lorca, Neruda and other poets of the Spanish language learn from Whitman? What makes Neruda so universal and yet innovative? How and why has Borges haunted so many who have come after him? To what degree is the “magical realism” of García Márquez, inaugurated by Alejo Carpentier, actually magical at all? What is most strange, mystical, and/or Mexican about Octavio Paz? Or rather, what is most Pazian about Mexico?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I intend the format of these seminars to be informative but informal; part lecture, and part discussion where digressions are welcome. We may even laugh quite a bit. At these seminars, you ought to feel among equals or else with some who are just a few steps ahead, beckoning you forward. ¡Que nos veamos pronto!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Healy</member_name><member_id>7634517</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280272668000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280148324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Third session of: Intro. to Spanish &amp; Latin American Lit: Neruda &amp; Vallejo</name><id>14214561</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280268000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/14214561/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/4/global_8983348.jpeg</photo_url></item>