<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1667 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.381985</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 547-0759</phone><name>Lizard Lounge</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669136</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119650</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>From &lt;a href="http://www.thecoverupboston.com/" target="_blank"&gt;thecoverupboston.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When we first came up with the Cover-Up series, it was all leading up to this night: re-enacting &lt;b&gt;The Last Waltz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever since we started mentioning we were doing this show, musicians started losing their minds, itching to be a part of this night. And with good reason - &lt;i&gt;the Last Waltz is one of the great nights in the history of music&lt;/i&gt;. On November 25, 1976 the finest rock and roll musicians in the world (and Joni Mitchell) got together on one stage and made some noise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Luckily, a young Martin Scorsese was there to capture the whole thing on film. If you haven't had the chance to see the DVD, I strongly recommend checking it out. There are so many great moments. In my mind, that's what the Last Waltz was all about: capturing a moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a way, the Cover-Up series was inspired by The Last Waltz. Now, The Band didn't invent the spirit of musicians getting together and creating a special night, playing the music they love. But they certainly perfected it. And we will do our best on &lt;b&gt;November 21&lt;/b&gt; to honor that spirit with a serious rock and roll lovefest. And yes, we are playing the Joni Mitchell song. Sorry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring: &lt;b&gt;The Rationales, The Phil Aiken Army, The Teenage Prayers, &amp;amp; The Beau Roland Band&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With special guests: &lt;b&gt;Ad Frank, Andy Cambria (Broken Blossoms), Brendan Boogie, John Powhida, Mike Verge, Pip (Blizzard of '78) and many more&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details and tix at &lt;a href="http://www.lizardloungeclub.com/printcalendar.asp" target="_blank"&gt;www.lizardloungeclub.com/printcalendar.asp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff</member_name><member_id>2268166</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259028363000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fans of Live Music</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-live-music</urlname><id>444171</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Live Music</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258684209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cover Up presents "The Last Waltz"</name><id>11916812</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258855200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-live-music/events/11916812/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/a/9/global_11892425.jpeg</photo_url></item>