<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/3/a/event_78681562.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;To all of you that have children or grandchildren, that you would like to bring to see Santa, I am opening my home on Sunday December 18th, as Santa will be visiting my grandkids Mason 9 and Alyssa 4, at 6pm. Please get here by 5:30. there will be a box to deposit gifts for your child to the left of my garage. My suggestion is gifts no more than $15-$20, so noone feels slighted. Bring the kids in first, if you like, then go out and get the gifts to put in the box. Please put the child's full name on the gift, in case we have other children with the same first name. park on my side of the street only. This is just one of many thank you parties I am planning to all my friends, who have been such a wonderful support "family' to me, this past year. My phone number and address will be emailed to everyone, that responds with a "yes". In your reply, please indicate names and ages of children attending, so I have enough goodies for all. I will be taking pics with my digital camera, so supplying me with your email now, would be a good idea. The question will be asked here, so it will be kept confidential, once you reply with a yes. If you're a maybe, then reply with a yes, and let me know later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa will read "The Night before Christmas" and have a sing-a-long.&amp;nbsp; Better be nice, not naughty!!! ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas to all, susan&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324649965000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323632751000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Santa Claus is coming to town...Pelham specifically!</name><id>44121302</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324247400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/44121302/</event_url></item>