<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;After hit performances with Sunrise, It, and Battleship Potemkin, the Coolidge Corner Theatre is proud to welcome back the Berklee College of Music Professor Sheldon Mirowitz and his students from the Department of Film Scoring for a special presentation of their original new score for the stunningly restored 1929 silent film classic Piccadilly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A tale of rivalry, betrayal, and murder, director E.A. Dupont’s Piccadilly has been called “a film noir before the term was in use” and “one of the true greats of British silent film.”  When Valentine Wilmot (Jameson Thomas), the suave manager of posh London nightclub Piccadilly Circus fires his star dancer, the business falls into decline.  After seeing club scullery maid Shosho (Chinese-American screen goddess Anna May Wong), entertaining her fellow kitchen workers with a sensuous dance, Wilmot, in desperation, hires her to perform.  She becomes an instant sensation, her rise to celebrity bringing her admirers and enemies.  When Shosho becomes the object of Wilmot’s erotic obsession, both her boyfriend, Jim (King Hou Chang), and Wilmot’s former lover and dancer, Mabel (Ziegfeld Follies star Gilda Gray), become bitterly jealous, culminating in tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A stylish evocation of sultry jazz-age London, Piccadilly features dazzling cinematography by Werner Brandes and a revelatory performance by the gorgeous Wong. Charles Laughton, in his first feature film, has a cameo as a greedy nightclub diner, and Ray Milland appears as a nightclub extra. Don't miss this one-night-only opportunity to experience this silent-film gem on our giant silver screen accompanied by a live orchestral performance conducted by Berklee’s talented composers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directed by:Ewald André Dupont // featuring:Anna May Wong, Gilda Gray, Charles Laughton.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;I'll be at Panera as close to 5.30 as possible with a meet-up sign on table. I will head across to the Coolidge at 6.15 (6.30 latest) to get in line. We'll gather in the lobby after the movie for those who'd like to go for a post-movie discussion at a local pub.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The silent films scored by Berklee College of Music tend to be among the most popular events at the Coolidge. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;It is strongly advised that tickets be purchased before the event as this will likely sell-out&lt;/span&gt;. Please note that members get in free, so if you are not currently a member, this would be a great time to become one.  &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/piccadilly"&gt;http://www.coolidge.org/content/piccadilly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See you at the movie!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See meet up details below....</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Caroline </member_name><member_id>10711981</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336525020000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335519495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Piccadilly - Sounds of Silents</name><id>62362752</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336431600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/62362752/</event_url></item>