<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Divine presence awaits you as we come together in celebration of St. Valentine.&lt;br /&gt;Together we will invite the magic of LOVE into our ritual space and drink from her true blessings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Would you like to feel more connection to the Divine in your life?&lt;br /&gt;* Are there unconscious patterns that show up in your life that you're ready to release?&lt;br /&gt;* Are they blocking you from loving yourself and others more fully?&lt;br /&gt;* Are you ready to experience more passion in your life than ever before?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During this safe and sacred gathering you will have the opportunity to connect deeply with yourself, the Divine, and other beautiful souls through movement, meditation, breath and sound.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and discover how meaningful connection - intimacy and love - is available right here, right now, any time you want it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Valentine Puja is open to singles and couples, beginners and seasoned practitioners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may wish to wear comfortable, colorful clothing and bring a bottle of water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive by 5:45 pm as we will begin on time; the Gathering will end at 8 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of parking in the lot behind the studio or on the street.  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pushana (Robyn Vogel)</member_name><member_id>7622528</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299369688000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Tantra Practitioners/Teachers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>new-england-tantric-meetup</urlname><id>804252</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>New England Tantric Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295923422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantra Gathering: Valentine's Day Puja, Opening To The Beloved </name><id>16173934</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296946800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/new-england-tantric-meetup/events/16173934/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/1/4/global_2913860.jpeg</photo_url></item>