<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Exterminating Angels by Jean-Claude Brisseau, France, 2007, 102 min., Cost: $9, $8 students/seniors/MFA members&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Francois, a filmmaker, is preparing a thriller. During screen tests for a brief nude scene with an actress, he discovers the pleasure some women can have in the transgression of minor erotic taboos. Driven by the desire to contribute something new to the cinema, he decides to make a film that mixes fiction and reality and centers on something which unexpectedly becomes an enigma and a taboo: the minor transgressions that are a source of pleasure. His research into eroticism raises basic questions. But like Icarus approaching the sun, he only burns his wings. Writes Variety &amp;quot;there is no question that the venture is both titillating and intellectually rigorous.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an ironic life-imitates-art twist, shortly after the script was written, a handful of actresses who screened for Brisseau's earlier film, Secret Things, accused the director of inappropriate conduct.  Although he was largely exonerated from wrong-doing -- and shooting of Exterminating Angels had wrapped before the trial -- the accusation adds a frisson to our experience of the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Co-presented by French Cultural Servics and in conjuction with Francophone week in Boston, March 16-25.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is hosted by Nicole who will be holding a meetup sign in the theater during the credits. After the film, we will convene at a local cafe (most likely meetup favorite Boston Shwarma) for a post-film discussion. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174420963000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172857809000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exterminating Angels - Life Imitates Art?</name><id>5530286</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174248000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5530286/</event_url></item>