<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A hike to Bridal Veil Falls via the Coppermine Trail in Franconia Notch!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of a series of hikes for those of us who want to start getting (back) into hiking and need to build up some stamina and endurance before attempting the rockier terrains and steeper inclines! Hikes will be taken at a slower pace, with gains of 1000 feet or less and most will be 3 - 4 miles and take about half a day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Coppermine Trail has an aura of mystery and romance about it. It takes you along Coppermine Brook to Bridal Veil Falls, one of the most beautiful waterfalls in the White Mountains. But the mystery does not come from the waterfall itself. Along the way, you will find a plaque on a large boulder along the brook with an enigmatic inscription: In Memoriam to Arthur Farnsworth “The Keeper of Stray Ladies” Pecketts 1939 Presented by a Grateful One. For the rest of the hike, you can ponder who Arthur Farnsworth was, whether he met a tragic fate along Coppermine Brook, why the tribute was placed in such an obscure place, and who was this “grateful one” who chose to eulogize Mr. Farnsworth in this manner (read on and find out!). The Coppermine Trail itself is a pleasant walk on the western side of Cannon Mountain. Most of it grades gently uphill along Coppermine Brook. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/BridalVeilFalls020713.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Even though this hike is for those of us just starting out (or starting again) please be prepared for a walk which may feel strenuous at times! Bring proper clothing (no jeans, decent hiking boots, a jacket) and carry at least 2 quarts of water and some snacks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The Coppermine Trailhead is located on the east side of Route 116 at Coppermine Road in Franconia, New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-93:&lt;br /&gt;    * Take Exit 38 off of I-93. The exit is signed &amp;quot;18, 116, 117, 142, Franconia, Sugar Hill&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn west which will be towards Routes 18, 116, and 117.&lt;br /&gt;    * After barely 0.1 mile you will reach a flashing traffic light in downtown Franconia which is the junction of Routes 18 and 116.&lt;br /&gt;    * Go straight through the intersection (after stopping at the light) onto Rt. 116 and follow that road for 3.4 miles.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn left onto Coppermine Road and park close to Rt. 116.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Jct. of Routes 112 and 116:&lt;br /&gt;    * From the junction of Routes 112 and 116 in Easton, head north on Rt. 116.&lt;br /&gt;    * The trailhead will be on the right 3.0 miles after passing the town hall in Easton center.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn right onto Coppermine Road and park close to Rt. 116.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trailhead and parking:&lt;br /&gt;    * After turning onto Coppermine Road, park as close as possible to Rt. 116. Don't bother driving farther down this road as it is a private development and trail parking is not allowed elsewhere.&lt;br /&gt;    * The &amp;quot;trail&amp;quot; follows Coppermine Road for 0.4 mile before turning onto a woods road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a camping MeetUp this same weekend...but you don't have to be camping to come on the hike!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/calendar/14649380/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be at the trailhead by 9:45am.  I have a bright orange backpack - or alternatively, a small blue camelback and a big smile.  My cell phone is 774-262-9620</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Chilton</member_name><member_id>7634175</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288670713000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283560521000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting (Back) Into It Hike to Bridal Veil Falls!</name><id>14651294</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285509600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14651294/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/b/9/global_17679001.jpeg</photo_url></item>