<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Organizer - Michael Blair @ (978) 808-1932  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Paddle and Plod 2008 - 8 Days / 16 Peaks / 1 River  &lt;br /&gt;July 5 - 12&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;The plan is to spend a day rafting down the whitewater rapids of the Kennebec River.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will spend two nights camping (Thursday and Friday) along the Dead River in The Forks, ME and one day rafting (Friday) on the Kennebec River with Magic Falls Rafting Company. W e will relax by the river and the campfire Thursday night before leaving early Friday morning to go rafting. Lunch will be on the river. After the rafting trip we will have a group cookout provided by Magic Falls before hanging by the camp fire again Friday night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 6:00 PM on Thursday night at Magic Falls.  According to Google Maps it is about 249 miles and should take about 4 hours 35 minutes to get there from Boston.  &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?daddr=The+Forks,+The+Forks+Plantation,+ME&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;dirflg=&amp;amp;saddr=boston+ma&amp;amp;f=d&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=45.33608,-69.96762&amp;amp;sspn=0.010181,0.018711&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=7" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for a map with the basic directions.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost is $96.40 per person and includes two nights of camping, one day of rafting and dinner after the rafting trip on Friday.  When booking your trip be sure to indicate that you are with the Blair Group for July 10-12. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Magic Falls Rafting Company  &lt;br /&gt;(800) 207-7238  &lt;br /&gt;www.magicfalls.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum gear and equipment required to participate in this event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Footwear&lt;/u&gt;: Waterproof shoes for the river.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clothing&lt;/u&gt;: Lightweight to midweight synthetic shirt/pants - no jeans or cotton sweat shirt/pants.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Food and Water&lt;/u&gt;: Food for Thursday night, Friday morning, and Saturday morning (they feed us chicken/steak Friday night but you may also want to bring something extra).  Bring your own &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; if you would like.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/u&gt;: Quarters for the showers, fire wood if you have any, headlamp or flashlight with spare batteries, sunscreen, insect repellent, and a camera.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have a couple of small backpacking stoves and one camp stove with some pots and a pan (probably not enough for everyone to eat at the same time) so feel free to bring one if you have one.  Same goes for coolers - I will have one or two but don't hesitate to bring your own.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will also need to have some cash for a tip to the guide of your boat - we usually give $10 a person, $20 if the ride was good)  PLEASE tip, these kids make $50 a day and not all rafters tip.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an effort to coordinate ride-sharing please indicate in your RSVP if you are able to give a ride or if you are looking to get one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact me with any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215900379000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213705881000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Whitewater Rafting on the Kennebec River 07/10</name><id>8157937</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215727200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8157937/</event_url></item>