<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/e/0/event_163931232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This beautiful walk meanders along a babbling brook on Middle Mountain Road, a gated logging road in the pristine southern part of the trails of Mt. Toby. The road is wide for dogs to romp and people to socialize and has lovely scenery of woodlands and water. As with any wooded trail, be prepared for mud if it has rained, ice if it has snowed and some ruts and rocks no matter what the weather. This walk is more rustic than some, but well worth it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We should be able to enjoy some late fall foliage - bring your camera!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amount of Time: We plan to walk up and back on the road for about a total of 1.5 hours but the amount of time you wish to walk is up to you since it is a road that is easily followed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, all dogs must start on leash until we know everybody gets along. After that it's all romp and play time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHERE TO MEET: Access is from Rte 116 (Amherst Road) in Sunderland. From either direction, turn onto North Silver Lane, then turn right on Reservoir Road, then left on Cross Mountain Rd. Go about a quarter-mile up Cross Mountain Road, park on the left. I have a RED HIGHLANDER.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the parking lot per directions, below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gene R</member_name><member_id>11009036</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352565527000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350998021000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Middle Mountain Road</name><id>88196222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351958400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/88196222/</event_url></item>