<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a &lt;b&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/b&gt;.  If you are wondering why there so few RSVPs, take a look at this &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;.  Please be respectful of others who may want to RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Calling all games, are you aware that the Wii is home to traditional game playing experiences and that video games can be more than just war games and shooters?  In addition to game companies producing video game interpretations of classics such as Boggle, Jenga, Settlers of Catan and others, there are also other games that feel awfully like traditional board or party games.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One game that fits this is Wii Party and that will be the game we will play at this event.  It's various modes combine traditional dice rolling, card playing with mini-game activities.  There are even twists on Hot Potato, Bingo and even a Couples Relationship Compatibility test. ;-)  If you like the Wii and you like board games, come to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will also be partner-based.  You and a partner will play the game together deciding who should do each mini-game.  This should add an interesting social dynamic like they have on reality tv shows like the Amazing Race.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The food theme for this Mini-Meetup will be &amp;quot;fruit.&amp;quot;  You are free to interpret that however you want, if you decide to bring something.  (Non-sticky foods are encouraged).  We will have some default, healthy interpretations of that theme on hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, if you own a Wii, please feel free to load your Mii onto your Wii Remote and bring it on over. :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the location:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pickman Street is located between the Commons and the water.  Parking on Pickman can be tight, but there should be ample parking along either Pleasant Street (by the Commons) or Collins Street (by the water)&lt;br /&gt;It will take place on the third floor unit.&lt;br /&gt;Note: there will be two cats present that will be very very sad if they have to get locked up.  They are very polite however.  If anyone would like to attend but has allegeries please send me a private message.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291678268000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287416393000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Wii Party</name><id>15146587</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291489200000</time><rsvp_limit>9</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/15146587/</event_url></item>