<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Salisbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.273173</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 799-4406 </phone><name>Worcester Art Museum</name><city>Worcester</city><id>719621</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802015</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>145.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Scott is teaching this class at the Worcester Art Museum. &lt;a href="https://educationreg.worcesterart.org/CourseStatus.awp?~~10IADPH400" target="_blank"&gt;Sign up there today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optimizing Your Images: Intermediate/Advanced Photoshop WAM Digital Photography II--Advanced Retouching&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have a great image but think it could be better? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking the photograph is just half of the equation. The next step is optimizing it using your digital darkroom AKA: Adobe Photoshop.  Do you have a great image but think it could be better? Here are the techniques you’ll need to bring it to the next level. You will learning real world Photoshop techniques that are being used in the photographic industry right now to optimize the images you see in magazines, catalogs, and on websites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants are asked to bring images as digital files to the class.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Overview of classes:Scott is teaching this class at the Worcester Art Museum. &lt;a href="https://educationreg.worcesterart.org/CourseStatus.awp?~~10IADPH400" target="_blank"&gt;Sign up there today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;• Layer Masks: understanding what they are and why you’d use them. Learning to stack them. Understanding layer mask opacity and how to use the brush tool to edit your images non-destructively.&lt;br /&gt;• Using curves and levels and why you’d choose one over the other. Creating adjustment layers for non-destructive editing.&lt;br /&gt;• Clone tool and the Healing brush. How to use them and why you’d use one instead of the other. Dodge and Burn. How these can help with the optimization of images.&lt;br /&gt;• Hue/ Saturation and Channels. Using these to correct colorcasts, and also creating beautiful black and white images. How to use these techniques to fix skin tone on people.&lt;br /&gt;• Advanced selections and Transform tool. Using your selection tool move objects from one photo to another.  Transforming you images and selections.&lt;br /&gt;• Pen tool. What is it and how it can give you clean selections (clipping paths) around objects? How it applies to real world jobs.&lt;br /&gt;• Photoshop Actions. Learning to batch your images to save you time. Using liquefy for believable and unbelievable results.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Applying these techniques to:&lt;br /&gt;Portraiture - Faces&lt;br /&gt;Architecture&lt;br /&gt;Objects&lt;br /&gt;Landscapes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott is teaching this class at the Worcester Art Museum. &lt;a href="https://educationreg.worcesterart.org/CourseStatus.awp?~~10IADPH400" target="_blank"&gt;Sign up there today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280358997000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278866824000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Want to Learn how to Optimizing Your Images</name><id>dmnxnynkblc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280354400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/14067843/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/9/global_10864777.jpeg</photo_url></item>