<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 Ashburton St.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02895</zip><lat>41.837766</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.351.POOL</phone><name>Snookers Pool Lounge</name><city>Providence</city><id>1094702</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415001</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the Monday Happy Hour series! &lt;br /&gt;LAST MINUTE LOCATION CHANGE! Sorry for the late notice but there&lt;br /&gt;is a private party tonight.  Come down to shoot a little pool instead of hopping in one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Aqua at the Providence Marriott&lt;br /&gt;This week's host:  Octavia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week we will venture out to a new location, with a new host!  Aqua is the outdoor bar at the Providence Marriott hotel.  Aqua has been voted Best Outdoor Lounge in Rhode Island and is described as an oasis in the middle of the city that blends water, fire and sound creating a temptingly cool escape.  Sounds like the perfect spot for the last Monday in August!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE: Pool is only open to hotel guests and members so no swimming!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Octavia</member_name><member_id>8075116</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283265414000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282995522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Happy Hour - Aqua at Snookers</name><id>14570205</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283205600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/14570205/</event_url></item>