<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>365 Gulf Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06071</zip><lat>41.990002</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Soapstone</name><city>Somers</city><id>345574</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.449997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I was going to list a hike for Tuesday evening, but then I saw Al's sunset walk to Soapstone Mountain and thought I'd just join that.  It's not much of a hike, only about a twenty minute walk to the top, but should be a nice view of the sunset.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've not been to one of Al's sunset events yet, but I know he encourages us all to bring food and drink, even wine, to share.  He's also planning to bring a grill and maybe even find a place for a fire pit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a flashlight for the walk out and definitely some kind of bug spray!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There: &lt;br /&gt;(1) From Enfield: take 190 east... &lt;br /&gt;Pass the intersection of rte 83 one mile later look for the right onto Gulf road.. &lt;br /&gt;Take Gulf road south for about 1.5 miles, look for the parking area of Soapstone mth on your right.. &lt;br /&gt;if you see Handle road you just missed it.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) From Hartford: Take 84 east &lt;br /&gt;at exit 67 = rte 31 &lt;br /&gt;take a left (north) on 31 go about a mile up &lt;br /&gt;Take a right on rte 30 (East) &lt;br /&gt;follow that till you meetup with rte 74.. &lt;br /&gt;stay on rte 30 by going left at the 30 sign where 74 splits off again.. &lt;br /&gt;Follow 30 up about 3.5 miles, this is a bit tricky, there is a left turn here called Burbank st.. &lt;br /&gt;if you miss it and get to the intersection of 30 and 140, just take a left (east ) onto 140 and take the first right onto Burbank Road... stay on Burbank road (changes into gulf road a little ways up) for about 2.5 miles...after Handle Road its the left entrance way parking lot to soapstone... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the lot right at the entrance way.&lt;br /&gt;Al drives a blue older Toyota Avalon and I'm in an older red Taurus wagon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187304381000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1187049059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Al's Sunset Walk</name><id>6175224</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1187131500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6175224/</event_url></item>