<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 1 North</address_2><address_1>225 Newbury St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.580079</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-774-0934</phone><name>The Village Green</name><city>Danvers</city><id>964098</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.968733</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;We know those dancing shoes are nice and shinny let&amp;rsquo;s get some use out of them again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Village Green in Danvers offers a variety of food and great entertainment:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those looking for a comfortable and friendly place to meet new people, come to The Barn on Friday or Saturday nights. The Village Green has been hosting&amp;nbsp;the hottest dance club on the North Shore for over 30 years.&amp;nbsp;They are pleased to announce on Saturday Nights they will be providing Live Music with some of the areas best Bands playing Rock &amp;amp; Roll, Top 40, Oldies, and more of the greatest dance music. We know you have been waiting a long time for this and now it is here for the New &lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Year!!!!&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;We will be dancing the night away with the awesome hits from&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt; The Reminisants, so let&amp;rsquo;s go have some fun and put those dancing shoes to good use&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A little information about the band:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Reminisants have been entertaining audiences of all ages throughout New England since 1973. The band's repertoire features dance music that appeals to a variety of musical tastes across several generations, a sampling of their songs include: Run Around Sue, Surfin&amp;rsquo; USA, Pretty Woman, 96 Tears, Mustang Sally and much, much more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;Some info you will need to know before coming down to the Village Green:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weekend Nights the Dress Code is Business Casual. Ladies and Gentlemen may wear Dress Jeans as part of our&amp;nbsp;Dress Code.&lt;strong&gt; Dress Jeans means no rips, tears, nothing faded, studded&lt;/strong&gt;, etc... Any type of gym clothes, sneakers, t-shirts, are not allowed. Your going out for the evening to dance, meet, and talk with people so look good you never know what might happen...... I am sure that we will walk away with more great memories from this event that we will add to all the rest, so come on out and join in on the fun and make some new lasting memories with some great people!&amp;nbsp; You NEVER do know what will happen but either way you KNOW we will have fun!!!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not sure if we will be able to get 1 table for all of us which means we may not all be sitting together if this is a problem then this event may not be for you.&amp;nbsp; Please remember that when you are putting in your RSVP, although as always we do hope that you will come out and have some fun with us. You say you don't dance?&amp;nbsp; Come out and people watch, I am sure you will get an eye full!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Cost:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a $7.00 charge to get in the door and they have a full bar, actually a few of them in the dance hall and at the Tavern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Were to Meet:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be inside come in and look around for us, we will try to get there early and save a table &amp;amp; chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Parking:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Village Green has a huge parking lot, but it gets pretty full and the snow that is still on the ground doesn't help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Other things:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is:&amp;nbsp; 978-304-2811.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event.&amp;nbsp; If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change.&amp;nbsp; Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;As always we look forward to seeing you at this event!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Thank You, Donna, Janet &amp;amp; Vicki &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be inside in the Barn side where the dancing is.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Vicki</member_name><member_id>4058114</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299423342000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Cause we have fun and you should join in on it.</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299025983000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go dance!</name><id>16759404</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1299372300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/16759404/</event_url></item>