<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>154 Moody Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.373974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charles River Museum of Industry &amp; Innovation</name><city>Waltham</city><id>6957112</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.236580</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join the Greater Boston Divorced and Separated Support meetup for this museum event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this is a child-friendly event.   Bring your kids or grandkids, or great grandkids, nieces, nephews, etc.   bring a friend's child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located on the scenic banks of the Charles River in the historic 1814 Boston Manufacturing Company textile mill, CRMII is on the National Register of Historic Places as America’s first factory. Hands on exhibits feature American innovation and invention from 1812 to modern day, including the Boston Manufacturing Company, The Orient Bicycle and Metz Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;Admission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adults: $7 &lt;br /&gt;

 Students: $5 &lt;br /&gt;

 Seniors: $5 &lt;br /&gt;

 Children under 6, active &amp;amp; retired military, &amp;amp; Museum members: Free&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some exhibits that look appealing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;Self Illuminated&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Running July 15, 2012 – January 15, 2013&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Electric ForestThe Charles River Museum of Industry &amp;amp; Innovation will host Wayne Strattman, the world’s foremost maker of kinetic plasma sculpture, in a major solo exhibition opening July 15. Strattman, known to millions via the high-voltage plasma he designed to light up the Borg ship in the Star Trek movies, will be showing off a (literally) luminous array of eye-dazzling works that pushes what’s possible with light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Strattman is represented in almost 1,000 museums worldwide, and has had over 4,000 private commissions, Self: Illuminated will be his first solo museum show, and the first to feature work not made for commercial or scientific contexts. The six month exhibit, with almost one hundred individual pieces grouped into ten installations, will be complemented by several events celebrating glass and technology-based art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wayne Strattman has been manipulating glass, gases and electricity for more than 25 years. He is personally responsible for pioneering many of the techniques now intrinsic to his medium. His book, “Neon Techniques”, is still the industry standard reference book after 15 years of continuous publication. He holds a large number of innovative lighting patents, and his commercial clients include Disney, Osram-Sylvania, the Sam Adams Brewery, Sega Gameworks, casinos and motion picture companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strattman’s work is clearly rooted in his background of physics and engineering. However, as the show title intimates, the subject is human cognition, perception, and memory, not just the blaze of cool technology. Pieces range from a huge chess board that mimics the complexity of the human relationships to a forest of molecule trees. Tarot cards, woven wire faces, engraved snatches of conversation, and gold boxing gloves make appearances along with chemical phosphors. One installation will involve a thirty-four foot wall of his patented Luminglas®, the electrically charged, lightning-filled panels commissioned of him by Paramount pictures for Star Trek’s Borg ship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;Steam Power&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water power gave birth to the industrial revolution, but it was steam that drove its growth. Steam powered the factories, which produced more and more each year. Steam powered the railroads, which delivered passengers and goods. Steam powered tools and machines, electrical generators and automobiles. In its day, steam was king.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The museum’s main gallery was once the boiler room and engine house for the Boston Manufacturing Company, with soaring ceilings, giant boiler, and an engine pier that supported a massive steam engine with a 20-foot flywheel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this area you’ll see steam-powered engines and equipment, including collections of live-steam model locomotives, full-size marine engines, a steam generator, and Waltham Pumper #1, the city’s first horse-drawn, steam-powered fire engine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;Marvelous Machines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scattered throughout the museum is an assortment of machines that perform various tasks that many folks rarely encounter. A vintage apparatus that makes 40,000 candy bags per hour. A behemoth of a machine that makes tiny tacks and the rivets you find in blue jeans. A player piano with its works exposed, and an automatic machine that once turned out microscopic screws for pocket watches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add to these a water wheel governor, an Edwardian-era telephone booth, switchboard, and a foot-powered printing press, and you’ll agree that the Charles River Museum of Industry &amp;amp; Innovation has a delightful surprise around every turn. Each is fascinating and in its own way beautiful. You’ll never think about machines the same way again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #f38897"&gt;Tips for Visiting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Finding Us:&lt;/em&gt; The museum is located at the very back of the mill complex. Keep the giant smokestack in view; we’re located just below it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Parking:&lt;/em&gt; Most of our visitors park in the Municipal Parking Lot on Pine Street, but there are several public parking lots and meters within walking distance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where to Eat:&lt;/em&gt; Waltham has more than 100 great restaurants, many of which are found near the museum on Moody or Main Street. Choose from incredible ethnic cuisine, fine dining, or good old American.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Food and Drinks in the Museum:&lt;/em&gt; Food and drinks are not allowed in the museum galleries except during private functions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography:&lt;/em&gt; Still photography and video in the museum is permitted for personal use only. Tripods and lighting can be used with permission. Commercial photography/videography is by appointment only; location fees apply. No photographs or video may be reproduced, sold, or distributed without permission of the museum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Coats:&lt;/em&gt; Coat racks are available. Please do not leave valuables. The museum is not responsible for lost or stolen items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Strollers:&lt;/em&gt; Baby strollers are allowed throughout the museum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;No Smoking:&lt;/em&gt; Smoking is not permitted anywhere in the museum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Make a day of it&lt;/em&gt;: become a history hunter and try out our &lt;a href="http://www.crmi.org/learn/kids-and-families/hidden-history-tour/"&gt;Hidden History Tour.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Special Events:&lt;/em&gt; See what &lt;a href="http://www.crmi.org/events/"&gt;events&lt;/a&gt; are happening today at the Museum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron R.</member_name><member_id>4515948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358391980000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352872619000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Charles River Museum of Industry and Innovation (kid-friendly event)</name><id>91328692</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356206400000</time><rsvp_limit>32</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/91328692/</event_url></item>