<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Photo Opening featuring Matt Kahn's Galapagos photos at Aram?s Comjean?s studio.&lt;br /&gt;Note: once inside the Building look for signs for RED Pine Studios, Parking: park on street on legal spots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a photos from Matt?s + Aram?s Collection hanging in the new space.  The opening begins at 6:00.  Around 7:30 there will be 3 photo talks/slide shows by Matt?s + Aram?s + maybe me Biagio (only if there is time each presentation will be about 15 minutes.   Light refreshment will be served. &lt;br /&gt;Please join in the fun, mingle with other up and coming photographers and shares your comments on the Photo show.  Thanks Aram, Matt + Biagio&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Web link to Red Pine Studios: &lt;a href="http://www.redpinestudio.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.redpinestu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google Maps link to Studio located just outside Union SQ Somerville:  &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?q=285+Washington+St,+Somerville,+MA+02143,+USA&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;oi=map&amp;amp;ct=title" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that  I (Biagio) do plan to run more events when the weather gets warmer like: &lt;br /&gt;Outdoor photo shoots of Mount Auburn Cemetery, Forest Hills Cemetery (Jamaica Plain, MA), Great Meadows National Wildlife Refuge (Concord , MA), VT leaf peepping weekend trip in the fall Sept/Oct time frame., etc&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come into the Building start look for signs for RED Pine Studios.  Enter then Walk straight take your first right walk straight again till you see a jog in the hallway then turn  about right and to see a door with signs for RED Pine Studios.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1203980693000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Chance to mingle with other up and coming photographers and shares your comments on the Photo show.</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203351774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Pine Studios Photo Show in Somerville  </name><id>7355220</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203807600000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/7355220/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/f/global_3262703.jpeg</photo_url></item>