<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One of my favorite films of the musical classics genre, Singin' in the Rain can now be seen the way it is supposed to be seen - on the BIG screen.  I'm very excited about this as I have only seen it on the small screen.  As it extra bonus, this screening is planned as a sing-a-long.  According to the Brattle website, lyric sheets or projected lyrics will be provided for the audience at this event.    Hope to see you there for a fun time.  Umbrellas and tap shoes are optional.  After the film, we will head to a local restaurant for some nourishment and good conversation and perhaps a little singing too. &lt;br /&gt;Susan&lt;br /&gt;P.S. You can buy tickets in advance online at:  &lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/movie_detail/080817.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Brattle website:&lt;br /&gt;One of the most classic musicals of all time, Singin? in the Rain tells the story of Don (Kelly) and Lina (Hagen), a famous on-screen romantic duo. However, their on-screen love is mistaken by Lina for the real thing, she attempts to woo Don who struggles to spurn her advances left and right. When their latest film is turned into a ?talkie?, and not only that, a musical, it comes out that Lina?s voice is, well, terrible. Obviously something must be done. Luckily, Don meets chorus girl Kathy (Reynolds), who has a voice sweet enough to carry the role, and also Don?s heart. Kathy is hired to dub Lina?s voice, and she and Don fall in love despite Lina?s objections. The film is a hit, and as the public clamors for a live performance the truth about threatens to come out.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the front to the right side, and I'll have my MEETUP sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219180348000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214854932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Singin' in the Rain  </name><id>8247717</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219006800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/8247717/</event_url></item>