<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>222 Anderson</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.670340</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zero Station</name><city>Portland</city><id>151559</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.256200</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>deposit</description><amount>250.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2012 Advanced Permaculture Design Certificate Course in Portland Maine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Two long weekends at the beginning of October&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/c/f/event_5904271.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course is designed to reinforce PDC learnings and expand individual design capacity and confidence using a real-word mentored design project for each student.  This course is only offered about every 2-3 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Audience:&lt;/strong&gt; PDC grads, potential permaculture designers and practitioners and those who want to take their &lt;strong&gt;permaculture design skills&lt;/strong&gt; to a deeper level or actively participate in creating a positive post-carbon future.  In addition to deepening design skills, we will dig into the "nuts &amp;amp; bolts" of setting up and running a design business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is not a teacher training course, but contact us if you would like advice about finding a good permaculture teacher training program.  This course may still be of value since teaching permaculture implies a solid foundation and experience with design.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-requisites:&lt;/strong&gt; The requirement for enrolling in the Advanced Permaculture Design Course is the successful completion of a Permaculture Design Certificate Course including the creation of a completed design. (Unfortunately, we cannot make any exceptions to this policy; copy of certificate will be required and, if not locally obtained, we may request a copy of a design you participating in creating).   &lt;em&gt;Contact LisaF if you need advice on PDCs happening nearby if you need to complete your certificate before taking the Advanced Course.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This course will cover advanced permaculture design techniques and skills, advanced mapping strategies, client intake and interaction strategies, advanced details of various sustainable building and energy technologies, business considerations for a permaculture design business and in-depth work with permaculture methods of food production and resilience-building.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the coursework – a combination of lecture, discussion, film, handouts and sample site work - students will be prepared to complete the course by independently preparing a "real life" comprehensive permaculture design project.  Each student will present her/his design to the class and their clients and will conduct an independent follow-up site visit with the course instructors for feedback and validation of design concept and methodology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekend #1 Preliminary Syllabus&lt;/strong&gt; October 5,6,7 9am to 5pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep pattern literacy &amp;amp; landscape reading - with a special treatment of Pattern Languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced mapping &amp;amp; data gathering strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing for a post-carbon future / green building &amp;amp; renewable energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced water strategies (aquaculture, greywater, black water, water catchment and storage)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrating design with surrounding community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eco-Village and "Re-Village" Considerations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Species Selection and Building Perennial Polycultures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced season extension&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intro to The Business of Design: Setup, Planning, Client Management, Marketing, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Special Requirments of Institutional Clients (non-profits, businesses, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced design techniques and presentation creation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating comprehensive client design and maintenance reports including budgets and implementation schedule.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/4/3/5/event_9474325.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Weekend #2 Preliminary Syllabus&lt;/strong&gt; (Friday October 12 8:30 am to Sunday October 14 5pm)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second weekend we go into Studio mode, focusing on mentored independent student design work, drafting and report creation based on data gathered previously (prior to the course or between course weekends).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of a comprehensive graphical permaculture design, including overlays, for a subject property.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of a comprehensive client report to accompany the design including implementation plan, budget and maintenance program.  Addenda will include all collected data, photos, maps, support documents, relevant regulatory documents (zoning, ordinances, covenants or other restrictions) video, completed interviews, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation of designs to class and instructors and clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scheduling follow-up site design presentations (to take place within 3-4 weeks after course) to complete the advanced certification process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Fee:&lt;/strong&gt; $1,100 (10% Discount for Graduates of Portland Maine Permaculture PDC's).  Up to $200 can be paid in &lt;a href="http://www.hourexchangeportland.org/"&gt;time dollars for HEP members&lt;/a&gt;.  A $250 Deposit (partially refundable) holds your spot in this course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Includes:&lt;/strong&gt; Course time, handouts, hearty veg/vegan supper Friday &amp;amp; Saturday night, design supplies, post-course mentoring and feedback on design project.  Lunches will be potluck or BYO (to be confirmed later).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Required Texts:   &lt;a href="http://books.google.com/books?id=lf7wAAAAMAAJ&amp;amp;q=inauthor:%22B.+C.+Mollison%22&amp;amp;dq=inauthor:%22B.+C.+Mollison%22&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ei=BqVXTu3AEqPz0gHxnLiyDA&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;oi=book_result&amp;amp;ct=result&amp;amp;resnum=2&amp;amp;ved=0CC8Q6AEwAQ"&gt;Permaculture, A Designer's Manual&lt;/a&gt; by Bill Mollison and &lt;a href="http://books.google.com/books?id=g1ofAQAAIAAJ&amp;amp;dq=inauthor%3A%22B.%20C.%20Mollison%22&amp;amp;source=gbs_similarbooks"&gt;Permaculture:  Pathways &amp;amp; Principles Beyond Sustainability&lt;/a&gt; by David Holmgren plus online readings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.beyondpermaculture.org/about.htm"&gt;Charles &amp;amp; Julia Yelton&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="http://about.me/lisa.m.fernandes"&gt;Lisa Fernandes&lt;/a&gt; supporting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking is directly in front of the building (Rockingham Electric is opposite); just NOT in front of adjacent bakery:)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349655280000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314365483000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Advanced Permaculture Design Certificate Course in Portland Maine</name><id>31025001</id><duration>201600000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349442000000</time><rsvp_limit>13</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/31025001/</event_url></item>