<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone!  Welcome to the NH rock climbing meetup!  I live in Barrington, NH (about 15 min from Dover) and joined the Boston meet up, however they meet far from my house and it was hard to meet up.  I decided WE needed a meetup closer to NH.  After seeing how many others were thinking the same thing I wanted to step up and begin one! &lt;br /&gt;I have a climbing gym in the barn behind my house (how convenient for meet ups!)  There are four walls, several ropes and hundreds of holds, lots to play on!  I have gear to share if you don't have any.   The gym is run as a non profit ( donations are accepted) and a signed waiver is required.  Don't worry if you don't know how to belay I can teach you.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am hoping to meet some new members at this meeting and see returning faces!  Also I am looking for anyone interested in being asst. organizers, coming to this meeting will help.    &lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to meeting you all!  :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Another note:  I do have a child and will be hosting some climbs w/ families included.  It's fun to include the little ones once in a while so if you have children look for these meetups.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>One and half miles down Scruton Pond Rd is #194 Maroon ranch w/ large barn in back.  Come in driveway or park out front.  Come out back through fence and entrance is right there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kellie Barr-Foster</member_name><member_id>6992283</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215731056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>You will love it because you will meet others who share the love of climbing.  It's always more fun when you climb with other people!</why><group><who>Rock Climbers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>rockclimbing-134</urlname><id>1120342</id><group_lat>43.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>The NH Rock Climbing Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213143164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NH Rock Climbing July Meeting</name><id>8119296</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215558000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/rockclimbing-134/events/8119296/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/1/global_3885009.jpeg</photo_url></item>