<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301991</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-628-4422 or 1-888-263-4388</phone><name>AMC Framingham Premium Cinema</name><city>Framingham</city><id>715731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390305</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>NEW STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 7:15, so let's meet BY 6:45 right inside the doors of the theater. If you're late or want to RSVP last-minute, my cell: 508-308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you on Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1809961243/info" target="_blank"&gt;Four Christmases&lt;/a&gt; is sure to get you in the holiday spirit (or at least, dread going to see your 2nd cousins again this year)! Here's the summary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;When upscale, happily unmarried San Francisco couple Kate and Brad find themselves socked in by fog on Christmas morning, their exotic vacation plans morph into the family-centric holiday they had, until now, gleefully avoided. Out of obligation--and unable to escape--they trudge to not one, not two, but four relative-choked festivities, increasingly mortified to find childhood fears raised, adolescent wounds reopened... and their very future together uncertain. As Brad counts the hours to when he can get away from their parents, step-parents, siblings and an assortment of nieces and nephews, Kate is starting to hear the ticking of a different kind of clock. And by the end of the day, she is beginning to wonder if their crazy families' choices are not so crazy after all.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this meetup a few days before to narrow down the time. Let's meet right outside the theater (or just inside the doors if Jack Frost is nipping). Then we can go get our discounted tickets ($8.50 for FMM members and their guests -- exact change makes me like you more) and get snacks and whatnot. I have $3 vouchers for small popcorns and small sodas, if anyone's interested in them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests are always welcome, but please just make sure to include them in your RSVP so I know how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you next Wednesday!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My cell phone number, if you're late or need directions or have a last-minute RSVP:&lt;br /&gt;508-308-4897.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic. :-)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1230685897000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229031570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Four Christmases</name><id>9323237</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229558400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/9323237/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>