<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>28 Mugford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.505630</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Me &amp; Thee Coffee House</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>11779572</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.851257</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Me and Thee coffeehouse winter season is amazing, can't miss this one either!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shawn Mullins&lt;/strong&gt; translates life into song. His musical accomplishments include a dozen self-produced records, two number one charting songs, Grammy nomination and thousands of live performances. ¶ Nashville based &lt;strong&gt;Carey Murdock&lt;/strong&gt;, who opens the show, is an Americana artist who frequently performs on both sides of the Atlantic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N ATLANTA-BASED FOLKSINGER&lt;/small&gt; best known for his Top Ten hit “Lullaby,” &lt;strong&gt;Shawn Mullins&lt;/strong&gt; was serving as a member of the U.S. Army Airborne Infantry Division when he released his first self-titled cassette in 1989. Following the release of 1991’s &lt;em&gt;Everchanging World&lt;/em&gt;, he left the military after eight years to pursue music on a full-time basis. After three years spent fruitlessly searching for a record deal, Mullins established a new label, &lt;span&gt;SMG&lt;/span&gt;, and released the LPs &lt;em&gt;Better Days&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Big Blue Sky&lt;/em&gt; in the interim. &lt;em&gt;Jeff’s Last Dance, Vol. 1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Vol. 2&lt;/em&gt; arrived in 1995, and Mullins returned a year later with the solo effort &lt;em&gt;Eggshells&lt;/em&gt;. Released in 1998, &lt;em&gt;Soul’s Core&lt;/em&gt; marked his first album for a major label, Columbia Records; it also signaled his critical breakthrough, as the single “Lullaby” became a chart-topping single on the adult Top 40 charts. The album eventually went platinum, paving the way for an anthology of the singer’s early work with 1999’s&lt;em&gt;The First Ten Years&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fall 2000, Mullins released the official follow-up, &lt;em&gt;Beneath the Velvet Sun&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;The Essential Shawn Mullins&lt;/em&gt; collection arrived in 2003, followed by &lt;em&gt;9th Ward Pickin’ Parlor&lt;/em&gt; for Vanguard Records in 2006. He remained with Vanguard for 2008’s &lt;em&gt;Honeydew&lt;/em&gt;, which was inspired by (and recorded in) his native Georgia. &lt;em&gt;Live at the Variety Playhouse&lt;/em&gt; was released that same year, capturing a sold-out Mullins performance in Atlanta. Since that time, Mullins has undergone a series of transformative experiences (including the birth of his first child), leading to a second coming for the veteran artist. Evidence of Mullins’ newfound level of musical and lyrical ambition courses comes through with &lt;em&gt;Light You Up&lt;/em&gt;. This captivating new song cycle will likely be viewed as a flat-out revelation even by Mullins’ most fervent fans.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I charge $1 per person per event to cover Meetup costs but you must also BUY YOUR OWN CONCERT TICKET ($28) AT THE BROWN PAPER TICKETS WEBSITE. You can also buy tix at the door if they are not sold out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to meet for dinner first in Marblehead, we get 10% discount at the Landing on Front Street. Park on Washington Street or Mugford Street and walk down Front Street to the Landing so you won't need to move your car later..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in foyer OR if you can get there, meet at the Landing Restaurant for pre-concert dinner at 6.15PM</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361597057000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361114135000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shawn Mullins at the Me and Thee in Marblehead - Carey Murdock opens</name><id>105002022</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361581200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/105002022/</event_url></item>