<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>29 Elm Street, Left Door</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.393749</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Trish's House</name><city>Somerville (near Porter Square)</city><id>7085092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120018</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This is an event I am holding in my meetup group called Collide: Creating at the intersection of technology, science arts and culture. I think many of you would also enjoy it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Collide/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Collide/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things that has fascinated me and part of the motivation for my starting diverse meetup groups is the idea the more diversity and randomness, the more possibilities for true innovation and new ideas. Cross-pollination is a powerful creative force. That can take the form of inspiration for an art piece or for a new product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this experimental night....let's get creative, and purposely stretch our abilities to create from unlikely intersection points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In small groups we will create a fantasy business, project, product, service, etc...by connecting and utilizing the expertise of the random participants. Everyone must be included in some way. In our last meeting we had a hugely diverse group with artists, engineers, nonprofits, a chimney sweep, etc. It can be outrageous and funny or something practical. The goal is not to focus on something that will actually manifest, but rather to exercise our abilities to break the box all together...see new connections and spark possibilities for our own businesses, projects, lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food and beverage will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A voluntary $5 contribution is requested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can make it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Trish Blain</member_name><member_id>50944272</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355624797000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354205984000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creative Collisions -- Multiple Meetup Event</name><id>93337822</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355443200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/93337822/</event_url></item>