<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Laurel Marsh Trail loop is about 3 miles. Mostly easy hike great for beginning hikers with some sections including raised boardwalk over the marsh and bridges. Some wet areas, a few small hills, great Hockanum River and marsh views, water birds, mature forest, giant white pines, and mountain laurel. Park at Laurel Marsh parking lot on south side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60, and meet there at 10 AM. The lot is not well marked but can be seen with a low but heavy wooden fence. The hike should take about 1.5 hours. Dogs on leash are fine if well behaved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approximate location/directions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;to parking lot and start (South side of Middle Turnpike West (Route 44) just east of I-84, Exit 60 in Manchester, CT): &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=870+Middle+Tpke+W&amp;amp;city=Manchester&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06040"&gt;http://www.mapquest.com/maps?address=870+Middle+Tpke+W&amp;amp;city=Manchester&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;zipcode=06040&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By clicking on "Yes" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349055957000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348203474000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Laurel Marsh in Manchester, CT</name><id>83409292</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348322400000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/83409292/</event_url></item>