<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>480 Trapelo rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.387310</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Wheelworks</name><city>Belmont</city><id>586783</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.189026</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wheelworks Multisport Tri Night 2008 with Dede Griesbauer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us May 2nd for Tri Night 2008, meet Dede, win prizes, raise funds for CYCLE Kids and start your season right!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The highlight of the evening will be a presentation from a world-class, Boston-based professional triathlete, Dede Griesbauer. Among her many accomplishments are the 1st place female finish at the UK Ironman Championship in 2006 and her top 10, first American finish at Kona for the Ironman World Championship race in 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following Dede's presentation there will be a drawings for a 2008 Specialized bike frame, Oakley sunglasses, Restaurant gift certificates, Night out dinner + movie combos, a Weekend vacation home rental in Maine, and much more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Proceeds from raffle ticket sales will go to the Wheelworks Multisport team fund and $1 from each ticket sold will be donated CYCLE Kids -- an independent, local nonprofit organization designed to introduce children to the joys of cycling through activities teaching bike safety, healthy eating and fitness, and environmental awareness. Join us!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raffle tickets may be purchased in advance or at Tri-Night. Attendance is not required to win. Just remember to write your name and phone number on the ticket. Contact vp@ww-ms.orgThis e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, May 2nd&lt;br /&gt;7pm-9pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:00 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet and greet with team members, friends, family, and sponsors.  Enjoy light food and drink, win some door prizes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7:30pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presentation by Dede Griesbauer, professional triathlete, 2007 top 10 Ironman World Champion finisher in Kona.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Belmont Wheelworks&lt;br /&gt;480 Trapelo Road&lt;br /&gt;Belmont, MA 02478&lt;br /&gt;tel 617.489.3577&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8:30 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drawing for the raffle prizes (Need not be present to win) including:  a 2008 bike frame, triathlon gear, entertainment packages, weekend getaway to Maine, and more...&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209942419000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>it will be fun, you can get some great tips, and we'll probably go out for drinks afterwards!  (I will be biking there, so we can also get a group to ride back to somerville/cambridge together!)</why><group><who>Triathletes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Tri</urlname><id>584357</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8399963379</group_lon><name>Mass Tri</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1208964702000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tri Night</name><id>7796423</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209769200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Tri/events/7796423/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/2/global_1776498.jpeg</photo_url></item>