<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I was impressed with this nice little spot, totaling 170 acres.  Goldsmith Woodlands is an Avis property located in Andover, quite close to Harold Parker State Forest.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the Walk&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the parking area and leave at 1:10.  The walk will be slow and we will stop often to enjoy any wildlife we may spot and to enjoy the scenery.  I saw a red-breasted nuthatch here recently. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; The walk will be about 3 to 4 miles long.  I'd suggest warm clothes, as the trails near the pond can be chilly, depending on the day.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;There are no restrooms on site, so please plan accordingly&lt;/u&gt;!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Trails&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trails are fairly easy.  There aren't any swift changes in elevation. There are few rocks and large tree roots that can make other properties difficult to walk through.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hiker Code of Conduct&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please try not to get too far ahead of the group. I go to a lot of effort to organize these walks, and it's not enjoyable when people run ahead and create their own event. If you have an emergency, I completely understand. Otherwise, these are designed to be leisurely, social walks, with time to appreciate the critters around us!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can always use more organizers, and if anyone feels that the pace of the walk is not appropriate for their needs, they should consider organizing their own event in the future.  I am glad to see that some others have been leading moderate and fast-paced walks recently.  Cheers and thank you for this! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;History&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An 1830 map shows the Goldsmith family in possession of the woodlands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the early 20th century, Goldsmith Woodlands were a favorite summer retreat.  Bessie Goldsmith collected rent from those who had cottages on her land.  Cellar holes and swing hinges on trees are still visible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of these cottages belonged to Zack, a caretaker of these woods and a handyman for the summer residents.  His name lives on in the designation of Zack's way, Zack's house and Zack's hop pit, a large cellar hole on the hill overlooking the pond.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1974, Bessie Goldsmith, a dedicated conservationist, donated her woodlands and land inherited from her brother Clarence to the Fund for the Preservation of Wildlife and Natural Areas.  AVIS became the caretakers in 1977 with funds given for maintenance out of Bessie's trust.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stories about Bessie Goldsmith's somewhat eccentric behavior in her devotion to protecting her woodlands are legendary.  She lived in a rustic cabin on a knoll overlooking Foster's Pond.  She was known to point her shotgun at trespassers and if she caught people picking blueberries, she demanded they turn the full pail over to her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Address&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;491 South Main St., Andover, MA, diagonally in the front yard.  If you take route 28 from route 495, leave yourself some extra time.  It can be a little slow going with all of the stop lights and traveling through Andover center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;How the Waiting List Works&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When someone from the hike drops, everyone on the waiting list is automatically emailed. The first person on the the waiting list to add themselves to the hike will get in. I realize that this doesn't seem fair for the first person on the waiting list, if someone lower on the list gets in. However, I found that the automatic waiting list resulted in a very high percentage of no-shows. A number of people didn't check their email, even days before the hike, and therefore didn't know they had gotten in to the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking area- You won't ,miss us- It's a tiny lot!  </how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1291599804000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290284376000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Walk at Goldsmith Woodlands- Many Stops- Followed by Coffee/Snack</name><id>15510885</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291485600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/15510885/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/6/6/global_8499174.jpeg</photo_url></item>