<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>P.O. Box 270896</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06127</zip><lat>41.762336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Online</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>1447422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.680638</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Register and learn more at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=375" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=375&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Nyrik and I would like to thank you for the opportunity to share our approach to real estate investing with your members. We get a great deal of satisfation from sharing our experiences with others and helping them avoid many of the pitfalls that we have experienced first hand. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

After hearing us teach, Tom attended one of our weekend classes. This class is&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;the same class that we will be teaching to CT REIA on November 12 &amp;amp; 13. At that time, he owned 5 rental properties in Massachusetts and was extremely frustrated because most months he had to support his properties with outside sources of cash. He had bought them using conventional financing and his model required that everything function perfectly in order for the properties to cash flow. Unfortunately, given the current economy, he found that he was having a difficult time collecting rents on time and in many cases going through the eviction process. These two factors resulted in negative cash flow. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Tom went on the road to Pennsylvania with us and he bought 2 bank owned houses. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

One of the houses was 506 E.Division Street. It is a 4 bedroom 1 and 1/2 bath that need very little work. We negotiated a purchase price of $9,250.00 and the rehab cost was $3,817.00. The after repair value of this house is $57,000.00. This means that he has created over a 400% return on his cash immediately. Tom has now rented the property for $600.00 per month with the tenant paying all utilities including water and sewer. If Tom has 6 months of vacancy, he will still make over a 20% return from cash flow on his investment. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Tom is so excited from this new approach to investing that he is joining us for our Tax Sale Road Trip next month. He is one of a number of students that have come on REO road trips with us, bought properties and then joined us on road trips to other markets or to the tax sale. The reason they want to pay to learn these new markets is simple. They made more money on their first deals than they spent on the education. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Since Tom has done these deals, and more, he has chosen to not only sell his MA investments, but move to Pennsylvania and create a business providing much needed management services to other students. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

After we spoke at the 2011 New England Real Estate Investors Conference and Trade Show, more members had questions than we had time to address. We loved spending time with all of you at the monthly meeting, speaking to all the brave people who stayed for the panel discussion Saturday night and really getting into the details of our investment approach. Still so many of you had more questions and concerns as to how our approach would fit your portfolio building needs. As a result, we are going to offer a free teleseminar on Thursday, November 3rd. It will be a forum where were will be able to answer any questions that folks have. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

We are looking forward to teaching you, in great detail, our approach to investing on November 12 &amp;amp; 13th. The cost of $595.00 is for 2 people, not one. For those who are interested in going on our Tax Sale Road Trip in December, it is important to know that the weekend class is a pre requisite to going on the Road Trip. The students must have the educational foundation from the weekend so that we can hit the ground running when we get to Pennsylvania. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Thank you again for allowing us the opportunity to bring our story to your members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320369729000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320181951000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Teleseminar - Buy House for Less Than Price of a Car</name><id>39551272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320364800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/39551272/</event_url></item>