<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>371 Summer St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.393651</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dilboy VFW Hall in Davis Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1104348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119526</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;TICKETS STILL AVAILABLE AT &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/85629422/"&gt;NERD FUN's Meetup SITE!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since last year's Halloween party was such a huge success, the Sci-fi/Fantasy Meetup is throwing another big bash this year! We'll have food, music, dancing, games, decorations and a costume contest with cash prizes. Admission is $25 per person to cover the cost of the event. We sold out last year, so don't wait to the last minute to RSVP!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costume contest:&lt;/strong&gt; First place is $100, second place is $75, third place is $50, so come in costume and be prepared to compete! There is no "theme" for the party or the contest, so let your imagination run wild.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food:&lt;/strong&gt; Food is being catered by Putterham &lt;span&gt;Grille &amp;amp; Catering from Chestnut Hill&lt;/span&gt;. We'll have a spread of appetizers including Cheese, Fruit, Veggies and Dip, and Chips and Salsa. The dinner menu will consist of a choice of four hot Italian entrees (Cheese Lasagna w/Meat Sauce, Vegetarian Lasagna, and Chicken with Mushroom and Alfredo Sauce (Gluten-Free)), served buffet style with Garden Salad and Hot Rolls. Oh, of course, we'll have desserts and Halloween Candy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drinks:&lt;/strong&gt; A full cash bar will be on site, and their drinks are cheap! Pricing last year was $2.00 for water/soda/juice, $3.75 for most domestic beers and wine, $4.25 to $4.75 for single liquor drinks and imported beers, $5.50 for two liquor drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; The Dilboy VFW is located a short walking distance from the Davis Square T stop, but it also has a private parking lot that we will be able to use (it is surrounded by a chain-link fence, is well lit, and there are clear signs to lead you to it). Please note that the front entrance to the VFW will not be accessible for this event, so you must enter at the back (where the parking lot is). We'll have signs outside in case you get lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, while we have to charge a cost for this party, we've tried very hard to keep costs as low as possible. No one is making any money off this event, all of the money we collect is going into making this party a fantastic night to remember and meetup costs. (Since I know people will ask if it is possible to not pre-pay and pay in person on the night of the party, the answer is no, unless we have not sold out, and we'll announce that change if it happens before the event.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robyn</member_name><member_id>9373103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1351905544000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>22</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>76</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344691688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Party and Costume Contest</name><id>77293662</id><headcount>91</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351378800000</time><rsvp_limit>76</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/77293662/</event_url></item>