<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We hope you're able to join us for a last-minute evening of playing the &lt;strong&gt;strategy game&lt;/strong&gt; Dominion and its expansions. We'll have Dominion, Intrigue, Prosperity, and Hinterlands, though we welcome your sets as well should you like to bring them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who have never played Dominion, it is a tactical/strategic card game played with 2-4 players with a plot as follows:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You are a monarch, like your parents before you, a ruler of a small pleasant kingdom of rivers and evergreens. Unlike your parents, however, you have hopes and dreams. You want a bigger and more pleasant kingdom, with more rivers and a wider variety of trees. You want a Dominion. In all directions lie fiefs, freeholds, and feodums. All are small bits of land, controlled by petty lords and verging on anarchy. You will bring civilization to these people, uniting them under your banner. But wait. It must be something in the air, several other monarchs have had the exact same idea. You must race to get as much of the unclaimed land as possible, fending them off along the way. To do this you will hire minions, construct buildings, spruce up your castle, and fill the coffers of your treasury. Your parents wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be proud, but your grandparents, would be delighted.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is very quick to learn, each game is different, and there are countless strategies on how to win.&amp;nbsp;Each player starts with an identical, very small deck of cards. In the center of the table is a selection of other cards the players can "buy" as they can afford them. Through their selection of cards to buy, and how they play their hands as they draw them, the players construct their deck on the fly, striving for the most efficient path to the precious victory points by game end.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you like strategy games or want to learn more about this genre, this event will be for you. &amp;nbsp;We welcome new players with open arms and will gladly teach you how to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats, but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a 3 year old, who will be headed to bed as people arrive. We also have a twelve month old, who isn't much of a game player, but he will eventually go to bed as well. Expect to see him awake while you are here, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326050228000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325874941000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Dominion Night</name><id>46966892</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325984400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/46966892/</event_url></item>