<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Managing and Retaining Volunteers!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Format&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Introductions (15 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.  Moderated discussion on specific topic (1 hour).  &lt;br /&gt;This meetup will benefit organizations seeking to build and manage successful volunteer programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.  Announcements, opportunities, connections (10 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.. Exchange business cards/social networking. (15 mins)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to our Building:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We?re located at 1 Broadway, Cambridge, MA 02142.  We?re approximately 100 feet from the MBTA Red Line's Kendall/MIT station. Buses 64, 68 and ct2 also stop nearby 1 Broadway.  There is usually pretty ample street parking that?s not metered after 7PM, but there?s also a parking garage attached to the building.  You?ll know our building because there is a Wainwright Bank in the first level.  Folks will have to sign in in the lobby, but then they should come to the 5th Floor.  We?ll meet people there or have signs up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Host Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting will be hosted by Molly Gropeter, in the building where her business is located:&lt;br /&gt;Using a new technology, Annkissam specializes in building custom work flow systems for nonprofits. We build software that specifically supports an individual nonprofit?s unique operations, reporting, outcome measurements and more. The technology that we use allows us to do this more efficiently than other technologies thereby allowing us to build custom systems that are affordable for small and medium sized nonprofits.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the room 15 minutes early.  You'll recognize me from my photo!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jari Poulin</member_name><member_id>4665005</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206659145000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>Great people, opportunity to network, learn and share from a dynamic group of nonprofit professionals.</why><group><who>Positive Changemakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nonprofit-allies</urlname><id>591859</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nonprofit Connector</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203469695000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Managing and Retaining Volunteers!</name><id>7366317</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206486000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nonprofit-allies/events/7366317/</event_url></item>