<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360073</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Building E51-345</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>337655</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Feature Presentation&lt;br /&gt;IBD 100® --- FRIEND OR FOE? Presented by MIKE KINKEAD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you ever wonder whether Investors Business Daily's IBD 100 is an effective source of new investment opportunities, or are IBD 100 stocks too late to the party or even excellent short sale candidates?  In other words, is the IBD 100 list an effective source of high performing stocks?  At this Tuesday IBD Meetup, MIKE KINKEAD will present an analysis of the IBD 100 stocks from November, 2006 to this July's market correction to answer the following questions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- How well do these stocks perform during their tenure on the IBD 100?&lt;br /&gt;- What is the probability of achieving at least a 20% gain on an IBD 100 stock in no more than eight months? A 50% gain or more?&lt;br /&gt;- What percentage of IBD 100 stocks lose money?&lt;br /&gt;- Is there a clear way to determine which stocks will be the high performers when they arrive on the IBD 100 list?&lt;br /&gt;- Do the Black Boxes help identify the winners?&lt;br /&gt;- What role does the William J. O'Neil Industry Group Rank play in determining a stock's performance on the IBD 100?&lt;br /&gt;- Does a stock's time on the IBD 100 list capture the bulk of the stock's gain or was it captured prior to arrival?&lt;br /&gt;- Why don't other high performing stocks hit the IBD 100, such as the solar stocks in the first half of 2007?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us to contribute to an exciting conversation about this area of the CANSLIM® neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIO OF MIKE KINKEAD&lt;br /&gt;MIKE KINKEAD has been active in our group since Buddha's Delite. He has repeatedly shared his insights into fast-growing growth stocks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIKE is currently a vice-president at Urban Wallace Associates, a marketing and management consulting company that helps build new businesses and strengthen existing ones. He has started and built three software and information companies, and has been directly involved in the creation of five other for-profit and non-profit organizations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1974 MIKE started Saddlebrook, a banking software company, and as its CEO, grew the business to over $28 million in revenues. Saddlebrook was on the INC. 500 and INC. 100 lists of most rapidly growing, privately held companies in the United States. In 1989, MIKE co-founded and was CEO of SandPoint Company. SandPoint's innovative flat fee information pricing approach changed the online business information game, and Hoover, SandPoint's software product, was selected as the most important new information product of the year at the 1994 Online Conference. In 1994, Ziff-Davis acquired the company. In 2001, MIKE co-founded and was the CEO of timeBLASTER Corporation, a company focused on helping people make more effective and efficient use of information on the Web. timeBLASTER currently offers an application for serious eBay collectors and under the name of Acumenta, also offers an online research capability to genomics and proteomics researchers in the life sciences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIKE was a principal at and investor in Reach Internet Incubator and ran the entrepreneurial services team that launched 18 companies. MIKE has also held executive positions at The Thomson Corporation, Individual, Inc. and Icebreaker, Inc., companies in the information and software industries, and prior to joining Urban Wallace, was most recently the CEO of Metatomix, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1986, MIKE helped start the Massachusetts Software Council (now the Mass Technology Leadership Council) where he served as Chairman and continues to serve on its Executive Committee and Board, runs the offsite Board retreat every year and also facilitates the Sales &amp;amp; Marketing Roundtable for the Council. In 1999, MIKE was one of six founders of the CommonAngels, a Boston-based angel investing group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIKE is a Level III IBD Investor. He received an undergraduate degree in an experimental computer science program under Jay Forrester at MIT and an MBA from the Harvard Business School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PREMEETING (Optional)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the premeeting period ERIC EKLOF will lead the first ever meeting of the Cool-Trade Boston User's Group (CTBUG). The premeeting will run from 5:30 to 6:50 - before the meeting starts. It is a way to conserve travel time &amp;amp; costs. Anyone is welcome to attend and you do not have to be using the software as we will have it projected on the big screen to play with, explore and learn! If you have questions please feel free to email ERIC direct at eklofsr@sover.net .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MEETUP AGENDA&lt;br /&gt;- 5:30-6:50 ERIC EKLOF leads the Cool Trade Boston Users Group. See above. Users of any robotic trader are welcome. This is an optional meeting. Open to all. &lt;br /&gt;7:00 - Meeting Begins:&lt;br /&gt;- Group discussion led by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;- Technical Analysis update by Harlan&lt;br /&gt;- Stockpicks section&lt;br /&gt;- Feature Presentation by Mike Kinkead (see above)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have friends that you talk stocks with then bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free meeting. There is no membership required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1189724939000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>71</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186643564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investors Business Daily Tuesday Meetup</name><id>6150466</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1189551600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/6150466/</event_url></item>