<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>255 Grossman Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.211508</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Border's Books &amp; Cafe</name><city>Braintree</city><id>715069</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.999105</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us as we discuss the novel &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;The School of Essential Ingredients&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;. We will meet in the cafe area at the front of Borders Bookstore. We will place a copy of the book on the table so that new people can find the group easily. New members are welcome to join the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Book Synopsis: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Once a month on Monday night, eight students gather in Lillian's restaurant for a cooking class. Among them is Claire, a young woman coming to terms with her new identity as a mother; Tom, a lawyer whose life has been overturned by loss: Antonia, an Italian kitchen designer adapting to life in America; and Carl and Helen, a long-married couple whose union contains surprises the rest of the class would never suspect.&amp;quot; The students have come to learn the art behind Lillian's soulful dishes, but it soon becomes clear that each seeks a recipe for something beyond the kitchen. One by one they are transformed by the aromas, flavors, and textures of what they create, including a white-on-white cake that prompts wistful reflections on the sweet fragility of love, and a garlic and red sauce that seems to spark one romance but end another. Over time, the paths of the students mingle and intertwine, and the essence of Lillian's cooking expands beyond the restaurant and into the secret corners of their lives, with results that are often unexpected, and always delicious.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will put a copy of the book on the table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272388072000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1270038790000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South Shore Readers: School of Essential Ingredients</name><id>13046666</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272214800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/13046666/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/d/b/global_14044571.jpeg</photo_url></item>