<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302966</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-990-7411</phone><name>CENTER OF LIGHT</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1213795</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434031</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Most everyone wants peace in their hearts and in their minds. The secret desire of human hearts and souls is for there to be peace among peoples, nations, and individuals. How can each one of us play a part in making this a reality? What spiritual practices actually make us transform into beings who live in peace and work toward peace in the world? Come join Mother Clare Watts as she describes the practices of the mystics that help bring peace to the earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested Donation: $25 - Bring a Friend for Free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 Additional seminars will be offered that week end:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Mother Mary: A Full Incarnation of the Divine Feminine (Friday November 18 at 7:30pm) &lt;br /&gt;

 - Purity and the Link to Happiness (Saturday November 19 at 10:00am)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please visit the meetup group for more information about these seminars &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare Watts is an ordained Priest and Master Teacher in the Order of Christ-Sophia. &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare founded the Boston Center of Light, formerly called the Christ-Sophia Center, &lt;br /&gt;

 where she continued to serve until 2001. At that time she moved to Seattle to begin a new Center of Light. &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare live in Dolores Colorado where she supervise the effort of the Sophia Peace Center. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare worked as a Certified Professional Midwife for 18 years, having her own midwifery practices in Kentucky &lt;br /&gt;

 and Massachusetts. She received her Masters Degree in 1996 in Counseling Psychology. Mother Clare attended three years of &lt;br /&gt;

 postgraduate training in Jungian Analysis at the Boston Jung Institute. She had her own psychotherapy practice alongside &lt;br /&gt;

 her midwifery practice until she ended both in 2001 in order to attend full-time to her work as a Priest and Master Teacher. &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare has four grown children. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Mother Clare is the author of an autobiographical book chronicling her life of spiritual seeking and the &lt;br /&gt;

 process that led to her being ordained into spiritual Mastery in the Christian mystical tradition. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please visit www.MotherClareWatts.com, to read excerpts and order her book, Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path to Enlightenment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321580337000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319133703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World Peace: Practices of the Mystics that Help Bring Peace on Earth</name><id>38113042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321576200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/38113042/</event_url></item>