<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>86 Joy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.378270</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 666-2200</phone><name>Joy Street Artist Studio</name><city>Somerville</city><id>272683</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.086680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Greetings, everyone! &lt;br /&gt;

 May you all be safe, and dry! As the storm raged on, I'm sure you all were left daydreaming about ways to stretch those artistic muscles. It is with great excitement that I invite you to my studio next month, where the heat and creative juices will be cranking every Thursday night! &lt;br /&gt;

 Details: &lt;br /&gt;

 What: uninstructed figure-study (same model/pose throughout) &lt;br /&gt;

 Length: 12 hours &lt;br /&gt;

 Dates: Nov 15th, 29th, Dec 6th, 13th &lt;br /&gt;

 Time: 6:30-9:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

 Cost: $100 the entire amount must be received in full (cash or check) on the day of the first session. If payment is not received by this date, you will not be admitted. &lt;br /&gt;

 Pre pay available, contact respond to this listing &lt;br /&gt;

 Make-up Sessions: There are no make-up sessions provided for this series; it will run on the scheduled dates, only. You will be notified if a session must be rescheduled due to inclement weather. &lt;br /&gt;

 Storage: Moving your work around too much of a hassle? For the duration of the series, you can store your paintings and drawings from the sessions right here in the studio! &lt;br /&gt;

 Materials: &lt;br /&gt;

 Pastels not allowed. Sorry, folks! Canvas/paper: 24 X 30 or smaller Oils: odorless mineral spirits, or other odorless solvents Acrylics: always welcome! Water is available from the hallway sink! Charcoal and graphite are great as always! &lt;br /&gt;

 I hope you'll join me for these four weeks! Amazing music, a stellar model from NYC, art storage and all for about $8 an hour...no foolin'! &lt;br /&gt;

 Jump on it! Space is limited to 9!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>12089530</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354242758000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Art Models and Artists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NE-artists-models-group</urlname><id>408475</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>New England Artists/Models Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353718075000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4 session figure pose!  Meets weekly.  1 pose for the duration!</name><id>qkhwsdyqpbmc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354231800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-artists-models-group/events/92566002/</event_url></item>