<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Skyline Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.282416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Green Hill Park</name><city>Worcester </city><id>918893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.775371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Worcester Photography Group –April Click &amp;amp; Shoot  &lt;br /&gt;What:  A shoot with models in Green Hill Park&lt;br /&gt;When:  Saturday – April 18, 2009, 1 pm until (whenever people leave).&lt;br /&gt;Where: Green Hill Park, Worcester. MA. Entrance off Route 9, meet at Veterans Memorial parking lot and pavilion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s spring and time to get out and shoot. Add some sunny weather and some lovely models on a TF/CD shoot and it will be a fun day. There are lots of great background locations in Green Hill Park and Plenty of room for a whole crew of people. We can share models and switch up locations. It's going to be a great time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your camera and if you know a model or two, have them come on out to play! If you don't know any models –  don’t worry – we will do a casting call on Model Mayhem looking for willing models. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do know a few models - please note that Models need to come already prepared to shoot (or bring their own MUA/Stylist. We are not providing MUAs or outfits.) So when they show up - they should be ready to be photographed!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'd suggest you bring some munchies and refreshments.... esp water and sunscreen! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Special Note: Photographers must be willing to give JPGs of their best shots to Lou Swinand, who will compile them and give each model a CD with their pics.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rain date: Following Saturday, April 25.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lou Swinand is organizing this shoot so if you have any questions just find him on the members list and zip him an email! Thanks Lou!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meeting at the Pavillion</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240413679000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238538164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Click and Shoot- Let's Photograph a Few Models at Green Hill Park</name><id>10082288</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240074000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/10082288/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/3/global_7929683.jpeg</photo_url></item>