<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.368332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-558-7208</phone><name>Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>669040</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.071600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>One of the great benefits of sailing is the ability to reach far-away destinations, exotic locales, and discover new lands and creatures. Whlile many historic explorers enjoyed such benefits, Charles Darwin managed to combine them all, and document his findings for everyone to enjoy. His trip to the Galapagos spawned his master work &amp;quot;Origin of Species&amp;quot; and laid the groundwork for the understanding of evolution. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To celebrate sea, earth, creatures large and small, and the spirit of sailing exploration, this month we will visit the Museum of Science to see the Omni Film &amp;quot;Galapagos&amp;quot;. From the MOS website (&lt;a href="http://www.mos.org):" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mos.org):...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Join marine biologist Dr. Carole Baldwin on a tour of one of the world's most intriguing natural environments: the Galapagos Islands. See in brilliant IMAX® clarity the volcanic archipelago's famous tortoises, sea lions, lizards and birds, and then dive beneath the ocean to find fantastic sea creatures, some of which were previously unidentified.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As sailors, we should have a great appreciation of the sea and its inhabitants. Who knows, maybe one day one of our members will sail to the Galapagos as well. The show starts at 6pm, so please arrive by 5:30pm to get your ticket and chat beforehand. The cost of movie admission is $9. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 16327</member_name><member_id>16327</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175808661000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173228031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Sailing April Meetup - Galapagos!</name><id>5543596</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175635800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/5543596/</event_url></item>