<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>52 Brattle St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374305</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-0683</phone><name>Cafe of India</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>836643</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122097</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi - In our efforts to provide a mix of events within reach of those of us on a budget, let's take advantage of one of Boston's locally available resources at Longy School of Music on Friday, May 8th in Harvard Square.  The concert starts at 8pm and is FREE. We'll meet for dinner at Cafe of India on 52 Brattle nearby to be kind on the wallet and so as to finish in time for the concert. Please join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edward M. Pickman Concert Hall&lt;br /&gt;Pacifica Competition Concert&lt;br /&gt;- Prokofiev: String Quartet in F major, op. 92&lt;br /&gt;- Brahms Piano Quintet in F minor, op. 34 with Christopher Carson, pianist (Pacifica Quartet competition winner)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, the Pickman Concert Hall is promoted by Longy as one of New England’s finest small concert venues. Favored for its honest acoustic, the birch paneled 300-seat auditorium provides an intimate concert setting, especially well suited for chamber music. Pickman Concert Hall hosts over 250 musical events each season, including concerts &amp;amp; master classes featuring Longy students, faculty &amp;amp; guest artists, as well presentations by local artists and performance organizations.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Susan C. Try to arrive closer to 5:45-6:00 pm if possible.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan C</member_name><member_id>6899147</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242431848000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240235791000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Longy School of Musica Pacifica Competition Concert and pre-concert restaurant</name><id>10224773</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241820000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/10224773/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/d/6/global_5526982.jpeg</photo_url></item>