<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Colovos Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.137072</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Gregg Hall - Environmental Technology Building</name><city>Durham</city><id>1200877</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.936242</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I've changed some details that you should review - new parking directions, a way to download the waiver form in advance for faster registration, and the location of bathrooms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should you know how to use a map and compass to know where you are, to navigate to where you want to go, or to help you survive in an emergency situation? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Faye Doria of The New England Hiking Meetup&lt;/b&gt; and Up North Orienteers will hold a map and compass skills workshop on Saturday, April 17, 2010 to teach you these skills, and give  &lt;br /&gt;you an opportunity to practice them in the woods.  The event  &lt;br /&gt;will be held rain or shine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From 10:00 am to noon&lt;/b&gt;, you can progress through a series of stations to learn and practice the following skills: &lt;br /&gt;read the map for scale, declination, climb, and features &lt;br /&gt;use your compass to navigate to features on a map &lt;br /&gt;use your compass and surroundings to return to a point &lt;br /&gt;determine distance traveled using the scale on the map &lt;br /&gt;navigate around impassable obstacles &lt;br /&gt;how to easily find a particular spot &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From 11:00 am to 1:00 pm&lt;/b&gt;, you can practice the same skills on a longer orienteering course in the woods.  All participants must be off the course by 3:30 pm.&lt;b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The cost is only $5.00 for the map and compass workshop and the practice course in the woods.&lt;/b&gt;  You will be asked to register and sign a waiver form.  Note that there are no restroom facilities at the site.  Bring your own compass, or you can borrow one on site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to UpNoOr.org to download and complete the UNO Waiver Form pdf for faster registration.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the workshop:&lt;/b&gt;  From Route 4, exit at Route 155A (UNH - Whittemore Center).  Turn towards Durham and travel 1.2 miles on that road to the UNH Campus.  At the traffic light take a right onto College Road and travel 0.3 miles.  It best if you park there in Lot F.  Then walk down South Drive and go under the RR overpass.  Gregg Hall and registration will be directly ahead of you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please park in a legal parking space, as the UNH police issue $100 tickets for cars parked anywhere that is not a proper parking space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bathrooms are available in Kingsbury Hall, just east across College Road from Lot F (3 minute walk from registration).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Check in at the registration table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Faye</member_name><member_id>3391935</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271721804000</updated><rating><average>4.30000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267047822000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Map and Compass Skills Workshop </name><id>12698648</id><headcount>44</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271512800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12698648/</event_url></item>