<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Two or Three Things I Know About Her&lt;/b&gt;  France 1966 90 min.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although this is on a weeknight, the short running time of this film should get us all home at a reasonable hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two or Three Things I Know About Her&lt;/b&gt; is a highly eccentric and audaciously complex, but sincere, passionate, and infinitely fascinating exposition on identity, modernization, international politics, and consumerism.  Strictly Film School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Two or Three Things I Know About Her&amp;quot; is one of the most beautiful films of the young Jean-Luc Godard. All of Godard's various roles and grand illusions fuse in this ironic and passionate 1967 work: a largely improvised examination into 24 hours in the life of a young, working-class woman, Juliette Janson (Marina Vlady), married to a garage mechanic (Roger Montsoret), living with him and their son (Christophe Bourseiller) in the suburbs of Paris and working as a hooker to supplement the family income.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &amp;quot;Two or Three Things&amp;quot; scenario is based on a series of articles in the French newsweekly &amp;quot;Le Nouvel Observateur,&amp;quot; pieces that exposed the then-current phenomenon of prostitution among &amp;quot;average&amp;quot; Parisian housewives. Godard treats the material partly as if his film were a TV documentary framing a Cinemascope romantic drama. He shows frequent shots of the reconstruction of the city. He himself narrates the film, musing on politics, philosophy and &amp;quot;Being and Nothingness.&amp;quot; We are always strongly aware that we are watching a film, and that it is Godard's voice that keeps speaking to us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is clear that the director is infatuated with the Russian-French Vlady, as he and his great cinematographer Raoul Coutard bathe her in light. (Godard proposed to Vlady twice during the movie and was turned down). It is clear also that he adores Paris, the &amp;quot;her&amp;quot; of the film's title.  Chicago Tribune&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jean-Luc Godard's &amp;quot;Two or Three Things I Know About Her&amp;quot; was so ahead of its time that a lot of people ? even French New Wave enthusiasts ? are just now catching up to it, nearly 40 years after its release. Godard's got a lot on his mind, mainly outrage at the French government's ongoing construction of a new Paris. The city is actually the &amp;quot;her&amp;quot; from the title, and Godard inserts shot upon shot of a city under chaotic assault, not unlike what Vlady's prostitute is enduring at the hands of her johns. For Godard, this is progress in name only, enriching corporations at the expense of the citizenry. L. A. Daily News&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.cinematicreflections.com/2or3Things.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cinematicr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two things also worth mentioning: This is yet another free screening at the HFA. There is also an ongoing exhibition at the Carpenter Center based upon this film and so I  strongly suggest to get there early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As the credits roll, I'll be standing near the front row with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208041441000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205366099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Godard's 2 or 3 Things I Know About Her at the HFA</name><id>7520946</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1207868400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7520946/</event_url></item>