<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;A Grin Without a Cat&lt;/b&gt; Directed by Chris Marker (La Jetee, Sans Soleil)&lt;br /&gt;France 1977/2001, 35mm, color, 180 min&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note this is a 3 hour documentary on a Sunday night and so our post-movie &amp;quot;discussion&amp;quot; will be brief- maybe we'll go to Grafton Street Pub for a drink afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A work of extraordinary journalism, but it is also a work of deft and subtle poetry.  NY TImes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Marker's remarkable documentary about the rise and fall of the New Left in the 1960s and 1970s was originally released in 1977, but was reworked in 1993 in the wake of the Cold War's end and the collapse of the Soviet Union.  All Movie Guide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a movie about the world at war with itself, and the result is riveting, sublime and unforgettable.  Chicago Tribune&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More impressionistic than analytical, &lt;b&gt;A Grin Without a Cat&lt;/b&gt; is a grand immersion.  Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After a number of years working anonymously with a filmmaking collective dedicated to activist production, Marker reemerged to again make films under his own name. &lt;b&gt;A Grin Without a Cat&lt;/b&gt; was released in its original four-hour long form in 1978, ?reactualized? by Marker years later, and reworked again?given a 1993 coda, in the version presented here.  Described by Marker as &amp;quot;scenes of the Third World War,&amp;quot; this epic film essay surveys the rise and fall of the worldwide revolutionary movement of the 1960s and 70s, encompassing France in May of 1968, U.S. anti?Vietnam War riots, the Czech uprising and its encounter with the Soviet military, and much more.  The resulting experience is what critic J Hoberman has described as a ?grand immersion? into Marker?s distinctive poetic genius, which intermingles all kinds of archival material (including an intriguing analysis of the Odessa steps sequence in Eisenstein?s Potemkin) with willfully eccentric sequences such as the film?s interpolation of footage of an ?impressively pagan Belgian cat festival?full of giant floats, puppets, and masques?into a series of public events marking the end of the left.?  HFA Description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.dailypress.com/topic/mmx-18532_lgcy,0,3827120.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dailypress...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those keeping score at home, &lt;b&gt;A Grin Without a Cat&lt;/b&gt; got a 100% rating on Rotten Tomatoes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Due to the film's length, Tom will be holding a meetup sign at the Harvard Film Archive before the movie starts so that we can sit together as a group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211324978000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209767276000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chris Marker's A Grin Without a Cat</name><id>7860808</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211151600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7860808/</event_url></item>