<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1310 Boylston Street</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.344559</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Citizen Public House &amp; Oyster Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>2160131</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097862</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>55.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Who wants to Pig Out? Well if you do, this is your chance. This meal has also been posted as a &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/50958062/"&gt;Breakfast, Bunch, Lunch and&amp;nbsp;Dinner&lt;/a&gt; group&amp;nbsp;meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citizenpub.com/"&gt;Citizen's Public House&lt;/a&gt; just added a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citizenpub.com/pig-roast/"&gt;Family Style Pig Roast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to their brunch menu. The meal starts with various assorted shellfish, such as: fresh oysters, little neck clams, and cocktail shrimp. Then shortly after, the guest of honor, a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Whole Suckling Pig&lt;/strong&gt;,which has been slowly roasted for&amp;nbsp;14 hours is served&amp;nbsp;with sides such as Brussels Sprouts, Broccoli Gratin, Whipped Yukon Gold Potatoes (sides will vary depending on what&amp;rsquo;s fresh and in season).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone's cost is $38 per person however beverage, tax and tip are NOT included in this price so figure a total cost of about $55.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do NOT need to pay a deposit and are able to include a guest if you have a good RSVP history. However, if you have a poor RSVP history you MUST pay a $38 per person deposit for you and any guest, which is refundable based on Citizen's cancellation policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Citizen's is a ten minute walk from Fenway (green line) or Kenmore station (green line).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There should be plenty of FREE parking at the meters along Boylston Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING VALIDATION AT 1330 BOYLSTON GARAGE .... ENTRANCE ON JERSEY STREET $4 FOR UP TO 3 HOURS ... AFTER 3 HOURS YOU MUST PAY FULL PRICE &lt;br /&gt;

 ------------------------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;

 Below, I have listed the Reservation Rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please understand the NO-SHOW policy was established to ensure everyone who wants to join can and it will be fairly and strictly enforced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I had to provide my credit card for this reservation and will be charged for each cancellation which is less than 72 hours from the reservation.&amp;nbsp;You MUST be certain you can attend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules for Events with Reservations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it is less than 72 hours from the meal and you are not able to attend because of an emergency (and NOT because you have a better offer) or you are running late on the day of the brunch, you MUST call or text me at (617) 445-7549.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All RSVPs are on a first reply, first seated basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the meal is full and you wish to attend, please select WAIT LIST RSVP. When a spot opens, your RSVP will be changed to YES based on the time of your WAIT LIST RSVP and if you answered the RSVP question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the meal and you have not attended nor contacted me, you will be REMOVED and BANNED from Happy Hour.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I change your RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update meal confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;72&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; hours of the reservation, it is counted as a NO-SHOW if you do not contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for this meal you are removed from the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so please, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will arrive at 12:30 PM to welcome you from the Citizen's bar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331490450000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330195842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pig Roast Brunch at Citizen's Bar on Sunday March 11th</name><id>53784512</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331484300000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/53784512/</event_url></item>