<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Lets celebrate the coming arrival of winter by going ice skating! We will skate for an hour or so and then maybe go for a drink nearby.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.bostoncommonfrogpond.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Capture the scent of wood smoke in the air. Hear the sound of metal blades skimming over smooth ice. Close your eyes and your senses return you to 1634, as you skate on the Frog Pond in America's oldest public park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here at the coolest gathering place in Boston you can join local residents and visitors alike as they glide over the carefully manicured, refrigerated surface. In 1997, people were able to skate on this type of surface for the first time in Downtown Boston. The Frog Pond Skating Rink is now open from November to mid-March with at least 100 days of seasonal skating. Whether you're practicing for a 9.9 at the Winter Olympics or simply trying to stand on two feet, the ice at the Frog Pond will always be accommodating.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission $4 per person (adult)&lt;br /&gt;Skate Rental $8 (or bring your own)&lt;br /&gt;Lockers $1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snack Bar&lt;br /&gt;Open daily with a full menu of hot and cold treats. (Hot Chocolate, burgers, fries, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is located in the Boston Common Garage at affordable rates ($10 flat fee evenings and weekends) and is just a short leap from the Frog Pond. The garage entrance is located on Charles Street between the Public Garden and the Boston Common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are located near two T stops. On the Green Line: ?Park Street? and on the Red Line:&lt;br /&gt;?Charles Street.? Both stops are about a five-minute walk to us.&lt;br /&gt;Boston Common Frog Pond Skating Rink&lt;br /&gt;84 Beacon Street, Boston, MA 02108&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 617-635-2120 * Fax: 617-635-2217&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195517131000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1195072004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ice Skating on Boston Common's Frog Pond</name><id>6741598</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195344000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/6741598/</event_url></item>