<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>105 Marcy St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075943</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Players Ring</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>671462</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.751850</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Players&amp;rsquo; Ring&amp;nbsp;continues its 20th season:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;An Evening Of Apocalyptic Theater&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join John Herman and friends as they present "An Evening of Apocalyptic Theatre." There will be drama, comedy, romance, and even music. As a companion to the stage show, audience members gain access to a special web-based apocalyptic short play anthology that will include the plays performed, as well as additional apocalyptic plays by writers from around the country. There will also be an original album of music and a collection of visual art inspired by the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/6/e/event_88381902.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Last year&amp;rsquo;s similar production generated 17 new plays, 8 original songs, and 8 illustrations. The nine-play stage show "An Evening of Steampunk and Robot Theatre" raised $3,000 dollars for charities including A Safe Place, 20/20 VisionQuest, and the Lamprey Arts and Culture Alliance. The production also garnered national attention with coverage in over 100 individual arts and culture blogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get your tickets now! There may not be a tomorrow...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/d/2/4/event_99336132.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rira.com/"&gt;Ri~Ra Irish Pub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; -Meet @ 6pm&lt;/strong&gt; for drinks/dinner.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #8e532f ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;22 Market Square...let me know if you're coming so I can reserve a table.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tickets&lt;/strong&gt;: Only $12 each with the Seacoast Outdoors discount!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrive @ the theater 7:30, show begins @ 8pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/6/f/2/event_99119122.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reserve&lt;/strong&gt; by phone at&amp;nbsp;603/ 436*8123 and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;say you're with &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Seacoast Outdoors Meetup to receive a discount&lt;/span&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Then pay at the door. Or, buy tickets online.&amp;nbsp; These shows do sell out so make sure you reserve!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A couple argues in a bomb shelter over a dog puzzle. A man gets an unexpected visit from Intergalactic Salvage. CERN scientists experience the romance of multi-verses. "An Evening of Apocalyptic Theatre" debuts nine original short plays including new works by Hugo and Nebula award winning science fiction author James Patrick Kelly and best selling author of The Great Typo Hunt, Jeff Deck. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Directors and actors are donating their time in an effort to raise money&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cocheco Valley Humane Society&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jaden's Ladder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;assists survivors of domestic violence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Millspace Project&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which is building a civic center for arts, culture, and history in the renovated Newmarket Mills&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"This is an opportunity to enjoy dynamic theater while also making a difference,"&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;says producer John Herman who received forty-five play submissions&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;after an open call for writers on Facebook, Twitter, and Google+&lt;/span&gt;. Herman will also shave his head&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;halfway through the show's run to raise money for St. Baldrick's Foundation, a volunteer-driven charity that funds more in childhood cancer research grants than any organization except for the U.S. government.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details, including a link to companion music, illustrations, and all forty-five submitted plays, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.JohnHerman.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;www.JohnHerman.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/b/0/event_22902928.jpeg" width="326" height="220" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.playersring.org/"&gt;The Players' Ring Theater&lt;/a&gt; - &amp;nbsp;Since 1992, the mission of The Players' Ring has been to promote the efforts of local artists through the production of original works, while providing an affordable theatre space to local production companies. &amp;ldquo;The Ring&amp;rdquo; as we know and love it, nurtures all artists and provides an environment where artists can thrive, grow, take risks and make daring choices. The Players' Ring is located in a nineteenth century brick building on Marcy Street on the grounds of Prescott Park in Portsmouth, New Hampshire. The historic building is owned by the City of Portsmouth and is fitted out as a &amp;ldquo;black box&amp;rdquo; theatre. With a seating capacity of 75, The Players' Ring annual attendance is approximately 6,500. Since its creation, more than 30 local production companies have presented plays at The Players' Ring. While some form to produce a single special event, some production companies produce shows on an annual basis. Over 200 actors, directors, playwrights and technicians work together to produce plays at The Players' Ring each year. Over the past five years, over $180,000 has been distributed to those involved in Players' Ring productions. Original works account for half of each season&amp;rsquo;s offerings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release -&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Participation in this activity is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors. &amp;nbsp;Always check email &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332083071000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327440728000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening of Apocalyptic Theater @ The Players' Ring</name><id>49468362</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331935200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/49468362/</event_url></item>