<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>First Church</name><city>Northampton</city><id>1410543</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.631051</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Folks,&lt;br /&gt;Constant Contact is giving a local presentation about their product. I saw this event when I was checking out their site for a client. I thought folks might be interested. the cost is $35:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  Wednesday, October 27, 2010, 6 – 8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Where:  First Church&lt;br /&gt;125 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Northampton, MA&lt;br /&gt;Event type:  Presentation&lt;br /&gt;Presenter:  Corissa St. Laurent, Constant Contact&lt;br /&gt;Price: $35&lt;br /&gt;Contact: Ed Quinn at 413-529-0430 or eq@valleycdc.com&lt;br /&gt;Note:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join me for an informative and inspiring session on email marketing. You will learn how to create a successful strategy based on proven marketing techniques, to reach your specific audiences through the use of an easy and cost-effective online tool. In the first session, “The Power of Email Marketing,” you will learn the best practices for email marketing and how to structure campaigns that engage your audience and get them to take action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the second session, “Getting Started with Constant Contact,” you will learn about Constant Contact’s online tool for email marketing through a live demonstration of the product. Learn how to modify and create your own branded email template, how to import your contacts, add a sign-up box to your website and social sites, and everything else you need to know to immediately get started on the path of email marketing!&lt;br /&gt;Link www.valleycdc.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Hoag</member_name><member_id>7353473</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288221464000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nohowebdev</urlname><id>540457</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Northampton Web Developers/ Web Designers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287846279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Power of Email Marketing with Constant Contact</name><id>15202930</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288216800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nohowebdev/events/15202930/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_1616503.jpeg</photo_url></item>