<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>32 Derby Sq. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.521436</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Old Town Hall</name><city>Salem</city><id>1209335</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.894648</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/128048" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; buy tickets here - it may sell out &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bridget Bishop has been cried out upon and accused of witchcraft. The year is 1692 and you are on the jury of her pre-examination trial. Hear actual court testimony, cross-examine the witnesses and decide for yourself whether she should be set free or held for formal trial.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.gordon.edu/images/RightColumn/cryinnocent_2007_03_21_10_23_03.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The arrest of Bridget takes place 10 minutes prior to showtime. Please check in with the box cart on Essex Street (near the Old Town Hall) to receive instructions on where to meet.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gordon.edu/historyalive" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; official website &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;LOCATION&lt;br /&gt;Cry Innocent is performed the Old Town Hall, 32 Derby Square, Salem, Massachusetts. The box office cart is located on the Essex Street side of the building. Salem Pioneer Village is located in Forest River Park, Salem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Praise for Cry Innocent&lt;br /&gt;A must see for everyone, Cry Innocent is the longest continuously-running show north of Boston. Featured on the Discovery Channel, the Travel Channel, A&amp;amp;E, Nickelodeon, TLC, NPR, BBC, CNN, and MTV. Cry Innocent: The People versus Bridget Bishop was commissioned by Norman Jones, professor of theatre and was written by Mark Stevick, professor of English. The 2010 production is directed by Kathleen McGovern and under the artistic direction of Kristina Wacome Stevick.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ADMISSION&lt;br /&gt;$10 adults&lt;br /&gt;$9 seniors (65 and older) and students (13 and older with ID)&lt;br /&gt;$8 children 6-12&lt;br /&gt;FREE for children under 6&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People can stick around after for the Zombie Mayhem at 3pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be eating lunch beforehand at the &lt;a href="http://www.gulu-gulu.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Gulu Gulu Cafe&lt;/a&gt;. I will get there at 11:30. Post in your RSVP if you'll be meeting for lunch too.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have my red meetup shirt on, will be near the "box office" cart before the show, and at Gulu Gulu Cafe for lunch at 11:30</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286744859000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286470423000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cry Innocent Play in Salem</name><id>15035207</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286730000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15035207/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/c/global_6131516.jpeg</photo_url></item>