<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This hike has been on the calendar for weeks but someone deleted it.  This is a re-post.  I'm afraid I don't remember everyone that signed up originally, but at this point just show up like you were going to.  It doesn't matter if you RSVP.  in fact I'm really annoyed this was deleted, &amp;quot;accidentally&amp;quot;.  I'm asking Diane who is responsible...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Official Winter Season 4000 footer hike!  &lt;br /&gt;Please rsvp if you would like to join me on a 14.2 mi hike in full winter gear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please DO NOT rsvp if you have no previous winter hiking experience.  You must have your own snowshoes, microspikes, headlamp and other appropriate winter gear.  I also ask that you be in great physical shape and have been consistently hiking 4000 footers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sawyer River Road IS CLOSED.  This means this hike will be 14.2 miles, where 4.2 miles is an out-and-back ROAD WALK. It is an easy road walk and worth the extra distance. Carrigain is a beautiful hike with 360 views from the ridge and the summit, but it is also exposed to some degree.  Wind proof clothing is recommended.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A near-full moon will coincide with the winter solstice/abbreviated daylight, but I will also recommend you bring your own headlamp.  Depending on the speed of the group we may need to use them on the way out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm posting this for Wed &amp;amp; Thurs.  This hike will be weather dependent, so I'll plan the hike for the first nice day.  Feel free to rsvp for either day.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must assume all responsibility for your own safety; this is a social hike and I am NOT trained in wilderness safety.  &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I repeat: You must assume all responsibility for your own safety; this is a social hike and I am NOT trained in wilderness safety.  &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293151930000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1292258672000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Carrigain FULL WINTER HIKE--repost after deletion</name><id>15720719</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293024600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/15720719/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/e/0/global_19641552.jpeg</photo_url></item>