<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/b/3/event_47016531.jpeg" width="616" height="72" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; This sounds like a lot of fun.&amp;nbsp; I will be at the theater by 7, in the lobby wearing a meetup pin.&amp;nbsp; We will head in for seats at 7:30.&amp;nbsp; Because it is a weeknight and will get out late, I am not planning an after event...sorry but it will be late for a school night.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I strongly recommend buying your tickets in advance.&amp;nbsp; You can buy them on Fandango.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Come and see the Mystery Science Theater Crew in Actions and add some snark of your own to the proceedings.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I will be taking the T to the theater, but there is a parking garage right across the street from the theater. Details: The stars of 
&lt;em&gt;Mystery Science Theater 30&lt;/em&gt;00 are coming to movie theaters nationwide to take on the cheesy 1962 fantasy epic&amp;nbsp;
&lt;em&gt;Jack the Giant Killer&lt;/em&gt;. Michael J. Nelson, Kevin Murphy and Bill Corbett of RiffTrax invite you to join them on Wednesday, August 17th for hilarious riffing on a not-so-classic movie bursting with Vikings, giant rubber monsters and a leprechaun in a jar! This one night event will be your only chance to see the guys fire their wisecracking commentary at&amp;nbsp;
&lt;em&gt;Jack the Giant Killer&lt;/em&gt; on the big screen.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;The event will be broadcast live to movie theaters nationwide on Wednesday, August 17 at 8:00pm ET / 7:00pm CT / 6:00pm MT / and 8:00pm PT (tape delay). Audiences will be treated to a brand new short from the guys, as well as two original animated shorts from Rich &amp;ldquo;Lowtax&amp;rdquo; Kyanka of Something Awful.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Movie theater audiences will receive FREE digital goodies after the event including a downloadable short, avatars and a digital photo of the guys. A URL will be revealed on-screen at which you can receive your free digital goodies after the live event.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin and be in the lobby by 7.    Showtime is 8PM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314032371000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312914196000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>RiffTrax LIVE: Jack the Giant Killer</name><id>28856181</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313622000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/28856181/</event_url></item>