<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Drop by &lt;b&gt;the Living Room&lt;/b&gt; to meet cool, like-minded people, unwind after work, and/or sample some cocktails at this trendy waterfront destination!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Bonus if you can arrive at 5:30 to help us stake out space!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us if you want to &lt;i&gt;cross-promote your events and campaigns&lt;/i&gt; while enjoying great cocktails, are &lt;i&gt;new to the area&lt;/i&gt; and looking for groups to get involved in, or you've been looking for &lt;i&gt;like-minded progressives&lt;/i&gt; to hang with in Boston. Newcomers always welcomed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't drink? That's fine. Plenty of folks don't. The emphasis here is less on the cocktails and more on the socializing. And even more so on the justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;No Program. No Speaker. Just us.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hey organizers!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word &lt;b&gt;bring flyers for the free lit table&lt;/b&gt; - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to get there:&lt;/b&gt; Find the Living Room at 101 Atlantic Ave, Boston. From Haymarket Station, turn right down Surface Road. After four blocks turn left on to Atlantic Ave. The Living Room is located at the intersection of Atlantic Ave and Richmond Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Socializing for Justice - www.sojust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 2006, we've been building this great sandbox where we can bring progressives of all stripes together and try out new ideas in this &amp;quot;Movement Moment&amp;quot;. Spaces like this are crucial as we start to reframe and build new visions for our movement(s).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With almost 1500 members and 4+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find the great people, organizations and community you're looking for while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615" target="_blank"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/photos/" target="_blank"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison Brill</member_name><member_id>4034719</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291681139000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288469160000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cocktails for Justice</name><id>15280893</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289948400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/15280893/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/5/f/global_18037119.jpeg</photo_url></item>