<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We are going to hike a section of the Tunxis Trail that will include Tory Den and the Mile of Ledges.  This section is in Bristol and Burlington and will begin near Old Marsh Pond on Marsh Road.  I am planning a 6 mile loop through this section.  This hike will not have my usual &amp;quot;ups&amp;quot;.  The elevation gain is only 300 ft but it is rocky terrain.  Plan on much rock climbing.  This is NOT a &amp;quot;I layed on the couch all winter and think hiking sounds easy&amp;quot; event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should take no more than four hours.  I am planning to park on Marsh Rd near Old Marsh Pond.  We will hike in on the Tunxis Mainline Blue Trail.  We will then go left onto the yellow dot trail to explore Tory Den.  We will hang a right onto Greer Rd then back onto the blue trail onto the Mile of Ledges and back the way we came.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a rugged and interesting section of our state's blue blaze trail.  It offers picturesque rock ledges, a few climbing tight squeezes, and the historic Tory Den.  During the Revolutionary War, Tories or British sympathizers,used the den as a hinding place.  The Leatherman also used this as a resting place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are getting into warmer weather so include with you plenty of water, snacks, layers of non-cotton clothing, bug spray, and sunscreen.  Water proof hiking boots are a must.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The address is really close but the trial head is closer to East Plymouth Road on the tight corner.  Parking is on the shoulder of the road across the street from the pond.  This parking is very limited.  That is why attendance is limited.  Folks may need to park across the bridge and hike back to the trail head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Bristol&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=500+Marsh+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06010-2284&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.699701&amp;amp;longitude=-72.992616&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>6</waitlist_count><updated>1270476649000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268788890000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking Mile of Ledges and Tory's Den, Burlington, CT</name><id>12896731</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270303200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/12896731/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>