<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>39 Powisset Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02030</zip><lat>42.225706</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.785.0339</phone><name>Powisset Farm</name><city>Dover</city><id>1268374</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.260249</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Trustees of Reservations will hold its May Hike of the Month on May 23rd from 1pm to 3pm at Powisset Farm on Powisset St in Dover .  Join a ranger from the Trustees and walk through the open fields.  Learn about our Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) program, our efforts to attract a native bee population, and look for wild turkeys and white-tailed deer in the meadows.  After the hike feel free to visit the chickens and pigs or venture across the street to Noanet Woodlands for a longer hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Powisset Farm: 109 acres  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This farm has been revived as a Community Supported Agriculture project, with a loop trail exploring the surrounding woodlands, fields, and wetlands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Powisset Farm a special place?&lt;br /&gt;We think it’s the restored farming operation, a Community Supported Agriculture (CSA) program, on a landscape with a history of pastures and planted fields dating back three centuries. Take a leisurely walk through the farmstead – complete with chickens and pigs – then follow an easy, one-mile loop trail past woodlands and wetlands through the far reaches of the 108.5-acre property.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are always welcome to stroll down the farm lane, say hello to the pigs, and admire the rows of vegetables and herbs. Beyond the cultivated land, Powisset Farm features an upland oak forest, a pair of brooks, vernal pools, and wooded wetlands. You’ll enjoy broad views across furrowed croplands and thick hayfields; the latter attracting white-tailed deer, wild turkey, and grassland-nesting bobolinks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mowed trails through the hay fields link to adjacent Hale Reservation, and Noanet Woodlands lie across the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails&lt;br /&gt;An easy loop trail, less than a mile long extends beyond the farmstead past woodlands and wetlands before returning to the barnyard. A trail spurs lead into adjacent 1,200-acre Hale Reservation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When to Visit&lt;br /&gt;Trails: Year-round, daily, sunrise to sunset. Allow a minimum of 1 hour. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;39 Powisset Street&lt;br /&gt;Dover, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95/Rt. 128: take Exit 16B (109 West). Follow for less than 1 mile and take a right on Dover Rd. Follow for 2.5 miles. Take left into farm immediately after big gray barn. Farm office is on ground floor, underneath barn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Medfield Center: Take Rt. 109 east, take left onto Hartford St. Follow for 1.5 mi. and take left onto Walpole St. Follow for 0.75 mi. and take right onto Powisset St. After 0.25 mi., take right immediately before big gray barn. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274638806000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1273507862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Powisset Farm walk</name><id>13437728</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274634000000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/13437728/</event_url></item>