<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We've taken Ron Paul from nowhere in the polls to 8%. We can get him up above McCain and Giuliani for sure, but it's going to take a lot of work on our part. Come join this effort to help Dr Paul win NH. Our founding fathers risked their lives and fortunes for freedom. All we need to do is knock on doors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're going to make a big push to canvas on Dec 1st. We will be getting folks in from around the country to help out, and throw a big rally in the evening, hopefully with Ron Paul there to say thank you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For out of state folks. If you have a large meetup, please take RSVPs from your meetup, then have your meetup lead RSVP here with a total count. For folks out of state needing a place to stay, please register at Operation Live Free or Die. This organization is supported by the grassroots in NH.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unless you get packets independently, please meet at campaign HQ at 10am to get packets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a chance to meet Dr. Paul :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE: Instead of meeting in Concord (which is really far for us), there will be a meeting in Nashua at the welcome center or in Manchester at Murphy's Taproom (the New York crew will be in Manchester too, and they need more drivers). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Nashua welcome center is at 90 Broad Street in Nashua and Murphy's Taproom is at 494 Elm St, Manchester.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joe Ureneck</member_name><member_id>4211251</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196694320000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196449471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HUGE Canvassing Event!</name><id>6831545</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196521200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/6831545/</event_url></item>