<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Gordon Willis, the Man Who Shot The Godfather&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: sienna"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revered as one of the most artistically inventive and skilled cinematographers of the 1970s and 1980s, Gordon Willis (b. 1931) defined the pervasive anxiety and implacable darkness of the New American Cinema through his now famous collaborations with Francis Ford Coppola, Alan Pakula, Woody Allen and Hal Ashby. Despite the scandalous neglect of the Academy in overlooking Willis, (corrected just before we went to press with the announcement of a much deserved Honorary Oscar to be awarded this November) he has been recognized as one of the postwar American cinema’s great masters by the next generation of cinematographers who learned from his example and especially by those artists, such as Michael Chapman (Raging Bull)and John Bailey (Mishima), who were directly shaped by their experience as his assistant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manhattan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directed by Woody Allen.&lt;br /&gt;With Woody Allen, Diane Keaton, Michael Murphy&lt;br /&gt;US 1979, 35mm, b/w, 96 min.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shot in black and white anamorphic wide-screen, Willis’ lushly radiant cinematography transforms 1979 New York into a dreamlike fantasy city, albeit one filled with neurotic, terminally unsatisfied characters playing endless rounds of romantic roundelay. Woody Allen’s bittersweet valentine to his island hometown presents a deliriously romantic vision of the city tempered by an underlying sense of loss and pessimism about the ultimate futility of human relationships, a duality beautifully underscored by Willis’ brilliant camerawork, most famously in Manhattan’s iconic shot of Allen and Diane Keaton dwarfed by the vast architecture of the 59th Street Bridge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meetup at the &lt;span style="color: darkblue"&gt;Grafton Street Pub&lt;/span&gt; &lt;i&gt;as early as&lt;/i&gt; 5:30 in order to enjoy cocktails/appetizers/dinner before going to the film and Q &amp;amp; A with Gordon Willis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will reserve prepaid discount tickets with the Harvard Film Archive.  In order to attend, you will need to prepay ($10 via paypal, snail mail, or personal reconnaissance) and send me your first and last name.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be at the Grafton Street Pub at 5:30 sipping a Big Apple Martini and using a pathetic Meetup Sign as a doily.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255888653000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manhattan - Special Event</name><id>11654231</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258761600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11654231/</event_url></item>