<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;July 4th morning weather update...The weather man (I swear, he's schizo!) has changed his mind and is predicting some rain around noon, but says it should be cleared up by early afternoon - 1:30 ish. So you might want to time your arrival a little later. &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;I've sent out the directions so many times it's starting to annoy people.  If you still need directions, email me directly and I'll send directions back to you individually.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: green"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note About Food:&lt;/b&gt;  My refrigerator is tiny (as is everything else in my house!).  I have three large coleman coolers for food storage and two washtubs for beer and other beverages.  If you are bringing food that needs refrigeration, and you have your own cooler, it would help.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;I have about 20 lawn chairs and limited table space  -- look at the RSVP's and do the math!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;Yes, some people are bringing fireworks. Hooray! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;I was really hoping someone would mention spiking a watermelon. If anyone still wants to, rum works best &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/tongue.gif' border='0' alt='tongue' /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I live in an adorable, tiny cottage about eight feet from Crystal Lake in Ellington, Connecticut.  This was my childhood summer home, and some of my happiest memories are from the annual the &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Fourth of July Picnic&lt;/span&gt;, when everyone came by to swim, sail, kayak, canoe, water ski, drink, watch fireworks and, especially, EAT!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My yard is small, but the lake is glorious, and the next-door neighbors have agreed we can spill over onto their property.  I will have a couple of gas barbecue grills set up and ready to go.  There are kayaks and paddles available to use and maybe a small sailboat (I have to make sure all the rigging is in good repair). I might even get the hole in the canoe patched by then?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will provide cups, plates, napkins, utensils and ice.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring something to eat and something to drink.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional things that you might like to bring:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Folding chairs or other lawn furniture.  &lt;br /&gt;- Beach blankets, towels, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;- Pool floats, rafts, inner tubes, etc.  &lt;br /&gt;- Ice chest.  &lt;br /&gt;- LEGAL fireworks.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;I live very close to the public boat launch and, if someone has a larger boat they want to bring, I can sink a temporary buoy in front of my dock and you can tie it up.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND I promised try to remember the rules of the semi-legendary GREASED WATERMELON RACE. It involved Crisco, inner tubes, and tequila shots, I think.&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The town of Ellington (and quite a few lakeside dwellers) always shoot off fireworks over the water as soon as soon as it gets dark.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;NOTE:  This is an adults-only event&lt;/span&gt; because, between the presence of alcohol and water-safety issues, it really isn't a kid-friendly atmosphere.  Also, skinny dipping has been known to occur?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE!&lt;/b&gt;  I just checked Accuweather and the Fourth of July is supposed to be PERFECT!  I'm really looking forward to seeing all of you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just holler.  Someone will point.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Toni</member_name><member_id>4890008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216556674000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>17</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213297679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grownups' Fourth of July Barbecue at Toni's</name><id>8130868</id><headcount>49</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215187200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8130868/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/9/global_4437721.jpeg</photo_url></item>