<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>515 Thames Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02840</zip><lat>41.479485</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 619-2505</phone><name>The Sambar</name><city>Newport</city><id>877857</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.314245</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for a new adventure - great conversation with new/old friends, food, drinks, and TRIVIA at the Sambar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is laid back Trivia - if you know one answer - great - if not support those that do...we have had some very interesting topics..and it is always a fun night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our members love Trivia and we have been working with local restaurants to sponsor an early Trivia for Fall/Winter. We worked a schedule out with Sambar - a cozy restaurant in Newport with great food and drinks...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday night is a great night for fun out in Newport and it won't interfere with Monday night football &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please sign up&lt;/b&gt; and/or send me a message if you are interested in Thursday Night Trivia. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I arrive between 8- 8:15PM and we have been pretty good about an 8:30PM start time. &lt;br /&gt;It normally lasts between 1 1/2 - 2 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sambar has been working on an advertising campaign to bring this night to life as well as offering great prizes for every round  !!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking - Until beginning of November you have to follow what the signs say for parking in Newport. The last event our members found easy parking in the Ocean Breeze Cafe lot - less than two blocks after Sambar on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Lonnie or ask for Newport Friends Meetup Group and if you cannot find us - please call: 829-8516</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lonnie</member_name><member_id>6911660</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287116450000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newportfriends</urlname><id>429443</id><group_lat>41.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3099975586</group_lon><name>Newport Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286546981000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Early Trivia - Sambar - Always an Adventure - fun night!</name><id>15045028</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287101700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newportfriends/events/15045028/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/b/f/global_17999311.jpeg</photo_url></item>