<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DECEMBER'S EVENT HAD A LARGE NUMBER OF NO SHOWS.&amp;nbsp; MANY FOLKS WERE ON THE WAIT LIST AND YOUR LACK OF CONSIDERATION DID NOT ALLOW MORE TO ATTEND.&amp;nbsp; IF YOU WERE A NO SHOW, YOU WILL BE PUT ON THE WAIT LIST AND INFORMED THE DAY OF IF THERE IS ROOM TO ADD YOU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has been a&amp;nbsp;favorite&amp;nbsp;of the hiking group&amp;nbsp;for the last couple of years.&amp;nbsp; We get together at my condo club house and enjoy an evening of games and great food brought by all of you.&amp;nbsp;This&amp;nbsp;is a fun way&amp;nbsp;to&amp;nbsp;break up the long nights and to socialize with other hikers.&amp;nbsp;This event will be held at Janice's condo complex clubhouse&amp;nbsp;in South Windsor. We'll have a large fireplace with fire, music, tables &amp;amp; chairs, bathrooms, and full kitchen available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Games:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the games we have already: * Pictionary * Picture Picture * Worst Case Scenario * Trivial Pursuit * Scrabble * Fact or Crap * Jenga (well a knockoff version) We'd like to see someone bring these as well as anything else: * Bolderdash * Cranium * Cards (for various card games) Bring any other game you might think 4 - 6 people at least could play at the same time. Team games would be great too. Note this is an indoor game night. We are not doing horseshoes or lawn darts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplied already: * Paper and&amp;nbsp;serving items.&amp;nbsp;Please plan to bring to share any of: * Finger food * Snacks * Small entree (plan to feed 8 people!) * Drinks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hall Rental Donation, We would appreciate donations of&amp;nbsp;$5 each person to help offset the cost of the hall rental. Donations&amp;nbsp;will be made at the event so be prepared with cold hard cash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The address will be sent to those who respond "Yes"&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;day before the event.&amp;nbsp;Party directions and information will be sent out the day before to those attending.&amp;nbsp;There is always movement those last couple of days with RSVPs so make a decision early. Limitation on RSVP's is due to parking limitations. We all hope you can attend and enjoy a warm evening with great people. Last year this was a hit with over 60 people going each time and people brought great food and drinks to share!&amp;nbsp;If you RSVP "yes" and later can't go, please remember to change your RSVP so someone else can go!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is also a celebration for my birthday and so many great folks have been thoughtful enough to give me lovely gifts.&amp;nbsp; If you are in that frame of mind (sorry if I sound tacky......) a REI gift card would be lovely.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are a pair of hiking boots that I am saving my pennies for................&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also Snow Rebels will be on&amp;nbsp;sale again.&amp;nbsp; These fleece lined scarves are fierce face protection for&amp;nbsp;many winter&amp;nbsp;activiites.&amp;nbsp; It something I am creating.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be sent out the day before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>4</waitlist_count><updated>1326230903000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>54</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322977146000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game Night and Janice's Birthday event</name><id>43309542</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325977200000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/43309542/</event_url></item>