<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Lansdowne Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.247.1222</phone><name>The Lansdowne Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>1088408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094957</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>sliding to $10 @ the door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;SPECIAL UPDATE: Thankfully, Boston was spared the worst of the damage caused by Hurricane Sandy. All donations collected at our &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/events/88924452/"&gt;Election Night Viewing Party&lt;/a&gt; will be donated to &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/events/89854492/"&gt;Occupy Sandy relief efforts&lt;/a&gt;. If you're not able to join us, please donate &lt;a href="https://www.wepay.com/donations/occupy-sandy-cleanup-volunteers"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+_+&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join Socializing for Justice, and our co-host New Leaders Council - Boston, at The Landsdowne on November 6th at 8PM to de-brief, de-compress and de-stress as we watch the results come in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You &lt;a href="http://www.sojustvote.com"&gt;SoJust Voted&lt;/a&gt;, you made phone calls, you knocked on doors, you donated, and now that election season is coming to a close, you SoJust need to relax. Whether we’re tearing our hair out or celebrating, it’s safe to say we could use a drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But please remember to vote first!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Find your polling place at &lt;a href="http://www.wheredoivotema.com"&gt;www.wheredoivotema.com&lt;/a&gt; and see who progressive organizations have endorsed at &lt;a href="http://www.SoJustVote.com"&gt;www.SoJustVote.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Lansdowne, 9 Lansdowne Street, Boston &lt;br /&gt;

 Venue is physically accessible, must be 21+ &lt;br /&gt;

 Complimentary appetizers - cash bar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; $5-$10 collected at the door. Free Admission with an “I Voted!” sticker. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;(All donations will be given to Occupy Sandy to support recovery efforts in NYC.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Take the Green line to Kenmore Square, bear left onto Brookline Avenue and take the second left onto Lansdowne Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we'll help you meet people - so no worries if you're new to SoJust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston? Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust is not a non-profit 501(c)(3). We're a grassroots volunteer-run member-supported cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have 2100+ members, hosted 130+ events and manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network, please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/donate"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/strong&gt; Members are all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. Some just moved to Boston and others were born here. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to know more about SoJust? Check out our &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352497392000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351449179000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Election Night Viewing Party with SoJust &amp; NLC Boston</name><id>88924452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352250000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/88924452/</event_url></item>