<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Come and join me for Creative Mediterranean-tinged fare and a popular weekend brunch, served in the heart of the South End. After brunch we can walk around and checkout some of the cool shops in the neighborhood and Union Park one of the most beautiful Streets in all of the South End.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metropolis Cafe&lt;br /&gt;www.metropolisboston.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;584 Tremont St&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02118&lt;br /&gt;(617) 247-2931&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Metropolis Cafe is an intimate dining spot that offers a cozy atmosphere with a unique menu of Mediterranean and French cuisine, plus a varied wine list and a great selection of beer. This eclectic menu features, steak, seafood, and chicken dishes that will leave all guests feeling amazed. Metropolis Cafe is located in trendy South End at corner of Tremont Street and Union Park. Weekend Brunch may fill this boutique cafe up quickly, but it's well worth the wait while you people watch on Tremont Street. If you want to restaurant to make you feel like you are at home with authentic Mediteranean and French dishes then this Boston gem is the place for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scene&lt;br /&gt;Seth Woods is behind this trendy South End restaurant and is considered a neighborhood favorite, especially during its acclaimed weekend brunch service. Befitting a relaxed bistro in one of the city's most vibrant areas, the Metropolis attracts a suitably diverse crowd. Pleasant, casual waiters traverse the cramped quarters with ease. Window tables provide colorful glimpses of bustling Tremont St. A small but well-chosen wine list--no liquor is served--keeps oenophiles content.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Food&lt;br /&gt;Best described as upscale comfort fare, served with aplomb, the Metropolis's menu includes clever twists on familiar favorites. A filet of wild salmon is encrusted with horseradish, while the expected tartare starter eschews tuna or steak in favor of farm-fresh asparagus. Desserts like rich chocolate pudding cake and sinful banana-caramel bread pudding provide a worthy finish. Brunch highlights include fresh huevos rancheros and the &amp;quot;South End ommelette&amp;quot; (sausage, mushrooms, and brie).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you at the Metropolis Cafe!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Need to RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243912921000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236311539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brunch at  the trendy Metropolis Cafe</name><id>9893485</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243706400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9893485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/1/0/global_7613392.jpeg</photo_url></item>