<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb Pearce continues to teach us about the amazing Enneagram of Personality. This week the focus will be on our career and life passion.  Here is a description of the workshop from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Not only is the Enneagram a great tool for personal growth and relationship dynamics, it's also a great tool to explore your work and career passions. What work environments fits your type and which don't. What careers are best suited for your type?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a sliding scale from $20-40 but for Unique People it is $15-40. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00 it helps the presenter and those who might pay less. No one is turned away because of money, so pay what you can honestly afford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcome to bring vegetarian appetizers and drinks, including wine.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** About Herb Pearce **&lt;br /&gt;Herb Pearce is an Arlington-based, individual, couples and family therapist, with over 30 years experience. A leading expert in the Enneagram, he has led over 2,000 Enneagram experiences in the last 18 years with talks, public workshops, counseling, and teambuilding trainings in corporations and organizations. Herb's trainings, talks and workshops provide a wealth of understanding and clarity and his presentation style is direct, but gentle and humorous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.herbpearce.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254525544000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250050453000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Using the Enneagram to Help Find Your Career and Life Passion</name><id>11092549</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253314800000</time><rsvp_limit>34</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/11092549/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/8/global_7203288.jpeg</photo_url></item>