<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Tremont Street</address_2><address_1>Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02132</zip><lat>42.283146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Common, Parkman bandstand</name><city>West Roxbury</city><id>905669</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.152390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come get your fill of thees and thous, jests and jibes in this comic tale of mistaken identities by that master of wit, William Shakespeare. Commonwealth Shakespeare Company is presenting “The Comedy of Errors,” with a professional cast &amp;amp; direction by Steven Maler. Bring a beach blanket and/or low-to-the-ground lawn chair, a box dinner/beverage if you want, and insect repellent. The performance takes place at the Parkman Bandstand on the Boston Common. Jeanne tells us that the performances are consistently outstanding, every year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a synopsis of the play and photos, visit &lt;a href="http://www.commshakes.org/shows/current_show/shows_current.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.commshakes...&lt;/a&gt;. There’s even a cool study guide! &lt;a href="http://sites.google.com/site/comedyoferrorsstudyguide/" target="_blank"&gt;http://sites.google.c...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeanne will plan to get to the Common extra-early, to park one or two blankets in a prime location, so we can sit together. Please call her that morning to give her an idea of numbers so she can decide whether the blankets should be twin or king-sized. &lt;b&gt;Look for her in the area immediately in front of the stage.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking the T is advisable. Take any train on the Green Line to the Arlington Street stop, or, if coming via the Red Line, get off at Park Street Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you drive, there is some parking in the Common Garage on Charles Street, but it may fill up. Take Soldiers Field Road to the Back Bay area, turn onto Arlington Street, then left onto Boylston Street. At the first light, turn left onto Charles Street for the underground parking garage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Parkman Bandstand&lt;/b&gt; is where the play takes place.  (If you look at a map of the Common it looks lilke a wagon wheel.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the weather is cloudy and rain is expected, call Jeanne on her cell phone. She will track information at the Parkman Bandstand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two performances are scheduled for August 9, so if the 1 p.m. performance were a wash-out, you would still have the option of attending the 7 p.m. show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The play is the thing!”&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you RSVP, we'll send you Jeanne's cell phone number.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marie A</member_name><member_id>4623326</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne Smith</member_name><member_id>8341850</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250030497000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Beanstalks and their Friends</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>tall-15</urlname><id>410040</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Beanstalks Tall Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249358825000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shakespeare  on The Common</name><id>11029746</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249837200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/tall-15/events/11029746/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/b/global_3153499.jpeg</photo_url></item>