<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 11</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.493217</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mt. Major</name><city>Alton</city><id>3041421</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.255547</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's try something a little bit different -- a late-day hike to the summit of Mount Major in Alton, NH.&amp;nbsp; The views of Lake Winnipesaukee and the surrounding area are breathtaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll be hiking via the Boulder Loop Trail which is about 1.6 miles.&amp;nbsp; The hike to the summit should take us 1&amp;nbsp;1/12 hours or so.&amp;nbsp; We'll stop for a snack at the top--be sure to bring water and some goodies!&amp;nbsp; We can decide then which trail to take back to the parking lot.&amp;nbsp; Bring a jacket/fleece even if it's a warm day--it could be cooler and breezy&amp;nbsp;on the open and rocky top of the mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be sure to wear good hiking shoes/boots as we will be hiking on gravel, boulders, and across some ledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It could be getting dusky as we hike down, so it's probably a good idea to bring a flashlight or a headlamp.&amp;nbsp; And don't forget your camera ! ! !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a combined event--we will also&amp;nbsp;be joined by members of Social Fun and Trailblazers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span style="color : #ad364c ; font-size : medium"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;If there is interest, we'll be stopping for dinner after the hike--Shibley's at the Pier sounds good, Pops Clam Shack is also a possibility.&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking lot and trailheads for Mount Major are located in Alton, New Hampshire on Route 11, 4.2 miles north of Alton Bay.&amp;nbsp; Heading north, the parking lot turn-off is located shortly after a scenic vista and is on the left-hand side of the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A little bit about Mount Major:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; Mount Major is a mountain loacated in Alton, New Hampshire, south of Lake Winnepesaukee and northeast of Straightback Mountain of the Belknap Rnage.&amp;nbsp; The scenic, rocky summit is a popular hiking destination, accessible by multiple trails including the Maount Major Trail, the Brook Trail, and the Boulder Loop.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1313876326000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313623631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Major--a late day hike</name><id>29906471</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313872200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/29906471/</event_url></item>