<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 South Meadow Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02330</zip><lat>41.893677</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Carver High School Auditorium</name><city>Carver</city><id>1408046</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.754706</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Friends,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This meeting is very important to MSSF and everyone who loves the forest. Please try to come.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DCR staff will share information about the resource management planning process, and hear your concerns and ideas about recreation, stewardship of resources and park facilities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information on the planning process, including an outline of topics to be covered in the plan, is available on DCR’s website &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmp.htm&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have questions about the public forum, please contact Jim Baecker at (617) 626-1335 or jim.baecker@state.ma.us&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;More&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Press Release:&lt;br /&gt;The Department of Conservation and Recreation (DCR) will hold a public meeting on October 28 to discuss development of a Resource Management Plan for Myles Standish State Forest in Plymouth and Carver. The plan will guide future preservation and stewardship efforts in the state forest, and will ensure consistency between recreational uses and protection of natural resources.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As a first step in the process, DCR has scheduled the public meeting for Thursday, October 28, 2010, from 7 p.m. to 8:30 p.m., in the Carver High School Auditorium, 60 South Meadow Road, Carver.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Myles Standish State Forest is a beautiful park, offering innumerable recreational opportunities,” said DCR Commissioner Richard K. Sullivan Jr. “With 16 ponds, five camping areas, plus hiking, cycling, and horseback-riding trails, it is the largest publicly owned recreation area in southeastern Massachusetts. Our goal at DCR is to protect the natural and cultural resources of the forest, and develop plans to manage it in the years to come. We welcome public input as we move forward with the Resource Management Plan.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Under the Patrick-Murray Administration, DCR has begun developing Resource Management Plans (RMPs) for all agency properties. DCR has evaluated individual parks and prioritized them based on their natural and cultural resources, management issues, and uses of the facilities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the October 28 public meeting, DCR staff members will share information about the  resource management planning process, and members of the public will be invited to talk about various aspects of the state forest, including how they use it, what aspects of it are important to them, and what they feel should be protected and how. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The presentation will be available on DCR’s website after the public meeting: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmppast.htm" target="_blank"&gt;www.mass.gov/dcr/news/publicmeetings/rmppast.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sharl</member_name><member_id>712534</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288311475000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287597259000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Very Important: Public Forum on Preparation of MSSF Resource Management Plan </name><id>15172754</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288306800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/15172754/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/e/global_13266574.jpeg</photo_url></item>