<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Anyone interested in showing up to this book signing? I would like to try to interview the author. Want to help? Contact me in advance to confirm your interest. Check out my youtube account here: youtube.com/wearechangeboston&lt;br /&gt;wearechangeboston@gmail.com&lt;br /&gt;here is the original link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2447" target="_blank"&gt;http://harvard.com/ev...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, January 20th&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;CHARLOTTE DENNETT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;argues&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The People v. Bush:&lt;br /&gt;One Lawyer's Campaign to Bring the President to Justice and the National Grassroots Movement She Encountered Along the Way&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is glad to welcome journalist-turned-lawyer CHARLOTTE DENNETT for a discussion of her new book, The People v. Bush: One Lawyer's Campaign to Bring the President to Justice and the National Grassroots Movement She Encountered Along the Way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Charlotte Dennett became outraged that Bush White House officials were acting above the law, she did something that surprised even herself. She ran for a state attorney general seat on a platform to prosecute George W. Bush for murder. She lost the race, but found a movement—one that continues its quest to hold leaders accountable to U.S. law and preserve a Constitutional presidency.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In The People v. Bush, Dennett recounts her seminal effort to prosecute the former president, introduces readers to a world where the actions of a few can indeed empower the many, and reports on the current state of the movement to hold Bush accountable for high crimes and misdemeanors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dennett’s wild ride through politics began when she read The Prosecution of George W. Bush for Murder by lawyer Vincent Bugliosi (best known for his prosecution of Charles Manson). In it, Bugliosi stated that one path to prosecuting George W. Bush could be taken by a state attorney general—should one take up the cause. Soon after, Dennett launched her attorney-general race in Vermont—a state known as much for its progressive edge as its pioneering spirit—signed up Bugliosi as her special prosecutor in the event that she won, and together the two made headlines across Vermont and the nation for changing the face of American grassroots democracy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dennett’s book also explores the political triumphs of other Vermonters such as Kurt Daims, who imagined, with two human rights lawyers, Bush’s arrest should he enter the town of Brattleboro; Dan DeWalt, who launched a call for impeachment in thirty-six towns; and Vermont Senator Patrick Leahy, who received wide support—but also criticism—for his 9/11 Truth Commission. With these stories and her own, Dennett shows that it’s not just possible but necessary to hold higher-ups responsible for heinous acts—not out of revenge, but to preserve justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CONTACT:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Info:&lt;br /&gt;617.661.1515&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media:&lt;br /&gt;617.661.1424 ex.1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email:&lt;br /&gt;rbcass@harvard.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Event Information&lt;br /&gt;DATE:  Wednesday, January 20th&lt;br /&gt;TIME:  7:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION:  Harvard Book Store&lt;br /&gt;1256 Massachusetts Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;TICKETS:  This event is free; no tickets are required&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlotte Dennett is an author and attorney who has been practicing law since 1997, with an emphasis on personal injury litigation and suing the government under the Freedom of Information Act. She's also been a reporter in the Middle East and is the coauthor with her husband, Gerard Colby, of Thy Will Be Done-The Conquest of the Amazon: Nelson Rockefeller and Evangelism in the Age of Oil. She and her husband live in Cambridge, Vermont.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photo courtesy of the author&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264205455000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261342502000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1/20 7pm CHARLOTTE DENNETT The People v. Bush One Lawyer's Campaign to Bring th</name><id>12121461</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264032000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/12121461/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>