<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's meet for a Saturday Morning Fall Foliage Walk @ Pond Meadow Park (PMP)! This is one of our favorite walking locations. We will be meeting and walking from the Braintree side of PMP.  One of the great things about walking at PMP is there are some shady areas along with some nice breezes once in awhile.  Let's meetup and get to know each other while walking around the pond! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We'll walk 2-3 loops today, possibly adding in the Weymouth entrance stretch.  2 laps plus that stretch will net us 3.9 miles in about 1 hr and 15-20 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Pond Meadow Park consists of a paved loop as well as paved walkways to and from both sets of parking lots.  This path is hilly with some flat terrain.  If you choose to head out into the woods the trails are marked but not paved.  The loop is 1.6 miles, with the walk to and from the parking lot it is 1.9 miles. It takes about 35-40 minutes to walk the loop. If we walk the loop twice it's a total of 3.5 miles and takes between 1 hr and 1 hr and 15 minutes, depending on pace. If we walk to the street of the Weymouth entrance it adds .4 miles and takes about 5-10 minutes. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please Note&lt;/span&gt;: Because the number of spaces available is limited for this event, we ask that members please RSVP "Yes" only if they are 99% sure they will attend.  If you do RSVP "Yes" and later realize you will not/can no longer attend, please change your RSVP from "Yes" to "No" so that someone else may have the opportunity to attend.  Also, &lt;em&gt;there is no need to RSVP "No" unless it is to change your RSVP from Yes to No&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Saturday Morning Fall Foliage Walk @ Pond Meadow Park&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, November 3rd @ 10:00am&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Pond Meadow Park &lt;br /&gt;

 470 Liberty Street, Braintree &lt;br /&gt;

 781-843-7663       &lt;br /&gt;

 Website:  www.pondmeadowpark.org &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: Flagpole in front of Ranger Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Event Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Angela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: At least 6 Yes RSVPs by 8pm on Friday, November 2nd. Attendance is currently limited to 20 total people, 14 for Walkabouts and 8 for Social Fun.  (The WL is set to Automatic, meaning as a spot opens up the next person on the WL will automatically be moved to the Yes list.  Please be sure to change your RSVP if you are no longer able to attend.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: 1 adult per member is welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Late Arrivals&lt;/em&gt;: We will wait our traditional 5-10 minutes for late arrivals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/em&gt; Please finalize your RSVP by 8pm on Friday, November 2nd.  Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and are subject to our No-Show policy.  The Event Organizer(s)/Host(s) reserves the right to cancel this event if we have less than 6 Yes RSVPs at the RSVP Deadline. &lt;br /&gt;

 Link to South Shore Walkabouts Membership Information Page which includes our No-Show Policy: &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/walkabouts/pages/Membership_Info/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/walkabouts/pages/Membership_Info/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: Heavy rains will cancel. We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle. Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case. (We will do our best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by 8:45am on the day of the walk.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rain Date&lt;/em&gt;: None.  Forecast looks clear.  The South Shore Walkabouts have another PMP walk scheduled and will probably have another one not yet scheduled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;From Route 3&lt;/em&gt;: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree. Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station. Follow Union Street to the first set of lights. Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street. Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary. Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street. (This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.) PMP is 500 feet up on the Right. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet by the flagpole in front of the Ranger Station.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351967159000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1351522892000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Morning Fall Foliage Walk @ Pond Meadow Park w/ South Shore Walkabouts</name><id>89028902</id><headcount>12</headcount><duration>5400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351951200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/89028902/</event_url></item>