<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boulder Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03223</zip><lat>43.960351</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Waterville Valley Ski Area</name><city>Waterville Valley</city><id>716569</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.509317</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mount Tecumseh sits in Waterville Valley and holds the distinction of being the smallest of the AMC 4000 footers in NH. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trailhead for this hike is located just right of the base lodge for Waterville Valley ski area. You should be able to park in the lot just below the main road. If you are coming up or down Route 93, take exit 28 and drive about 10 miles East on Rte. 49 and follow the signs to the ski area. Watch your speed, the police are notorious along this stretch of road!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail follows a small brook and goes up a new section of trail along a small ridge. At 1.1 miles, the trail drops and recrosses the brook before rejoining the original trail, an old logging road. The trail then veers right to ascend a long and continuous ridgeline to the top of Tecumseh. Total distance for this hike is 5 miles round trip. The trail is steady, wide, and pretty well marked. Anticipate snow and ice along the way, and all hikers should be prepared with full winter gear. The top is wooded with a brief steep pitch before hitting the top. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is relatively short with a moderate pitch and should be a good hike for an early winter ascent.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263308873000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262797028000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mount Tecumseh</name><id>12240853</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263135600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/12240853/</event_url></item>