<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;TAIL OF THE DRAGON AT DEALS GAP, with 318 curves in 11 miles, is America's number one motorcycle and sports car road. The nearby CHEROHALA SKYWAY is quickly becoming number two with its remote 60 miles of scenic mountain highway. The area also has other incredible roads like the MOONSHINER 28, DEVILS TRIANGLE, THE DIAMONDBACK, SIX GAP NORTH GEORGIA, THE SNAKE and GREAT FOREST SERVICE DUAL SPORT RIDING.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dealsgap.com/"&gt;http://www.dealsgap.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.tailofthedragon.com/"&gt;http://www.tailofthedragon.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll join the folks from &lt;a&gt;Boston Tier 1 Riders&lt;/a&gt;. We would certainly need to tow the bikes. Let us know if you have a truck/trailer and how many bikes it can hold. We will split the gas cost, so it would work out cheaper for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to give you all a rough idea, Robbinsville, NC is about 1000mi from Boston. So it will be total of about 2000mi of&amp;nbsp; cage driving. We'll can leave Boston on 05/12 morning and should be able to return by 05/17 evening. This is a tentative plan and can be changed depending upon everyone's interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;This will be an advanced ride.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please do not double RSVP on both &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tier-1-Riders/events/32550752/"&gt;Boston Tier 1 Riders&lt;/a&gt; site and NESB site. RSVP only on 1 site so that its easier to keep track of headcount.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gp1300</member_name><member_id>14409235</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337422336000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>west-connsportbikeriders</urlname><id>1535765</id><group_lat>41.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>West-Conn Sport Bike Riders</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321067428000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tail of the dragon - Deals Gap - 6 day trip - Summer '12</name><id>40868402</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336820400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/west-connsportbikeriders/events/40868402/</event_url></item>