<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is simply a morning paddle at a nice clean lake without the effect of all the recent flooding found in the rivers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to a nice morning paddle around the lake, I want to do my rolls, paddle float entry and wet exits right before its time for me to go.&lt;br /&gt;I have some volenteer activity i should attend to and still can if i finish up at 11:00. That means if anyone else wants to stay and paddle with other members or go to another site then I encourage that.&lt;br /&gt;I will bring along an additional recreational kayak with all of the extra acessories..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Bolton Lake:&lt;br /&gt;Rte 384 East to Bolton. &lt;br /&gt;at the end will meet rte 44 and 6&lt;br /&gt;stay to the left = rte 44&lt;br /&gt;The first light has a small shopping area and a post office on the right, pass that and follow rte 44 to the next light.&lt;br /&gt;A cemetary on the right then a church right before the light.&lt;br /&gt;=Intersection of rte 44 and South rd&lt;br /&gt;Look left a very short distance before the light, this is the boat launch area.&lt;br /&gt;I will have the blue Toyota Avalon with 2 kayaks on an old sailboat trailer.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1148303100000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1147801440000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Morning Paddle at Bolton Lake, Bolton CT</name><id>4938656</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1148130000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/4938656/</event_url></item>