<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by neuro-linguistic programming (NLP). Here are the details of the April meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First off, a reminder: we start the meeting at 6:30 for those new to NLP, those who want a review, and those who want to come early to socialize/network.  At 7pm we will jump into the main event for the evening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The main event: Triumphing over Adversity - NLP Strategies and Techniques&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've all faced adversity in our lives: lost jobs, failed relationships, setbacks in our life goals, health issues, financial losses, and many more.  In the current economy particularly, many of us are facing varieties of economic adversity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what can we do about it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this meetup, we will tackle the two major aspects of adversity: the way we &amp;quot;frame&amp;quot; or perceive the adverse situation, and the strategies we use to overcome that situation.  Depending on how we use our time, we will learn and practice one or more of the following techniques: meaning reframes, submodality shifts, Decision destroyer, and Future resourcing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring a past, present, or future adversity, and let's triumph over it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to discuss specific issues that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;We meet on the first floor of Sturtevant Hall, 197 Herrick Road, which is near the library on the central quad of Andover Newton. &lt;br /&gt;Andover Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get a campus map and directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ants.edu/ants-difference/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ants.edu/a...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk straight ahead into the meeting room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243896652000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237506111000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP April Meetup - Triumphing over Adversity</name><id>9992040</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239921000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/9992040/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/6/8/global_3512920.jpeg</photo_url></item>