<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One City Hall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.359377</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>City Hall Plaza</name><city>Boston</city><id>877405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058043</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Start Time: Saturday, July 17, 2010 at 9:00am &lt;br /&gt;End Time: Sunday, July 18, 2010 at 9:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;Location: CITY HALL PLAZA BOSTON &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=128172070537640&amp;amp;ref=ts" target="_blank"&gt;1ST AFRICAN FESTIVAL OF BOSTON&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://shalupe.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://shalupe.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; This is a free event!&lt;br /&gt;Come dance and Enjoy the African beats of local and International Artist..&lt;br /&gt;All of the cultures of Africa are coming together on..July 17th at&lt;br /&gt;the City Hall Plaza from 9 am- 9 pm...&lt;br /&gt;The City of Boston will be the heart of Africa! Don't miss it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOSTON, MA. On Saturday July 17, Boston City Hall Plaza will become the heart of Africa. People from all over New England will come to celebrate Africa's rich heritage. This day of celebration will also be a day of education and turning the page on 50 years of negative perceptions of Africa. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Did you know that Africa is turning 50? In the 1960s, 31 African countries, from the North (Algeria) to the South (Malawi) to the East (Kenya) to the West (Ivory Coast) to the Center (Central African Republic) achieved independence from colonial rule. Today, the sounds of freedom are ringing as these countries mark their 50 years of independence. To make this sound ring around the world, the Shalupe foundation (www.shalupe.org), in collaboration with the festival committee, is organizing the First African Festival in Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston’s First African Festival aims to inform the Greater Boston and New England community about all the resources and tools this great country has to offer as we look forward to the next 50 years. Come and collaborate to strengthen the African community this summer. The vision of the festival is to celebrate Africa and place it in the limelight. The underlying message is to give a platform to everyone in the African community…like they have never had before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thousands of people will be crossing our paths that day. Anyone who has a business, organization, etc. that needs a push, let them know. Shalupe is setting up the stage for the African community in MA to soar. This festival will also (if embassy representatives attend) help boost tourism to our respective countries. Fifty years of negativity is long, especially after independence. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clarification on the Goals of the Festival: We will all come together at this festival to make a positive impression. We are here. Let's make ourselves known, and have a strong voice as a community as we celebrate our diverse music, dance, and foods. The festival will kick off with a drum call parade starting at 10am at Boston Common and proceeding to Boston City Hall Plaza where there will be a full day of musical and cultural performances from local and international African bands. Highlights will include performances by world-renowned artists Teeyah (Cote d’Ivoire) and Bouro Mpela (DRC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1st African Festival of Boston&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, July 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;9:00am – 7:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Speakers/DJs/Performance Schedule&lt;br /&gt;Time Speaker/Performance&lt;br /&gt;9:00am African music playing (DJs)&lt;br /&gt;10:00am Sound Check&lt;br /&gt;10:30am 1st African Festival of Boston Welcome&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Official welcome by Shalupe Foundation&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Sponsors&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Appreciation to City&lt;br /&gt;10:45am Opening Prayer&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Pastor Bahinda&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Iman Barrier&lt;br /&gt;11:00am – 12:00pm Drum Call/Parade&lt;br /&gt;African music playing (DJs)&lt;br /&gt;(setting up for Jamurrell Band &amp;amp; Fatou)&lt;br /&gt;12:00pm – 12:30pm Jamurrell Percussion Band&lt;br /&gt;12:30pm – 1:00pm Fatou Ndiaye &amp;amp; Silimbo Company&lt;br /&gt;(singing for Gov. Deval)&lt;br /&gt;1:00pm – 1:10pm Governor Deval Patrick&lt;br /&gt;1:10pm – 1:20pm State Rep. Gloria Fox&lt;br /&gt;1:20pm – 1:30pm State Rep. Susan Bump&lt;br /&gt;1:30pm – 2:15pm Mamadou Diop&lt;br /&gt;2:15pm – 2:25pm City Counselor Ayanna Pressley&lt;br /&gt;2:25pm – 2:35pm Mr. Alfred Marder&lt;br /&gt;2:35pm – 3:00pm African music playing (DJ)&lt;br /&gt;3:00pm – 3:45pm Bouba Diabate &amp;amp; Samba Lolo&lt;br /&gt;3:45pm – 4:00pm TRANSITION&lt;br /&gt;4:00pm – 4:30pm UMeleni&lt;br /&gt;4:30pm – 4:45pm TRANSITION&lt;br /&gt;4:45pm - 5:30pm Atlas Soul&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm – 5:45pm TRANSITION&lt;br /&gt;5:45pm – 6:30pm Lamine Toure &amp;amp; Sabar Band&lt;br /&gt;6:30pm – 6:45pm TRANSITION&lt;br /&gt;6:45pm – 7:45pm Bouro Mpela&lt;br /&gt;7:45pm – 8:00pm 1st African Festival of Boston Closing&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8722; Official closing by Shalupe Foundation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrating Nelson Mandela's Birthday&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*FREE BEFORE 1030PM*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OFFICIAL AFRICAN FESTIVAL AFTER PARTY Om Restaurant | Lounge &lt;br /&gt;92 winthrop stCambridge Ma. Hvd Sq.SUN.JULY 18th. 9P-1A| 21+&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO RSVP OR FMI CONTACT: Afriqueevents@live.com OR Call: 781.354.1580&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1st AFRICAN FESTIVAL OF BOSTON&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SATURDAY, JULY 17, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CITY HALL PLAZA, BOSTON MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS TO CITY HALL.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Public Transportation:&lt;br /&gt;Take the MBTA Green or Blue line to Government Center station. Or take Orange or Blue line to State Street station. From the Red line, transfer at Park Street station to Green towards Lechmere. The 92 and 93 buses also stop outide City Hall on Congress Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving From the North:&lt;br /&gt;Use I-93 South and take Exit 24-A for Government Center. Stay in right lane on ramp. At top of the off ramp, proceed across Surface Road onto Clinton Street. At end of Clinton Street, proceed left onto North Street. City Hall is directly ahead across the intersection of North Street and Congress Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving From the South:&lt;br /&gt;Use I-93 North and take Exit 23 for Government Center. Stay in left lane on ramp. At top of ramp, left lane becomes two lanes wide. Stay in lane marked for Government Center. This lane crosses Surface Road onto North Street. Follow North Street to intersection with Congress Street. City Hall is directly ahead across the intersection of North Street and Congress Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from the West on Storrow Drive:&lt;br /&gt;Storrow Drive Traffic should access I-93 South. Use I-93 South and take Exit 24-A for Government Center. Stay in right lane on ramp. At top of the off ramp, proceed across Surface Road onto Clinton Street. At end of Clinton Street, proceed left onto North Street. City Hall is directly ahead across the intersection of North Street and Congress Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from the East or West on the Massachusetts Turnpike:&lt;br /&gt;Massachusetts Turnpike (I-90) Traffic should access I-93 North. Use I-93 North and take Exit 23 for Government Center. Stay in left lane on ramp. At top of ramp, left lane becomes two lanes wide. Stay in lane marked for Government Center. This lane crosses Surface Road onto North Street. Follow North Street to intersection with Congress Street. City Hall is directly ahead across the intersection of North Street and Congress Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from the East via the Sumner Tunnel:&lt;br /&gt;Traffic using the Sumner Tunnel should stay in the left lane marked for Government Center. Left lane exit ramp splits in two. Keep to left at this split for Government Center. From the top of the ramp, turn left onto New Chardon Street and proceed to Congress Street. Take a left onto Congress Street (passing under the Government Center Garage) and proceed to the intersection with North Street. Boston City Hall is directly on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking Suggestions:&lt;br /&gt;Street parking downtown is extremely limited, though a few parking meters are nearby on Union Street and on Cambridge Street. There is no public parking in City Hall itself, but there are several commerical parking garages within walking distance. For short-term parking for City Hall visitors, one low-cost option is the MTA Parcel 7 Garage. With validation from a local merchant, max 3 hours of parking costs $3. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279462594000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279162413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1ST AFRICAN FESTIVAL OF BOSTON</name><id>14107617</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279395000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/14107617/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/f/global_16434943.jpeg</photo_url></item>