<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I'm trying to get together a group for a biweekly D&amp;amp;D 4e Eberron campaign. This will be a somewhat mid- to long-term campaign, starting at 1st level and going as far as we end up going. Ideally it will have a good mix of intrigue, exploration, lots of danger and general merriment. Given how things usually go, it will likely be a comedy of errors (aren't they the best?) It's going to run biweekly Friday nights, 7:30pm to lateish at my house. First session is next Friday, June 5th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm pretty much open to anybody (with some provisos, see below). We (my wife and I) are classic New England liberal types and unless you're a raging conservative, we'll undoubtedly get along really well with you. If it's any bonus, I'm an Australian expat so you'll be able to make dingo jokes too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, the obligatory provisos that make me sound like a douchebag:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are clean, sober, have a good grasp of hygiene and can carry on normal social interactions without coming off as sketchy of skeevy, then we'd love to have you. Please no 4chan refugees if at all possible, but we could probably make an exception if you're nice enough. If you smoke that's ok, but we're a non-smoking house so you'd probably have to puff outside. Please no Creepy Gamer story candidates. My wife and I have had some bad experiences and have no wish to repeat them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The aim is to have a group that wants to have fun, can joke around a bit, but wants to actually play rather than sit around and discuss the latest episode of Lost (although a little bit of that is okay too because damn, that was one hell of a season finale, huh?). That said, if you're looking for a hardcore number-crunching grognard session, this likely isn't for you either. I guess what I'm saying is that we're shooting for a nice, casual balance of play and banter.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Szewczyk</member_name><member_id>4695834</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244588453000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243532753000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eberron 4th Edition Campaign</name><id>10515065</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244244600000</time><rsvp_limit>6</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/10515065/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>