<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>20 South Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.760615</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.561.6950</phone><name>West Hartford Public Library</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>942298</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.741979</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Taken directly from the Library's calendar on their website &lt;a href="http://www.westhartfordlibrary.org/programs_calendar:" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westhartfo...&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------    &lt;br /&gt;Open discussion of the The Adventures of Tom Sawyer by Mark Twain. Discussion led by librarian Joseph Cadieux.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Adventures of Tom Sawyer is not merely a literary classic. It is part of the American imagination. More than any other work in our culture it established America's vision of childhood. Mark Twain created two fictional boys, Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn, who still seem more real than most of the people we know. In a still puritanical nation, Twain reminded adults that children were not angels, but fellow human beings, and perhaps all the more lovable for their imperfections and bad grooming. Neither American literature nor America has ever been the same.    &lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------    &lt;br /&gt;This is at the board room of the main library in West Hartford Center from 7:30-8:30.  No reservations needed.  You can park in the Isham St. garage in back of the library-Blue Back Square- and have your parking ticket validated.  There are some great places to eat or get coffee before or after (Cheesecake Factory, Counter Burger, Barnes and Noble, and more...) -so just let me know if you are interested!  This may be one of the last &amp;quot;Big Read&amp;quot; - Mark Twain events of the year.  (I am so sad!). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the library and parking info: &lt;a href="http://www.westhartfordlibrary.org/about/howtofindus" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.westhartfo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278079059000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275154660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion: The Adventures of Tom Sawyer by Mark Twain.</name><id>13633305</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1277940600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/13633305/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/1/global_15356177.jpeg</photo_url></item>