<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Lowell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.465790</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Kayak Launch</name><city>Concord</city><id>12876262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.355484</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Folks, I know this is a weekday and lots of you will not be able to come.  &lt;strong&gt;Please do not RSVP "NO" if you are not coming.&lt;/strong&gt; If you are not already on the "weekdays paddlers" list, and would like to be added,  let me know.  Further weekday paddles will only be announced to paddlers on the "weekday paddlers" list (with the exception of the after-work paddles), but they will still show up on the homepage as a scheduled meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's celebrate Earth Day with a paddle on the Concord River under the Old North Bridge, up to Great Meadows Wildlife Refuge.  It's about 1.5 miles with the current from the launch at Lowell Road up to the Great Meadows Wildlife Refuge Containment ponds.  (I don't expect the current to be terribly strong.) We can beach our kayaks and walk across a dike and look for wildlife in the containment ponds.  &lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/refuges/profiles/index.cfm?id=53511"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/refuges/profiles/index.cfm?id=53511&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/refuges/profiles/index.cfm?id=53511"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; On the way back we'll need to paddle against the current.  We'll try to stop at the Old North Bridge and have a picnic lunch if it is not too difficult to get out of our kayaks at that location (water level is high).  From there, we can head back and pass the launch (alternate lunch spot) and see how far up the Assabet River we can get since the water level is high this time of year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Launch&lt;/strong&gt; at Lowell Road in Concord where it goes over the Concord river.  Drop off kayak down an access road to the river, then park on road.  The access road to the launch is south-west of the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive in time to be in your kayak and ready to paddle by 10:30 AM.  It's difficult to tell how many hours we will be out, as it will depend on how long we enjoy the containment ponds, how long we break for lunch, and how far up the Assabet River we get.... Be prepared to spend at least 4 hours, and possibly longer.  On our way back from the Old North Bridge, on the way to the Assabet River, we will be passing the launch area. People with limited time can bail out there and the rest of us can keep going.  If you bail out there, you may have to load your kayak onto your car on your own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required:&lt;/strong&gt; PFD (worn), whistle.  &lt;em&gt;Optional/recommended&lt;/em&gt;: pump/bailer, insect repellent, sunscreen, water, lunch/snack, change of clothes in drybag, shoes for walking at Containment Ponds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***PLEASE NOTE*** The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy H</member_name><member_id>7962459</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366661535000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366119863000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekday Paddle and Walk Concord/Assabet Rivers</name><id>114603622</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366641000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/114603622/</event_url></item>