<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Trailblazers, I just found out about this trip otherwise I would have given more notice so if anyone wants to do some kayaking this coming weekend join us for some good kayaking or canoeing. Come early around 9:00-9:30 to set up and get to know everyone. Call the number below and reserve your free canoe. Join natural resource experts and fellow paddlers for a two-hour tour of the Branch River by canoe and kayak. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moose Mountains Regional Greenways will partner again with Branch Hill Farm, UNH Cooperative Extension, and the NH Department of Environmental Services to present the fourth annual Branch River Paddle on Saturday, May 31. A donation of $10 is requested to help cover event costs. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants will embark at 10 a.m. from the intersection of Route 125 and Applebee Road, just east of Exit 18 off the Spaulding Turnpike. Paddlers will follow the Branch River 4.5 miles to the Salmon Falls River around Sandy Point, meeting natural resource experts along the way who will describe the importance of the river, wetlands and other habitats. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Geoffrey Njue from UNH Cooperative Extension will describe the importance of buffers in protecting water quality. Bob Craycraft, also from UNH Cooperative Extension, will show the role that bugs, mussels, snails, crayfish, worms, and other invertebrates play in demonstrating water quality. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paddlers will disembark on Branch Hill Farm conservation land for a picnic lunch hosted by Branch Hill Farm. Transportation back to parked vehicles will be provided. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participation will be limited to 40 watercraft on a first-come first-served basis, and pre-registration is required. For more information or to register, call Branch Hill Farm at (603) 473-2535 or email infommrg.info. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moose Mountains Regional Greenways is a non-profit organization that works to conserve and connect the most special natural resource areas of New Hampshire's northern Strafford and southern Carroll counties. For more information about Moose Mountains, call (603) 817-8260 or visit www.mmrg.info. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;University of New Hampshire Cooperative Extension provides New Hampshire citizens with research-based education and information, enhancing their ability to make informed decisions that strengthen youth, families and communities, sustain natural resources, and improve the economy. For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://ceinfo.unh.edu..." target="_blank"&gt;http://ceinfo.unh.edu...&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mission of the Department of Environmental Services is to help sustain a high quality of life for all citizens by protecting and restoring the environment and public health in New Hampshire. For more information, visit www.des.state.nh.us.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212415797000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's a wonderful way to spend the day!</why><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212057660000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Canoe or kayak tour of the Branch River</name><id>8033991</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212242400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/8033991/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/f/global_4282111.jpeg</photo_url></item>