<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cummings Center, Suite 435-K</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.558906</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 864-7076</phone><name>Eternal Balance</name><city>Beverly</city><id>1226709</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.887042</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>40.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Some words from Dunja:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dear Breathers and those new to the Art of Natural Breathing!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;I am always surprised how a breathing session leaves me more spacious, less contracted and full of life and gratefulness.  After fifteen years of teaching and practicing this work I am still surprised each time I enter the state of expansion, tingling, vibrating and flowing in and out of the boundaries defined by my regular identity. Especially in cathartic breath work, the Art of Natural Breathing, it becomes apparent how much we can melt, marveling at not having to hold on so tight to who we are but rather discovering our essence while we let go more and more of who we are not. Thoughts? I am not my thoughts so who am I? Emotions? I am not my emotions so who am I? Physical sensations? I am not my body so who am I? Inhaling and exhaling deeply and with consciousness allows for the opening into the mystery of who you truly are beyond time and space. “What the session is already over? I thought only fifteen minutes had passed?”  Witnessing the relativity of time and space, feeling old belief systems dissolve and becoming compassionate towards the unknown, as well as filling yourself with the stuff the universe is made of are all qualities you will experience in an Art of Natural Breathing class. Light, matter, energy, flow, water, fire, earth, sky come be and breathe recognizing you were free all along! It is amazing, wondrous, mysterious, exhilarating, scary and wonderfully hilarious! Spring into Spring while you breathe out winter and inhale the power of the yet unborn, your own wondrous being.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Art of Natural Breathing is a powerful form of breath work, a catalyst for transformation. The spring and summer classes will initiate a physical and spiritual clearing process. Every time you breathe the primitive and limbic part of your brain, as well as the neo cortex will form new connective patterns, allowing you to release what does not serve you any longer. Strengthening these integrative aspects of your brain, will also give your consciousness and soul a chance to fully be expressed through your physicality creating more energy and awareness. Breathing in this connected way will also help you to connect deeper with yourself and those around you. The Art of Natural Breathing is fantastic for your mind, body, relational and spiritual self.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olga </member_name><member_id>10158912</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361657072000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members with unlimited potential</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club</urlname><id>1467921</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Holistic Lifestyle  Women's Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359509592000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Art of Natural Breathing</name><id>102059982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361646000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Holistic-Lifestyle-Womens-Club/events/102059982/</event_url></item>