<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.367558</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charles Hayden Planetarium</name><city>Boston</city><id>6023562</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070702</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;REGISTRATION UPDATE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dangerousencounters.eventbrite.com/"&gt;http://dangerousencounters.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c"&gt;Per the Museum:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ad364c"&gt;Any reservations not picked up by 6:45 the day of the event will be reissued to walk-ins (so anyone who isn't able to register in time, might still be able to attend last minute by showing up at 6:45)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be a table in the museum lobby (as it will say in the confirmation email you receive from Eventbrite) starting at 6:00 to pick up your seating pass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After you pick up your seating pass, Meet us down the hall in the Red Wing in front of the simulator ride and we can walk over to get in line for the Planetarium around 6:40.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best seating is generally on the right after you go in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sonesta Hotel for a drink afterwards is a separate event:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080 ; font-size : large"&gt;Drink Encounters: The Hunt for Spirits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's right around the corner and has lounges inside and potential for outside drinks if the weather is nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;__________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dangerous Encounters: The Hunt for Asteroids | Wednesday, April 25; 7:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Join us in the Charles Hayden Planetarium, New England's most technologically advanced digital theater, to journey into the asteroid belt and hear the latest news from two figures at the forefront of planetary defense.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Richard P. Binzel, PhD, professor of planetary sciences, MIT; member of NASA's Task Force on Planetary Defense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Timothy B. Spahr, PhD, director, Minor Planet Center, Harvard Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission : &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Free, register online&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (see above)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near-Earth Objects (NEOs) pose a long-term hazard to our planet. Past scars tell of many devastating impacts, some of which nearly snuffed out life on Earth. Astronomer Timothy Spahr collects and analyzes data from an average of 1,000 new asteroids per day, notifying NASA headquarters when an object's orbit will bring it close to Earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Richard Binzel is an expert in what these NEOs are composed of, where they come from, and how they may be a factor in future space exploration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In June 2011, a newly discovered asteroid named 2011MD passed within 7,500 miles of Earth—the fifth-closest recorded asteroid encounter. How much of a threat does an asteroid impact pose today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission is free thanks to the generosity of the Lowell Institute.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>8776856</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335585124000</updated><rating><average>4.46000003815</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>104</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330961234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dangerous Encounters: The Hunt for Asteroids (Admission is Free)</name><id>55041072</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335392100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/55041072/</event_url></item>