<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>187 Chelmsford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.608450</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-887-5677</phone><name>The Best Western</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>334113</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340760</lon></venue><fee><label>Guest Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Jack Lavoie, local investor, is coming to share his methods of buying and selling/holding real estate and his recent rehab projects.  Jack plans on sharing his reasoning behind holding certain properties and the things his experiences have taught him about real estate investing.  Jack was planning on speaking later on this year, as it is a very busy time for him now, but due to a last minute rescheduling of our planned speaker, Jack is stepping in early to share what he's been doing with the NEREIA members.  Also, as an appraiser in NH, Jack is going to share the most common mistakes people make in pricing their property, that cause them to overprice.  Come learn practical applications of real estate methods used by this local investor, and member of the NEREIA organization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Jack:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack Lavoie is a 20+ year veteran of the real estate industry as an appraiser, broker and investor.  Jack has bought and sold scores of single family houses and apartment buildings using a variety of acquisition and exit strategies, including lease options.  He is the owner of Jack Lavoie Real Estate, LLC and IBuyNHhouses.com and is considered the “go to guy” for real estate questions by his collegues (brokers, appraisers, investors).  Jack has mentored dozens of successful real estate investors in his career.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk into the front of the building, and straight ahead you will see our Welcome table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter and Rhiannon </member_name><member_id>6208546</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340119156000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Buyers &amp; Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nereia</urlname><id>593272</id><group_lat>42.6199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3600006104</group_lon><name>New England Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336579324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Practical Real Estate Tips</name><id>vxsvqyqjbjb</id><headcount>74</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339023600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nereia/events/64083692/</event_url></item>