<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 may street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.257946</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Photo Studios</name><city>Worcester</city><id>2095731</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.825211</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

DETAILS: Calling all photographers, models, makeup artists, hair stylists, designers, and those aspiring: The Great Model Shoot is an exciting networking event at what is becoming the largest photo studio in New England. Every shoot is unique, so don't miss it! All are welcome, from first-timers to seasoned professionals. THE BIG IDEA: Network with others in the field! Build an amazing portfolio! Get experience! Learn and share ideas in a fun group setting... &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

COST: Models $20 / Photographers $40 / for the ENTIRE day! / MUA, Hair, Designers: no cost! In return for donating time, skills and supplies for styling models. Price basically covers our cost to run the studio and includes lunch. (Ask us how to become a WPS member to get a discount on events!) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

WHAT TO BRING: Models should bring a variety of outfits and accessories that they would like to be photographed in. Feel free to go all out and be as unique as you want. Come early to get the most out of the day. This month is the "Fall Edition" All attendees are encouraged to bring business cards. WPS also invites you to bring equipment/lighting, props, halloween or themed costumes, or just show up with your awesome personality. ;) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

_______________________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

GMS CODE OF CONDUCT: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

This event will be PG-13. There will be no nudity at this event, and any scantily-clad models MUST wear a robe between sets and during breaks. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Alcohol and drugs are strictly prohibited at all times. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

If you are attending one of our Great Model Shoots or other events, please take a moment to review this. If you are under 18 years of age, you MUST have a parent or legal guardian come with you. You may not have an older sibling, or other relative (unless they are your legal guardian) sign you into the GMS. Your parent or guardian must fill out the Model Release with you and have a valid ID. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Inappropriate behavior will result in a verbal warning by a WPS staff member. If such behavior continues, you will be asked to leave. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

These rules are put in place for everyone's safety and comfort. Any questions about Code Of Conduct or studio rules can be directed to Patrick (patrick@worcesterphotostudios.com) &lt;br /&gt;

_______________________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FAQ FOR MODELS: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/306632636059731" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/306632636059731&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FAQ FOR PHOTOGRAPHERS: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/330971083625886" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/330971083625886&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

FAQ FOR STYLISTS: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/290608480995480/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/groups/thegreatmodelshoot/doc/290608480995480/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

_______________________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

[event image credit: John Preves / Model: Roberta Mandella.]&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Patrick C. Sullivan</member_name><member_id>2373486</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Hendrickson</member_name><member_id>12134347</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chris Rinne</member_name><member_id>47667932</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350259236000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344869736000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Great Model Shoot: v19 Fall Edition</name><id>77536902</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>39600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350219600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/77536902/</event_url></item>