<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>; see directions below</address_2><address_1>182 Memorial Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.358536</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Building 6, Room 120</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>408704</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.089280</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>David Fry will be in Boston and has consented to bring his expertise to us on ETFs. How to use ETFs effectively is a topic that members have requested repeatedly. We are pleased to offer this talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Fry's talk is the only item on the agenda.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Using ETFs for Your Investment Plan by David Fry, Founder of ETFDigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to sort thru all the ETFs available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Which ETFs to assemble for an aggressive, growth or conservative investor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncorrelation and how important that is to achieving true diversification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Commodity, currency or leveraged ETFs - how to use them or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using a discount broker versus a wrap account financial advisor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ETFs versus index mutual funds? Why use either.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assembling an ETF hedge fund using limited but conventional easy-to-understand strategies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shorting.  Why?  And how?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why use fundamental analysis?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why use technical analysis?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to combine both.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ETF Digest Sacred Cows.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Biographical sketch of David Fry:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.etfdigest.com/daveBio.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.etfdigest....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dave Fry has devoted over 35 years to the business of trading and portfolio management. &lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;His registration as an arbitrator with both the National Association of Securities Dealers (NASD) and the National Futures Association (NFA) attests to his extensive experience and spotless compliance record.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dave founded the ETF Digest in 2001 and was among the very first to see the need for a publication that provided individual investors with information and advice on ETF investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;By 2002 ETF Digest trading programs were making triple-digit gains, despite the sharp overall market decline at that time, and Dave's newsletter began attracting favorable coverage in Barrons with three positive reviews in 2002, 2004 and 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dave is a frequent commentator on ETFs and other issues important to individual investors, and his perspectives are featured in financial news sources such as the Wall Street Journal, MarketWatch, Investors Business Daily, Smart Money, Dow Jones Newswire, National Business Review, MSN Money, Yahoo! Finance, Bankrate.com, Emerging Markets Monitor, IndexUniverse.com, and ETF Investor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;As the scope of ETF investing has expanded dramatically over the past few years, Dave has maintained a vital position as an investor advocate. He speaks out in favor of new ETFs to cover important market sectors and has seen new ETFs issued as a result. He is also very active in pointing out problems in the ETF marketplace to sponsors, issuers, brokers, and the media. Dave is committed to remaining at the forefront as this major investment trend continues to grow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of the highlights of Dave's career before he launched ETF Digest include the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In 1999, he founded TechInvest Inc. and began sharing his expertise through the Internet in his TechTrend Advisor newsletter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;From 1997-99, he was Managing Director, Proprietary Investments, at JWH Investment Management (JWHIMI), an affiliated company of John W. Henry &amp;amp; Company. In that capacity, Dave was responsible for the management of private investments as well as some corporate accounts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;For a period of 10 years prior to joining JWHIMI, David owned and operated an NASD broker/dealer, Fry &amp;amp; Co., and an SEC registered investment advisory firm, Asia-Pacific Investment Management Inc. He was also a registered Commodity Pool Operator, Commodity Trading Advisor, and Introducing Broker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior to operating his own investment firms, Dave was a Vice President, Investments, at Shearson Lehman Bros., and held a similar position at Paine Webber.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;During his tenure with registered firms he maintained the following licenses: Municipal Bond Principal (Series 53), Options Principal (Series 4), General Securities Principal (Series 24), General Securities (Series 7), Commodity (Series 3), State Securities License (Series 63), and State Insurance License (Life).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mr. Fry's site may be found at: &lt;a href="http://www.etfdigest.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.etfdigest....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking and Walking Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the MIT map to the building: &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/bin/map?locate=room_6-120;zoom=level2;selection=6;selectlayer=Buildings;selectfield=facility;centerx=711153;centery=495644" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We suggest you park as you do for Building E51 and walk to Building 6 - the building highlighted in red. Walk down Amherst Street, cross Ames Street, walk down the sidewalk until you get to Building 6, then walk in through the big doors in the center of the building.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1210601140000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>91</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204609013000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Using ETFs for Your Investment Plan by David Fry, Founder of ETFDigest.com</name><id>7459624</id><headcount>92</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210201200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/7459624/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/e/global_938062.jpeg</photo_url></item>