<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>One of the true gifts in a busy life is an extended period of silence, a&lt;br /&gt;time when we intentionally turn our attentions away from the rush of&lt;br /&gt;responsibilities and commitments, images and messages, and quietly attune&lt;br /&gt;ourselves to an inner space. However, in a world so completely focused on&lt;br /&gt;action it is sometimes challenging to move from responding with immediate&lt;br /&gt;reactions into a space of silence and reflection. In silence we deepen our&lt;br /&gt;awareness and understanding of ourselves, others and situations. We can&lt;br /&gt;expand our thinking from limited to unlimited which leads to innovation and&lt;br /&gt;creativity. Through silence we can also enter into a relationship with the&lt;br /&gt;Divine through which we receive spiritual power and can become instruments&lt;br /&gt;to serve others. Through the power of silence our greatness is revealed to&lt;br /&gt;ourselves and to others. Anyone who has spent time in a retreat setting&lt;br /&gt;knows the challenge of carrying back into life and work the deep sense of&lt;br /&gt;inner peace and power they have touched while away from the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No two people approach the transition into silence in the same way. For some&lt;br /&gt;it begins with visualization; for others it is something more tangible -&lt;br /&gt;running, sitting in front of a candle, or playing a musical instrument.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Silence is a subtle language that connects us to one another through the&lt;br /&gt;eyes, with a smile, or a gesture. Fluency in this subtle language calls for&lt;br /&gt;our ability to observe the small details of life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In silence I discover my innate qualities, the qualities that are intrinsic&lt;br /&gt;to who I am. Here in silence I touch my eternal self, and I come to trust&lt;br /&gt;this deepest essence. The experience of recognizing my intrinsic and unique&lt;br /&gt;qualities increases my own power to receive. In silence I touch my inner&lt;br /&gt;strength and experience trust, faith, safety, beauty, worthiness. It is from&lt;br /&gt;this base of inner strength that my actions evolve.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to Winchell room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>10101462</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261425989000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Great Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight</urlname><id>1499616</id><group_lat>43.0</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Owning Greatness Through Raja Yoga  Manchester Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249227991000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Power of Silence</name><id>11014594</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261252800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Celebrating-Human-Greatness-Meetup-Group-Spiritual-Insight/events/11014594/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/8/global_9988136.jpeg</photo_url></item>