<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Bedford Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.989769</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-622-7531</phone><name>Millyard Museum</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1036347</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.467545</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;Holiday Open House at the Millyard Museum&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 5, 2009&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;10:00 a.m.-4:00 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;FREE Admission (Note: Admission to the Research Center is also free this day.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  No RSVP is required for this event. For directions and other information, visit www.manchesterhistoric.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy cider and cookies with your neighbors, family and friends on this special day that will feature talks and book signings by New Hampshire authors, a tour of the Millyard Museum, and shopping in the Museum Shop. The Shop features a variety of items including books about Manchester history and related topics (many by local authors), limited edition ornaments (including our newest ornament &amp;quot;The Ash Street School&amp;quot;), and inexpensive gifts including boxed sets of Victorian tea cups and matching saucers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;SPECIAL &amp;quot;OPEN HOUSE&amp;quot; OFFERS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Manchester Historic Association members will receive an additional 10% discount over their normal membership discount (at least a 20% total discount; please note: member discounts do not apply to Joanne Katherine Design items, and books sold directly by authors). Anyone who joins the Association, renews their membership or buys a gift membership at the Open House will receive a free limited edition 75th Anniversary brass ornament depicting the MHA's historic building (a $10.95 value).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that all books mentioned will be available for sale in the Shop, or at the authors' tables.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;10:00 a.m.-4:00 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Joanne Wiren of Joanne Katherine Design will be on hand to show her beautiful line of custom made jewelry. A portion of the proceeds will benefit the Manchester Historic Association. For a look at her designs, visit www.joannekatherinedesigns.com/.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;10:00 a.m.-4:00 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Meet New Hampshire authors! In addition to the featured authors, Mike Pride and Joe Smiga - three other authors will be on hand to chat and sign books: Robert B. Perreault (&amp;quot;Postcard History Series - Manchester&amp;quot;), Clifton LaBree (&amp;quot;New Hampshire's&lt;br /&gt;General John Stark&amp;quot;) and D. Quincy Whitney (&amp;quot;Hidden History of New Hampshire&amp;quot;). For details of when these authors will be in the museum, please call (603) 622-7531.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;10:30 a.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Pride, editor emeritus of the Concord Monitor, will give a short talk about the newly re-published book, &amp;quot;Abraham Lincoln in New Hampshire&amp;quot; by Edwin L. Page. Page's book details Abraham Lincoln's trip through New Hampshire in March 1860. It provides a wealth of information and insight on Lincoln's visits to Concord, Manchester, Exeter and Dover. Lincoln gave important speeches at each of these towns, that helped pave the way for him to become the first Republican president of the United States. Mike Pride has updated Page's book with new research, and also wrote an informative introduction. The Millyard Museum's current special exhibit, &amp;quot;Abraham Lincoln: Manchester Remembers&amp;quot; chronicles Lincoln's visit to &lt;br /&gt;this city in 1860.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;11:30 a.m.-12:15 a.m&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Aurore Eaton, Executive Director, will give an introductory tour of the Millyard Museum - from Paleo-Indians to the Segway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;1:30 p.m.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When studying history we often ask ourselves &amp;quot;What if?&amp;quot; Local author Joe Smiga asked himself these questions about current events: &amp;quot;What if Iranian submarines launched missiles at the United States? But this can’t be possible. . .how could this happen? Is the U.S. ready for a counter attack?&amp;quot; Smiga explores this speculative topic in his novel &amp;quot;Behind the Lies,&amp;quot; a thriller focusing on tensions in the Middle East.Join us for a change of pace from &amp;quot;past history&amp;quot; and explore an imagined &amp;quot;future history.&amp;quot; For more information, visit www.joesmiga.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALSO: Visit the Manchester Historic Association website for information on our &amp;quot;Hands on History&amp;quot; Family Programs through December: &lt;a href="http://www.manchesterhistoric.org" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester Historic Association website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Manchester Historic Association</member_name><member_id>10139829</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1275143079000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>History fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-History-Network</urlname><id>1505455</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester History Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250180069000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Holiday Open House at the Millyard Museum</name><id>11103866</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-History-Network/events/11103866/</event_url></item>