<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Meeting at the Women's Federated Forest and hiking in to Soapstone Hill.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Signage is small but very close to the town lines for New Salem and Petersham.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;It's quite a drive to reach the parking lot....maybe 1 1/2 - 2 miles in, just a guess.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is an easy to moderate hike from the Women's Federated Forest to a nice ridge trail to reach the summit of Soapstone Hill. I'd like to take a lunch break at the summit of Soapstone Hill while we take in the views of the Quabbin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;We can return either back along the ridge trail or descend down from Soapstone Hill, walk along the reservoir and return via gate 36 of the Quabbin which is a bit longer. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Total hike time with break will be approximately 2-2 1/2 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There is limited parking yet if we fill it up and still need some more space, we can find alternate parking nearby and will attend to that if it happens. There are other spots we can park in withing the WFF or just down the street at Quabbin Gate 35 on Old Dana Road if we have to&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I have this posted on three local meetup sites so we'll see what happens&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/fwsf.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/fwsf.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/6/8/event_89472392.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Federated Women's Club State Forest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;quabbin strollers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;West St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Petersham MA 01366 &lt;br /&gt;

 978 544-3939&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Massachusetts Federation of Women's Club State Forest lies in Petersham and New Salem on Route 122. Its 984 acres stretch to the south and west in the watershed of the Quabbin Reservoir. Please Note that NO pets are allowed on DCR Watershed Property. Groves of pine and stands of maple, birch and hemlock invite the visitor along the wooded roads. The road along Fever Brook is outstanding for its scenery. A wildlife sanctuary compromising 140 acres has been set aside in the center of the forest, and a dam on Fever Brook holds back sufficient water to attract migrating and native wild fowl. In the southwest section is the forest's chief geological feature, the Gorge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campground Map&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View on screen | Download printable version (pdf)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things to know before you go…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limited Service campsites are available on a first come/first serve basis. Register at Erving State Forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Note that NO pets are allowed on DCR Watershed Property&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park Directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The forest is located in mid-central Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the East/Southeast/Northeast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-495 to exit 29, Rt. 2 west &lt;br /&gt;

 Follow Rt. 2 west for 42 miles to exit 16, Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Turn right at the end of exit ramp onto Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2 miles on Rt. 202 south and take a left onto Rt. 122 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 3.6 miles on Rt. 122 south to State Forest Rd. on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

 Take this right and follow for 1.7 miles to the gated park entrance. (See Erving State Forest for vehicle access).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take 1-90 west to exit 10, I-290 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 7.3 miles on I-290 north to exit 19, I-190 north. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 18.75 miles on I-190 north and merge left onto Rt. 2 west. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 30.5 miles on Rt. 2 west to exit 16, Rt. 202 south &lt;br /&gt;

 Turn right at the end of the exit ramp onto Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2 miles on Rt. 202 south and take a left onto Rt. 122 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 3.6 miles on Rt. 122 south to State Forest Rd. on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

 Take this right and follow for 1.7 miles to gated park entrance. (See Erving State Forest for vehicle access).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the West&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Rt. 2 east to exit 16, Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Turn left at the end of exit ramp onto Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2 miles on Rt. 202 south and take a left onto Rt. 122 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 3.6 miles on Rt. 122 south to State Forest Rd. on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

 Take this right and follow for 1.7 miles to gated park entrance. (See Erving State Forest for vehicle access).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Southwest/Northwest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take I-91 to Exit 27, Rt. 2 east. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 20 miles on Rt. 2 east to exit 16, Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Turn left at the end of the exit ramp onto Rt. 202 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 2 miles on Rt. 202 south and take a left onto Rt. 122 south. &lt;br /&gt;

 Drive 3.6 miles on Rt. 122 south to State Forest Rd. on the right. &lt;br /&gt;

 Take this right and follow for 1.7 miles to gated park entrance. (See Erving State Forest for vehicle access).&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350946668000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350760750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Impromptu Foliage Hike to Soapstone Hill(great views of Quabbin)</name><id>87834122</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350837000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/87834122/</event_url></item>