<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfa.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the ninth to the seventh centuries BC, the Assyrians emerged as the dominant power in the Near East, controlling all of present-day Iraq, Syria, Jordan, Lebanon, Israel, and Egypt, as well as large parts of Turkey and Iran. It was the largest empire known until that time.  “Art and Empire: Treasures from Assyria in the British Museum” includes the most powerful and moving of these reliefs. Military dress and equipment and horse trappings and harnesses illustrate life in the army. Carved ivories, furniture fittings, and metal vessels showcase the luxurious, cosmopolitan lifestyle enjoyed by the king and his court. An array of three-dimensional objects—figures of deities, clay tablets, clay seals and sealings—address the administration of the empire, trade, legal and social issues, and interrelationships between religion, magic, and medicine. Exorcisms, omen texts, mathematical texts, and literary compositions from the royal library (where the king sought to gather together all the world’s learning in one place) enshrine the wisdom of ancient Mesopotamia, the cradle of western civilization.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org/exhibitions/sub.asp?key=15&amp;amp;subkey=6028" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mfa.org/ex...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$28.50 for adult and $26.50 for students and can be bought online at the website above.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send out my contact info before the meetup</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228071951000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People of Indian Descent/Expats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indianheritage-41</urlname><id>1168585</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Indian Friends Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226551586000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Museum of Fine Arts -- Art and Empire: Treasures from Assyria in the British Mus</name><id>9153325</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227373200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indianheritage-41/events/9153325/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/9/global_4274761.jpeg</photo_url></item>