<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Argilla Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01938</zip><lat>42.685432</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Crane Beach</name><city>Ipswich</city><id>9758342</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.779739</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's take a fall hike at Crane Beach and see the beautiful foliage. We'll meet at noon at the entrance to the Dunes Hiking area, Hike the dunes out to the point and then make our way back on the beach. Look for the big Crowd as this is a popular event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It costs $8 Per Car for entrance to the park, so I encourage Carpooling to share the cost to get in. &lt;strong&gt;Please Arrive no Later than 12:15 so we can get the hike going in a timely fashion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Park at the right hand corner of the parking Lot near the dunes path entrance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dog's are allowed on the beach only. The dunes are a restricted habitat for some rare birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After we'll head to the Ipswich Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill for Burgers and beers after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ipswich Sports Bar &amp;amp; Grill&lt;/span&gt;, 24 Hammatt Street, Ipswich, MA 01938, Phone: (978) 356-7444.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Crane Beach, you’ll enjoy one of the finest beaches and outdoor recreation destinations on the East Coast. With its clean, inviting water, miles of shoreline, and mesmerizing views, Crane Beach has been a favorite with the ocean-loving public for generations. Whether you intend to take a refreshing plunge, play in the sand, or just soak up the sun, this unparalleled seaside experience is sure to provide lots of fun – and great memories, too. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 5.5 miles of trails traverse dunes and track the beachfront on both the Ipswich Bay and Essex River Estuary sides of the Castle Neck peninsula. Moderate hiking. These trails are part of the Bay Circuit Trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When to Visit &lt;br /&gt;

 Year-round, daily, 8am to sunset. &lt;strong&gt;Allow a minimum of 2 hours for the hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear shoes meant for hiking and Warm clothes. It tends to be windy in the fall. I would also recommend bringing a bottle of water and a Camera for some beautiful fall images.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria</member_name><member_id>2096131</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350936358000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>14</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>58</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349986658000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crane Beach Hike with a late lunch</name><id>86576422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350835200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/86576422/</event_url></item>