<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>765 Massachusetts Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366604</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Life Alive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10068632</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105347</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Last minute update!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Well, we got a few warm days there... Good. Now the cold is coming back for more... So anybody who can bring thermal wear, please do so. Let's meet at Life Alive in Cambridge from 3pm to 3:30pm and then hit the streets. Bring warm clothing for yourselves too!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A demain!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dear Boston Volunteers,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After the successful sleeping bag drive and coffee drive, we, Boston Volunteers decided to make yet another move to help the homeless.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We got appreciations, good stories and suggestions from the last drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will go out during day time for a change, and this way it might be easier to find our target clientele...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since it is still cold during the night, anyone who brings thermal wear (undies, socks, tops), as well as hats, gloves, and/or mitts is sure to strike a hit. Coats, sleeping bags, blankets are all good choices as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, we will serve some Coffee and snacks during the drive. I'm thinking that this time, since it's during the day, we might get some food for whoever wants it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Same plan:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring some snacks like Cookies, Chips, soda etc to the event for serving. Basically comfort foods, we all need some!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a backpack to stuff everything in, that would be a good idea to bring it, because we are walking around town, so it makes it easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please buy some Men/Women underwears and socks and bring them to the event (this is critical, didnt want to put this as event title). They were a huge hit also last time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring some money so that we can buy coffee and/or food to the homeless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please RSVP if you like to donate money or under garments or food, or both!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The final location will be updated shortly, but this will be in Cambridge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will go out for food ourselves around 5pm and whoever wants to come to our gathering at the wild rover later on that night, that would be awesome to share our stories!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Best regards!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Freddy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;P.S. This event is not through a partnership organization, we, Boston Volunteers, are organizing this by ourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Boston Volunteers &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big Enough to Deliver, Small Enough to Care &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonvolunteer.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>If you need to find us once there, call me! (781-308-4595)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Phani  Sukhavasi</member_name><member_id>11051234</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>frederick</member_name><member_id>25269862</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360009753000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Boston Volunteers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BigEnoughtoDeliver</urlname><id>1343564</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Volunteers. Big enough 2 deliver, small enough 2 care</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359326233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Coffee, food and conversation for Boston's homeless</name><id>101671292</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359835200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigEnoughtoDeliver/events/101671292/</event_url></item>