<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>186 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.352486</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Outside Boylston T Stop on the Common</name><city>Boston</city><id>709649</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064532</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Many of you indicated a love of walking. Every year a different theme is chosen for our annual Labor Day 5-hour totally unique walking tour a year in the making. So lace up your shoes and meetup with us for what we call &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/tours/Front_Page_News" target="_blank"&gt;Big Foot&lt;/a&gt;. This year's title is &lt;i&gt;Front Page News: 20th Century Boston&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Modern day Boston has some of the best preserved historic buildings and neighborhoods in the world. Boston is a well-balanced mix of old world charm and modern convenience.  Boston must maintain this balance to ensure it is a city people want to visit and call home. Lessons from the 20th Century news stories will help us understand how Boston can continue to develop its urban vitality.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 5-hour walking tour walks through the 20th century newspaper headlines of Boston. See the places where the famous and infamous events took place that shaped a city and impacted the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stops include: Charles Street Jail, St. Joseph's Church, The Erich Lindemann Mental Health Center, the Molasses Flood, Howard Athenaeum (Old Howard Theater), The Adams Courthouse, Rose Kennedy Greenway, The Freedom Trail, Old and New City Hall, United Shoe Building, Chinatown, and Cocoanut Grove.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;20th Century people and events covered include:  World Wars I &amp;amp; II, Korean War, Vietnam War &amp;amp; Ho Chi Minh, Malcolm X, Amelia Earhart, Calvin Coolidge, John F. Kennedy, Cardinal O'Connell, Sacco &amp;amp; Vanzetti, the Brinks Robbery, the Boston Celtics, Boston's infamous 20th Century mayors including James Michael Curley, Urban Development, Telecommunications, Public Transportation, and the impact of the Automobile.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A lunch break will be taken at noon at Faneuil Hall Marketplace. $15 per person ($6 for &lt;a href="http://www.bostonbyfoot.org/join/member/" target="_blank"&gt;Boston By Foot members&lt;/a&gt;). Tickets may be purchased directly from your guides.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a group of people with Boston By Foot bags, pins and shirts.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Justin Winsor</member_name><member_id>7593944</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Olivia - BBF Guide</member_name><member_id>7693825</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224676619000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Bostonians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonbyfoot</urlname><id>1214263</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston By Foot Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215901376000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Big Foot: Walking the 20th Century News Headlines in Boston</name><id>8329033</id><headcount>93</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220276700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonbyfoot/events/8329033/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/8/global_5230056.jpeg</photo_url></item>