<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Let's start off the week with a Monday Evening Walk in the Park @ Pond Meadow Park!  This is one of our favorite walking locations.  We usually donate a portion of our event fees to the upkeep of PMP.  We will be meeting on the Braintree side of PMP at the top of the path where the Bike Path Rules are posted immediately next to the parking lot next to the map and ranger station.  More than half of those who voted in the Poll stated they could meet us as early as 6pm (about 1/4 said they could meet even earlier) and folks have been asking for earlier events, hence the 6pm start time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Please Note: There are only two entrances to PMP - in Braintree and Weymouth.  There is only one place to meet on the path and that's where the Braintree and Weymouth paths converge.  If we walk against the flow of traffic and you will be more than 10 minutes late you could potentially meet us at the merge as we will wait 5-10 minutes for late (Yes RSVP) arrivals, and within 5-10 minutes of our departure we will pass the convergence of the paths.  However, if we walk the right away we won't pass that point until almost 1/2 hour into our walk.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The loop is 1.6 miles, with the walk to and from the parking lot it is 1.9 miles.  It takes about 35-40 minutes to walk the loop.  This is taking place early enough for us to be able to do two laps which will total 3.2 miles, if we so desire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great Walk for those planning to participate in the 5k Training.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If this time is too early/late for you and you would like to walk PMP please note it in your RSVP so we may note your feedback for scheduling future walks and events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, July 13th, 2009&lt;br /&gt;5:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Pond Meadow Park&lt;br /&gt;470 Liberty Street, Braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee: Annual Members - FREE, Members and Guests - $2 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizer(s): Angela &amp;amp; ??  (If anyone is interesting in co-organizing, please e-mail me!  This is one of the few walks that will still take place w/o a co-org.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: At  least 6 Yes RSVPs by 12pm/Noon on Friday, July 10th.  Attendance is unlimited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by NOON on Monday, July 13th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inclement Weather: Heavy rains will cancel.  We will walk if it is overcast or there is a slight drizzle.  Please plan to bring a lightweight jacket with a hood just in case.  (We will do our best to notify everyone if this event is cancelled by 1pm on the day of the walk.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree.  Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station.  Follow Union Street to the first set of lights.  Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street.  Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary.  Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street.  (This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.)  PMP is 500 feet up on the Right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE NOTE:  We recommend you park outside of the gate, as the gates are locked at approximately 7pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet by the flagpole near the ranger station and map.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247693956000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246923895000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Evening Walk in the Park</name><id>10817078</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247520600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/10817078/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/8/global_3818056.jpeg</photo_url></item>