<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 York St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.311540</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203- 562-5694</phone><name>Toad's Place</name><city>New Haven</city><id>664418</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.929350</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The 11th annual 99.1 WPLR Shamrock &amp;amp; Roll 5k is being held on Sunday, March 2nd. It begins and ends at Toad's Place. What a great way to get in touch with the Irish in everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did this race last year and had a blast! There is usually free Guiness and music at the finish line. The course is a little hilly, but the music, food and Guiness make it all worth while.... besides, you'll have your friends at your side to keep you motivated....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.active.com/event_detail.cfm?EVENT_ID=1519108&amp;amp;CHECKSSO=1&amp;amp;RESET=0" target="_blank"&gt;CLICK HERE TO REGISTER&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each participant is responsible for his/her registration for the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please feel free to email me if you have questions, otherwise, I will email my cell number to all racers a day before the race.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** A few people have inquired about walking with pets during the race.... In checking the registration website, it doesn't say anything about either. I do remember some people walking the course last year, but don't remember dogs. Usually if the course is pet 'un-friendly' they would state it. Just remember that there are a lot of people doing this race, pet walkers would most likely be asked to start at the back of the pack and that the pet would most likely not be allowed in Toad's for the after-party. But otherwise, will leave the final judgement up to the pet-owner.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a green jacket in honor of my Irish Heritage and St. Patrick's Day</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204639487000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><why>It's that time of year when it's easy to find every reason NOT to excercise and I'm giving you a reason to lace up your shoes and get outside! The run is good for your heart, the laughter is good for your soul, and the Guiness is a bonus!!</why><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200436833000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Shamrock &amp; Roll 5k</name><id>7123724</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204466400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/7123724/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/c/global_3039644.jpeg</photo_url></item>