<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2 Ceres St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.078238</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Portsmouth Green Drinks.</name><city>Portsmouth </city><id>740315</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.756991</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Energy fans, do you like to talk &amp;quot;Energy&amp;quot; well come enjoy a get together every third Thursday of the month in Portsmouth for &amp;quot;Green Drinks&amp;quot; it is essential people coming together to talk about energy, sustainability, back to nature, etc.  There are speaker monthly, this month we will be welcoming Portsmouth Slow Foods as our guest speaker.  This is a great opportunity to learn how to eat more food that is grown and raised here on the Seacoast.  This is a great opportunity to get out and meet some like-minded folks. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Portsmouth Slow Foods &amp;quot;is a non-profit organization of people who love and respect food. We are farmers and gardeners, chefs and home cooks, and food lovers of all ages and backgrounds. We're working together to slow down the pace of life so that we can enjoy our local and regional food traditions, support local growers and food producers, get to know one another, and help make sure that good, clean, and fair food is available to everyone on the Seacoast. We host frequent potlucks, work on group projects, and present educational events. We're a local chapter of Slow Food USA and Slow Food International. We welcome all. Please join us!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226012451000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221046716000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portsmouth Green Drinks</name><id>8728377</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224194400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/8728377/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/0/global_5210896.jpeg</photo_url></item>