<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Wondering what to do on this late-summer Saturday afternoon? Wishing you could spend some time getting photos for the upcoming Monthly Meeting Challenge (Black and White)? Need to work off the hangover from the previous night's Main Street Gallery opening of our Yin and Yang photo show?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, the Seacoast Photographers Group has the answer for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 A group shoot around downtown Portsmouth, put together by Tim Golden, Joe DiMattia, and myself for the Southern NH Photographers Facebook group. There will be a couple dozen of your colleagues and friends, as well as several models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Joe and I have worked out two location areas, all within walking distance of the meeting spot. One includes alleys, grunge areas, and riverside spots while the other includes historic buildings, parks, and waterfront areas. We'll split the group and switch halfway through, so you'll have a chance to shoot both locations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at my office between 2:30 and 3PM. It's right next to the parking garage. Plenty of spaceto hang and wait, and plenty of bathrooms. Exit the garage at the Fleet Street entrance, turn left on Fleet Street, pass Gilley's, and then our building is the next one on the left. Don't be late or you'll have to scramble around to find us. OK, you can just call or text me and I'll tell you, but it'll cost a slice of pizza and a swig of Elmer T Lee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 What do you mean, "why"? A great day shooting interesting subjects in a beautiful location with friends and colleagues. That's why. Sheesh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Bring?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Wear layers of weather-appropriate clothing and comfortable shoes. Bring your camera and a portrait lens. If you have a PocketWizard, bring that, too, as we'll have strobes with softboxes and beauty dishes available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring snacks if you're inclined to get grumpy in the late afternoon, and a bottle of water if you like. There are only a bajillion restaurants and cafés in Portsmouth, so you can nosh as we go if you prefer to travel light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you plan on staying on toward sunset, consider bringing a tripod. We may shoot at the top of the garage (great views for free!) so you can probably leave it in the car until then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Info...&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The cost of $15 will be distributed evenly to all models that attend to offset time and travel costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come in the front door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>4289009</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>joe dimattia</member_name><member_id>10641381</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347973137000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Photography Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastPhotographers</urlname><id>1528260</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast Photographers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347465464000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Daytime Group Shoot in Portsmouth (with Models)</name><id>82057892</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347735600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastPhotographers/events/82057892/</event_url></item>