<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in how our universe is constructed, as well as our own multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy, this is the group for you!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will also learn how to reclaim your ancient birthright for ascension, and how to protect energetically against 2012 cosmic energies, which will otherwise cause devistating damage to our DNA which affects our spiritual capabilities as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details, click on the "Pages" tab above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time we&amp;nbsp; be viewing and discussing a DVD and illustrated handbook, called "Elements of Discovery", which includes the following fascinating information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1)&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;15-DIMENSIONAL ANATOMY&lt;/strong&gt; and the Key Components of the Divine Creation Process. In order to understand our place in the universe, we must have some basic understanding of how creation occurs and how we are connected to creation itself. By understanding the anatomy of the system we are experiencing within, we can begin to remember our connection to the hologram, we call reality, as well as our connection to Source. Also includes the personal 15 Dimensional Anatomy, key aspects of how that is created and how our personal anatomy is intricately connected and influenced by all of creation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Includes:&lt;/strong&gt; the Stair Step Creation process, Reality Fields, The Holographic Template, Kathara 12-Tree Grid, Hova Bodies, Axi-A-tonal Lines, Meridians, Chakras and Hara Line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;(2)&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;EXPLORING THE GOD WORLDS&lt;/strong&gt;. Once we can begin to remember the structure of our own anatomy and the system we are experiencing within, it then becomes important to gain a larger understanding of the larger energetic structures that Source creates to experience It Self. Understanding this structure allows us to get a better view of what it means to "be in heaven". Where is heaven and how do we get there? Is it just wishful thinking or is there really such a place. By the end of this presentation, we can begin to remember the absolute beauty of creation and the precise detail through which Source Eternally creates the process of manifestation and Ascension. We can remember that Ascension is not just something that we "hope" occurs but that it is something that is an organic process of the creation process itself and something that is "suppose" to occur for all life forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Includes:&lt;/strong&gt; Order, Intelligence, and Consciousness, Rules and Balances, Unifying the Polarities, The Ecka Maps, Veca and Ecka Code Lock Keys, The God-Worlds Multiplying, Radial Bodies and Eckasha God-Seed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(3)&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;strong&gt;COSMIC CLOCK&lt;/strong&gt;. The Cosmic Clock entails understanding Time Cycles and the different time cycles that occur naturally as part of reality fields, within the Time Matrix. Through understanding the interwoven time cycles of creation we can remember how things connect together, within the larger structure of our universe and the time matrix itself. This entails understanding of the Stair Step Creation Process, or how the energy of Source steps Itself down, to allow for manifestation to occur. Time Cycles explain the realities of Time Portals and how something like movement through space and time is quite possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Includes:&lt;/strong&gt; Time Cycles of our Planetary System, The Monadic Code, StarBorn and StarBurst Cycles, Time Flux, Arc of the Covenant Gate System StarFire and the Hub Worlds, StarFire Cycle and Expedited TakEyon Cycle Reset, The ManU&amp;nbsp; Window, Portals and Star Gates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, or to order this product, please bring up the following link: 
&lt;a href="http://www.azuritepress.com/products_us/eod.php"&gt;http://www.azuritepress.com/products_us/eod.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go up first driveway with Meetup sign, enter through front door and go downstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311130634000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Awakening Indigoes</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>IndigoInsights</urlname><id>1319438</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Indigo Insights: Awakening to our Full Potential</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306214530000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Elements of Discovery: Multi-Dimensional Anatomy, God Worlds, &amp; The Cosmic Clock</name><id>19501601</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311112800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/IndigoInsights/events/19501601/</event_url></item>