<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;** UPDATE **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As of 3pm on Friday, 10/31, the address of the party has been emailed to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; RSVP's. If you are RSVP'ing after this time and wish to attend, call me (Ben) at 203-554-5144 for the address.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So it’s Halloween, and you’re an adult. Your choices are to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A) sit around your home while hordes of screaming urchins repeatedly knock on your door, demanding that you ransom the egg-lessness of your personal property for the treats that you’d rather keep for yourself, all the while envying the candy-grubbing fun they’re having&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;B) go to a Halloween party at a bar or club, get drunk on crappy beer, black out and wake up in a jail cell to find yourself in the company of the Addams family, slutty catwoman, Iron Man and a giant phallus&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;C) go to the NHC Halloween party at Antoinette’s place and have a rollicking good time in the company of your friends in the NHC. Not to mention Mr. Adams, Mr. Daniels, and Mr. Beam. Yes, the real treats. The treats that you never got as a snotty-nosed, Ninja Turtle costume-wearing brat back in the day. The treats that, if you have enough, always lead to tricks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So what’s it gonna be?? (the answer’s C! C!!!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wear a costume. Or not. Your choice. But anyone that shows up looking like him or herself, or even a reasonable facsimile of him or herself, will have to draw straws to see who will be given the costume of….Edward 40-hands! Don’t know what that is? Look it up. Then go get a real costume ready. :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And maybe we’ll have a best costume contest. Why not? The prize will be a bottle of…something. Don’t know yet. The judge will be our hostess, Antoinette. Fair warning: If you dress up like Jeter, you might find that you win, but you also might find that she won’t let you leave. ;-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring some snacks to share, and a bottle or ten of your favorite adult beverage. Spooky punch will be provided.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Antoinette’s address in Hamden will be sent out to “Yes” and “Maybe” RSVP’s on the afternoon of the 31st. In the meantime, if you have any questions, you can email me (Ben).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>33</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225670926000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224020843000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The NHC’s Scary-Ass Fun-As-Hell Halloween Fiesta Spooktacular</name><id>8962044</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225497600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8962044/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/9/a/global_5877226.jpeg</photo_url></item>