<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be a single day trip of 21 miles. Long carspot and a second car needed. I want to go with capable hikers - please already be in shape before the hike - not lead on this journey. Email me if you have any questions on the trip. I suggest this not be your first 20-mile hike ever.   I have copied from Michael Blair (thanks even though I didnt ask) and modified a list of gear:  Below is a list describing the minimum clothing and equipment required to participate in this event. If you show up without it you will not be allowed to participate.   Footwear: Hiking boots/Trail shoes. Waterproof gaiters are optional.  Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater - ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON.  Outerwear: Waterproof/windproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants.  Food: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, Water: 2 to 3 quarts of water, we will hopefully find a spot or two to run filters Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Trekking poles. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Waterproof cover for your pack.   NOTE- since this location is off of most of our maps, I will provide a photocopy for your reference -- but you still need a compass.  You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip. I will bring a group first aid kit that contains basic items but you will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emily Singer</member_name><member_id>7452900</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306294215000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306111857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2nd Annual Wapack Trail End-to-End Traverse</name><id>19332731</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306112400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/19332731/</event_url></item>