<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>YES that is Midnight showing!!

Talk about Paranormal Activity.

A low-budget horror film drawing comparisons to the Blair Witch Project is creating big buzz with a unique marketing campaign.

Users of micro-blogging site Twitter are using their influence to 'demand' that Paranormal Activity — which cost $15,000 US to make, according to Rolling Stone — be screened in their city.

Paranormal Activity — written, directed and edited by Oren Peli, whose only previous credits are for a video game, according to Internet movie database IMDB — is about a couple disturbed by something that goes bump in the night.

Currently showing in only 19 American states, and one Canadian province, the website for Paranormal Activity allows viewers to click on a button, select their country and city, and enter their e-mail address and verification code to request that the film open there.

If 1,000,000 visitors 'demand' the film, it will open nationwide, making it the 'first-ever major film release decided by you,' the site says. Nearly half a million 'demands' were made by Tuesday night.

The film became a trending topic on Twitter Tuesday night. Tweets were a mix of users asking friends if they want to see the movie, users asking where they can download the movie, and users asking just what exactly the movie is.

User @raefabulous wrote: "Paranormal Activity is trending...extremely odd seeing as how today was the first I'd ever even heard of it"

The marketing campaign seems to be working, according to another user.

"All this talk about Paranormal Activity is gaining my interest. The media hype is working!"
Here's the trailer:
&lt;xobject width="425" height="344"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/RXkMo092Uug&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1&amp;" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="344" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>in lobby</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259529780000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254946204000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paranormal Activity</name><id>11574073</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255060800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/11574073/</event_url></item>