<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mystic Valley Parkway </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.419809</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Green by Condon Shell on the Mystic River</name><city>Medford</city><id>1765791</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.141887</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This plein-air outing is part of the &lt;a href="http://medfordfestival.org"&gt;Medford on the Mystic Arts Festival&lt;/a&gt;, a collection of events during the entire month of October. Our activity will be included in a larger event on Saturday, October 22nd, called the Mystic River Celebration at the Condon Shell in Medford Square. So please mark your calendar for Sat. Oct. 22 (rain date: 10/23) for a day of productivity! =) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Our rough schedule for the day is: set up your workspace around 10am; work at your own pace. At 2pm, we'll gather at the Condon Shell green for an informal peer critique session. I'm guessing most of us will want to wrap up for the day at that point. Hopefully that sounds reasonable to everyone. Feel free to set up earlier if you work better that way. The Celebration itself runs 11am-4pm and will have kids' activities, music, etc. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Hopefully you won't mind if folks wander over and visit you as you work. The festival's theme is the Mystic River, so I was hoping we might sort of clump ourselves near the Shell/River/Footbridge vicinity. It would also give us some moral support to at least be in easy walking distance from one another.&amp;nbsp; Of course you are free to choose whatever Medford Square subject inspires you - you are the artist! When you are situated, let me know where you are so I can mark it out on a map of the square and post the map at the Condon Shell. That way people who are interested in seeing you at work can find you. With luck, the uniqueness of the circumstances surrounding our project will lend it some added interest and value to potential buyers. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 An exhibit of the completed pieces will be held on Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday, Oct. 29-30, 1-4 pm at the &lt;a href="http://www.royallhouse.org/"&gt;Royall House and Slave Quarters&lt;/a&gt; in Medford. If you plan to participate in the exhibit, please let me know ASAP so I can have a count as space is limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you plan to sell your piece at the exhibit, please price it to include 25% of the selling price as a commission split between the Royall House Association (15%) and CACHE Medford (10%), the festival organizer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://studiojcd.com/PleinAirArtistGuidelines.pdf"&gt;Please download this PDF for the full artist guidelines.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319394171000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>painter-84</urlname><id>576650</id><group_lat>42.4500007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Plein Air Artists Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309306151000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Medford Square landmarks during October citywide festival</name><id>23895081</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319292000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/painter-84/events/23895081/</event_url></item>