<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.349976</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-292-0080</phone><name>Caprice Lounge/Underbar</name><city>Boston </city><id>725513</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065216</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Depuis le lancement des Boston French Party , nous avons reçu de nombreuses demandes pour organiser des soirées le week-end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afin de vous remercier de votre présence ces 15 derniers mois,  c'est  chose faite: le lancement officiel du Boston French Friday aura lieu Vendredi 10 Octobre, à l'Underbar, à partir de 22H30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pour commencer cette série, nous avons l'honneur de recevoir Marco Peruzzi, DJ originaire de Marseille, légende de la nuit New-Yorkaise et membere éminent de la &amp;quot;French Touch&amp;quot; depuis qu'il a repris avec son frère le très célèbre Pink Elephant de New York dont il est le DJ résident.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nous vous attendons nombreux et nombreuses pour montrer à Marco Peruzzi que les Français de Boston savent faire la fête et honorer un DJ Français de classe mondiale comme il se doit !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since we started the Boston French Party in July 2007, we have been asked to organize parties on the week-ends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to thank you for your continuous trust over the last 15 months, we are now organizing parties on the week-ends! The first official Boston French Friday will be held next week, Friday October 10, at Underbar, from 10:30PM on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To make this party unforgettable, we brought &amp;quot;la creme&amp;quot;of the DJs: Marco Peruzzi, the resident DJ from Pink Elephant in New York. Originally from Marseille, Marco Peruzzi has been, with the help of his brother, making the Pink Elephant one of the most famous clubs in New York, and the house of the &amp;quot;French Touch&amp;quot; in Manhattan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us on Friday to show Marco Peruzzi that Boston knows how to party and to honour a world class French DJ !&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julien</member_name><member_id>1573841</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225240603000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Francophones</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>voulezvous</urlname><id>541017</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Voulez-vous français Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223249414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston French Friday!</name><id>8903236</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1223692200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/voulezvous/events/8903236/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/a/d/global_5759805.jpeg</photo_url></item>