<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Middletown</address_2><address_1>85 Miner Hill Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06457</zip><lat>41.549698</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miner Hill Golf Course</name><city>Middletown</city><id>567976</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674248</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>ADV TIX DISCOUNT</description><amount>100.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>GOLF 102 - Scramble Tournament Playing Lesson – for less than $17/hour&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DON’T PAY $75 per hour for inferior lessons when you can get GOLF 101 Lessons for less than $17 per hour!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your spot today – visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;Have you always wanted to play Golf? Do you want to improve your Golfing Skills and play better?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GOLF 102 takes you out on the Golf Course with our Certified Golf Teaching Professional to help you improve your Golf skills -while you play 9 holes in Tournament Scramble.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GOLF 102 gives you personalized playing lessons that will help with all aspects of your game. Each GOLF 102 lessons in 2 full hours – and as an added bonus – keep playing golf FREE of charge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 GOLF 102 lesson plus FREE Golf is $40&lt;br /&gt;3 GOLF 102 lessons plus FREE Golf is $100 (less than $17 per hour)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lessons are held on Wednesdays 5:30pm to 7:30pm –&lt;br /&gt;After your GOLF 102 Lesson - continue Golfing for FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Classes are held at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Miner Hills Golf Course&lt;br /&gt;85 Miner Hills Drive&lt;br /&gt;Middletown, CT 06457&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exit 20 off I-91 Country Club Road&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10 minutes from Hartford * 10 minutes from New Haven&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read about Golf 101 in the Hartford Courant: &lt;br /&gt;Visit &lt;a href="http://www.courant.com/features/hc-golf-lessons.artaug15,0,2543524.story" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.courant.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Connecticut, Massachusetts, New York and New Jersey, people have been taking advantage of &lt;br /&gt;the GOLF 101 and GOLF 102 low price for quality Golf lessons!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reserve your spot today – visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learn to Golf and Improve Your Skills Without Breaking The Bank with Golf 101 and Golf 102 Lessons &lt;br /&gt;- 6 Hours of Hands On Lessons for Only $100 (includes Golf Balls, Golf Clubs and ALL FEES) &lt;br /&gt;- That is less than $17/hour for quality Golf Lessons from a Certified Teaching Professional!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– 6 Hours of hands on group lessons for only $100 (less than $17 per hour) with a Certified Teaching Golf Professional  - small class size of 9 people gives you personal attention&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Includes clubs and all course fees * Choose any 3 classes to fit your schedule &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2009, more than 100 New Golfers graduated from Golf 101 lessons * 2010 Classes are filling up quickly! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;· We will notify you of any postponements and to reschedule your makeup class *&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GOLF 102 is designed to give you real life Scramble Tournament Playing experience with Playing Lessons with our Certified Golf Teaching Professional Instructor guiding you through the Golf Scramble with &lt;br /&gt;Golfing Playing Lessons to take you out on the Golf Course and improve your Golf Skills with real life experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you want to prepare for an upcoming Golf Tournament or game&lt;br /&gt;or if you just want to improve your Golf Swing and golfing Skills, Golf 102Golf Tournament provides you with real life Golfing experience that can only come from playing in a Scramble Golf Tournament. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an added bonus to your Golf 102 Scramble Tournament Playing Lessons, you can continue Golfing at no extra charge after you finish your Golf 102 Playing Lesson on this beautiful 9 hole Golf course in Middletown, CT Connecticut&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Reserve your spot today – visit &lt;a href="http://www.GolfLessonsCT.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.GolfLesson...&lt;/a&gt; or call (860) 436-9449&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet the GOLF 101 Instructor at the clubhouse</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282171736000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Classy CT Match Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Match-Singles-Events</urlname><id>357950</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>CTMatch Singles Events Music Dance Speed Dating Golf Comedy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281924508000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GOLF 102 - Scramble Tournament Playing Lesson – for less than $17/hour </name><id>14433563</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282167000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Match-Singles-Events/events/14433563/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/7/a/global_16478682.jpeg</photo_url></item>