<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt; We are going to Rock Bottom (not Jacob Wirth's as I wanted) after Alice. Care to go? Sign up at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/calendar/12782656/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt; so I can fine tune my dinner reservation I made for twenty people, scaling it up or down. Can't find us before or after the show? Just sign up now and head over after. It is going to be quite chaotic this opening day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Care to battle the crowd attempting to see this movie on opening day, say, a 7:00 pm show, getting in line around 6:15 pm? It might be difficult for all of us to sit together, but we can invade Rock Bottom afterwards. Tickets are not yet available for sale on Fandango, but it might be good to purchase tickets online when they come out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Purchase tickets&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.fandango.com/purchase/movietickets/process03/ticketboxoffice.aspx?tid=AAPNV&amp;amp;mid=130209&amp;amp;row_count=1707586638"&gt;https://www.fandango....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Alice in Wonderland&lt;/b&gt; in Disney Digital 3D (But no IMAX yet, boo!): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Opens March 5, 2010 | Runtime:1 hr. 49 min&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From Fandango&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/aliceinwonderland_114678/movieoverview"&gt;http://www.fandango.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;From Walt Disney Pictures and visionary director Tim Burton comes an epic 3D fantasy adventure 'Alice in Wonderland', a magical and imaginative twist on some of the most beloved stories of all time. Johnny Depp stars as the Mad Hatter and Mia Wasikowska as 19-year-old Alice, who returns to the whimsical world she first encountered as a young girl, reuniting with her childhood friends: the White Rabbit, Tweedledee and Tweedledum, the Dormouse, the Caterpillar, the Cheshire Cat, and of course, the Mad Hatter. Alice embarks on a fantastical journey to find her true destiny and end the Red Queen’s reign of terror. The all-star cast also includes Anne Hathaway, Helena Bonham Carter, and Crispin Glover&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be in the lobby of the AMC Lowes Boston Common starting at 6:00 pm casually holding up a red MEETUP sign, trying not to look like a tour guide. He was thinking of waiting fifteen minutes, then jumping in what he is guessing will be a massive line forming at 6:15 pm. Only can make it last minute? No problem! Grab a seat wherever, and we can regroup in the hallway near the exit of the auditorium, wait for a bit, then hit Rock Bottom, two blocks from the theater. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show will be in Digital 3D, but as of yet, AMC Boston Common does not yet have an IMAX Theater. It's &amp;quot;Coming Soon&amp;quot; as it has been for the past year. Yes, there are IMAX options in &amp;quot;Greater Boston&amp;quot; but on a weekday T.J. finds it too difficult to get his car in Braintree and head north fighting traffic (boo, traffic!) to the Reading or Norwood Jordan's Furniture. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Tim Burton's Alice in Wonderland, according to Wikipedia&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alice_in_Wonderland_(2010_film"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In this extension of Lewis Carroll's original stories Alice Kingsley, now 19, attends a party at a Victorian estate shortly after the death of her beloved father. The formal affair, unbeknownst to Alice, is an engagement party planned by her mother and sister. Just as the arrogant and boorish Lord Hamish Ascot proposes to Alice under a gazebo and before the eyes of hundreds of snooty society-types, Alice spots a white rabbit wearing a waistcoat and pocket watch. In shock and confusion, she runs off into a maze and follows the White Rabbit through it. She eventually tumbles down a rabbit hole into Underland, more commonly referred to as &amp;quot;Wonderland&amp;quot; by its inhabitants. It turns out she had visited this place ten years earlier but had entirely forgotten about it. She then reunites with her childhood friends, including the Mad Hatter, who explains to Alice that they need her help in over-throwing the Red Queen. This evil character has taken control of Wonderland from her benevolent sister, the White Queen. Alice is also told that she is the only one who can slay the Jabberwock, the dragon who terrorizes the inhabitants of Wonderland under the rule of the Red Queen. Alice then embarks on an adventure of self-discovery in the process of saving Wonderland and her friends there from both the Jabberwock and the Red Queen's reign of terror&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... The film has been rated PG by the MPAA &amp;quot;for fantasy action/violence involving scary images and situations and for a smoking caterpillar&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A collection of Tim Burton directed films from IMDB (Internet Movie Database):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000318/"&gt;http://www.imdb.com/n...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Pee-wee's Big Adventure (1985) &lt;br /&gt;* Beetle Juice (1988) &lt;br /&gt;* Batman (1989) &lt;br /&gt;* Edward Scissorhands (1990) &lt;br /&gt;* Tim Burton's The Nightmare Before Christmas (1993) (Not a director, but a producer)&lt;br /&gt;* Batman Returns (1992) &lt;br /&gt;* Corpse Bride (2005) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... please ignore Mars Attacks, Planet of the Apes, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, and Big Fish. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Jacob Wirths&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;37 Stuart St, Boston (a block and a half from the movie theater)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jacobwirth.com/"&gt;http://www.jacobwirth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dinner Menu&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.jacobwirth.com/pages/menu_dinner.html"&gt;http://www.jacobwirth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beer List&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.jacobwirth.com/pages/beer.html"&gt;http://www.jacobwirth...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>27</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268078809000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266421916000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Alice in Wonderland (Opening Day) @ AMC Lowes Boston Common</name><id>12627793</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267833600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12627793/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/5/global_13166229.jpeg</photo_url></item>