<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>cherry+webb lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02790</zip><lat>41.513925</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-644-5522</phone><name>westport town beach</name><city>westport</city><id>757593</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069237</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since we get an extra hour of sleep on Halloween night, why not spend some of Sunday outside in the almost 60 degree weather?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If people think they'll still be sleeping off Halloween fun at 11am, let me know and I can push the time back a bit.  Trying to capture the best of the sunlight hours we get these days. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fall River - Freetown state forest is huge and gorgeous, its amazing that its part of Fall River, though it feels like worlds away.  I'm thinking of doing a semi-short hike to the Ledge, a beautiful rock cropping over a lake.  I haven't hiked in that part of the forest, though I'm estimating it to be only a few miles (total) from the trail maps. If its significantly shorter, I'll probably explore the other trails too.   I might bring a light lunch/snack and sit by the lake for a bit if its nice enough, and anyone's welcome to do the same.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just a chance to explore a new area, get out and meet people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is hunting season so I'd recommend any one who can to wear bright orange (ideal!) or yellow.  If there's at least a few of us with reflective gear, we should be all set. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More information, trail maps, etc: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/free.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the Bell-Rock Rd. Parking area (Super Easy to Get To!):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 195 (Providence) - take Exit 5 for Rt. 79&lt;br /&gt;Or, from Southern areas, take Rt. 24 North &amp;amp; you'll merge onto 79&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once on Rt 79 North / Rt. 24 North, take Exit 9 to continue on 79 North&lt;br /&gt;Off the exit, go right onto Main St/79 North&lt;br /&gt;Take your 2nd right onto High street and continue down High Street about 2 miles.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;High Street becomes Bell Rock Rd. and there is a parking area not too far down on the Left hand side.  I believe it is Parking Area &amp;quot;B&amp;quot; on the trail maps if anyone looks at them online.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257606354000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256683033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking - Fall River/Freetown State Forest</name><id>11727080</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257091200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/11727080/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/8/c/global_5586652.jpeg</photo_url></item>