<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351654</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>33 Harrison Ave</name><city>Boston</city><id>4579062</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061310</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Greater Boston Alliance for 9/11 Truth and Justice presents Barbara Honegger and Mark Basile along with hot cider and soup Sunday, Dec. 4th, 2:00 pm, Encuentro 5, 33 Harrison Ave, 5th fl. Chinatown Barbara will speak with powerpoint about her interviews with military personnel eyewitnesses to the events of 9/11/2001 at the Pentagon&amp;#151;including evidence of major explosions in the Pentagon prior to the impact of an aircraft or missile. Mark, featured in the new Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth DVD, Experts Speak Out, will present scientific evidence that the Twin Towers and Building 7 were brought down by pre-set explosives (including the new explosive at that time, military-grade nanothermite), not by the impact of the planes and resultant fires. Barbara Honegger, M.S., served as White House Policy Analyst and Special Assistant to the Assistant to the President in the Domestic Policy Council, and for more than a decade (2000-2011) was the Senior Military Affairs Journalist with the Naval Postgraduate School, the premiere science and national security graduate research university of the Department of Defense. Ms. Honegger is the author of the pioneering book October Surprise, first to reveal the origins of the Iran/Contra scandal; and was the only expert witness testifying solely on the Pentagon at the Sept. 2011 Toronto International Hearings on the Events of 9/11/2001. Her interview with Pentagon survivor-witness April Gallop served as a key basis for a critical 9/11 lawsuit filed against Donald Rumsfeld and Dick Cheney Dec., 2008 in NY. Mark Basile, B.S. Chemical Engineering Worcester Polytechnic Institute 1986. His skills for analyzing 9/11: Materials characterization with electron microscope with x-ray fluorescence for elemental analysis, metallurgical techniques, thermal analysis with differential scanning calorimeter and other techniques. Analysis of constituents and contaminants. Developing optically based chemical detectors for liquid chromatography. Commercialization of detectors including tunable fluorescence, tunable and multichannel uv/vis absorbance. He can explain 9/11 analysis so the non-scientist can understand. Come learn, question, debate, discuss, socialize, and enjoy soup and cider.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan Serpa</member_name><member_id>15067391</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323029386000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322350167000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hot cider and soup with Barbara Honegger and Mark Basile </name><id>42459272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323025200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/42459272/</event_url></item>