<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>315 Morse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02062</zip><lat>42.170719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-278-8977</phone><name>Hibachi Steak House</name><city>Norwood</city><id>247437</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.198219</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group and their Guests as we celebrate our 4th Anniversary w/ a fun and entertaining hibachi-style dinner at the Hibachi Steakhouse off Route 1 in Norwood!  Save your appetite for this delicious dinner and join us for our 4th Anniversary Celebration in our own private room!  Members of the SSDOMG ranked this as one of their top SSDOMG Favorite Restaurnats and the Organizer Team couldn't agree more.  We'll be in the back function room.  Once you arrive and pick out your seat feel free to mix and mingle as we will be ordering closer to 7pm as they start feeding us shortly after we order and we want to give everyone a chance to socialize before we are entertained by the chefs cooking our meals right in front of us.  Join us for a couple of hours of celebrating, fun, socializing, entertainment and food!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;+++Prices range from $4-$10 for appetizers and $10-$30 for entrees.  Our entire party must be present to order and eat.  Due to the set-up of the tables you will generally be socializing with those seated in your immediate proximity, however, the room is ours for the evening.  Therefore, we encourage you to arrive on time or a few minutes early to have the opportunity to socialize and mingle.  We will do our usual round of introductions once everyone's drink order has been placed.  We do have the private function room for our Group so socializing should be fairly easy before and after our food is prepared and enjoyed.+++&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are building in some extra social time similar to that of a 'cocktail hour' in that we will be placing our orders around 7pm ot give folks 15-20 minutes to mix and mingle before taking our seats for dinner.  You are all in for a fun and entertaining evening - in more ways than one - so don't miss out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fun &amp;amp; Entertaining 4th Anniversary Dinner&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, August 26th, 2010 @ 6:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Hibachi Steakhouse&lt;br /&gt;315 Morse Street&lt;br /&gt;(Off Route 1 South)&lt;br /&gt;Norwood, MA 02062&lt;br /&gt;781-278-8977&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hibachistkhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hibachistkhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hibachistk...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Angela &amp;amp; The SSDOMG Organizer Team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; All Members are FREE.  Guests: TBD (probably $2).  Annual Membership is $10.  This is the last chance to become a 2010 Annual Member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt;  Max of 28 people, which is the capacity of the room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; 1 per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility:&lt;/b&gt; This is handicap-accessible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, August 25th @ 8pm (All Yes RSVP changes to No after this time will be considered a No-Show unless you contact Angela directly.  Please see our No-Show policy on the About pages.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Inclement Weather:&lt;/b&gt; We will be there come rain, sun or thunderstorms!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to Hibachi Steakhouse:&lt;/b&gt; Take &lt;b&gt;Route 95/128&lt;/b&gt; North to &lt;b&gt;Exit 15B (Route 1 South)&lt;/b&gt; toward Norwood. Go South on Route 1 for approximately 4.5 miles. Hibachi Steakhouse is located at &lt;b&gt;215 Morse St&lt;/b&gt;, reached by turning &lt;b&gt;left&lt;/b&gt; off &lt;b&gt;Route 1&lt;/b&gt;. They have a &lt;b&gt;large sign&lt;/b&gt; that is clearly visible from Route 1. If you find yourself passing the &lt;b&gt;Norwood Stop &amp;amp; Shop&lt;/b&gt; on your right, you have gone about &lt;b&gt;1/2 mile too far&lt;/b&gt; and need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll also include a Mapquest link to bring up directions from Borders in Braintree that most of our members should be able to pick up from the Braintree Rotary: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/Directions-from-Borders" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/Di...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the Lobby area.  The reservation is under "Angela" and the "SSDOMG/Meetup."  You may find us at our tables in the function room in the back room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283698635000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281038883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fun &amp; Entertaining 4th Anniversary Dinner</name><id>14332013</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282861800000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/14332013/</event_url></item>