<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Salt: A World History&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;by Mark Kurlansky&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Discussion moderated by:&lt;/strong&gt; Abdul&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/3/5/5/event_37734101.jpeg" width="199" height="302" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;Mark Kurlansky, the bestselling author of Cod and The Basque History of the World, here turns his attention to a common household item with a long and intriguing history: salt. The only rock we eat, salt has shaped civilization from the very beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of humankind. A substance so valuable it served as currency, salt has influenced the establishment of trade routes and cities, provoked and financed wars, secured empires, and inspired revolutions. Populated by colorful characters and filled with an unending series of fascinating details, Kurlansky's kaleidoscopic history is a supremely entertaining, multi-layered masterpiece.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Unbroken: A World War II Story of Survival, Resilience, and Redemption&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;by Laura Hillenbrand&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Discussion moderated by:&lt;/strong&gt; Sherri&lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;
  &lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/3/9/b/event_37734171.jpeg" width="200" height="303" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;On a May afternoon in 1943, an Army Air Forces bomber crashed into the Pacific Ocean and disappeared, leaving only a spray of debris and a slick of oil, gasoline, and blood. Then, on the ocean surface, a face appeared. It was that of a young lieutenant, the plane&amp;#146;s bombardier, who was struggling to a life raft and pulling himself aboard. So began one of the most extraordinary odysseys of the Second World War.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The lieutenant&amp;#146;s name was Louis Zamperini. In boyhood, he&amp;#146;d been a cunning and incorrigible delinquent, breaking into houses, brawling, and fleeing his home to ride the rails. As a teenager, he had channeled his defiance into running, discovering a prodigious talent that had carried him to the Berlin Olympics and within sight of the four-minute mile. But when war had come, the athlete had become an airman, embarking on a journey that led to his doomed flight, a tiny raft, and a drift into the unknown.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Ahead of Zamperini lay thousands of miles of open ocean, leaping sharks, a foundering raft, thirst and starvation, enemy aircraft, and, beyond, a trial even greater. Driven to the limits of endurance, Zamperini would answer desperation with ingenuity; suffering with hope, resolve, and humor; brutality with rebellion. His fate, whether triumph or tragedy, would be suspended on the fraying wire of his will. In her long-awaited new book, Laura Hillenbrand writes with the same rich and vivid narrative voice she displayed in Seabiscuit. Telling an unforgettable story of a man&amp;#146;s journey into extremity, Unbroken is a testament to the resilience of the human mind, body, and spirit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Abdul</member_name><member_id>2464273</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312240983000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-458</urlname><id>228874</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301956644000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>July Book Discussion: Salt and Unbroken</name><id>17182691</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1311719400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-458/events/17182691/</event_url></item>