<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>212 Hampshire St.,  212 Hampshire St., Inman Sq., Cambridge</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.373707</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ryles Jazz Club</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>189977</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.099915</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>---------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Last week, there was a a huge fire in Peabody. Two of our own, Grey German, Becca and their new baby lost their house, car and all their possessions in this fire. The really good news is that everyone is safe and sound. Apparently Becca and the baby got out as the alarms were going off. The bad news is that pretty much everything burned up.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Salsa Sundays is hosting a benefit this Sunday with all the profits from the evening going towards helping our good friends Grey and Becca. We're cooking up a lot of great ways to support on Sunday. In addition to your entry fee going to help out, we'll be having a raffle with prizes from Boston's dance community. There will be prizes from Metamovements, Salsa y Control, Hacha y Machete, Rumba y Timbal, Masacote Entertainment, and more To Be Annouced. Other raffle prizes will include some special services donated by members of our salsa community. Pay attention to your e-mail for more details during the week. We're working on some special performances for the night as well. Details throughout the week..&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Many of you know Grey as the Director of The Mambo Slaves, have taken lessons from him or just enjoyed his performances, social dancing and company. We're asking everyone to come out and support this Sunday. Bring your wallets and buy a raffle ticket or two. There's tons of great prizes and you'll be a part of a community helping their own. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Special Benefit....It's going to be a great party!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;See you all on Sunday,&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DJ Rob Suave&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know this is a last minute send, but hopefully you guys can make it.  I'm sure there will be many people there.  Unfortunately, most of my company and I will be out of town, so we can't make it, but we'll be there in spirit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ana :)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unfortunately I'll be out of town, but look for DJ Rob, also a  meetup member.  He'll be at the DJ booth :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213135545000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>It's for a very good cause</why><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212557450000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Salsa Benefit for Grey German &amp; Family</name><id>8075252</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212962400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/8075252/</event_url></item>