<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>157 Old Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02664</zip><lat>42.145061</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North River Art Soc</name><city>Marshfield Hills</city><id>6343912</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.739334</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry folks but this event has sold out.  No more space available.  If you are interested in future events of this nature, please let me know and we will plan an additional event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North River Art Society in Marshfield will host an all day Figure drawing/painting marathon on Sunday, May 6th. A total of 9 hours of Figure Drawing/painting starting at 10am and lasting until 8pm. The event will be broken into 3 sessions with varying formats so that everyone will be sure to get what they want at some point during the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 1: 10am-1pm &lt;br /&gt;

 This will be a split room session.The models are Kylie and Melanie.Melanie will be doing short poses on one side of the room while Kylie will do a long pose on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 2: 1:30-4:30pm &lt;br /&gt;

 We will have Ed ,Andrea, and Julia modelling together for this session.They will be in the center of the room and we will setup in the round.They will do 5 10 min poses to the first break and then pick one of those poses to do for the remaining time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Session 3: 5:00-8:00 &lt;br /&gt;

 The final session will be a split room like the first session.We have Rachel and Nicole as our models.Rachel will do short poses on one side while Nicole will do a long pose on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost: $25 for the day. For one session or all sessions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: Karl Nestelberger, &lt;br /&gt;

 email: karlnestelberger@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;

 phone: 508-641-7543&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: 157 Old Main St Marshfield Hills, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please Note: This should be a great event and it is open to everyone. No photography will be allowed. Please RSVP and let us know which sessions you plan to attend. Food and beverages will be available throughout the day but please feel free to bring something to share. More snacks always make for a better event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North River does have easels, but if your setup isn't too big, please feel free to bring your own.We will be tight on space so please think along the lines of french easels if possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't miss out on the fun. Hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>karl nestelberger</member_name><member_id>38295022</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336397264000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Art Models and Artists</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>NE-artists-models-group</urlname><id>408475</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0299987793</group_lon><name>New England Artists/Models Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334025115000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FULL - Registration closed.  10 hour Figure Drawing Event</name><id>59925552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336312800000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NE-artists-models-group/events/59925552/</event_url></item>