<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The AMC has decided to return to Canada again for August Camp.  I am providing you the information to attend but will not be there this year.  I am more than willing to answer any questions you have about August Camp and what to expect.  Please check out the photo album from last year's trip to see the amazing place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deposits will need to be in by January 1 as this trip will fill all four weeks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each year the &lt;b&gt;Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC)&lt;/b&gt; has a camping/hiking trip called &lt;b&gt;August Camp&lt;/b&gt;.  This years destination is Banff Alberta.  Last year I went on this trip and had an amazing time.  I am sending out this information as an FYI.  If you have more interest, go to &lt;a href="http://www.augustcamp.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.augustcamp...&lt;/a&gt;  for all the details.  I am not planning on attending this year.  I am not acting as a trip coordinator.  All reservations and payments are on you. If you would like to attend let me know and I can give you information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is information from their home page from the event:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Base camp is at Beaverfoot Lodge campground in the Beaverfoot Valley surrounded by stunning mountain scenery. Our location is between Field and Golden, British Columbia and is bordered by Yoho National Park to the north and Kootenay National Park to the south. Our activities will take us to Yoho, Banff, Kootenay, Glacier and Jasper National Parks with their snowcapped mountains, vast glaciers and ice fields, turquoise lakes, thundering waterfalls, wildflowers, hot springs and fossil beds.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;August Camp offers several hikes each day for all levels of ability. Car camping and backpacking excursions, river rafting, canoeing and kayaking are also planned. Delicious cooked meals and trail lunches are provided; great camaraderie and nightly campfires make for a memorable experience. Round trip transportation  between Camp and the Calgary International Airport (YYC) will be provided. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Applications are accepted beginning January 1, 2010 in the order in which they are received.&lt;br /&gt;Early registration is advised since some camp sessions were completely subscribed in 2009..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An AMC Tradition!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Week 1: July 16 - July 23  &lt;br /&gt;Week 2: July 23 - July 30&lt;br /&gt;Week 3: July 30 - Aug. 6  &lt;br /&gt;Week 4: Aug. 6 - Aug. 13&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rates , Reservation Information, and Refund Policy:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.augustcamp.org/acreservations2011.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.augustcamp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Suggested Reading:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.augustcamp.org/acsugreading2010.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.augustcamp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Address registration questions to:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trish Niece at 203-265-9584 before 9:00pm or&lt;br /&gt;Sue Keroes at 781-275-2536 before 9:00pm or&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;e-mail Registrar at registrar@augustcamp.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC):&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.outdoors.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note, a passport will be needed for this trip to Canada.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310836849000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291581631000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC August Camp to Banff  Canada</name><id>15649491</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310832000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/15649491/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/3/global_12379267.jpeg</photo_url></item>