<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gowen's Corner Plaza at Route 33 and Bayside</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03840</zip><lat>43.042721</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-436-5740</phone><name>The KRI Center for Consciousness Studies</name><city>Greenland</city><id>1518855</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.847672</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Connecting With Your Guides Through Journeywork&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; As a psychic medium, I am often asked by clients how to connect directly to your guides.&amp;nbsp; Many throughout the ages have achieved this through the Shamanic Journey.&amp;nbsp; A shamanic journey is a special state of trance consciousness that enables communication with the energy or spirit of the universe.&amp;nbsp; Through this practice you will discover and communicate with both animal and spirit guides.&amp;nbsp; In addition to these connections, you will be able to ask questions about yourself and your purpose, helping you to find guidance on your path.&amp;nbsp; The tools given to you during this three hour workshop will enable you to continue this technique on your own and will assist you on your spiritual growth.&amp;nbsp; When attending this class, please bring a blanket, water to drink, a pillow, an eye cover and a journal.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt; Suggested book to bring with you - Animal Spirit Guides by Steven D. Farmer, PhD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monday, July 11th from 6-9 PM - 10 spots available&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where - KRI, The Center for Consciousness Studies, 1 Bayside Rd, Unit 5, Greenland, NH
 &lt;br /&gt; Located in the Gowen&amp;rsquo;s Corner Plaza on Route 33 in Greenland.
 &lt;br /&gt; Directions - from I-95, take exit 3 to Route 33 West.&amp;nbsp; The Center is located 2.6 miles on the right at the corner of 33 and Bayside
 &lt;br /&gt; Space is limited, pre-registration required, cost - $45
 &lt;br /&gt; To register contact Isabeau at 603-973-2317&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the class visit 
&lt;a href="http://www.isabeauesby.com/Isabeau_Esby/Calendar.html"&gt;http://www.isabeauesby.com/Isabeau_Esby/Calendar.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From the I-95, take exit 3 (95 northbound) or exit 3B (southbound) to Route 33 W.  The Center will be 2.6 miles on the right, directly on the corner of 33 and Bayside, in the Gowen's Corner Plaza.  The entrance is just to the left of Bayside Custon F</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabeau Esby</member_name><member_id>5847842</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1310426118000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastParanormal</urlname><id>751976</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Seacoast Paranormal Research Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305771345000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Journeywork Class - Connect With Your Guides</name><id>18922311</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310421600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastParanormal/events/18922311/</event_url></item>