<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So the Flex SDK is open source now, but what does that mean to you? You are a Flex developer but you have never even looked at the code powering the Flex SDK.  This presentation is focused on Flex veterans as well as beginners who want to get their hands dirty with the inner workings of the Flex SDK. This will equip you with the knowledge to get started developing for the Flex framework itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will cover the following topics:&lt;br /&gt;- Resources to learn about the inner workings of the Flex SDK (Coding Conventions, Specs, etc...)&lt;br /&gt;- Subversion, ANT, Mustella... What they are, and how they are used with the Flex SDK.&lt;br /&gt;- Obtaining the Flex SDK source code.&lt;br /&gt;- Setting up Flex Builder for working with the Flex SDK.&lt;br /&gt;- Common pitfalls when getting set up.&lt;br /&gt;- Finding bugs to fix&lt;br /&gt;- How to run check-in tests.&lt;br /&gt;- How to submit a patch, creating diff files.&lt;br /&gt;- Getting involved in the community.. BugQuash, reviewing patches, spring cleaning the bug system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Presenter:&lt;br /&gt;Nate Beck, Senior Adobe Developer from T-Mobile&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nate Beck is a flasher / flexer from Seattle, WA. He has been playing around and working with Flash since 2001, and has been programming Flex since version 1.5 (2004). He loves the Flash platform so much that he usually ends up experimenting with Flash in his free time. He can be found frequently at Barnes &amp;amp; Noble browsing the computer programming section.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nate is currently the Senior Adobe Developer for T-mobile's retail research and development team.  His job is to quickly prototype time and money saving solutions for the company. Nate was also the lead Flash developer for Snapvine.com and has an extensive background in widget and social network development. Nate's widgets are loaded millions of times each day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nate also is an avid gamer, His Xbox Live gamer tag is Knaughty.  So if you play Halo or Tiger Woods Golf '09, hit him up. Oh, and if you see that gamer tag playing Viva Pinata… that's his wife (or so he says).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Recently, Nate has been posting a &amp;quot;Tip of the Day&amp;quot; on his blog (&lt;a href="http://blog.natebeck.net/tips-archive/" target="_blank"&gt;http://blog.natebeck....&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are looking to contact Nate, please do so through LinkedIn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Blog - &lt;a href="http://blog.natebeck.net" target="_blank"&gt;http://blog.natebeck....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * LinkedIn - &lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/jnbeck" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.linkedin.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Mason</member_name><member_id>4527001</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249603114000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Flex Developers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OnlineFlexMeetupGroup</urlname><id>934376</id><group_lat>41.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8199996948</group_lon><name>Online Flex Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247519967000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Getting Dirty with the Flex SDK</name><id>10867910</id><headcount>31</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248390000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OnlineFlexMeetupGroup/events/10867910/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/e/f/global_5719263.jpeg</photo_url></item>