<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This will be a fairly easy hike lasting about 3 hours.  It's not very steep or rugged and, weather permitting, the mountain affords wonderful views from the White Mountains to the&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ocean&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;And&lt;/span&gt; there &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;should&lt;/span&gt; be &lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;some&lt;/span&gt; nice &lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;fall&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;color&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/a/a/event_8764778.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;Meet in the parking lot at the base of the mountain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="http://www.agamenticus.org/recreation.html"&gt;Mount Agamenticus Conservation Region&lt;/a&gt; consists of more than 10,000 acres and is located within an additional 30,000-acre expanse of conservation land in southern Maine.  This land is comprised of a rich and unique coastal forest that supports the highest diversity of animal and plant species in all of Maine.  The mountain and the surrounding area provide residents with an ideal location for hiking, biking and sightseeing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;While most of Southern Maine is heavily developed, this stretch of conservation land is a natural treasure that will be preserved for the enjoyment of generations to come.  Mount A’s trails are for hikers, bikers, equestrians and ATV riders.  To ensure long-term trail quality and to protect against erosion, trails are designated for specific uses.  Trail signs, color blazes and the trail map tell which uses are permitted on each trail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.agamenticus.org/recreation.html" style="color : #441f13"&gt;Mount Agamenticus&lt;/a&gt; is one of the many lost ski resorts of New England. There still stands traces of the ski slopes and lift systems which are now merely relics.  The Mountain Top Lodge though still exists and has been kept open for groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time/location subject to change due to weather and other factors.  ALWAYS check for updates prior to leaving your house.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349661766000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349279682000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HikeAmenticus!</name><id>85305192</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349535600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/85305192/</event_url></item>