<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>About Appleton Farms&lt;br /&gt;Wander among crop fields and livestock pastures, wetlands and forest, at America’s oldest, continuously operating farm. A gift of Colonel Francis R. Appleton, Jr., and his wife Joan, Appleton Farms is one of the oldest continuously operating farms in the country, established and maintained by nine generations of the Appleton family.  Six miles of footpaths, bridle paths, and farm roads, some of which are part of the Bay Circuit Trail, crisscross the 698 acre farm.  This doesn't even include the 5.5 miles of grassy avenues that are the carriage paths or grass lands, which serve as a link in the Bay Circuit Trail and the &amp;quot;Discover Hamilton&amp;quot; trail system.  The Grass Rides encompass 255 acres.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're a bird lover like me, grasslands here harbor one of New England’s largest populations of bobolinks and meadowlarks.  The meadowlarks are here year-round, but unfortunately the bobolinks have begun their long migration to South America.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to bring &lt;br /&gt;Bring a &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;picnic lunch&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, water and bug spray.  Binoculars, a camera and sunscreen are also a good idea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dogs are not allowed on the farm as there are ground nesting birds and horses on some of the trails&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Hike &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;I would strongly recommend stopping to use the restroom before your arrival as they are located a little less than a mile from the parking area in the Carriage Barn in the Farmstead&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will leave promptly at 9:40. The hike will be about 4 miles long.  This will be a gentle-paced hike with a number of stops to enjoy nature.  Most of the focus will be on the farm or pasture land.  &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Remember to bring your lunch and towel or blanket with you on the trail as the picnic area is about a mile away from the car&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  We will picnic part way through the hike.  Toward the end of the hike, for those of you who are interested, we will walk a small loop through the wooded carriage paths or grass rides.  Keep in mind that this area can be very buggy- At the risk of sounding repetitive, I would definitely bring bug repellant for the hike, just to be safe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's usually based on an honor system, but members of the trustees of reservations are free whereas &lt;u&gt;nonmembers pay $3&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to learn more about Appleton Farms or print out a trail map, here's the link: &lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/appleton-farms.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note: We will meet in the &lt;u&gt;parking lot located on Highland Street&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Directions are below, but you should probably use Google or MapQuest also to get a better sense of it. The parking area is close to the intersection of Highland and Goodhue Street in Hamilton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: &lt;br /&gt;Highland St. parking area:Take I-95 North to Rte 128 North to Rte 1A North (exit 20A). Travel about 4.5 mi. north on Rt. 1A.  When you  pass Cutler Park on the left you are about 1/2 mile from your next turn.  Turn left onto Cutler Rd. (You will see the First Congregational Church on the corner).  Follow for 2.2 mi. At the intersection with Highland St., turn right, and right again into parking area (20 cars) that also serves Appleton Farms Grass Rides. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: &lt;br /&gt;Take I-95 South to exit 54 for MA-133 toward Georgetown/Rowley Follow Rte 133 to Rte 1A South. After about 2.2 miles start to look for the VERY SMALL Appleton Farms sign on your Right.  Turn Right onto Waldingfield Rd. Follow for about 3/4 of a mile and take the first and only left fork onto Goodhue Street.  (Keep in mind Goodhue Street is not marked).  Follow for about 1/2 mile and then turn left onto Highland Street. The parking area is about 1,000 feet up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to seeing some of you again and meeting some of you for the first time!&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in the parking lot with meetup stickers on.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>8</waitlist_count><updated>1283270273000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274627405000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Slow Appleton Farms Nature Walk- Please read full description</name><id>13568416</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283088600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/13568416/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/c/1/global_15222961.jpeg</photo_url></item>