<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Arch Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03431</zip><lat>42.938739</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Keene High School</name><city>Keene</city><id>563529</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.312463</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Student Scholars for 9/11 Truth &lt;br /&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;Monadnock 9/11 Truth Alliance&lt;br /&gt;present:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The New England 9/11 Symposium:&lt;br /&gt;Family Members and Researchers Speak Out&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, May 17th, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Keene High School,&lt;br /&gt;Keene, NH&lt;br /&gt;Admission $15&lt;br /&gt;Doors Open at 9:30 a.m. All Day Event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.911blogger.com/node/14630" target="_blank"&gt;A Message from Daniel Sunjata, star of FX's Rescue Me &lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In addition to Sunjata, the New England 9/11 Symposium will feature eight other spectacular guests!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bob McIlvaine, Sr&lt;/b&gt;. - McIlvaine lost his son, Bobby McIlvaine, Jr., on 9/11. Mr. McIlvaine attended every 9/11 Commission hearing and has been a vocal critic of the official account of 9/11. As a member of September Eleventh Families for Peaceful Tomorrows, McIlvaine has traveled all over the world speaking about 9/11, his perspective on the events of that day, and demanding justice for his son and the other innocents who perished along with him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Daniel Hopsicker&lt;/b&gt; - An investigative journalist, author, and documentary film maker, Hopsicker arrived in Florida two months after 9/11 to look into activities of the alleged hijackers and their connection to Huffman Aviation. What he uncovered became the basis for ?Welcome to Terrorland: Muhammed Atta and the 9/11 Cover Up in Florida.? Hopsicker is still located in Florida and his up to date research can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.madcowprod.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.madcowprod...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michele Little&lt;/b&gt; - Little lost her brother, FDNY Firefighter, David M. Weiss, on 9/11. Along with 9/11 Family Members Donna Marsh O?Connor and Christina Kminek, Little called for a real investigation into 9/11 at the National Press Club on 9/11/06. Michele is also an advocate for the First Responders of 9/11 and works to raise awareness of the health issues that these heroes are currently facing. She is also one of the founding members of &lt;a href="http://www.2ndresponders.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.2ndrespond...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sander Hicks&lt;/b&gt; - An author and investigative journalist, Sander delivers the type of hard-hitting journalism that all journalists should. Hicks is the founder of Soft Skull Press and the owner of the Vox Pop, a progressive coffee house and outlet for independent media and publishing. Hicks has done extensive research into the ISI/Pakistan connection to 9/11 and published ?The Big Wedding,? detailing the whistle blowers and the many conflicts of interest within the 9/11 Commission. Hicks will speak about his current investigation into the mysterious death of Dr. David Graham.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donna Marsh O?Connor&lt;/b&gt; - O?Connor lost her daughter, Vanessa Lang Langer. Along with 9/11 Family members, Michele Little and Christina Kminek, O?Connor called for a real investigation into 9/11 at the National Press Club on 9/11/06. O?Connor has been very active in recent years in spreading the truth about 9/11. She is also on the advisory board of &lt;a href="http://www.911truth.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.911truth.o...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Barrie Zwicker&lt;/b&gt; - Zwicker is an award-winning Canadian alternative media journalist, documentary producer, and political activist. Mr. Zwicker?s presentation will pertain to ?media blackout? of the alternative view of 9/11, a subject of which Zwicker has been published a book (?Towers of Deception) and produced three documentaries (The Great Deception, The Great Conspiracy, and Deep Complicity).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jason Bermas&lt;/b&gt; - Bermas is a documentary film maker and activist. The two films Bermas has produced so far, Loose Change 2nd Edition and Loose Change Final Cut, are responsible for bringing the 9/11 Truth Movement onto the brink of becoming mainstream. Bermas is also the host of Louder Than Words Radio on the GCN Radio Network. Please visit &lt;a href="http://www.loosechange911.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.loosechang...&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jon Gold&lt;/b&gt; - Longtime researcher and activist. Gold was instrumental in the production of 9/11: Press For Truth and has been an advocate for the 9/11 First Responders and the Feal Good Foundation. Gold is involved with ?9/11Truth Tuesdays? at the Wayne Movie Theater in Wayne, PA, which has turned out to be an incredibly successful public outreach venue. To view Gold?s extensive 9/11 archive please visit: &lt;a href="http://www.yourbbsucks.com/forum/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yourbbsuck...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other presenters may come, too. For more information please visit &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sst911.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sst911.org...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.monadnock911truthalliance.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.monadnock9...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211204007000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Special networking opportunity</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207149174000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The New England 9/11 Symposium</name><id>7657597</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211031000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/7657597/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/c/a/global_3737066.jpeg</photo_url></item>