<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Walkers Brook Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01867</zip><lat>42.518757</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-942-2001</phone><name>Bertucci's </name><city>Reading</city><id>149834</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093274</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Robert Najmulski of FAIR (Federation for American Immigration Reform
&lt;a href="http://www.fairus.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.fairus.org&lt;/a&gt;) will be in Massachusetts August 1-2 and is giving a presentation at the Liberty Clubhouse in Worcester. He will be holding an informational meeting where he will advise TP and other grassroots activists as to how to continue our push for reform here in MA. Just as Jessica Vaughan of the Center for Immigration Studies has been an invaluable asset
&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to many of our organizations in advocating for policies here in MA, Robert is taking a look at some of our other options and opportunities.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Of course Secure Communities is still at the top of our wish list but there is legislation in the General Court we can advocate for and now, as you know, Gov. Patrick's reawakened support for instate tuition for illegals. A well coordinated campaign by tea party activists statewide can not only usher in the reform we want but also draw positive attention to our movement and draw in new activists. Robert will provide educational materials as well as advice and assistance. I hope to see you there.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;***Robert Najmulski will be speaking at a meeting as well on August 1st, 7:00 - 9:00PM @&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liberty Clubhouse, Osgood-Bradley Building, 18 Grafton Street, 4th Floor Worcester.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Private Dining Room</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christen Varley</member_name><member_id>9247789</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1312395891000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Patriots</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Tea-Party</urlname><id>1404985</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Tea Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311521653000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greater Boston Tea Party August Reading  Meeting</name><id>26842601</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312326000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Tea-Party/events/26842601/</event_url></item>