<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let us all get together at a nearby restaurant after the movie. &lt;b&gt;Please only RSVP for this meetup&lt;/b&gt; if you are interested in dinner or drinks after the movie. I need to make a reservation as we tend to be a large group. If you are interested only in the movie, please RSVP for the meetup setup for the movie on the same day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please also mention the restaurant that you are interested in your RSVP comment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---Few places that I can think of---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.afghancuisine.net/index.asp" target="_blank"&gt;Shish Kebab House&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1988, the Shish Kebab House has offered the Hartford area delicious Afghan Cuisine, such specialties as Mantoo and Ashak dumplings or our award winning kebabs ranging from traditional lamb kebab to mouth watering beef tenderloin and succulent lamb chops to unique Salmon and Swordfish kebabs cooked traditionally over a bed of coals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thecounterburger.com/" target="_blank"&gt;THE COUNTER - Custom Built Burgers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Step into The Counter® and you’re greeted with a clipboard and an extensive list of fresh mouth-watering ingredients that allow you to build your own gourmet burger. Our 312,120+ different burger combinations make every burger as unique as each customer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.maxrestaurantgroup.com/oyster/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Max's Oyster Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Max's Oyster Bar is the fourth creation of restaurateur Richard Rosenthal and his partner Bob Cooke, formerly of Legal Seafood Restaurant Company. The understated atmosphere of muted colors and comfortable seating allows diner's to focus on the truly important, the food. Featuring modern renditions of classic American seafood, Max's Oyster Bar menu has something for everyone. While seafood is the focal point, there are selections for even the most land bound. Ethnic influences are apparent throughout a menu filled with new interpretations on traditional fare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To see the show times for this theatre:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bowtiecinemas.com/blue-back.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bowtiecine...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To know more about Blue Black Square and points of interest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bluebacksquare.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bluebacksq...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For parking options:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bluebacksquare.com/parking/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bluebacksq...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bluebacksquare.com/directions/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bluebacksq...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On going Events&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bluebacksquare.com/events/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bluebacksq...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send detailed information closer to each event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287371212000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285432915000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movies and Fun on Fridays! - Dinner After Movie</name><id>14892468</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287190800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/14892468/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/3/global_16960115.jpeg</photo_url></item>