<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>************* New Information as of June 29th, 2007  ***********&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello again Boston Karaoke Members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you can see, we now have &lt;br /&gt;  - 21 members who are definitely coming and&lt;br /&gt;  - Another 12 that might come&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We expecting a very strong turnout.  I am looking forward to meeting everyone tomorrow at 8:00PM sharp.  It will be alot of fun.  If you have any questions, please call my cell phone# 617-429-6571.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Boston Karaoke Meetup Coordinator,&lt;br /&gt;Phil&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***********************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello Boston Karaoke Members:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a wonderful Karaoke Meetup in May with a very respectable rating of 4.5 (out of 5) from the participants.  Please read some of the comments posted by the people who came to that Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, it's time to do it again.  I have scheduled the next Boston Karaoke Meetup on Saturday June 30, 2007 to give you plenty of time to plan.   Please mark your calendars and make a commitment to join us.  You'll be glad you did, that's what everyone else has told to me after attending a Karaoke Meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've also had great comments from the members about the Limelight in Boston so I am booking us there for another private studio for 2 hours.  They have a great list of songs that covers every genre of music.  You will most certainly find something that suits you and you can sing it in front of a supportive audience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last month, we enjoyed songs from Neil Diamond, Stevie Wonder, Elvis Presley, Frank Sinatra, Beatles, George Michael, Michael Jackson, Tina Turner, etc., etc. sung by our very own members!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, please RSVP right away, as that gets everyone else going.  Just tell us what you are planning to do and if your plans change later, there is no problem changing your RSVP.  Sign up right away, I thank you in advance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your Meetup Coordinator,&lt;br /&gt;- Phil&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Philip L</member_name><member_id>1522860</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183438852000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonkaraoke</urlname><id>212993</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1180189281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Karaoke Meetup - Saturday June 30, 2007</name><id>5820470</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1183248000000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonkaraoke/events/5820470/</event_url></item>