<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 W Hollis St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.757661</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603.821.5260</phone><name>603 Lounge</name><city>Nashua</city><id>696941</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464450</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We're really excited to announce that we are starting up a monthly video screening in Nashua - on the 1st Tuesday of every month. We'll have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesday-Northerly (hopefully Plymouth - maybe Campton). If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, maybe we'll have a Truth Party somewhere!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have several videos that are fairly current to show and may take a poll on this site to see which one you'd like to see. This week, since we aren't giving you much advance notice, we may just have a chat and planning session. We'll be testing out the video equipment and the wi-fi network. If all works well, we can share our favorite YouTube videos, or if there's time and interest, show an entire DVD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll also go over how each attender can become more involved and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have some free DVD's and everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We'll develop a collection of books for sale at these meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive at 6:30 if you can, in order to get your dinner and beverage orders in. The owner has offered us all a 10% discount off of everything on the menu and I hope he'll be able to join us for the videos. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and then on to the equipment setups and video showings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is on West Hollis Street, also across the street in the Nashua City Hall side parking lot and around the block in a lot that is behind the 603. I'll give directions on how you get into that lot when I figure it out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com" target="_blank"&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online at eRideShare.com&lt;/a&gt;. Carpooling arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above to go to the online ridesharing group. It may take a little getting used to, but now that gas has gone over $3.90, it gets more interesting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What you will have to do is set up an individual username &amp;amp; password on eRideShare.com. Then, our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. Once you've figured out how the system works, just bookmark &lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mv911t.eridesh...&lt;/a&gt; and remember the password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. Then you can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, donations for the ride-sharing are always appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll greet everyone - I'm the guy on the left in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215124286000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214679438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua monthly video screening &amp; planning meeting</name><id>8235118</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214951400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/8235118/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/0/global_4598208.jpeg</photo_url></item>