<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366253</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-3721</phone><name>Pandemonium Books &amp; Games</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>875759</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105592</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Adventure&lt;/b&gt;: Extermination, a one-shot adventure, in which a group of young warriors from the Soaring Hawk clan, sent to bolster a fort garrison, arrive only to find it the site of a brutal struggle for survival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;b&gt;System&lt;/b&gt;: World's Edge, a gritty low-fantasy indie role-playing system currently undergoing development and playtesting.  Check out the &lt;a href="http://www.worldsedgeonline.com" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Players&lt;/b&gt;: 3 to 5 people looking to have a good time and try something new.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Characters&lt;/b&gt;: A wide selection of pre-made characters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Much has been said about the events that transpired at Dimgulch Bastion during the early Spring of the 1214th year of the Union.  Certainly, it was the first major threat to the systems of tunnels, passages, and forts linking the core of our lands to the prosperous and newly discovered gold fields of the Far South.  In retrospect, much has been made of the actions of the handful of initiate warriors of the Soaring Hawk clan who arrived at the Bastion at the height of crisis.  Some have called them heroes, others cowards, fools, and worse.  The real truth of those days, is however, locked within the hearts and memories of the few who escaped Dimgulch with their lives.  I was one, and what we faced within the darkness of the Bastion was not a question of heroism, but a question of extermination...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interested?  I'm looking to use this as an avenue for meeting some new and interesting people in the Boston role-playing scene.  If there's sufficient interest, I'd be happy to run the adventure for multiple groups, so if you are interested, but can't make the listed time, shoot me an e-mail anyway.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jay</member_name><member_id>1685722</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>fallen</member_name><member_id>5197434</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254856424000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253923783000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[Players Needed] Extermination: A Gritty, Low-Fantasy One-Shot Adventure</name><id>11468334</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254070800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/11468334/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>