<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From the Harvard Coop site&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://harvardcoopbooks.bncollege.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/BNCBHomePage?storeId=52084&amp;amp;catalogId=10001&amp;amp;langId=-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://harvardcoopboo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;An Evening with Seth Grahame-Smith&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where&lt;/b&gt;: Brattle Theater&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When&lt;/b&gt;: Monday, March 5th, 2010, 06:00 PM-08:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Seth Grahame-Smith is the author of The Big Book of Porn (Quirk, 2005) and The Spider-Man Handbook (Quirk, 2006). His revision of a Jane Austen classic blew readers' minds and became an instant national bestseller. In his newest book, he tackles our greatest president. Seth Grahame-Smith will be reading from and signing copies of his new vampire thriller, &lt;b&gt;Abraham Lincoln - Vampire Hunter&lt;/b&gt;. Tickets are $5 and can be purchased in advance at The Coop starting Feb. 8 or by calling 617.499.2012, or at the door the night of the event. Ticket purchases include a $5 coupon - redeemable for Abraham Lincoln - Vampire Hunter or any other book at the Harvard Coop&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting outside the Brattle Theater starting at 5:30 pm. This is going to be chaos. We can grab seats at 5:40 pm up front. T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. Let's group up at the exit outside and try to grab dinner somewhere in Harvard Square. Bring suggestions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Abraham Lincoln: Vampire Hunter&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Abraham-Lincoln-Vampire-Seth-Grahame-Smith/dp/0446563080/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1266441008&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Release Date&lt;/u&gt;: March 2, 2010. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon, Publishers Weekly review: &amp;quot;Following the success of his bestselling &lt;i&gt;Pride and Prejudice and Zombies&lt;/i&gt; with another mélange of history and horror, Grahame-Smith inserts a grandiose and gratuitous struggle with vampires into Abraham Lincoln's life. Lincoln learns at an early age that his mother was killed by a supernatural predator. This provokes his bloody but curiously undocumented lifelong vendetta against vampires and their slave-owning allies. The author's decision to reduce slavery to a mere contrivance of the vampires is unfortunate bordering on repellent, but at least it does distract the reader from the central question of why the president never saw fit to inform the public of the supernatural menace. Grahame-Smith stitches hand-to-hand vampire combat into Lincoln's documented life with competent prose that never quite manages to convince&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... YEE-Ouch! What a horrid review! Let's try the in-house review:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Indiana, 1818. Moonlight falls through the dense woods that surround a one-room cabin, where a nine-year-old Abraham Lincoln kneels at his suffering mother's bedside. She's been stricken with something the old-timers call 'Milk Sickness.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'My baby boy...' she whispers before dying.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Only later will the grieving Abe learn that his mother's fatal affliction was actually the work of a vampire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;When the truth becomes known to young Lincoln, he writes in his journal, 'henceforth my life shall be one of rigorous study and devotion. I shall become a master of mind and body. And this mastery shall have but one purpose...' Gifted with his legendary height, strength, and skill with an ax, Abe sets out on a path of vengeance that will lead him all the way to the White House.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;While Abraham Lincoln is widely lauded for saving a Union and freeing millions of slaves, his valiant fight against the forces of the undead has remained in the shadows for hundreds of years. That is, until Seth Grahame-Smith stumbled upon The Secret Journal of Abraham Lincoln, and became the first living person to lay eyes on it in more than 140 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Using the journal as his guide and writing in the grand biographical style of Doris Kearns Goodwin and David McCullough, Seth has reconstructed the true life story of our greatest president for the first time-all while revealing the hidden history behind the Civil War and uncovering the role vampires played in the birth, growth, and near-death of our nation&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Okay, so that is somewhat better...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Seth Grahame-Smith&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Seth-Grahame-Smith/e/B001JP4STO/ref=ntt_dp_epwbk_0" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Seth Grahame-Smith is a film and television writer/producer, semi-frequent blogger, and bestselling author. His first novel, &amp;quot;Pride and Prejudice and Zombies,&amp;quot; debuted at #3 on the New York Times bestseller list. Since its release in April 2009, it has sold over a million copies and has been translated into 20 languages. Seth is also the Co-Creator/Executive Producer of the upcoming MTV comedy series, 'The Hard Times of RJ Berger.' He lives in Los Angeles with his wife and son&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions to the Brattle&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brattlefilm.org/brattlefilm/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brattlefil...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Brattle Theatre is located in Brattle Hall at 40 Brattle Street just one block from the Harvard Square MBTA Red Line T stop. We are located between Eastern Mountain Sports and the Cambridge Center for Adult Education. The building is shared with Algiers Cafe, Casablanca Restaurant, and Harvard Square Optical, and the theatre entrance is on the left side of the building—look for our sidewalk poster case and marquee&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268262150000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266441900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>An Evening with Seth Grahame-Smith @ Brattle Theater</name><id>12631032</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268089200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12631032/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/1/global_13170945.jpeg</photo_url></item>