<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>801 Greenwich Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02886</zip><lat>41.714203</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-877-270-1393</phone><name>Crowne Plaza</name><city>Warwick</city><id>674988</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>TempleCon is a gaming convention like no other, and it's coming to the Crowne Plaza Hotel in Warwick, Rhode Island on the weekend of February 5th-7th, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TempleCon 2010 features the finest in modern role-playing, bringing you over 50 role-playing events including the premiere of the Unhallowed Metropolis theatre game by its creators Jason Soles, Nicole Vega, and Simon Berman.  In addition, TempleCon is hosting multiple Unhallowed Metropolis table-top sessions including one led by Nicole Vega, plus the release of the hardcover version of the Unhallowed Metropolis “Up the River” campaign with a book signing by author Simon Berman and artist Robert Tritthardt, additional Guest of Honor Game-Master sessions of Call of Cthulhu led by artist and performer Rick Sardinha and writer C.J. Henderson, Eclipse Phase sessions run by writer and designer Jack Graham, as well as 25 RPGA events, plus sessions of Deadlands, Dogs in the Vineyard, Shadowrun, and more, plus a stunning array of other hobby gaming events, all held in an uncommonly high-class venue for the ultimate convention experience. Also expect more industry guests, independent game developers, live performances, panels, classes, vendors, demos, parties, and all sorts of other debauchery, and you'll know why people everywhere are saying that TempleCon is taking the classic geek culture stereotype and knocking it on its ear.  Join us this February for the best TempleCon yet! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-register for TempleCon 2010 before January 15th and save!  &lt;a href="http://meetup.rpfgb.org/pages/TempleCon_Pre-Registration_Page" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://templecon.org/10/index.php?option=com_virtuemart&amp;amp;Itemid=70&amp;amp;vmcchk=1&amp;amp;Itemid=70" target="_blank"&gt;http://templecon.org/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  Pre-registration is $10 per day for Friday only or Sunday only, $20 per day for Saturday only, and $35 for the weekend, and our group rate and military/student rates save you even more!  On-site registration at the convention is $15 per day for Friday or Sunday only, $25 per day for Saturday only, and $50 for the weekend, with a military/student rate of $45 for the weekend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, please check out &lt;a href="http://meetup.rpfgb.org/pages/TempleCon_Official_Website" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.templecon.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.templecon....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  Feel free to stop by our forums and join the discussion or start one of your own: &lt;a href="http://meetup.rpfgb.org/pages/TempleCon_Forums" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.templecon.org/forum/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.templecon....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or, drop us an email at information@templecon.org with any questions that you might have about the convention. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the co-founder and Creative Director for TempleCon, so I'll be running around all over the convention.  :)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Madame Ximon</member_name><member_id>3059616</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265791458000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston</urlname><id>359705</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Role-Playing Fellowship of Greater Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262501571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>TempleCon 2010</name><id>12203959</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265378400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/roleplaying-fellowship-of-greater-boston/events/12203959/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/c/f/global_3081279.jpeg</photo_url></item>