<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June’s FREE Community Evening of Guided Meditations, our gift to you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connecting to Spirit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;Wed. evening, June 13th, 7:15 -8:30 pm (&lt;em&gt;Please plan on arriving early to get settled&lt;/em&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;(also offered on Friday., June 1st, at Earthsong Yoga in Marlborough, see calendar)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I believe the most powerful gift you can give yourself, and thus to others, too, is to be connected to your Sense of Spirit and to bring that into your daily living.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Tonight you’ll be guided into easily connecting to and feeling your sense of spirit, and then to bring it into various aspects of your life - your environments, behaviors, capabilities, beliefs and values, sense of self and your greater vision. This alone is a very powerful experience; but we’re going to take it even further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;From there, we’ll then do a guided process that will have you bringing this strong sense of spirit to problematic areas in your life and other contexts in which you want to feel your spiritual self present.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Just imagine feeling connected to your sense of your Spiritual self, and expanding that feeling more and more and more AND having it more available to you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;So PLEASE find a way to join us! All are welcome. Please share this with your e-mail lists and groups, your friends, and your family, and invite them to join you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I really did enjoy your guided meditations tonight. I arrived here feeling so exhausted and found during the experiences tonight an opening and energy re-awakening inside. It was very healing for me to have this experience, and there were many tools I will leave here with.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Space is limited, so registration is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;PLEASE, BE CONSIDERATE, AND IF YOU SIGN UP, THEN SHOW UP, OR LET US KNOW IF YOUR PLANS CHANGE.  We'll be waiting for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;“Thank you so much! Friday night was amazing. I felt like it was the first time I was truly meditating. My mind was quiet and accepting.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Can’t wait! &lt;br /&gt;

 Warmest heart, &lt;br /&gt;

 Ann&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Ann Ide, M.A., www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This event is co-sponsored by Roots and Wings and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be downstairs in the Roots studio (either come in back door of bldg. or go down stairs towards back of first floor)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340156236000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337202689000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June's Free community evening of guided meditations (2nd date and location)</name><id>65087862</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339629300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/65087862/</event_url></item>