<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone, &lt;br /&gt;Ten canoes, three wives, one hundred and fifty spears...trouble.  &lt;br /&gt;Set centuries ago and in mythical times, Ten Canoes is a surreal tragi-comedy in the Ganalbingu language of the remote Arafura Swamp region of north-eastern Arnhem Land. This is the first major Australian feature film completely filmed in an indigenous Aboriginal language.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;An enchanting fable rich in authenticity and shot through with unexpected humor.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Hollywood Reporter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Once you become accustomed to the mystical vocabulary describing a world without modern science and technology, it amounts to using different terms to describe universal experience.&amp;quot; NY Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is scheduled to screen at Kendall for only one week and  I thought it would be a good choice as one of our Summer Sunday Al Fresco screenings. The 4 pm screening time is an approximation and will be updated the week before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is one of the many outstanding reviews: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://entertainment.timesonline.co.uk/tol/arts_and_entertainment/film/film_reviews/article1860553.ece" target="_blank"&gt;http://entertainment....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A man teaches his younger brother an important lesson through an ancient fable in this period comedy-drama shot in Australia...  As narrator David Gulpilil Ridjimiraril Dalaithngu sets up the story, we watch a group of tribesmen led by elder Minygululu (Peter Minygululu) set out on an expedition to gather bark for canoe building and collect the precious eggs of the magpie geese. It has become clear to Minygululu that his younger brother Dayindi (Jamie Dayindi Gulpilil Dalaithngu) is infatuated with the youngest of his three wives, and Minygululu wants to be sure Dayindi doesn't do something he'll regret later on. To teach his brother a lesson, Minygululu shares with him a long story about Ridjimiraril (Crusoe Kurddal), a warrior who finds his brother Yeeralparil (also played by Jamie Dayindi Gulpilil Dalaithngu) has become a rival for the affections of his bride. However, while Minygululu's story caries a clear message for his brother, it also goes on long enough with enough twists, turns and digressions that it gives Dayindi little opportunity to get into mischief during the trip.  AllMovieGuide&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is the custom, Tom will be holding a Meetup sign near the front-row after the movie and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182888252000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181781613000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>10 Canoes- An Australian Aboriginal Tale</name><id>5889072</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182715200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5889072/</event_url></item>