<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Oxford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375309</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Harvard University Science Center </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>9749932</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117943</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;“We’re here, we’re queer, get used to it” has been for decades the stock in trade of the gay rights movement so far — but the struggle in more recent years for equal rights in love and marriage has generated a tidal wave of positive political and social change and invited a larger part of the mainstream America (and global population) to identify and empathize with those working on behalf of gay rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Might the secular movement experience a similar revival with increased focus on our shared values of love and compassion?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this exclusive event, Herb Silverman, President of the Secular Coalition for America and David Niose, the President of the American Humanist Association -- two of the biggest organizations representing nonreligious Americans-- join forces to tackle this question, while each debuting their new books exploring secularism and US politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is presented as part of the ongoing 2012-2013 distinguished speaker series "An Ethic of Love", sponsored by the Humanist Community at Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday, October 14, 1:30pm at the Harvard Science Center (One Oxford Street) Hall E. The Humanist Mindfulness Group will host meditation at 12 Eliot Street at 3:00pm. FREE BRUNCH at 12:30pm before the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the Fall 2012 Humanist Learning Lab pilot, free childcare will be offered at all "An Ethic of Love" events. The HCH has reserved a limited number of free parking spots in the Littauer Lot -- first come, first served.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350243367000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349956038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Politics of Love: Dave Niose and Herb Silverman</name><id>86506812</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350232200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/86506812/</event_url></item>