<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 635-4505</phone><name>Boston Common Frog Pond</name><city>Boston</city><id>795283</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Dear Incubators new members, old members, and inbetween,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guess what??  This Sunday August 16th, which by now is tomorrow, yours truly turns the big 2-6 years old and I haven't had a real b-day get together in a long time and wanted to invite all of you to be a part of it as the incubator's been a big part of my life the last two years.  Speaking of which, another milestone, I've been organizing you all for just over a year now.   With that you are all invited this Sunday, whether I have met you before or not, I encourage you all to come out!  What's a b-day without meeting some new friends and reminiscing the old favorites, lol.  So here's the plan for Sunday!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's the last day of Shakespeare in the Common, this years play is the Comedy of Errors,  So my hope was to gather those who are around there for the play and obviously some social and fun time beforehand.  I was thinking along the lines of a picnic with food, snacks, non-alcoholic beverages, improv games, board games, perhaps some frisbee and of course good seats for the play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'd like to get there asap and have a really loungy type of day just conversing and having fun.  The play starts at &lt;b&gt;7pm&lt;/b&gt; and I wanted to grab a big patch of real estate around &lt;b&gt;4pm&lt;/b&gt; for a good view.  So feel free to come anytime here there and inbetween but it would be great to enjoy the day with all of you who are around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now beforehand for those that might be intersted, at 3pm, there's a weekly Boston Frisbee meetup in the same area, So if you are up for a little activity before relaxing, let me know!  It's completely chill and not competitive unless you want it to be, there's a beginner's game too for those who havent thrown a frisbeen in awhile or just want a more chill atmosphere.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While I am at it, I'll probably hit up a movie in the morning at the theater right there and yoga in the early afternoon at Back Bay Yoga, so if anyone wants to join me for any part or all of those, the hand is out there to be shook.  Just figured I'd invite you all in to my entire day and all that's a part of me because for me I've already had the pleasure of getting to know a part of you, your laugh, your smile, your weird meetup photos, lol.  Look forward to seeing your faces again in person!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Def let me know if you can make any portion of it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>That's me, right there front and center!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250814381000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250312003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jason's 26th Birthday Blast!! SUNDAY SUNDAY SUNDAY!!!</name><id>11116350</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250452800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/11116350/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/5/global_10193829.jpeg</photo_url></item>