<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Note: Due to time conflicts, our meeting is now on Monday January 12th at 7:00.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the power outages and illness, we had a small (but primo quality) group of five or so people last time.  We touched on David R. Hawkins 'The Levels of Consciousness' last time and it made for a great conversation, so we'll be exploring it more deeply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The principle is that by becoming aware of the ascending levels of consciousness (from shame, guilt and apathy up to love, joy and peace) we'll focus on our ability to work our way upward to a happier, more empowered consciousness level.  (We're all working on this now, or we would not be part of a group like this :-)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;It's our responsibility to help raise the consciousness level of the world.&lt;/span&gt;  We do this by raising our OWN level of consciousness. [/b&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's no need to argue or convince anyone; as our consciousness level increases others feel 'energized, purposeful, inspired and unified', and THEIR consciousness level increases.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is very powerful because it is not a one-on-one effect:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- One individual who lives and vibrates to the energy of optimism and a willingness to be non-judgmental of others will counterbalance the negativity of 90,000 individuals who are operating at lower level of consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abraham Maslow calls people who live this way 'self-actualized', and Wayne Dyer describes them (us) as 'connectors' to signify their harmonious connection with the field of intention.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He says that Connectors:&lt;br /&gt;- are people who have made themselves available for success&lt;br /&gt;- believe in synchronicity and aren't surprised when the positive things they intend really happen.&lt;br /&gt;- are grateful for everything, even those things that seem to be obstacles.&lt;br /&gt;- live in a state of appreciation and bewilderment.&lt;br /&gt;- aren't complainers or fault finders.&lt;br /&gt;- are conscious of our oneness and make no distinction between 'us' and 'them'.  (We're all us.)&lt;br /&gt;- have an uplifting effect on others.  Their peacefulness causes others to feel calm and assured,&lt;br /&gt;- radiate serenity and peace.&lt;br /&gt;- choose to feel good regardless of what is happening around them.&lt;br /&gt;- think from the end.&lt;br /&gt;- are generous.&lt;br /&gt;- are highly inspired, as opposed to filled with information.&lt;br /&gt;- have a strong sense of their destiny.&lt;br /&gt;- have a high energy level, that converts hatred to love, and chaos to harmony.&lt;br /&gt;- may be labeled as aloof or distant because they don't gravitate to gossip or bashing.&lt;br /&gt;- avoid loud, opinionated people and don't wallow in violent TV shows, sensational news or war   statistics.&lt;br /&gt;- do not need to win, are not argumentative.&lt;br /&gt;- are never offended because their egos are not aren't involved in their opinions.&lt;br /&gt;- are inquisitive; they can never learn enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOTS of terrific ideas to talk about here- hope you can make it!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Laurie&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Just look for the group of friendly, laughing people...  :-)  You can't miss us,</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315421340000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1229480026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Levels of Consciousness</name><id>9350525</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231804800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/9350525/</event_url></item>