<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>317 North Main St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots and Wings Yoga and Healing ArtsCenter</name><city>Natick</city><id>1329422</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;September&amp;rsquo;s FREE Community Evening at Roots and Wings, our gift to you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080 ; font-size : large ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Living in a Vacation Frame of Mind&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you think maybe you sometimes struggle harder than necessary?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does your day feel like hard work, filled with "have-to's" and "shoulds"?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you feel rushed or stressed as you move through your day?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How does that compare to how you feel on vacation?&amp;nbsp; A little different?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come join us; and through a series of guided meditations&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;discussions and processes, you can &lt;em&gt;experience and learn about living in an enlightened, vacation frame of mind, no matter what day, time of year, or what's on your to-do list!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, you &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; relax and let go, and still get everything done that you need to, and perhaps even more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : small"&gt;"Ann was wonderful! I came into the room after the rush of the day and was immediately at peace. Her calm, focused and patient nature was so welcoming. I am still using the techniques taught.&amp;nbsp; I'm very grateful to Ann for sharing her time and knowledge." Linda M.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;So treat yourself to this wonderful free event for you. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Please invite others to join you&lt;/span&gt;. Share this with your friends, family and groups. The class is appropriate for everyone, and all are welcome!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Space is limited, so your RSVP is required.&amp;nbsp; Please plan on arriving around 7:05 to get settled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Also, please be considerate of your hosts (us!), and honor your "yes" rsvp by either showing up or letting us know if your plans change by changing your rsvp. Many of you have been wonderful about this, and we very much appreciate your understanding, consideration and support!&amp;nbsp; Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Hope you'll join us!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;Ann&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #333399 ; font-size : small"&gt;Class leader: Ann Ide, M.A., www.newpossibilitiescoaching.com, certified master practitioner and trainer in Neuro-linguistic Programming and Hypnotherapy, and certified NLP Life Coach. Ann coaches people to move beyond struggles and mere survival, to new levels of harmony, happiness and success. With her expert questioning, inner exploration processes and personal change interventions, clients become emotionally and spiritually aligned to more easily create the happiness they want.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #333399"&gt;This &lt;em&gt;public&lt;/em&gt; event is co-sponsored by Roots and Wings and New Possibilities Coaching as a community service; and is being shared with you because of it's applicability to successfully utilizing law of attraction principles through greater allowing and connection to your Greater Spirit-Self. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in the Wings studio on the first floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318613051000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316711969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening of Guided Meditations for Living in a Vacation Frame of Mind</name><id>34567832</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318461300000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/34567832/</event_url></item>