<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 North Main St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.207015</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Legislative Office Bldg. (LOB)</name><city>Concord</city><id>1081385</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.537692</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Liberty Day at the state house: February 21st 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 --- &lt;br /&gt;

 A GUN Ban to OPPOSE, A study cmte to oppose: &lt;br /&gt;

 Constitutional Carry to SUPPORT as well as other bills &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 CRIMINAL JUSTICE AND PUBLIC SAFETY CMTE, Representatives Hall &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 OPPOSE: &lt;br /&gt;

 10:00 a.m. HB 290-FN, prohibiting unlicensed persons from openly carrying a pistol or revolver in a public building. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 SUPPORT &lt;br /&gt;

 11:00 a.m. HB 609, relative to possession of a firearm on school property. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 SUPPORT &lt;br /&gt;

 1:00 p.m. HB 451-FN, repealing the license requirement for carrying a concealed pistol or revolver. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 OPPOSE &lt;br /&gt;

 2:00 p.m. HB 396, establishing a committee to study requiring safety training or instruction prior to the purchase or acquisition of a firearm. &lt;br /&gt;

 --- &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 SUPPORT Also a chance to attend the NDAA NULLIFICATION hearing HB399 10:00am in LOB203 &lt;br /&gt;

 Please add this to your calendar and show up! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For those that have not been to the NH State House, this is the perfect occasion. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 A chance to witness activism first hand with a group of like minded friends while helping us defend against our reps taking away more of our rights as well as defending the ability to carry a firearm concealed. &lt;br /&gt;

 Be part of the process, join us this day! &lt;br /&gt;

 PS. Get a chance to meet some of the most liberty oriented state reps in the country.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361470023000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360602096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Defend our Liberty Day at the NH state house</name><id>104094462</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361458800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/104094462/</event_url></item>