<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1305 Memorial Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01089</zip><lat>42.093048</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Eastern States Exposition</name><city>West Springfield</city><id>4305542</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.618622</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a NO dog, people only fieldtrip to watch an AKC Dog Show! Dog shows tend to run from 8:00am-3:00pmISH. We don&amp;rsquo;t have the scheduled time for each event but you can count on seeing a lot of dogs (I&amp;rsquo;m personally making it an all day trip)! This show will have something for everyone by exhibiting dogs in All Breed Conformation, Obedience, Agility and Rally! These sports are all very demanding and require a lot of time and training in order to get them up to show quality level. The all breed conformation is mostly known as beauty pageants for purebred dogs that are judged against their own individual breed standard. This is the sport usually seen on TV (Westminster Dog Show) when the dogs run around in a circle and are who ever is structurally built correctly wins. Obedience is a sport that puts you and your dog&amp;rsquo;s bond and relationship to the test by judging how in tune and responsive your dog is to your commands and signals. Agility is a fast pace and exhilarating obstacle course where the dog is instructed to jump over hurdles, run through tunnels, weave through poles and climb obstacles such as A-Frames, Seesaws and Dog Walks. And Rally is a sport that has stationed exercises with instructed signs for you and your dog to work through. There will also be food and some amazing vendors to shop from so don&amp;rsquo;t forget your wallets! This show is being hosted at the Eastern States Exposition Grounds on 1305 Memorial Ave in West Springfield, MA 01089 and although most people will probably go on Sunday the 27th, the event is going on Friday Saturday and Sunday. This is a great and inspiring opportunity to see just what our dogs are capable of&amp;hellip; so please come out for the day and surround yourself with 2,000 dogs! :0)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara jean crehan</member_name><member_id>14380588</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322403536000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1320527949000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>DOG SHOW!!!!</name><id>40089742</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322398800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/40089742/</event_url></item>