<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Miller Park Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03458</zip><lat>42.855562</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Miller State Park</name><city>Peterborough</city><id>978033</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.883503</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/6/5/5/event_48022101.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/0/5/event_47493541.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will take our cars up the auto road of Miller State Park to the summit of South Pack Monadnock then hike to the summit of North Pack Monadnock. There are views from both summits. &lt;strong&gt;I would rate this as a moderate hike&lt;/strong&gt;. It is mostly a line hike in that we will come back on the same trail the same way. The distance between summits is 2.3 miles one way (4.6 miles round trip).  But at North Pack Monadnock we will take in the additional views from the Cliff Trail adding approximately an additional mile to the hike for &lt;strong&gt;a total of a 5.3 mile hike so it is mostly a line hike with a short loop on the end at the turnaround point.&lt;/strong&gt; Descending the Cliff Trail has a steep section as we descend off to the side of the cliff.  But to me going down it is much easier than climbing up it.   &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As we are hiking along the ridge of a mountain the elevation gain/loss is a about 400 feet as we go downhill and uphill again in between the two summits so &lt;strong&gt;the total elevation gain is 1,570 feet round trip&lt;/strong&gt;. The heights of the two summits are 2290 and 2278 feet. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Admission to Miller State Park is $4 per person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can print out a map with the link below:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MilleronPakkMonad.pdf"&gt;www.nhstateparks.org/uploads/pdf/MilleronPakkMonad.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link to photos of a prior meetup here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/photos/all_photos/?photoAlbumId=2865101"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/photos/all_photos/?photoAlbumId=2865101&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So everyone is covered by the liability waiver any guest you want to bring should sign up as a member to come on the hike. Minors would need a waiver signed by a parent/guardian.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Coming from Wilton the park entrance is 0.1 miles past 876 Wilton Road.  Coming from Peterborough the entrance is 0.1 mile before getting to 876 Wilton Rd. Look for a White Suzuki Grand Vitara,  NH Plate 308 0904 at the summit parking lot.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350149168000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348621703000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Miller State Park-Summit to Summit Hike- S. Pack Monadnock to N. Pack Monad.</name><id>84102452</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349618400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/84102452/</event_url></item>