<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Get ready to sharpen your language skills with a &lt;strong&gt;Word Game Night&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll have Scrabble, Lexigon, Word on the Street, Boggle, Quiddler, Anomia, and Snatch-It. If you have another favorite, please bring it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So if you like any of these games or want to learn more about this genre, this event will be for you. &amp;nbsp;We welcome new players with open arms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to bring a favorite snack for the evening. We'll have plenty to drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* You should know that we are a household with cats, but they will be locked up for the evening. The house is also home to a 3 year old, who will be headed to bed as people arrive. We also have a twelve month old, who isn't much of a game player, but he will eventually go to bed as well. Expect to see him awake while you are here, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Parking is available on Upham Street, but it is tight. There is generally more parking available toward Orne St., and more parking is available on Orne and Dearborn Streets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*If there is a snow emergency, this event will be cancelled. Should it look like we'll receive snow that evening, we will be in contact via e-mail. Otherwise, you are always welcome to call to verify.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326668485000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324313169000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Word Game Night in Salem</name><id>44909522</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326589200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/44909522/</event_url></item>