<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>47 Webster Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02673</zip><lat>41.647800</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Private Home</name><city>West Yarmouth</city><id>1379277</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.253600</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>150.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Visit Cape Cod, Massachusetts for a mini vacation, weekend escape or getaway. Explore the 15 distinctive towns, arts &amp;amp; culture, quaint shops, wooded bicycle paths, plentiful events &amp;amp; festivals, and endless array of land and sea activities. Visit countless historic sites and landmarks, each telling the proud role that Cape Cod has played in American history. Cape Cod also offers fine dining experiences &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to Cape Cod to feel inspired. Come to Cape Cod to walk the pristine beaches, to revel in the arts and culture, to reclaim childhood memories of seashells, sandcastles and salt water taffy. Come to Cape Cod to indulge in the freshest fried clams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to Cape Cod to let yourself go and let it capture your heart... just come with us to Cape Cod. &lt;br /&gt;We all need a little Cape Cod, now more than ever! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Friday, October 1st, Saturday, October 2nd, Sunday, October 3rd and departing for home on Monday, October 4th (after cottage cleanup).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Location is in West Yarmouth. Be prepared to room with someone, however. I have procured a beautiful house that will sleep 16. Once that is filled ...you can book a motel in close proximity to the house. Contact me for more details regarding the motel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: Price for 3 nights will be $150.00. This will include your room, some meals or food and lots of fun with old and new meetup friends.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: You can do your own thing...water fun, fish, shop, shows, bicycle, kayak, historical landmark jaunts, sand dune tours, cruises, etc. You get the picture. BTW...don't forget our BIG seafood extravaganza (clambake) which we are organizing for (hopefully) Sunday nite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why: Because we need a vacation...lol! So come join us. Big house, campfire, fun events, great company...what's better than that? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, if you plan on coming, RSVP quickly, as space will go in a flash. Once our house is picked and should you decide to go, procuring reservations will be your own responsibility. We are looking for 16 &lt;br /&gt;people  (have 13 already)  to share the house. Cost will be the same...$150.00 for the weekend whether you stay 1 night or the full 3 nights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will organize cooking teams and cleanup detail...lol...just like camp! Please be a teamplayer...no divas, please! Everyone shares...everyone benefits!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will need checks sent as soon as you RSVP...as I will need to pay security from that and deposit for the house. &lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;FIRM COMMITTMENTS ONLY!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great opportunity...don't let it slip by! Jump onboard with us and have some lingering summer fun! I will send out more info as soon as I have it and if you have questions, you can email me or Susanne, or feel free to call me on my cell @ 203-808-5829!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will contact those who RSVP yes!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286412884000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283548778000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CAPE COD...Let Yourself  Go!!!</name><id>14649624</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285959600000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/14649624/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/e/4/global_17676996.jpeg</photo_url></item>