<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>470 Liberty St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.205223</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pond Meadow Park</name><city>Braintree</city><id>669075</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.982680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Last minute, I know, but I just checked the weather and whdh.com is saying close to 40 degress.  Many people have Monday off for the holiday, so lets get in a walk while it is warm enough! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet for a walk at Pond Meadow Park. We will be meeting on the Braintree side of PMP by the flagpole near the Ranger Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We should be able to walk around the loop twice which totals 3.5 miles altogether and takes about 1 hr 5mins - 1 hr 15 mins. &lt;br /&gt;Monday, February 15th 12:30 &lt;br /&gt;Pond Meadow Park &lt;br /&gt;470 Liberty Street &lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184 &lt;br /&gt;No phone #. &lt;br /&gt;www.pondmeadowpark.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Organizer(s): Julie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: At least 4 Yes RSVPs by 10am on Monday. Attendance is unlimited. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Please finalize your RSVP by Monday morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Best directions should be taken from mapquest.com or maps.google.com. Located on Liberty Street, 500 feet from the intersection of Liberty and Middle Street near the Route 3 overpass directly across from Zana Park Drive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note there is a rotary now instead of a regular intersection just before PMP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 17/Union St., Braintree. Exit on the side of the (Sunoco) Gas Station and Police Station. Follow Union Street to the first set of lights. Take a Right at the lights onto Middle Street. Follow about 1 mile to a Rotary. Go 3/4 of the way around the Rotary and exit onto Liberty Street. (This used to be a regular intersection where you took a left.) PMP is 500 feet up on the Right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>we will meet by the flag pole.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4336960</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266428252000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266078114000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Last Minute Walk at Pond Meadow Park</name><id>12595672</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266255000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/12595672/</event_url></item>