<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi gang,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the 10 who showed up for the June meeting about the psychological viability of naturalism. People had good suggestions for how to present naturalism in a positive light, and for effective, non-confrontational approaches to those with different worldviews. One or two of those attending were somewhat taken aback by the seemingly partisan nature of the proceedings: how to best promote naturalism. But this group exists not only to explore the implications of naturalism as a worldview, but to make it better known and win its acceptance in the wider culture. Hence our name, Allies of Naturalism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For July and August, I'm not going to announce topics or reserve a table at Z Square. But people are of course welcome to meet anyway and discuss what's on their minds. I encourage members to take the initiative in setting a topic or activity, so be in touch if you have something to suggest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meanwhile, if I don't see you have a great summer, and I'll announce the September meeting sometime in late August.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;best, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;twc  at  naturalism.org  &lt;br /&gt;617-480-8846  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General description of what we're about (this bit doesn't change from month to month):   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allies of Naturalism welcomes those interested in exploring and promoting a science-based, humanistic and progressive naturalism that can make a difference in our lives.  To see what's involved in being a humanistic and progressive naturalist (more or less), check out Naturalism.Org, centerfornaturalism.org and the Guide to Naturalism at &lt;a href="http://www.centerfornaturalism.org/descriptions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.centerforn...&lt;/a&gt;.       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Essentially, naturalism shows our full connection to the world and others, leads to an ethics of compassion, and gives us far greater control over our circumstances.  We don't need anything supernatural either above us or inside us to lead moral and meaningful lives: nature is enough.  Naturalism is a viable alternative to faith-based worldviews such as traditional religions and new age philosophies, offering a set of ideas with positive personal and social consequences.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The meetings offer a chance to meet fellow naturalists in an informal, relaxed setting, but with at least some structure.  That's to say that we'll try to have one or two topics suggested in advance for people to think about, and then discuss when we get together.  Ultimately the focus and format of the meetings will be determined by participants, but will certainly include time for socializing and networking.  Watch the discussion board for topic announcements and other details.  Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>no table reservation for July or August</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Clark</member_name><member_id>1910897</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216249478000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Naturalists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>naturalism-1</urlname><id>231723</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Allies of Naturalism</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213056529000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Allies of Naturalism July Meeting - ad hoc, no fixed agenda</name><id>8112198</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216076400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/naturalism-1/events/8112198/</event_url></item>