<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Worcester Photo Center was approached by the city and asked to contribute photographs to a rotating gallery space in Worcester&amp;rsquo;s City Hall. The Worcester Photo Center agreed to take on the project and manage the shows and space as of August 1st 2011. With this agreement we are pleased to announce our very first theme for the space and welcome you to join in by submitting images to be shown in the gallery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture of Worcester&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Architecture is a style and method of design and construction of buildings. We would like to have a wonderful showing of the many different types of architecture Worcester has among its buildings. We are looking for images that will showcase the diversity of it&amp;rsquo;s neighborhoods as well as it&amp;rsquo;s businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like to encourage folks to show off interesting details of buildings that are used everyday, as well as overall images of attractive structures found among the city streets. We encourage you to take a look at the Preservation Worcester web site and learn a little bit about the City of Worcester and its many fascinating buildings and their histories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.preservationworcester.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.preservationworcester.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This show&amp;rsquo;s goal is to showcase the vibrancy of the city&amp;rsquo;s working buildings and structures and special attention to will be paid to images that reflect this about the city.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details you need to know.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a juried show. We only have 25 frames to fill in the gallery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need to submit a digital image(s) via upload to a web site for jurying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deadline for submissions for the jury is &lt;strong&gt;June 30th, 2011&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make your images 8x10 (or 9x12) at 72 DPI jpegs and upload them here: &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#102065"&gt;http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#102065&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The File name should be &lt;strong&gt;your name_number of submission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Example: DonnaDufault_1.jpeg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are allowed to submit up to 3 images per person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be notified on July 8th if your image or images have been chosen for the show. This will be posted on the Meetup Web site message board, and if you accept emails from the site, I will do my best to send individual notices as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have been selected, you will be asked to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;print your image, mat it with a &lt;em&gt;white&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt; mat, sign it&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;come to the framing session on July 23rd, 2011&lt;/span&gt;, so we can get these framed and ready to hang by the end of July. (More details will be placed on the Meetup Web Site, Please check the calendar for that day.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the mean time, the WPC is planning a &lt;strong&gt;Click and Shoot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; on Sunday June 12th for all members who would like the opportunity to be part of a group that explores the city and photographs in some of the best places the city has to offer. Please see the Meetup Calendar for more details on this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I asked that you mark your calendars now with these details and deadline so you can be up on all the happenings. I look forward to seeing this groups submissions for this show! There are already some wonderful images at the link!! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cheers, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna and Scotty &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This event is done online!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309407620000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Here is a chance to show off some of your photographs, be part of a great show, and have some fun doing it!</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301316525000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Submit images to the WPC "Architecture of Worcester" Juried Gallery Show</name><id>17084033</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309402800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/17084033/</event_url></item>