<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>140 Summer Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01746</zip><lat>42.177994</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 429 1500</phone><name>The Meadows</name><city>Holliston</city><id>959576</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.442941</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per household</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Members,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since I also organize the Mass. (Bigger) Small Breed Dog Group which didn't get to have a meet within the past 30 plus days, I am scheduling them into the June 21st, 3-5pm (time to be confirmed on Monday with the staff) meet at the Holliston MEADOWS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any small dog that is around 12 lbs or bigger may attend.  Pete Westland, trainer, will be present to answer questions informally.  And we will have access to an indoor-outdoor space that is connected.  Outdoor space is fenced in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm sending you this notice because some of you have dogs that qualify for this group, including:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joan L. and Jack&lt;br /&gt;Rose and Andy&lt;br /&gt;Ellen Jane, Ellen and their Maltese, Montecor and Franzel&lt;br /&gt;David B. with his Martinit and Cosmo&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Richard with their two Shih Tzus&lt;br /&gt;Dmitry with his Shih Tzu Cookie&lt;br /&gt;Nancy H. with her Maltipoo&lt;br /&gt;Possibly Vickie and Jim with their two Poms &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sorry if I've left someone out, but if anyone whose dog qualifies for both groups wants to attend this June 21st meet, but didn't get the invitation yet, please RSVP to me at:  laptopmaltese@aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have this meet no matter how few or how many people sign up.  It will be pot luck food and beverages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please tell anyone you know who owns a small dog in this weight range about this meet!  They can email me at:  laptopmaltese@aol.com or call me at (508) 380 6829.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small and Tiny dog best,&lt;br /&gt;Kim&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask someone where I am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kim Lemaire</member_name><member_id>1963654</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254074499000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Small dog owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>maltese-2</urlname><id>98818</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Boston Maltese and Tiny Dog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243611828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12 lbs and up MASS SMALL BREED DOGS,June 21st, 3-5PM, THE MEADOWS, Holliston, MA</name><id>10522867</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245610800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/maltese-2/events/10522867/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/6/c/global_83228.jpeg</photo_url></item>