<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374126</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-4700</phone><name>Harvard Film Archive</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669100</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, &lt;br /&gt;Yes, another film by that Apichatpong Weerasethakul! Last summer, Jihad  hosted this director's latest work Syndromes and a Century, which I attended and really enjoyed.  As a bonus, Mr. Weerasethakul will be present.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I contacted the HFA and they are willing to reserve tickets for us for this film and discussion. The tickets would be $8. Any film at the HFA with the director present has a good chance of selling out. So, not only would you save $2, but you would be guaranteed a seat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll need to know by Sunday, Jan. 13th so I can get the check out in the mail Monday morning. If you'd like to reserve a ticket reply to me by email- I'll need your full name so I can pass that along to the HFA staff. We will need at least 5 people to be able to reserve the tickets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By agreeing to this I hope you understand that you would owe me the $8 if for whatever reason you cannot attend, as I'll be paying the money up front.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blissfully Yours (winner of the Cannes Un Certain Regard Award) &lt;br /&gt;ia a delicate, ethereal dream of a film from the young Thai director Apichatpong Weerasethakul. Two women and a man voyage into the wild, away from civilization and its discontents. Under a lush canopy of green, the travelers settle onto the bank of a small river for a modest picnic and some languid sex, cooling themselves in the lucent water and plunging into a parallel stream of tears. As the filmmaker freely indulges in the forest's voluptuousness and his own feel for composition, his characters, freed from work, the city and everyday life , shed their clothes and tentatively bump against one another with both pleasure and frustration. In this secret place, where even the smallest gesture becomes an epic of emotion, these three people finally find a moment of quiet by letting the earth swallow them whole....the emergence of one of the more original and promising new voices to hit the international cinema scene in recent years, the primordial world offers only modest respite from everyday troubles. &lt;br /&gt;NY Times &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blissfully Yours follows a young Thai woman and her taciturn Burmese boyfriend, an illegal immigrant in need of a forged ID, as they venture out to the countryside for a bucolic idyll punctuated by matter-of-fact sexual interludes. Composed of meditative long takes, the film is casually erotic, playful -  and gently ruminative. Yet the film's serene, pastoral nature is not without an oblique political conscience, hinted at by the devastated Thai economy and Burmese military junta that lurk sinisterly in the deep background.   HFA Description &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                             A.Criticisms like &amp;quot;this is a typical art film - pretentious, slow, unengaging, for no                  discernible  reason but to torture the audience&amp;quot; ignore the wealth of thought loaded into each scene in Apichatpong Weerasethakul's &amp;quot;Blissfully Yours.&amp;quot;  Asia Pacific Arts  &lt;br /&gt;                                                                 So, this is  not to be confused with  the Bjorn Ultimatum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                             B.The film is sexually explicit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                             C. The director will be present! While this is usual a good thing, since there are no advance tickets available, I suggest getting to the Film Archive an hour in advance to secure a seat. Film screens at 7pm, I'd get there no later then 6pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things can be a little hectic whenever there is a speaker at a film, so be patient. We will be meeting as usual near the front row and then its off to discuss at a local restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As is our custom, Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row after the film and the director's Q&amp;A.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198718057000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blissfully Yours- A Film by Apichatpong Weerasethakul</name><id>6973387</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200787200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6973387/</event_url></item>