<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>286 Franklin St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.326660</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-945-2212</phone><name>Cafe Andala</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669158</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122250</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us for the discussion of Eating Animals by Jonathan Safran Foer on Tuesday August, 24th at 6:30pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Synopsis Courtesy of Barnes and Noble Website&lt;/u&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Safran Foer spent much of his teenage and college years oscillating between omnivore and vegetarian. But on the brink of fatherhood-facing the prospect of having to make dietary choices on a child's behalf-his casual questioning took on an urgency His quest for answers ultimately required him to visit factory farms in the middle of the night, dissect the emotional ingredients of meals from his childhood, and probe some of his most primal instincts about right and wrong. Brilliantly synthesizing philosophy, literature, science, memoir and his own detective work, Eating Animals explores the many fictions we use to justify our eating habits-from folklore to pop culture to family traditions and national myth-and how such tales can lull us into a brutal forgetting. Marked by Foer's profound moral ferocity and unvarying generosity, as well as the vibrant style and creativity that made his previous books, Everything is Illuminated and Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close, widely loved, Eating Animals is a celebration and a reckoning, a story about the stories we've told-and the stories we now need to tell. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be sitting in the lower level.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Elizabeth Ivey</member_name><member_id>9394837</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329675387000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1481208</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Cambridge Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279805490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Eating Animals by Jonathan Safran Foer</name><id>14179222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282689000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Book-Club-Meetup-Group/events/14179222/</event_url></item>