<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our next meet up is at Marleny Mesta and her husband Chris's house.  It will be outside so if it is raining on July 10th the rain date is July 11, 2010 @ 2pm.  Marleny will supply the hamburgers, please bring a salad or a dish that can be served at a picnic.  Also if everyone can bring a beverage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  From the East take Route 84 West and take the Trout Brook Ave Exit on your left.  At the end of the exit keep left at the fork in the ramp.  Stay Straight and go onto Clarendon Ave.  Turn right on S. Quaker at the end of Clarendon Ave, turn left onto Nutmeg Court and then take a slight left onto Rosemary CT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West take Route 84 East and then take the South Main St exit.  At the end of the ramp turn right and follow S. Main to the intersection of New Britain Ave.  Take a left onto New Britain Ave. and follow New Britain Avenue to S Quaker.  Take a left onto S. Quaker (Walgreens Pharmacy is on the corner of S. Quaker) then follow S. Quaker to Nutmeg CT and turn right onto Nutmeg CT.  Then take a slight left onto Rosemary CT and 16 is on your left. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Dworski</member_name><member_id>2589505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kurt Weingartner</member_name><member_id>8679708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279026527000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Spanish Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spanish-93</urlname><id>145906</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Spanish Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277079551000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Picnic en la casa de Marleny y Chris</name><id>13858794</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278784800000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spanish-93/events/13858794/</event_url></item>