<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Brookline Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02445</zip><lat>42.331988</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New England Institute of Art</name><city>Brookline</city><id>983195</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.115348</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Peter Campion is the Joseph Brodsky Rome Prize Fellow at the American Academy in Rome. Ron Slate on &amp;quot;The Lions&amp;quot; by Peter Campion: &amp;quot;Expansive and speculative, then withdrawing and bitter, The Lions is richly imagined and tightly trussed, made of turbulent poems that achieve a fine, dissatisfied balance. Peter Campion’s voice is essential to the telling of the struggle of our time.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Yuill is from northern Texas, though he now resides in Boston, Mass., where he teaches literature and creative writing at Boston University. Peter Campion on &amp;quot;Medicine Show&amp;quot; by Tom Yuill: &amp;quot;Yuill succeeds throughout this book in writing the kind of poem that so many younger American poets want to write—a poem of linguistic athletics, of cunning and discontinuous music, of high and low culture invigoratingly jumbled. So often, in the journals and the prize-winning first books, such ambition results in mannerism: for all their seeming subversion, the poems, because they rely on a cool ironic pose, end up maintaining an almost Edwardian sense of decorum. We get what Thom Gunn once called “mild irrationality.” In Yuill’s poems, however, irrationality has teeth. The lexical playfulness and the narrative ruptures flow from the messy stuff of genuine emotion. These poems also have the whole force of prosodic tradition driving their music, as the best possible rhythm section.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278544420000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278530372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Poets Peter Campion and Tom Yuill at New England Institute of Art</name><id>14031064</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278540000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/14031064/</event_url></item>