<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>After our first very stimulating and enjoyable meeting of the &lt;a href="http://bookclub.meetup.com/912"&gt;Interfaith Book Club&lt;/a&gt;, we welcome all! We look forward to some very interesting gatherings coming up. Welcome to Jacqueline, Teriann, John and Maureen, Kathleen, Warren and Brenda, Carol, David and Joe. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To recap, we decided that our first book we will look at together is: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Tent-Abraham-Stories-Christians-Muslims/dp/0807077283"&gt;The Tent of Abraham: Stories of Hope and Peace for Jews, Christians, and Muslims by Rabbi Arthur Waskow, Sister Joan Chittister, and Murshid Saadi Shakur Chishti.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet every third Tuesday evening of the month from 7:30 pm - 9 pm. I will prepare the discussion questions for our next gathering and we will discuss together based a chapter by chapter approach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I ran across an interesting website connected to our reading. Check it out: &lt;a href="http://www.tentofabraham.org/"&gt;Tent of Abraham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will shortly setting up a blog on the internet for our Interfaith Book Club so we can share and keep in touch, even if we cannot attend all the meetings. Let's keep in touch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would ask that any member who has not registered on this website, please to do so I can more easily keep in touch with you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, I setup a &lt;a href="http://www.interfaithbookclub.wordpress.com"&gt;new blog &lt;/a&gt;for our book club. We can continue to share even between meetings, or with those who would like to follow along with our book choice and share on line, even if they cannot come to the meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Others are welcome to join in with us on the third Tuesday of the month, and we encourage people of all faith traditions to be part of our adventure together. Until next time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fr. Carl Chudy&lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Xavier Missionaries&lt;br /&gt;Our Lady of Fatima Shrine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Tent of Abraham, Hagar, &amp;amp; Sarah is a gathering of Jews, Christians, and Muslims who have been building a 'Tent' of shared spiritual concern for peace, justice, and healing of the earth. Arising from this effort has been a call to take part in 'The Peace of Abraham, Hagar and Sarah'.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192750632000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-912</urlname><id>641113</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>The Interfaith Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190160274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Interfaith Book Club October Meetup</name><id>6384991</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192577400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-912/events/6384991/</event_url></item>