<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Garden St &amp; Waterhouse St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>7813011791 (Chris' Cell)</phone><name>Cambridge Common</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>442822</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>IT'S amazing how everything looks so very different covered in snow. I woke up this morning and my world had changed completely. Like Alice, I tumbled down the rabbit-hole and ended up in a land where cats talk and cards prod me with spears. Like Sarah Williams, I followed the goblin king(sir David Bowie) through my bedroom window and found myself trapped in the ever-changing &lt;i&gt;Labyrinth&lt;/i&gt;. The fences, the dumpsters, the trees: all freshly dusted with white. A new world! A new order!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Honestly, I think it's kind of nice. The white, for now, is pristine and couth. It's a patchwork quilt covering Boston's grit and grime. The bums, the litter, the dirt: all blanketed in white. It makes me smile, walking in this Winter Wonderland, getting hit by falling snow drifts and slipping on unshoveled sidewalks. It makes me smile, cramming on the T with smelly bearded men (and women) and following the herd like a piece of meat. Ah, winter in New England. Can't be beat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon enough, though, the snow will turn a lovely shade of brown and stick around until April, unsightly discolored lumps that really make Boston shine. Wonderful! I can't wait! The snow will turn to murky slush and my love for Boston will quickly follow suit. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just because we're all dreaming of Spring doesn't mean frisbee won't go on. We are determined, friends! Ten inches of snow have nothing on our miles of conviction and determination. Stacked high and proud, we will play regardless of what Mother Nature has to say. We'll defy her and anyone else that stands in our way! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or not. Maybe we'll all just show up, wuss out, and go out to dinner. Either way, come prepared: Tuesday, January 15th, 2008. 7 PM, Cambridge Common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't get too wet out there, and bring an extra pair of socks. Your feet will thank you and, hopefully, not fall off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris (#2)&lt;br /&gt;781 301 1791&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Pretty sure we'll be the only ones smart enough to play frisbee in ten inches of snow.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim O'Neill</member_name><member_id>4585507</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214939046000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Disc Lovahs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonfrisbee</urlname><id>501407</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Frisbee</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200328366000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snow Disc on Cambridge Common</name><id>7112048</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200441600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonfrisbee/events/7112048/</event_url></item>