<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Reservation Fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We are on a mission . . .  to explore three of the top sushi restaurants in Brookline and assess the relative virtues of each one. Where's the best atmosphere? Where is the freshest sushi? The most artistic sushi creation? The most unconventional? And the best version of one or more classic maki (I suggest using the Spider Roll but will defer to whatever other standard the group chooses.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin our quest at Gengi Ya, on Harvard Ave, where all-natural and organic sushi has been a trademark for over a decade. We'll move on to Gari Fusion, a tiny and unconventional sushi place, also on Harvard Ave, where we can enjoy beer, wine or sake with some of the most exotic and original sushi creations in the greater Boston area. We'll conclude the evening at Fugakyu, on Beacon Street, where an elegant atmosphere and extensive variety of sake and cocktails will further expand our horizons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need not join us at all three locations as long as I know where to expect you (and where not!). We have a formal reservation at Fugakyu at 8 pm, but the first two gatherings will be more casual. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, your reservation fee will be factored into the tax and tip for our party, but I will only do this for the Fugakyu portion of the festivities. I highly recommend bringing cash to facilitate settling the bills at our first two stops.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup will only let me put in 1 location, so I'm listing the addresses/phone numbers for all three venues&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;               &lt;br /&gt;Genki Ya (5:30 p.m.)&lt;br /&gt;398 Harvard St&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA 02446&lt;br /&gt;(617) 277-3100&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GARI Japanese Fusion Restaurant (6:45 p.m.)&lt;br /&gt;187 Harvard Street, Brookline MA 02446 &lt;br /&gt;(617) 277-2999&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fugakyu Japanese Cuisine (8 p.m. reservation)&lt;br /&gt;1280 Beacon St (On Beacon St in Brookline Near Coolidge Corner) &lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA 02446 &lt;br /&gt;(617) 963-0323&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Meetup tent card on our table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284420306000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283568954000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Sushi Crawl in Brookline</name><id>14652467</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284325200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/14652467/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/a/3/global_17707955.jpeg</photo_url></item>