<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>87 Perkins Row</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01983</zip><lat>42.631830</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-887-9264</phone><name>Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Topsfield</city><id>669386</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.925970</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's been a few years since I've been to the bird sanctuary, so I'd like to go back.  At the bird sanctuary, birds have been known to eat from your hands, so you may want to bring bird food. Hopefully the bugs aren't excessive, but just in case, make sure you bring bug spray. If you plan to feed the birds, please do not put bug spray on your hands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the  Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located 30 miles north of Boston, Ipswich River is Mass Audubon's largest sanctuary, encompassing 2,267 acres of woods, meadows, and wetlands. Eight miles of the Ipswich River meander through the sanctuary. A program barn provides comfortable seating for indoor programs, and the nature center overlooks an attractive bird habitat garden. Our outreach programs include: Birds of Massachusetts, Butterflies, The Ipswich River, Wetland Communities, Animals of the North Shore, Vernal Pools, and Invasive Plants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$4 for nonmember adults;&lt;br /&gt;$3 for nonmember children (3-12) and seniors &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston and the south: Take Rt I-95 north to exit 50 and follow Rt 1 north. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97, turn right onto Rt 97 south (toward Beverly and Danvers). Follow Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the north: Take Rt I-95 south to exit 53A and follow Rt 97 south. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97 in Topsfield, stay on Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile, and the sanctuary is on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool From Nashua:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be leaving the Exit 6 Welcome Center at 12:00 PM.  Please indicate in your RSVP if you plan to carpool.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or less than 4 YES RSVP's cancels.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224523030000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216245237000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FAN Event: Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary </name><id>8353886</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224349200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8353886/</event_url></item>