<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Bad Boy Made Good: The Revival of George Antheil’s 1924 Ballet Mécanique&lt;/b&gt; directed  by Ron Frank (2003, 74 min.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Honestly, I had no idea what to call this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Scored for 16 synchronized player pianos, two pianists, seven percussionists, seven electric bells, three airplane propellers, and one siren, the piece was a thundering, abrasive noise-fest unlike any heard before, with about 630 time-signature changes in its 1,240 measures.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ballet Mécanique called for technology that didn't exist at the time. It took a forward-thinking music publisher, a music technologist, a modern player-piano manufacturer, and the latest in computer technology before the piece was heard the way the composer wanted it-seventy-five years after it was written. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the link to the trailer where you can decide if it is either mesmerizing or annoying :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Eo0H8ztju78&amp;amp;feature=related" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; George Antheil was an American composer who wrote the music for a number of Hollywood films during the 30's and 40's, most notably Cecil B. DeMille's Union Pacific and Nicholas Ray's In a Lonely Place . In the 1920's he mixed with many of the major artists of his day, including James Joyce, Gertrude Stein, Ernest Hemingway, Pablo Picasso, Salvador Dali, and Eric Satie. In particular, he befriended Ezra Pound, who became his unofficial publicist, and the Russian composer Igor Stravinsky, his major musical influence. His musical output of the time, partly inspired by the Dada movement and the Italian Futurist composers, includes such percussive, mechanistic works as the &amp;quot;Airplane Sonata,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Death of the Machines,&amp;quot; and the &amp;quot;Sonata Sauvage.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;After the rediscovery of the original score of &amp;quot;Ballet Mecanique&amp;quot; by William Holab , the idea for the new performance was born. &lt;b&gt;Bad Boy Done Good&lt;/b&gt; -- directed and edited by Ron Frank, written and produced by Paul D. Lehrman (the MIDI expert who used computer-based MIDI technology to synchronize the 16 pianos), and narrated by Tony Kahn -- mixes scenes from the performance with interviews of various composers, musicians, and scholars and vintage footage and photos. It's a compelling look at a fascinating man -- essential viewing for lovers of 20th century music and a great introduction for those of us whose tastes are less noisily inclined. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the way, with actress Hedy Lamarr, George Anheil invented a jam-proof missile guidance system, the principles of which are used today in the spread-spectrum technology of cell phones. New England Film.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the film we'll go to a nearby eatery for our discussion-wish there was a restaurant serving 3-alarm  Chile con Carne. Anyway- hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/wink.gif' border='0' alt='wink' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be holding a Meetup sign near the front row at the end of the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255046687000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1920's Dada Music Extravaganza</name><id>11584582</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257632100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11584582/</event_url></item>