<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You are invited to a day of fun (and sun!) and artistry at Elm Bank (owned by the Massachusetts Horticultural Society) in Wellesley, Massachusetts, on June 12 (rescheduled from June 5 due to unstable weather). We will begin our day at 11:30 a.m. Stay as long as you like (Elm Bank closes at dusk). If you plan to attend, please RSVP on the calendar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be a day of journaling, watercolor painting, photography, drawing, walking in the gardens, daydreaming, conversing — whatever your heart desires! Please bring a picnic luncheon as well. (And since this is World Environment Day, let’s make sure all our activities are litter-free.) The Massachusetts Horticultural Society charges $5.00 admission, so please be sure to bring that as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elm Bank has several lovely gardens (including Weezie’s Garden, the Bressingham Garden, the Italianate Garden, and — of course — the Goddess Garden), sculpture, and walking paths. So bring your journal, your watercolor pad, your sketchpad, or your camera, and let the artistry flow. Or you can just sit in the sun, look at all the colorful blooms, and relax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details (including where to meet) to come later. Watch the Message Board and your e-mail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about Elm Bank, as well as directions, visit www.masshort.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll figure something out.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda</member_name><member_id>313324</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1276433169000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269547089000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Day of Outdoor Art &amp; Relaxation </name><id>12992478</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276356600000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/12992478/</event_url></item>