<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>207 Amory Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.316719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boylston Congregational Church</name><city>Jamaica Plain</city><id>9585882</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103134</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A few of us from Maine are planning to go down to Boston for this gathering focused on Transition and Resilience-Building across New England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area below to organize carpools (I'm suggesting 7am from Marginal Way Park and Ride in Portland, unless you want to go down the night before).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the event details I've received from the organizer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello Transition-ers and Resilience-Builders,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Save the date! Join people from Transition and resilience efforts across New England for a day of learning, story-sharing, connecting, and organizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 New England Transition and Resilience Gathering (&lt;a href="http://transitionus.org/event/new-england-transition-and-resilience-gathering"&gt;full event link here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note, this meetup is just for organizing carpools.  If you want to attend this event (which is free) you also need to register with the event organizers here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=b5yl6lfab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e6en7xske37e3416"&gt;http://events.r20.constantcontact.com/register/event?llr=b5yl6lfab&amp;amp;oeidk=a07e6en7xske37e3416&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, October 20, 2012  9:30am - 5pm, Coffee and Lunch Provided Exact Address TBD Jamaica Plain, Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 Convened by Transition Keene, Transition Newburyport, the Jamaica Plain New Economy Transition, and the New England Grassroots Environment Fund (NEGEF)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Thanks to the excellent work of activists and organizers across the region, New England is home to many thriving grassroots efforts to create economic and environmental justice by transitioning away from fossil fuels towards sustainable food, energy, and transportation systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 How might we increase the effectiveness of our work by connecting with one another?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us on Saturday, October 20th as we consider this exciting question. You’ll have the chance to meet folks from across New England, share stories, think systemically about the region, and consider next steps. There will be plenty of opportunities for informal conversation and connection.  Together, we will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hear stories and lessons from other Transition and resilience efforts, and share your own!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify possible training needs your group may have, from group development to community organizing to small business planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dialogue with capacity-building trainers from NEGEF and the expanded team of certified Transition Trainers in the Northeast about what learning modules might be helpful for your initiative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss how we might increase the resilience of our region as a whole in terms of food, energy, transportation, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn about regional planning that is already underway and consider how our efforts might link to such planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss how we might jointly benefit by creating a way to connect and communicate with one another going forward, and what shape that might take.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A member of one of the convening organizations will follow up with you shortly to discuss this gathering. Please feel free to spread the word to others in your initiative or network. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you or someone else from your initiative would like to convene or help plan this event, we welcome your involvement! Please reply to this email or call 617.477.8630 x307.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel stipends and some in-home hospitality in Boston are available. Please contact Sarah Byrnes (sarah@localcircles.org, 617.477.8630 x307) for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are also invited to a potluck with members of the Jamaica Plain New Economy Transition on the evening of October 19. We’ll hear stories from Transition Initiatives around New England. Please indicate in your RSVP if you plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more info and to RSVP, contact Sarah Byrnes - sarah@localcircles.org, 617.477.8630 x307. &lt;br /&gt;

 Thank you,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah Byrnes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jamiaca Plain New Economy Transition (JP NET)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resilience Circles Organizer, Institute for Policy Studies New England&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352251724000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345566957000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carpool to New England Transition &amp; Resilience Gathering</name><id>78707122</id><duration>43200000</duration><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350730800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/78707122/</event_url></item>