<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Woodland Road</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.457657</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781)439-1623</phone><name>Spot Pond Boating</name><city>Stoneham</city><id>1024754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088931</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For those of you who missed David's outing in July, there is a second chance! Join us for &lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;3 hours of casual kayaking&lt;/span&gt; that will include a ½ hr break for some lunch. Spot Pond has smooth, well-protected water, and it is large enough for us to easily enjoy a couple hours of kayaking. There is even an island to which we will make a visit. This will be a great chance to learn about somewhere you can rent kayaks right outside of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;

 People who have taken advantage of the Groupon offer can share their cost and the time with others who didn't sign up for the discount (Boating in Boston has informed me that the 5 hours must be used at one time but they can be shared with others). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;RSVP: Stephanie, smitchell@mosaicofmass.org&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;MEET:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;11 AM at the Spot Pond Boating Center at 4 Woodland Ave&lt;/span&gt; beyond the Stone Zoo. Bring something with you to eat and drink. Personal Flotation Devices will be provided with the rentals and it will be a requirement to wear them. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; 1 Groupon Deal was purchased and can be divided to help defray costs. Kayak rentals are $15 hr. Additional $5 for guests, which can be credited toward a Mosaic membership costing $25.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>12107851</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346022809000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345482327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayaking on Spot Pond -  Part II</name><id>78550572</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345993200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/78550572/</event_url></item>