<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Longwood Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.336981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Armenise Ampitheatre - Harvard Medical School</name><city>Boston</city><id>725373</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103103</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/1/4/event_55467412.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Calling all nerds and members of the Starfleet Academy!&amp;nbsp; This week's Science in the News lecture is Toward the Final Frontier of Manned Space Flight.&amp;nbsp; Join us in going where no man has gone before (or at least to the Longwood Medical Area).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you not familiar with SITN's lecture format, lectures are free, accessible, and open to the public. All lectures are given entirely by graduate students at Harvard and focus on hot topics in science research and news.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All lectures are on Wednesdays starting at 7 PM at the Armenise Amphitheater at Harvard Medical School. They are 2 hours in length, with a 10 minute break in between.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They will have light refreshments before the lecture (coffee, tea, cookies, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best way to get there is by T.&amp;nbsp; The closest Green Line stops are the E train at Longwood Medical Area, and the D train at Longwood.&amp;nbsp; The Harvard Medical School Quadrangle is on Longwood Avenue, across from the half traffic circle at Avenue Louis Pasteur.&amp;nbsp; The Armenise Amphitheater is the first building on the left (facing into the quadrangle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is parking at the Masco Garage at 375 Longwood.&amp;nbsp; Evening rate is $7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/quadmap.jpg"&gt;HMS Quadrangle Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/images/maps/LMAmap.jpg"&gt;Longwood Medical Area Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;msa=0&amp;amp;msid=101729904914405135624.000439a3efaa5a627500c&amp;amp;om=1&amp;amp;ll=42.338832,-71.10549&amp;amp;spn=0.011579,0.020921&amp;amp;source=embed"&gt;Interactive Google Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masco.org/directions/lma-public-parking"&gt;Masco Parking Garage Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll gather on the benches outside the main entrance of the Courtyard Cafe (or in the lobby if it's wet out). I will have a meetup sign. We should meet at 6:30 so we can go in and have refreshments before the lecture.&amp;nbsp; Afterwards, we can go to Bertucci's down the street for more food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a maximum of 25 RSVPs.&amp;nbsp; If you're on the waiting list, it doesn't mean you can't come to the lecture (it is open to the public, after all) - it just means I won't be looking for you, because I can only keep track of so many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us on the benches outside the main entrance of the Courtyard Cafe. I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1317917204000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315865311000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SITN Lecture - Toward the Final Frontier of Manned Space Flight</name><id>33285572</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317853800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/33285572/</event_url></item>