<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Quincy Market Building</address_2><address_1>1 Clinton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360783</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 267-8080</phone><name>Dick's Last Resort Faneuil Hall Marketplace</name><city>Boston</city><id>867477</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053787</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>***EVENT UPDATE - - Due to the popularity of Dick's Last Resort Mardi Gras Party, we have over 125 people between the 6 invited groups who have RSVP'd Yes or Maybe for this event. On Monday morning Dick's needs an exact number for the 6:30 Dinner Reservation. Please Update your RSVP to &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; followed by the comment &amp;quot;6:30 pm Dinner.&amp;quot; with guest names if you want to be seated at the reserved tables for dinner. Only those who RSVP for dinner will be seated in this section. All guests arriving later are welcome to hang at the bar, join us in our section as others depart, or be seated elsewhere if capacity permits. Dick's can not guarantee additional seating due to space limitations. RSVP's for this event will be closed on Monday morning when Dick's contacts us for an RSVP count and guest list. There may be lines so RSVP now or ASAP before Monday. THE RESERVATION FOR ALL 6 GROUPS HAS BEEN MADE UNDER THE RED SOX NATIVES.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event takes place Rain, Snow or Shine!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an Annual event at Dick's Last Resort. It is always crazy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Happy Hour will be attending along with my Red Sox Natives and several other groups including Social Fun, The Skidaddler's Ski &amp;amp; Sports Club, The Boston Gingers, The Booze Club.... We will have ONLY ONE RESERVED SECTION FOR THOSE ORDERING DINNER AND DRINKS at 6:30 p.m. Later arrivals can join us any time in our section or hang at the bar. We expect to be there well into the night as the live music stops after 11 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check the event calendar for future updates on this event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Circle February 16 in your black book cuz that's the day confetti and multi-colored beads will be flung as we celebrate Mardi Gras Madness 2010 at Dick's Last Resort. The wearing of feathers and masks will be encouraged as party-goers rule from quitin time til whenever. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to expect??? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No cover &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Live entertainment by Sidewalk Driver from 8 - 11 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2.75 Southern Comfort Hurricane Drinks &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$3.50 Harpoon IPA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free stuff (feathery masks. doubloons, beads, and other junk) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dick's full menu available for purchase &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Servers dressed in their most garish garb &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Characters (some flashing?) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discounted parking at the Garage at 75 State Street (Take the T, please) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There may be lines! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is sponsored by Harpoon Brewery so that insures it will be good. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get thre when you can and hang as long you're able. Don't be shy, say hi to your fellow happy ones. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're encouraged to bring a friend or two or three or four or more.....please add the number of guests with your RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link with the drink &amp;amp; appetizer menu, &lt;a href="http://boston.dickslastresort.com/downloads/Menu%20PDFs/Apps-Drinks/Boston%20Appetizer%20and%20Drinks.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://boston.dicksla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out this link, it is the dinner menu, &lt;a href="http://boston.dickslastresort.com/downloads/Menu%20PDFs/Dinner/Boston%20Dinner.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://boston.dicksla...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://mbta.com/...&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hopstop.co...&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. Aquarium (blue line), Haymarket (green &amp;amp; orange lines), State (orange &amp;amp; blue lines), Government Center (blue &amp;amp; green lines), and South Station (red line &amp;amp; commuter rail) subway stations are no more than a ten (10) minute walk away. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;AS ALWAYS YOU MUST MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there with the others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fenway Frank &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In a Reserved Section or at the Bar earlier </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266536458000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>38</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264559216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fat Tuesday &amp; Mardi Gras Madness 2010 at Dick's Last Resort</name><id>12434426</id><headcount>84</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266363000000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/12434426/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/c/b/global_8871019.jpeg</photo_url></item>