<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>285 Church Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.769122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Clare Gallery</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1070422</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.678352</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I really enjoy the reflective coziness of the Clare Gallery at Franciscan Center.  This opening should be very nice, including a talk and video presentation by the artist.  I copied this directly from the Franciscan Center's email announcing the exhibit: &lt;br /&gt;------------- &lt;br /&gt;Dear Friends of the Clare Gallery, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As we begin this new year, it is a treat and a blessing to showcase the work of Hartford artist John Karrer. His photography, along with his writings, provide an intimate portrait of this beautiful city and its surrounding area. Some believe Hartford has been left behind by the Creator. John shows us the Creator never left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us for an artist talk and reception Tuesday, February 1, 5:30-7:30 p.m. John will share an inspirational short video and his artistic philosophy of &amp;quot;seeing creation&amp;quot; in your daily life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Karrer has lived in the North End of Hartford for the last 40 years. Upon retiring from Weaver High school in 2002, he began a daily routine of morning walks in the woodlands of Hartford and the Greater Hartford area accompanied by his dog and a digital camera. His photography and writing capture the beauty and mystery of nature. The images and text stand side-by-side creating a narrative of John's experiences. Additionally, both help to communicate the spirituality and awe inherent in nature. Seldom is John far into his walks before he begins to experience the presence of what John calls The Creator. John states, &amp;quot;I am never more at ease and comfortable than on these walks-I feel the presence of The Creator. These interactions have strengthened my faith and made prayer more meaningful.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;----------------- &lt;br /&gt;The more general website for more info:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://spsact.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://spsact.org/...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The photo shown here is &amp;quot;Misty Morning Light.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297938536000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295833886000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hartford Artist John Karrer Opening</name><id>16158965</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297809000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/16158965/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/5/global_21014869.jpeg</photo_url></item>