<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Your Office or Home</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.358429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Virtual Event (replay available)</name><city>Boston</city><id>8340092</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059776</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/9/2/8/event_155455592.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The topic of this event is how to get compelling testimonials that attract clients. We'll talk about the art and science of testimonials and case studies including how to overcome your reluctance to ask for them. You'll come away with a simple, repeatable process that really works to get powerful testimonials – tasty testimonials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Marketing Cafe™ is the online radio show that features simple, yet highly effective ideas&lt;/strong&gt; for solopreneurs and small business owners like you who want to make a good living while making a difference in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; Thursday, Sept. 6, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 12 noon Eastern Time &lt;br /&gt;

 (&lt;strong&gt;48 hour replay&lt;/strong&gt; available if your schedule doesn't cooperate).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The featured guest speaker is Grace Judson.&lt;/strong&gt; Grace describes herself as a process-oriented intuitive word nerd. She blends a logical, analytical approach to helping her clients with a deep intuitive understanding of the value they offer. This combination, along with her writing skills, means she helps her clients go deep in discovering the power of their best work and the ways that their businesses are ready to stretch and grow into something even bigger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your host is marketing results coach Mark Reinert,&lt;/strong&gt; founder of Authentic Business Growth, LLC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;During this program you will learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategies to move beyond the common testimonials that bore people.&lt;/strong&gt; You already know those &lt;em&gt;'she was just great!'&lt;/em&gt; statements aren't helpful, but how do you get clients to say more productive things? (Now, you'll know.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How gathering testimonials is both an art (skill) and a science&lt;/strong&gt; (where you can repeat simple processes with good results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 3 things testimonials can do&lt;/strong&gt; for your prospective clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role of doubt in testimonials.&lt;/strong&gt; You'll be surprised at how doubt can can actually help you (but only if you do it right.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The single biggest mistake&lt;/strong&gt; most people make with testimonials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three tools that can help you get over your feelings of reluctance&lt;/strong&gt; to ask for testimonials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A simple, repeatable process&lt;/strong&gt; for gathering testimonials and case studies that speak powerfully in your client's voice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Show Access Info here:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk"&gt;http://wp.me/P29Qf9-rk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Reinert</member_name><member_id>7305695</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346959329000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonSmallBusiness</urlname><id>1319989</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Small Business Success Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346706254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How to Get Tasty Testimonials that Attract Clients</name><id>80670192</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346947200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonSmallBusiness/events/80670192/</event_url></item>