<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>802036</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the Kendall's website:&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Forks Over Knives&lt;/em&gt; examines the profound claim that most, if not  all, of the degenerative diseases that afflict us can be controlled, or  even reversed, by rejecting our present menu of animal-based and  processed foods. The major storyline traces the personal journeys of Dr.  T. Colin Campbell, a nutritional scientist from Cornell University, and  Dr. Caldwell Esselstyn, a former top surgeon at the world renowned  Cleveland Clinic. Inspired by remarkable discoveries in their young  careers, these men conducted several groundbreaking studies. Their  separate research led them to the same startling conclusion:  degenerative diseases like heart disease, type 2 diabetes, and even  several forms of cancer, could almost always be prevented&amp;mdash;and in many  cases reversed&amp;mdash;by adopting a whole foods, plant-based diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think this is probably an informational more than visual experience.&amp;nbsp; But if the subject speaks to you, join us...interestingly the critics haven't liked it nearly as much as the audiences have.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside the particluar theater without a sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan D.</member_name><member_id>6395817</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306013864000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305628140000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Forks Over Knives - time change</name><id>18671321</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306009800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/18671321/</event_url></item>