<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>cross street is Washington Street in Dudley Station</address_2><address_1>12 Dade Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02119</zip><lat>42.331779</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 445-0900</phone><name>Haley House Cafe</name><city>Roxbury </city><id>1088485</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.081993</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coloroffilm.com/"&gt;The Color of Film Collaborative&lt;/a&gt; in partnership with the &lt;a href="http://www.haleyhouse.org/pg/show/id/13"&gt;Haley House&lt;/a&gt; periodically present documentaries and narrative films via Dinner and a Movie. The next offering is scheduled for Saturday June 16, 2012 and is one of the Roxbury International Film Festival screenings. Let's get together and enjoy each others company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase tickets for $26.87 (includes dinner and movie but not beverages) at &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/251678"&gt;http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/251678&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinner will be served at 7:00 PM. The menu hasn't been determined but I'm certain whatever is served will be delicious for both carnivores and vegetarians. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Beer, wine and non-alcoholic beverages will be available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film, Road to Apartheid is about Ana Nogueira a white South African and Eron Davidson a Jewish Israeli. Drawing on their first-hand knowledge of the issues, the producers take a close look at the apartheid comparison often used to describe the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. Their film breaks down the rhetorical analogy into a fact-based comparison, noting where the analogy is useful and appropriate, and where it is not. There are many lessons to draw from the South African experience relevant to conflicts all over the world. This film is as much a historical document of the rise and fall of apartheid, as it is a film about why many Palestinians feel they are living in an apartheid system today, and why an increasing number of people around the world agree with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another timely film since our major group trip is to South Africa this August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Transit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://mbta.com/"&gt;MBTA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.hopstop.com/?city=boston"&gt;Hop Stop&lt;/a&gt; to create your route by public transit. &lt;br /&gt;

Orange Line subway to Ruggles Station then any bus to Dudley Station&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;tab=wl"&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; to arrange your driving directions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking lot on Dade Street as well as along Washington Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/a/9/event_16789577.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would also like you to know the &lt;a href="http://www.roxburyfilmfestival.org/index.php"&gt;Roxbury International Film Festival&lt;/a&gt; (RIFF) showcases and honors the work of emerging and established filmmakers of color as well as films important to our community. It has become the largest festival in New England dedicated to celebrating this genre. This is always a great time with fascinating people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run time is Thursday June 14th through Sunday June 17th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You can find us by texting or calling me (617) 445-7549</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339897418000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338481774000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner and A Movie on Saturday June 16th</name><id>67118222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339885800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/67118222/</event_url></item>