<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56 Hampshire Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.660774</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Portland Food Coop</name><city>Portland</city><id>2593311</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.252762</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Portland Food Coop's work on getting the new space ready at 56 Hampshire Street continues, so we have chosen a new date for our Open House. You may have seen an earlier date of July 28th posted in the newsletter, but things won't be quite as buttoned up as we'd like them to be by then. Since August is a month where most people are away at camps and on vacation, we've landed on a new date of&amp;nbsp;
&lt;strong&gt;September 1, 2011&lt;/strong&gt;.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;The Open house is free and open to the public (bring your friends!), with food, beverages, live music and mingling. &amp;nbsp;We'll have a photo booth set up to capture your lovely faces, and we're inviting special guests and the press. We'll send out an email closer to the date asking for volunteers to help out with decorations and finger food, please help us if you can!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;We're so excited to show off our new space; it's come a long way since construction started in transforming a former tobacco factory into the new home of the Portland Food Coop. And by September 1, we'll be ready to show it off to everyone. Have you stopped by yet to see progress? Stefan Apse, our project manager, is there most days and you can always stop by and say hi. We're also posting photos of the volunteers and construction on our Facebook page, so check us out there. (Are you a fan on Facebook? Please "like" the Portland Food Coop to keep up with progress on the space and other news!)
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
 &lt;br /&gt;Open House!
 &lt;br /&gt;Free and open to the public
 &lt;br /&gt;Thursday, September 1, 2011
 &lt;br /&gt;56 Hampshire Street, Portland
 &lt;br /&gt;5:00pm - 8:00pm
 &lt;br /&gt;Food, beverages, live music
 &lt;br /&gt;Please bring a friend and come see our new home!&lt;/strong&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;We hope to see you there!
 &lt;br /&gt;The Membership and Outreach Committees of&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;The Portland Food Coop
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;--&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Portland Food Co-op (
&lt;a href="http://www.portlandfoodcoop.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.portlandfoodcoop.org&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315760245000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310747365000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open House at New Portland Food Coop Location</name><id>25858431</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314910800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/25858431/</event_url></item>