<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The official screening time is 4:45.Also, the film has been rated NC-17 for sexually explicit themes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From director Ang Lee (Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon, Brokeback Mountain, Sense and Sensibility and who can forget- The Hulk)&lt;br /&gt;Lust, Caution  is an espionage thriller set in WWII-era Shanghai. Asian cinema icon Tony Leung (Hero) stars as Mr. Yee, a powerful political figure in 1940s Shanghai. Tang Wei, a rising star in mainland China, makes her feature film debut as a young woman enlisted as a secret agent to seduce and assassinate Mr. Yee, who works for the Japanese puppet government. Co-starring Joan Chen and Wang Leehom.  Kendall description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Going back to his Taiwanese roots, while using all the experience he has accumulated in the U.S. as an indie and mainstream Hollywood director, Lee has made an erotically-charged melodrama-thriller. The screenplay, by Wang Hui-ling and James Schamus (a regular Lee collaborator and also credited as producer here), is based on the short story by the revered Chinese author Eileen Chang, concerning the fate of a seemingly ordinary woman.&amp;quot; Emanuel Levy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a complete review: &lt;a href="http://www.rollingstone.com/reviews/movie/11772554/review/16496973/lust_caution_se_jie" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rollingsto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make- after the film Tom will be holding a meetup sign near the front row and then its off to a local restaurant to discuss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192484890000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190677577000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Lust, Caution by Ang Lee</name><id>6420676</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1192308300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6420676/</event_url></item>