<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Daniel St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06460</zip><lat>41.223049</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-874-7947</phone><name>Stonebridge</name><city>Milford</city><id>664364</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.055939</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let us have a night to just listen to some 80s &lt;br /&gt;Music &amp;amp; relax.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.thefugitivesband.com/&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;They will be at the Stonebridge &lt;br /&gt;50 Daniel St. Milford, CT&lt;br /&gt;203 874 7947&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;www.stonebridgerestaurant.com/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.danielstreetclub.com/&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In Downtown Milford on Friday, November 16.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have a Paranormal Meet Up on Saturday,&lt;br /&gt;But Friday night is a wind down night. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The band usually starts later in the evening around  9 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will give the directions to the Restaurant,&lt;br /&gt;But it has a small parking area.&lt;br /&gt;I usually park over by the Milford Green.&lt;br /&gt;The Milford Green is included in the directions below.&lt;br /&gt; If you are parked by the Milford Green, then walk towards&lt;br /&gt;The Subway Restaurant. &lt;br /&gt; Keep walking straight down the street on the right hand side around the Subway&lt;br /&gt;Towards the Milford Library and Fire Station &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;You will be going towards the Stonebridge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Directions&lt;br /&gt;I 95 Northbound &lt;br /&gt;I 95 North to Exit 36 (Plains Road) End of Ramp Take Right. &lt;br /&gt;Continue Straight Thru Light, Then thru Two Stop Signs. &lt;br /&gt;After Second Stop Sign, Go over Rail Road Bridge to Light, &lt;br /&gt;Take Left onto Bridgeport Avenue, &lt;br /&gt;Continue Straight thru Milford Green thru Second Light. &lt;br /&gt;Bear Left at Fork in Road. &lt;br /&gt;The Restaurant is on the Immediate Right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I 95 Southbound &lt;br /&gt;I 95 South to Exit 39A (Route 1 South). &lt;br /&gt;Go Under Thruway &amp;amp; Merge all the way to the Left Lane. &lt;br /&gt;Continue Forward onto Cherry Street. Count Four Lights. &lt;br /&gt;Turn Left at Citizen Bank onto Gulf Street. &lt;br /&gt;At First Light, Turn Right onto New Haven Avenue. &lt;br /&gt;Follow to Rotary. &lt;br /&gt;The Restaurant is on the Immediate Right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merritt Parkway (Northbound or Southbound) &lt;br /&gt;Proceed on the Parkway to Exit 54 (the Connector); &lt;br /&gt;Take First Exit Off of Connector (95 Southbound). &lt;br /&gt;Take First Exit (Exit 36 ? Plains Road) &lt;br /&gt;Follow I 95 Directions as stated above to the Stonebridge Restaurant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If their drummer, Mark, ever gets a computer, then he will become a&lt;br /&gt;Member of our group.&lt;br /&gt;If I ever get a chance to give the Forbidden Zone Collectables Store&lt;br /&gt;Story, then I will explain how he is a co founder of this group.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195437732000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192588788000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Listen to some 80s Music &amp; Relax in Milford</name><id>6563870</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195264800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6563870/</event_url></item>