<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>225 South St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01267</zip><lat>42.708329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>413.458.2303</phone><name>Clark Art Institute</name><city>Williamstown</city><id>800201</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.216465</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Day trip to Willamstown, MA to view the Picasso looks at Degas exhibit at the Clark, have a great lunch and explore the town. This is a carpool trip, meaning that we will need to take as many cars and have as many drivers as needed for the group. I will drive and can take 3 other people (one spot is already taken). When you RSVP, please say if you will drive and how many you can take. I expect we will share the driving in each car, as the trip is 2 and 1/2 hours each way - very scenic along the Mohawk trail (Rte 2) &lt;br /&gt;We may need to limit the attendance once we reach max capacity for the cars. We''l see :) &lt;br /&gt;Plan to meet for departure at 8 a.m.  in Concord at the Crosby's Market parking lot neat the Concord Train Depot on Sudbury Road. (Take Rte 2 west, turn right on Sudbury Road and follow to the lot on your right. Park in one of the commuter spots) &lt;br /&gt;We will plan to return to Concord, departing Williamstown around 5 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;Each person will be responsible for own museum admission ($15)  and food. Drivers will welcome donations for gas. &lt;br /&gt;Please do not RSVP Yes and then back out at the last minute as others may be depending on you. &lt;br /&gt;Thanks - Robin &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293805057000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Culture Vultures</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>culturevulturesBoston</urlname><id>1165987</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Culture Vultures - Singles over 50</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277821531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Day trip to Williamstown, MA -" Picasso Looks at Degas" at the Clark and lunch</name><id>13947416</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278849600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/culturevulturesBoston/events/13947416/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/6/b/global_16082411.jpeg</photo_url></item>