<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Take a right at the traffic circle</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.615929</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>TD/ Bank and Friendly's </name><city>Gloucester</city><id>3116401</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.661987</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join us for this Gorgeous ride along the coast of beautiful Cape Ann.&amp;nbsp; We will enjoy delightfully varying views of harbors, light houses, beaches, and salt marshes as we ride through the towns of Gloucester and Rockport.&amp;nbsp; The Historic Cape Ann.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The ride starts at Stage Fort Park, in Gloucester.&amp;nbsp; It will cover Gloucester, Rockport and Annisquam.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We will stop for a break (for Ice Cream or any snacks you may have brought) about halfway through at a little park in the center of Rockport; bring your own or buy from places nearby.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Afterwards let's go out for a late lunch in Gloucester.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will try to keep our pace roughly at 12 to 15 mile pace.&amp;nbsp; Will stop on occasion to make sure we have the group together.&amp;nbsp; If there seems to be a large gap between speeds we my have someone take off and lead the faster riders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is free parking right at Stage Fort Park and bathrooms are across from the parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things to bring:&amp;nbsp; Water, Sun Tan lotion, Money for lunch and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a ride for the super competitive as we do stop for everyone.&amp;nbsp; With that said we expect people to be able to ride 30 miles and be in reasonably good shape and to have good enough judgement to know if&amp;nbsp;this is or is not a ride for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No requirement for a road bike but probably not appropriate for a mountain bike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may reschedule if raining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that sign up for the ride I will email you cue sheets a few days before.&amp;nbsp; In the meantime I will be looking for a place for us to go for lunch afterwards.&amp;nbsp; IF anyone has suggestions that would be awesome.&amp;nbsp; Looking for a place reasonably priced and outdoor seating would be awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take 128 N&amp;nbsp;until you come to the traffic circle in Gloucester&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bear right heading to Gloucester (I believe that is Rte 127)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take an immediate right into the TDBank Parking lot go to the right of the building&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Head out back towards Friendly's&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park as far away from the businesses as possible so that their patrons can utilize the parking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again meeting time is at 10am Be ready to ride at 10:30 am.. The ride in reality is going to be about 28 miles we are cutting out a small section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the ride is over we will be heading to the Cape Anne Brew Pub for food and Libations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My phone number if you need to get a hold of me is 781-856-2933..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully Rob will send out a message too with his phone number in case you have trouble&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;getting a hold of me.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meeting time is 10am the ride will leave at 10:30 am.  Directions are listed below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rob Fox</member_name><member_id>4368625</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gary</member_name><member_id>10329460</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>11</waitlist_count><updated>1314579861000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312937729000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Ann Coaster Ride-30 Miles</name><id>28916231</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313935200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/28916231/</event_url></item>