<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>ROUTE 93</address_2><address_1>EXIT 2</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>42.793686</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>SALEM PARK N RIDE</name><city>Salem</city><id>1422891</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.221519</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ANYONE UP FOR  HOLIDAY TREAT?&lt;br /&gt; I have been to this parade a few times and found it very enjoyable and fun for those of us who refuse to grow up!  I would like to go again this year, and thought that some of you would enjoy it also.  If you’ve never been before, trust me that you will be pleasantly surprised.  &lt;br /&gt;Because of the distance to Portsmouth, let’s plan on carpooling from the Park n Ride at exit 2 in Salem NH.  We can plan of leaving at 4:30 to give us enough time to get to downtown Portsmouth, and find a good spot to watch the parade.  &lt;br /&gt;After the parade, we’ll go for food and drinks at Portsmouth Gas Light Co at 64 Market Street, downtown Portsmouth.  Our options will be fine dining or pizza.  I will leave that up to the group.&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP or call my cell, if you want to join us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or we can meet somewhere downtown Portsmouth, call my cell.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ClaireP  cell phone 603-247-0897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parade details from the Portsmouth web site: &lt;br /&gt;PORTSMOUTH, NH – The City’s 2010 annual illuminated Holiday Parade will be Saturday, December 4, and this year’s theme is “A Nautical Christmas” in recognition of Portsmouth’s maritime history and its status as official host community for the USS Virginia submarine undergoing maintenance at the Portsmouth Naval Shipyard, Mayor Tom Ferrini announced Monday.&lt;br /&gt;            The officers and crew of the sub will serve as grand marshals and prizes will be awarded to the entries that best reflect the nautical theme. The illuminated Holiday Parade traditionally takes place on the first Saturday evening in December, which this year is December 4, and is organized and directed by the City of Portsmouth.&lt;br /&gt;                       Floats, walking units and marching bands will join Santa Claus in the Holiday Parade that begins at 6 p.m. from Plaza 800 on Islington Street, proceeds down Islington Street to where it turns into Congress Street and then continues to Market Square and onto Pleasant Street before reaching its final destination of the South Playground. As many as 8,000 people are expected to line the 1.1-mile route.&lt;br /&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291502296000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289148938000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Portsmouth Holiday Parade</name><id>15368322</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291498200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/15368322/</event_url></item>