<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>Meetup.com Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>4.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all who attended the March NLP meetup.  It was another great meeting, this time focusing on the NLP tool/frame called Well-Formed Outcomes. In keeping with the spirit of NLP, rather than simply talking about it, we each tried out the well-formed outcome process on one of our own desired outcomes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For April: We're going to continue on with the theme of 'changing the world with NLP'.  We?ve talked about changing our internal state in February (circle of excellence), deciding what we want to do in March (well-formed outcomes), and now, in April, we?ll be talking about how we talk about it.  Language Patterns are one of the most powerful and most useful subsets of NLP ? we?re using language all the time!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fully going through NLP Language Patterns would be a week-long workshop in itself.  We?ll focus on 3 this month: verb tenses (aka verb relaxes), nominalizations/hypnotic words, and reversals.  By the end of the night, you will have a good start on shifting your and other?s perspective purely through the conscious use of language. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; To paraphrase Richard Bandler (one of the founders of NLP, and a master of language patterns):&lt;br /&gt;?I wonder just how very useful you will have found this evening when it is all over and all the information and skills you had needed has been successfully integrated into your brilliant un-conscious mind.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month's meetup does not depend on knowing about well-formed outcomes, or having attended last month's meeting.  It also does not presuppose that you know anything about NLP.  Everyone is welcome, from beginners to experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you.&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS  A reminder that the venue has changed.  In response to feedback, we are changing to a quieter, non-restaurant forum.  Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking.&lt;br /&gt;You can get directions here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing two flights of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177196611000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1174612091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Changing the World with NLP - Using Language Patterns</name><id>5596000</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177023600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/5596000/</event_url></item>