<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>53 Wall Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.309769</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 432-0148 </phone><name>Whitney Humanities Center Auditoriom</name><city>New Haven</city><id>957772</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.923866</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per month</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: chocolate"&gt;The Whitney Humanities Center is  the home of the Film Study Center and the primary venue for 35mm film screenings at Yale.  The Yale Film Society began to screen experimental and foreign films in 1958, and today it still organizes special screenings and invites filmmakers to campus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film portrays the holiday season,  I thought it would be nice for a December venue. Lets meet at 6:40 in the lobby of the auditorium,&lt;span style="color: red"&gt; &lt;b&gt;Those who would like to meet before the film for coffee we will be at Willoughby's Coffee at 6:00, Whitney Humanities Center is close, just at the other end of the block Church/Wall Streets.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Willoughby's Coffee&lt;br /&gt;258 Church Street&lt;br /&gt;New Haven&lt;br /&gt;corner of Church and Grove Street&lt;br /&gt;203-777-7400&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.willoughbyscoffee.com/locations.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.willoughby...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John Huston directed the movie, at eighty, from a wheelchair, jumping up to look through the camera, with oxygen tubes trailing from his nose to a portable generator; most of the time, he had to watch the actors on a video monitor outside the set and use a microphone to speak to the crew. Yet he went into dramatic areas that he'd never gone into before - funny, warm family scenes that might be thought completely out of his range. Huston never before blended his actors so intuitively, so musically.&amp;quot;  The film adaptation is largely faithful to James Joyce's short story, with some alterations made to the dialogue to aid the narrative for cinema audiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most significant change to the story was scriptwriter Tony Huston's inclusion of a new character, a Mr Grace, who recites an eighth-century Middle Irish poem, &amp;quot;Donal Óg&amp;quot; (tr. Lady Gregory: [2][3]. The effect of this is to act as catalyst for the &amp;quot;Distant Music&amp;quot; that provokes the memories Gretta and Gabriel discuss at the end of the film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Dead (USA, 1987) 83 min. 35mm.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;free&lt;br /&gt;John Huston's last film is a labor of love at several levels: an adaptation of perhaps one of the greatest pieces of English-language literature by one of Huston's favorite authors, James Joyce; a love letter to the land of his ancestors and the country where his children grew up; and the chance to work with his screenwriter son Tony and his actress daughter Anjelica. The film is delicate and unhurried, detailing a Christmas dinner at the house of two spinster musician sisters and their niece in turn-of-the-century Ireland, attended by friends and family. Among the visiting attendees are the sisters' nephew Gabriel Conroy and his wife Gretta. The evening's reminiscences bring up melancholy memories for Gretta concerning her first, long-lost love when she was a girl in rural Galway. Her recounting of this tragic love to Gabriel brings him to an epiphany: he learns the difference between mere existence and living... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yale.edu/whcfilms/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.yale.edu/w...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the lobby in front of the auditorium</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291353526000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287976746000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Dead</name><id>15217355</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291247100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/15217355/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/c/3/global_19042291.jpeg</photo_url></item>