<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Lansdowne Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347182</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.247.1222</phone><name>The Lansdowne Pub</name><city>Boston</city><id>1088408</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.094957</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Come and celebrate the holiday season with us! We will be enjoying drinks, some complimentary appetizers (you can also order dinner) and mingling with lots of of friendly and outgoing people.  We will relax, hang out and have fun. If you haven't been to a meet up in a while or are new to the group, this would be the perfect event to attend. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also be doing an ornament swap, so please bring a holiday ornament with you for the swap! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lansdowne is a great new pub on Landsdowne Street- very close to the T and plenty of parking in the area. The pub is donating appetizers for our group, but each guest is asked to chip in a few dollars to cover the cost of tip and tax for the appetizers. Each guest also pays for their own drinks and/or dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't make it for 6:30, please join us later. We will have a special area for our group. If you have trouble finding our group, please call Catherine at 774 232 0000. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will also be posted in a couple of other groups. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside pub.  If need to, please call 774 232 0000</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>23</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261270509000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259639296000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate the Season with a Holiday Party and Ornament Swap</name><id>11986931</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261092600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/11986931/</event_url></item>