<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Berlin Rd, Cromwell, CT</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06416</zip><lat>41.646690</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 265-4414</phone><name>Crowne Plaza Hotel</name><city>Cromwell</city><id>500475</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.730507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.ctreia.com/res/upload/pix_events/0/0/0/0/5/597.jpg" width="150" height="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Full details available at &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ctreia.com%2Fevents.php%3Fa%3Dv%26i%3D485&amp;amp;h=QAQEdYIci&amp;amp;s=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=485&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let this be your LAST Labor Day &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;Begin your road to Financial Freedom at CT REIA Monday September 10th.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could You Use An Unlimited Supply Of Money To Do All The Residential And Commercial Deals You Can Find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the September 2012 CT REIA Monthly Meeting, Alan Cowgill will show you how you can get all the money you need to buy single-family houses, commercial buildings, apartment complexes, or luxury homes, regardless of your credit or financial situation... within 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;You Will Learn: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* How to get all the money you need to buy single-family houses, commercial buildings, apartment complexes, or luxury homes, regardless of your credit or financial situation... within 30 days &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Crucial 5 steps to success, so that you can find all the private money you need: Build Credibility, Generate Leads, Secure Private Lenders, Buy/Sell Property, Pay Day &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* How to pre-screen your prospects and the "Magic" words to get them to commit &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Scripts you should use when talking to people you know, their voicemails, and/or referrals &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* Why these 4 commonly used types of financing can cripple your real estate business and how to stay away from them: Bank, Line of credit, Hard money lender, Creative financing &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;* How to do all of this with no monthly payments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Alan Cowgill: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Alan Cowgill started his career as a real estate investor in February of 1995, so he has over 11 years in real estate. Five years ago he went full time as a real estate investor and for the last 4 1/2 years he has done his deals exclusively using private lenders. Alan typically buys 5 houses/month and has bought or sold over 200 properties. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Alan is currently an author, a national speaker, and a private lending consultant. He's been featured in three newspaper articles about purchasing real estate through private lenders. He has appeared in three National Infomercials and he's more recently been published in two books titled "Walking with the Wise in Real Estate" and "Walking with the Wise Entrepreneur" where Donald Trump, Chuck Norris, Suzie Orman, Ron LeGrand and other well known figures also contributed to these books. 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347333923000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346246812000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT REIA Monthly Meeting: Unlimited Supply Of Money To Buy Real Estate</name><id>79888222</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>12600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347312600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/79888222/</event_url></item>