<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Mt. Auburn Street, 2nd Floor</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02472</zip><lat>42.365494</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-923-2800</phone><name>Watertown Center for Healing Arts</name><city>Watertown</city><id>1065386</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.183899</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I am thrilled to be offering this special Triple Goddess Puja with my dear friends and colleagues, Robyn Vogel and Penny Gold!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divine presence awaits you as we come together in celebration of St. Valentine.    &lt;br /&gt;Together we will invite the magic of LOVE into our ritual space and drink from her true blessings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Would you like to feel more connection to the Divine in your life?  &lt;br /&gt;* Do you long for more intimate connections?    &lt;br /&gt;* Are you ready to release that which blocks you from loving yourself and others more fully?   &lt;br /&gt;* Are you ready to experience more passion in your life than ever before?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this safe and sacred gathering you will have the opportunity to connect deeply with yourself, the Divine, and other beautiful souls through movement, meditation, breath and sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come and discover how meaningful connection - intimacy and love - is available right here, right now, any time you want it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Valentine Puja is open to singles and couples, beginners and seasoned practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may wish to wear comfortable, colorful clothing and bring a water bottle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive by 5:45 so we can begin on time. There is plenty of parking in the lot behind the studio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robyn Vogel&lt;/strong&gt;, MA, LMHC, of Tantric Healing Arts, is a Tantric Educator and Relationship Counselor. She loves love and has been helping others fall in love with themselves and others for twenty years! Robyn's workshops have been touted "healing, connecting, powerful and truly fantastic!"&amp;nbsp; She offers monthly Flirting with Heart workshops for women and Tantric Healing Arts gatherings for all to enjoy being in sacred ritual space together.&amp;nbsp; Most people that meet Robyn appreciate her deep compassion, open heart, and the way she holds sacred space for the depth of the human experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brynn Bishop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, of The Center for Passionate Living, is a Tantra Educator and Empowerment and Pleasure Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of body-mind integration and conscious relating. She guides people in clearing emotional blocks and awakening their vital energy to increase their capacity for intimacy and pleasure, and access their purpose and passion in life. &lt;/span&gt;Brynn&amp;rsquo;s workshops have been described as &amp;ldquo;welcoming, enlightening, transformative, empowering, heart opening and deeply nourishing.&amp;rdquo; Brynn is known for her wisdom, compassionate presence and mastery at having all aspects of the person feel safe, accepted, loved and whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Penny Gold&lt;/strong&gt; is a Certified Tantra Educator from Source School of Charles Muir, as well as a psychologist who has been helping people heal and grow relationships back into bliss for over 25 years. Penny was also on the board of BASSN (Boston Area of Sexuality and Spirituality Network) for many years and has led pujas for 3 years. &amp;nbsp;Penny is known for her warmth, passion and ability to bring together communities in a space of fun, safety and adventure.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299439106000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>It's time to release our armoring, open the heart and invite in love and connection!</why><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295919038000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Triple Goddess Valentine Puja: Opening to the Beloved</name><id>16172878</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296946800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/16172878/</event_url></item>