<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>12 Hampshire Ave</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.149565</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-509-2907</phone><name>Peters Foam Dome Home</name><city>Durham</city><id>1069031</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.932807</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, come out and learn how to build a solar hot water heater for under a hundred dollars or less!! I will teach you how to build one by using common hand tools. The solar hot water heater will produce about 20 gallons of water at 120 degrees in half an hour and 140 degrees in one hour. I'm estimating the whole process will take about two to three hours to build. If it is raining out I will reschedule the workshop! We will be joined by other meetup groups, so prepare to meet others who share a passion for saving money and being more sustainable! We will be having a potluck lunch so bring something to share. My home is still so new that the address may not be in "mapquest" or on a "GPS" system so you can use my neighbors house as an waypoint, use: "12 Hampshire Ave"in Durham I am right next to this address, I'm on the dirt road. Look for the blue mailbox. I will give a tour of my home and explain the basics of building your own home. We are asking for a donation of $5 for this event. If anyone has any questions don't hesitate to contact me at: 603-312-6735&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be having a workshop every month at my place. In September we will be&amp;nbsp;having a workshop on how to build your own "Wind Generator" &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315059913000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1312718503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Solar Hot  Water Workshop:  Build your own solar hot water heater!</name><id>28552001</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313845200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/28552001/</event_url></item>