<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Last year I tried getting groups together last season for a whale watch . It just didn't work out for some reason or another. So, let's give it another go!ot to be daunted, I am giving it another shot. &lt;br /&gt;Check out: www.7seaswhalewatch.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UPDATE 5/ 25:After sending out messages, posting this event on 5 sites, I do not have enough solid &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP for the discount. IF YOU DO WISH TO GO:  you will need to phone 7 Seas Whale Watch at 978.283.1776 to make your own reservation. The cost is: $45.00 (they discount to AAA, Military, Seniors, Educators, and more)   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRICE: $45.00 regular adult price  ( AAA discount $5.00 , Senior etc) &lt;br /&gt;Reservations are a MUST! &lt;br /&gt;Several discounts may apply &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Check Out : &lt;/b&gt;www.7seaswhalewatch.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Phone: 978-283-1776 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TIME: 1:00 is tentative ( I am writing this in MARCH and looking at last yr's schedule!!!) &lt;br /&gt;* I will update as soon as possible &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHAT TO BRING: It can get quite cold out on the water in May, so make sure to dress for it. Check the website for particulars&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK........ So, later on we can head over to Captain Carlo's for food and live entertainment outside on their fabulous , huge deck overlooking the harbor area!! . SUNDAYS ARE USUALLY 'REGGAE' ONES! Again, I will need to update what band will be playing. During the summer months it's sometimes reggae. &lt;br /&gt;Check out: wwwcaptaincarlos.com ( menu, pricing and entertainment) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;** NOTE: &lt;/b&gt;This event is shared among 5 meetup groups. I am hoping for a good turnout! Also, adults only.  This event is  weather permitting! I will be updating as we get closer to the date.&lt;br /&gt;Please check back. NEED TO CARPOOL? Add it to your RSVP or try contacting a fellow member near you.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will all meetup where we purchase tickets</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245935267000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237168547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Afternoon Whale Watch and More - Update: 5/25</name><id>9962489</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243789200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/9962489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/c/1/global_4288033.jpeg</photo_url></item>