<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>“Image Makers”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston Fashion Industry meetup subgroup&lt;br /&gt;for models, photographers, mua and stylist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group will spend more time shooting than meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Concept: a subgroup of the Boston Fashion industry meetup made up of members involved in creating images for fashion to collaborate on shoots.  I will start as the organizer of this group and hopefully others will volunteer to help organize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be a network of the people who make the print/video happen.  There will be production types:  photographers, videographers, mua, hair stylist , photo stylist and set designers; and talent: models and actors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are interested in participating in this group respond here. If you have questions send me an email at ron@positiveimage-boston.com or post on the message board at this thread.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The initial meeting will be at my studio: Positive Image.  We will discuss the “mission” of the group.  Models come prepared to be shot and shooters bring your cameras.  MUA bring your kit.  We will have a discussion first (no more than 1 hour) then we will shoot.  Photographers be prepared to provide low res digital images to the models for free so they can use them on their websites.  Models be prepared to sign a release for the photographers.  Experience level does not matter for all members of this group.  I expect some really experienced members and very inexperienced members. We will all learn from each other. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first meeting will be on Saturday Jan 24th at 11am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Positive Image&lt;br /&gt;135 Massachusetts Ave&lt;br /&gt;Boston&lt;br /&gt;617.542.2118&lt;br /&gt;We are on the corner of Mass ave and Boylston street,  diagonally across the street from the Hynes T stop on the green line.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ring the buzzer</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235087457000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232110803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>" IMAGE MAKERS GROUP"</name><id>9536758</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232812800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/9536758/</event_url></item>