<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT 3A</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.232529</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney and Thayer Woods</name><city>Cohasset</city><id>7285572</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.819710</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hike this special Trustees of Reservations property located in Cohasett and Hingham.  This hike offers many varied habitats including hardwoods forest, holly groves, open fields, a working farm, marshes, streams  and many large glacial boulders scattered thoughout the property.  The hike will also include the Milliken Memorial Path, designed in the 1920s which is lined with rhododendrons, azaleas, mountain laurel and other blooming shrubs brought in from more southerly climes, many of which should be flowering on hike day. The hike will also go through open fields to the top of Turkey Hill which offers great views of Hingham Bay, the Boston Harbor islands and the Boston skyline in the distance. This will also be our early lunch stop.  The hike will then continue throuth the 75 acre Weir River Farm property, which is a still active agricultural enterprise and through some historic sites included on that property. Later in the hike we will go through a series of interesting glacial erratics including Rooster Rock and Odes Den.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information can be found at these links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/whitney-thayer-woods.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/whitney-thayer-woods.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/weir-river-farm.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/weir-river-farm.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will be a relaxed one at a moderate pace with stops at some of the special places this hike has to offer. Estimated hiking time 4 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance appoximately 6-7 miles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs are welcome but they must be leashed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring lunch and snacks and one-two liters of water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet the Whitney Woods parking lot at 9:45 for a 10AM hike start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: From RT 3, take Exit 14(RT228) north for 6.5 miles through Hingham.  Take  right on RT 3A and follow for 3A south for 2 miles. Look for Parking lot on right opposite Sohier St in Cohasett.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going north on RT 3A thru Marshfield and Scituate is another option.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>From RT 3, take exit 14 and follow RT 228 North for 6.5 miles through Hingham. Turn right onto 3A South and follow for 2 miles. Look for entrance on right opposite Sohier St.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill Vickstrom</member_name><member_id>11406046</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338310328000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends of Myles Standish Forest</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>friendsofmylesstandishstateforest</urlname><id>1370268</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7399978638</group_lon><name>Friends of Myles Standish State Forest Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337472908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Memorial Day Hike - Whitney and Thayer Woods and Weir River Farm</name><id>65511612</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338212700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/friendsofmylesstandishstateforest/events/65511612/</event_url></item>