<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>781-740-6665</address_2><address_1>Martins Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.253452</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781.740.7233</phone><name>World's End</name><city>Hingham</city><id>1085516</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.871658</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So we'll take a rain, snow or shine walk at Hingham's Worlds End then go to the Wahlberg's family Restaurant Alma Nove for Drinks and Appetizers at the bar. I was told that we could order from the full menu in the bar area. I thought this would be easier to talk and mingle instead of a sit down meal. I hear the food is good but the menu is kinda pricey. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will post separate events for the walk and the restaurant just in case some can can only make it to one of the other. Please respond to both so I can make accurate reservations at the restaurant. Yes they asked me to make reservations - even for the bar. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes World’s End a special place? &lt;br /&gt;We think it’s the tree-lined carriage paths and sweeping views of the Boston skyline, only 15 miles away. The 251-acre coast-scape includes rocky shores, broad hillsides, and open fields bracketed by pockets of woodlands. The property is ideal for walking, picnicking, jogging, horseback riding, cross-country skiing, or simply enjoying nature and the outdoors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The retreating glacier helped create the geology of Boston Harbor, including the islands and the four spoon-shaped hills (called drumlins) that comprise World’s End. This landscape also features saltwater marshes, meadows, woodlands, and granite ledges covered with red cedars and blueberry thickets. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am a member of the Trustees of the Reservations and they have great properties. I suggest that if you like their properties please become a member. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/greater-boston/worlds-end.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alma Nove - www.almanovehingham.com/&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Roger L</member_name><member_id>7989869</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295914413000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1414</urlname><id>1281351</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7099990845</group_lon><name>South Shore Hike, Bike &amp; Social Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294009311000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>World's End Hike - Hingham - Then Cocktails at Alma Nove</name><id>15888522</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1295805600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1414/events/15888522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/0/c/global_20935804.jpeg</photo_url></item>