<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Steven Pinker&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rebecca Newberger Goldstein&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;present&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Beyond Belief:&lt;br /&gt;Science, Religion, Morality, and the Arts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store and Harvard Hillel are excited to host a conversation with cognitive scientist Steven Pinker and philosopher/novelist Rebecca Newberger Goldstein as they discuss big questions, such as: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What, if any, are the limits of science?&lt;br /&gt;Should religion step in where science falters?&lt;br /&gt;Why did Plato banish the poets? Was he right that the imagination is an impediment to knowledge?&lt;br /&gt;Does denying God doom you to moral relativism?&lt;br /&gt;Can atheists have spiritual experiences? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This event is free; no tickets are required.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Info: 617.661.1515&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media: 617.661.1424 ex.1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email: rbcass@harvard.com &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION: Harvard Hillel &lt;br /&gt;Beren Hall&lt;br /&gt;52 Mount Auburn St., Cambridge  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Steven Pinker, a native of Montreal, received his BA from McGill University in 1976 and his PhD in psychology from Harvard in 1979. After teaching at MIT for 21 years, he returned to Harvard in 2003 as the Johnstone Professor of Psychology. Pinker\'s experimental research on cognition and language won the Troland Award from the National Academy of Sciences, the Henry Dale Prize from the Royal Institute of Great Britain, and two prizes from the American Psychological Association. He has also received several honorary doctorates and numerous awards for graduate and undergraduate teaching, general achievement, and his critically acclaimed books The Stuff of Thought,  The Language Instinct, How the Mind Works, and The Blank Slate.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Rebecca Newberger Goldstein received her doctorate in philosophy from Princeton University. Her award-winning books include the novels The Mind-Body Problem, Properties of Light, and Mazel, and nonfiction studies of Kurt Gödel and Baruch Spinoza. She has received a MacArthur Foundation Fellowship and Guggenheim and Radcliffe fellowships, and she was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences in 2005. She lives in Massachusetts.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296255946000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268353541000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pinker Again: Unbelievable? - or Beyond Belief!</name><id>12853638</id><headcount>250</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269471600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12853638/</event_url></item>