<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/3/c/1/event_20866017.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;I'd like to celebrate my birthday in style, with the Patriots of course beating the Broncos ;) there is limited seating to watch the game, however if you don't care about the game, and want to play LCR at the table you can do that too...lol. Just mention in your reply or the question I've added if you need "Patriot seating" I can probably fit about 15 in my living room and of course another 10 at the dining table (no tv there). please bring something to share, or a scratch ticket for the hostess's birthday, as I will provide some goodies too. BYOB, and please park on the same side of the street as my house. see details of the game below... Patriots to host Broncos in AFC Divisional Playoff game The New England Patriots will host the Denver Broncos at Gillette Stadium on Saturday, January 14 at 8:00 for an AFC Divisional playoff game. The New England Patriots will host the Denver Broncos at Gillette Stadium on Saturday, January 14 at 8:00 for an AFC Divisional playoff game. As the number one seed in the AFC, New England plays the lower remaining seed. The Denver Broncos (8-8, #4 seed) defeated the Pittsburgh Steelers (12-4, #5 seed) 29-23 in overtime during the Wild Card playoff GO PATRIOTS!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send directions and my phone number, the day before, to those who say they are coming...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326590124000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326204395000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Watch the Pats on my Birthday on my new 37" TV ;)</name><id>47486552</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326585600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/47486552/</event_url></item>