<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Daniel St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.077300</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603- 431-5186</phone><name>The Press Room</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>879760</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.755843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : xx-large"&gt;Special SCARY HALLOWEEN BEAT NIGHT&lt;/span&gt; @ The Press Room&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;~ ~ Music and SPOOKY Poetry &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Upstairs&lt;/span&gt; - NO COVER ~ ~&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/3/2/event_79094642.jpeg" width="232" height="297" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come for dinner or just a drink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beat Night: It's music and poetry upstairs with no cover charge. Groovy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Hey (wo)man, be cool and get out of your pad on a Thursday night. We always have a hip time at the Press Room - and it's FREE!   Can you dig it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay for just an hour or, like, stay as long as you want.  It's cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Arrive 6:30. Show 7-9pm. (You can't talk much once the show starts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Goatee/Soul patch optional.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beat Night is an every-3rd-Beat Thursday happening @ The Press Room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/a/0/event_167209312.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Sometimes there's a hip band playing downstairs, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group, from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/b/c/event_79094012.jpeg" width="215" height="233" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with attendance at, and travel to and from, this event. Alcohol consumption and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Your participation is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.  Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Please memorize these HIPSTER RULES...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/0/5/0/event_167209232.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, You Wanna Be a Hipster? #1. Never refer to yourself as a hipster... Instead, say you are "just different" from everyone else. #2. Buy a Mac... In my experience, this is &lt;em&gt;essential.&lt;/em&gt; No self-respecting hipster would be caught dead at a coffee shop with a PC. #3. Lose an ungodly amount of weight by maintaining a diet of PBR, clove cigarettes, and french-press coffee. But never go on an actual diet... that would be conforming to mainstream ideas of body image. #4. Girls: Grow your hair super long or chop it off super short (of course, cut it yourself!) Guys: Longer hair is better... and you must acquire a humorous configuration of facial hair to be respected by your fellow hipsters. #5. Create a blog or tumblr account to post your daily insights and emo, black and white pictures, etc. #6. Delete every song on your iPod and precious MacBook that has ever cracked the Billboard Charts. #7. Be Ironic... Make sure EVERYTHING you say is dripping in sarcasm... talk about how you love the &lt;em&gt;Twilight Series&lt;/em&gt; because it's ironic, not because you have a thing for teenage, soft-core, vampire porn. #8. Throw out all the clothes you have... Then shop only at thrift stores, American Apparel, and Urban Outfitters. When a fellow-hipster comments on your stylish top, be sure to respond with "Oh my gosh... I got this for like &lt;em&gt;five dollars&lt;/em&gt; in the Haight/Salvation Army." #9. Perfect the art of name-dropping... Talk about bands no one has heard of, EPs that &lt;em&gt;Pitchfork&lt;/em&gt; has underrated, Jack Kerouac, Allen Ginsberg (and anyone else James Franco is playing in his next indie flick), Hunter S. Thompson... it doesn't matter if you know who these people are, as long as you know their names. #10. Finally, smoke weed... But in moderation. Do not be a stoner. Do not do other drugs. Get high with your friends in Golden Gate Park/Harvard Square and discuss the tangibility of souls or how our bodies are vehicles for experiencing the physical plane... you get the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#11. Drive an older American car because it's &lt;em&gt;ironic -&lt;/em&gt; and because it's cheap and you spent all of your music store clerk pay on those $100 skinny jeans that make you look like a girl if you're a guy and make you look anorexic if you're a girl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the S/O hipsters upstairs on the right facing the stage</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351256637000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349721086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Halloween Beat Night @ The Press Room</name><id>86068882</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351204200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/86068882/</event_url></item>