<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I saw this film in Janary at the Palm Springs International Film Festival.  It is a violent bracing look at the &amp;quot;mafia&amp;quot;.  Thanks to Angela for pointing it out to me.  I've been lax in looking for films with HIFF in the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Italy, 2009) Directed by Matteo Garrone. Screenplay by Maurizio Braucci, Ugo Chiti, Gianni Di Gregorio, Matteo Garrone, and Roberto Saviano, based on the book by Roberto Saviano. Cast: Marco Macor, Ciro Petrone, Salvatore Abruzzese, Carmine Paternoster, Maria Nazionale. Martin Scorsese was so impressed by this new Italian movie that he introduced it at the New York Film Festival and immediately signed on as the American ‘presenter.’ No surprise: Gomorrah is a shocking, revelatory look at organized crime in Naples that strips any semblance of romance from its Mafia connection. Gomorrah is based on the exposé by journalist Roberto Saviano, who has been living undercover with 24 hour police protection since he blew the whistle on the violence, exploitation and toxic pollution that has a grip around the throat of one of Europe’s busiest port cities. “I hope this movie will finally show people the ferocious face of Italy, which is the face that really runs things,” Saviano says. “I think many American moviegoers will be surprised.” 135 min.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be hanging out in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258763693000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257383503000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Gomorrah</name><id>11798401</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258590600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11798401/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>