<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>25 Dorrance Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.824062</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>City Hall</name><city>Providence</city><id>870854</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412847</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mayor David N. Cicilline, Connect Providence, and Get RI Magazine invite you to gather at Providence City Hall (25 Dorrance St) from 6:00-8:00pm on February 10, 2009, for the first annual Valentine?s Day social celebration of Rhode Island?s capitol.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I HEART PROVIDENCE is a free event featuring complimentary hors d?oeuvres and cash bar by Trinity Brewhouse, chocolate truffles by Sin (www.eatwicked.com) and heart-shaped pies by Cutie Pies. Attendees are encouraged to bring poems, songs, and/or stories dedicated to Providence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &amp;quot;After living in nearly every region of the U.S. and even outside of the country, I chose Providence as my home. This culturally diverse city is filled with such amazing and interesting talent that I'm encouraging everyone to pop the big February question 'Providence, will you be my Valentine?'&amp;quot;, exclaimed event creator and West Side resident, Mike Ritz.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Attendees may share why they &amp;quot;Heart Providence&amp;quot; by participating in one of two video confession booths during the event, courtesy of Vision Wink Productions (www.visionwink.com). Testimonials from I HEART PROVIDENCE will be remixed and distributed online through YouTube, Facebook, and other online social media mechanisms to promote the city inside and outside of Rhode Island's borders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Just In from the I HEART Providence website:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're counting on your love next Tuesday, Feb. 10th at City Hall from 6-8pm. After party to be announced at the event. Follow the link to learn about the music, the food, the drink, the confessions, and the beauties: &lt;a href="http://hosted.verticalresponse.com/276519/3522d70dac/1533000581/c1240c84a4/" target="_blank"&gt;Learn More Here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the corner of Eddy and Washington, City Hall side, or call me.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234479278000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233844370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st Annual I HEART Providence party</name><id>9679202</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234305900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/9679202/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>