<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>183 Amherst Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03054</zip><lat>42.846216</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Horse Hill Nature Preserve, just past</name><city>Merrimack</city><id>430291</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.546949</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/2/a/c/event_211353452.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike at Horse Hill Nature Preserve&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday Mar. 17th. 2 pm. 2 to 3 hour hike&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;183 Amherst rd. Merrimack NH 03054&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Claire P cell 603-247-0897&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-host: Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962 or ob@tds.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipment needed: mainly Good boots! Beyond that, ski pole or shoe grippers would help. But, are not required.         Skill level: If you can walk &amp;amp; talk? This is your event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This a Child &amp;amp; Dog friendly event. But, we usually go out after for drinks &amp;amp; food. &lt;br /&gt;

 Please join us for a nice easy going hike at Horse Hill Nature Preserve. &lt;br /&gt;

 The 563± acres of the Horse Hill Nature Preserve consist of gently rolling to fairly steep terrain and two hills of approximately 400' elevation. The land was cleared for pasture in previous centuries, has been logged several times, and now consists primarily of a mixed hardwood forest with trees between 20 and 60 years of age. The property includes a series of streams, ponds, swamps, and numerous wetlands totaling approximately 60 acres. A power line easement traverses the property, creating a shrubland undergrowth area. A small sandpit was created by previous owners, but sand has not been removed for several years. &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no need to RSVP no. Call Claire"s cell. If you need information @ 603-247-0897 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Directions: Starting on Amherst Road where it intersects with Continental Boulevard in Merrimack near exit 11 of the Everett Turnpike proceed 3.0 miles on Amherst Road. The entrance where the sign is, on the left side of the road is just past the mailbox for 183 Amherst Road. Coming from the other direction on Amherst Road the entrance is on the right side of the road, being the first right just past Fuller Mill Road. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Here is a link to a trail map along with trail descriptions: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.hhnp.org/Documents/Brochure_06_2010.pdf" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hhnp.org/Documents/Brochure_06_2010.pdf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For your comfort, please dress in layers, and be sure to bring microspike and poles as the trails may be slippery. &lt;br /&gt;

 Liability Release - AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and her heirs, and all members and participants of this Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. All meetup activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call or tex Steve Ob1. 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363554618000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363011779000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike or Snowhoe Merrimack NH.</name><id>108691052</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363543200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/108691052/</event_url></item>