<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sam Adams Park</address_2><address_1>One Faneuil Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.360001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Faneuil Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>374878</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.050003</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>SCIENTISTS &amp;amp; CITIZENS SPEAK OUT!&lt;br /&gt;December 15 &amp;amp;16, 2007&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray McGovern, CIA veteran and founder of Veteran Intelligence Professionals for Sanity, will present speakers Richard Gage, AIA Architect, Steven Jones, PhD Former Professor of Physics at Brigham Young University, UL Laboratories whistleblower Kevin Ryan, and Joel S. Hirshhorn, PhD Former Professor, Metallurgical Engineering University of Wisconsin, Former Senior Staff Member - Congressional Office of Technology. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a growing concern within the international scientific community that the official explanations put forth by the US government vis-à-vis The 9/11 Commission Report and the NIST and FEMA reports concerning the collapse of World Trade Center Towers 1,2 and often ignored Building 7, contain not only scientifically unsubstantiated theories, but, in many cases, either defy or ignore the laws of physics, metallurgy and a host of other applied sciences in their calculations and conclusions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cross-section of disciplines represented by each of the symposium participants provides applicable scholarly and professional viewpoints concerning the one theory the government and media refuses to entertain: controlled demolition. It is their hope, along with the sponsors of the symposium, that the world-renowned community of scientists, architects and engineers in the Boston area test for themselves the veracity of the claims made by government agencies, as well as those of their opponents, with the understanding that the laws governing the sciences must not be manipulated or ignored for political ends on either side of the controversy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The conference will be Saturday, starting at 9AM, with an evening session called &amp;quot;911 Sent Them to War&amp;quot; at 7PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston911truth.org/teaparty/911conference.php" target="_blank"&gt;Details on the Saturday conference at the Boston911Truth.org site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a rally Sunday at 11 AM at he Boston Common bandstand and a march across town to dump the 911 Commission Report into the harbor at the site of the original Boston Tea Party at 3PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be an after-party &amp;quot;A Brew and a Brainstorm&amp;quot; Sunday at the upstairs bar at Hennessey's on Union Street  at 4PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston911truth.org/teaparty/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Details on the Sunday rally at the Boston911Truth.org site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fees: $35.00 all day pass for Saturday conference and evening session, $25 conference only. Sunday rally and march: no charge - after-party: $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=====================&lt;br /&gt;Watch this area of the page for carpooling plans and lodging ideas for those wanting to stay overnight in Boston:&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;LODGING IDEAS:&lt;br /&gt;Hostelling International hostels (2 in Boston) offer shared space at a low rate.&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;CAR-POOLING IDEAS:&lt;br /&gt;We may do our usual plan of meeting north of Concord, travel to a meeting place in Manchester, and a park-&amp;amp;-ride lot in Nashua and then on down to Beantown from there. Details to follow. Contact us with suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeremy</member_name><member_id>3581956</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542177000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190048363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tea Party for 911 Truth Conference</name><id>6375532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197727200000</time><rsvp_limit>800</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/6375532/</event_url></item>