<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>It's time for the next Image Makers shoot&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be an outdoor location shoot on Saturday June 27th at the Mary O'Malley Park at Admirals Hill Commandants Way, Chelsea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bill Downey will be the creative director.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cost will be $20 per photographer.   Models will sign a release and photographers will provide everyone who participates with low-resolution digital copies of their images.&lt;br /&gt;Makeup artist will begin on the models at 11:30pm everyone else must arrive by 1pm &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This shoot is limited to 10 photographers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Image makers is a subgroup of the Boston Fashion Industry Meetup. We currently have 38 members consisting of models, makeup artist, photographers, stylist and designers and fashion writers. &lt;br /&gt;Our first meeting and shoot was on January 24th at Positive Image studio. Since it was the first meeting we spent about 2 hours talking and defining our mission then we had a shoot with models Hui and Jo-Jo. The models wore their own clothes and did their own makeup. During the first meeting we decided that the format for this group would be a photo shoot about every month with one person volunteering as the creative director for the shoot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second meeting/shoot was Feb 28th on location at a contemporary house. We spent a short amount of time talking and several hours shooting. This was a very well organized fashion shoot with excellent team effort. Clothes were provided by Designers: Olivia Chow, Elena Gorczyca and the Suneri Boutique. Models were Beata, Hui, and Lidia. Styling was by Olivia Chow and Olivia Kostigen.&lt;br /&gt;The 3rd shoot was at covershot studios in Lawrence.  There were about 10 shooters and 6 models.  Designers were Mary Colburn and Sherry Dwivedi.    See some of the photos here &lt;a href="http://fashion.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;http://fashion.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info will be posted as the shoot concept and casting develop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email me ron@positiveimage-boston.com or Bill Downey (planewriting@yahoo.com) if you want to participate in this shoot and don’t forget to rsvp here.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Ranere</member_name><member_id>975035</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1247769212000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Fashion Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFashion</urlname><id>59186</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Fashion Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244439679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Image Makers June outdoor location shoot.</name><id>10601417</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246122000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFashion/events/10601417/</event_url></item>