<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, the Coolidge Corner Theater presents a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting insights by noted scientists in a related field. Join us as for the second meetup for a Science on Screen film (the first was Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind). Science on Screen events cost $9.50 for regular members, $7.50 for students and Museum of Science members and are free to members of the Coolidge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Malcolm McDowell gives a terrificly unsettling performance as Alex DeLarge, the derby-topped, charismatic young hooligan who rules the nighttime London streets along with his gang of thugs -- singing, fighting, stealing, and violating with terrifying glee and abandon. That is until young Alex is caught and convicted after a particularly nasty bit of &amp;quot;ultra-violence&amp;quot; one night. Thus begins his journey from amoral punk to proper citizen by way of an experimental therapy meant to &amp;quot;cure&amp;quot; him of his deviant impulses...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marc Hauser?s research sits at the interface between evolutionary biology and cognitive neuroscience and is aimed at understanding how the minds of human and nonhuman animals evolved. By studying monkeys and apes in both the wild and in captivity, as well as human infants and adults, Hauser?s work has unlocked some of the mysteries of language evolution, conceptual representation, social cooperation, communication, and morality. He is a Harvard College Professor in the Departments of Psychology, Organismic &amp;amp; Evolutionary Biology, and Biological Anthropology, Co-Director of the Mind, Brain and Behavior Program, Director of the Cognitive Evolution Laboratory, and the author of more than 200 papers and five books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event will be hosted by Nicole who will be holding a meetup sign after the event, so we can all discuss the film over coffee and ice cream at JP Licks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176937551000</updated><rating><average>3.79999995232</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1175446281000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science on Screen: A Clockwork Orange</name><id>5625694</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1176764400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/5625694/</event_url></item>