<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>113 Goodnow Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01541</zip><lat>42.456543</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-464-2712</phone><name>Wachusett Meadow Wildlife Sanctuary</name><city>Princeton</city><id>669307</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.900800</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Meeting right outside the gift shop at 1pm. We can look at the maps there and decide together which trails we'd like to hike. Please wear appropriate clothing and foot wear for this hike depending upon conditions that day. Micro-spikes or other ice gripping devices may be needed, perhaps even snow shoes if Monday brings anything significant for snowfall. Bring enough water and snacks for three hours of hiking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Twelve miles of trails at Wachusett Meadow traverse vast meadows, woodlands, and wetlands. Brown Hill Summit, South Wachusett Brook, and Glacial Boulder are highlights among many other features. Wildlife is abundant in all seasons, and visitors may take advantage of opportunities to snowshoe, cross-country ski, and canoe in addition to hiking. Address: 113 Goodnow Road Princeton, MA 01541 978-464-2712 wachusett@massaudubon.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This sanctuary has the following universally accessible facilities: Nature Center, Restrooms. Nature Center/Trail Hours: Nature Center: Tuesday through Friday, 10 a.m. to 2 p.m., Saturday, 10 a.m. to 4 p.m., Sunday, 12:30 p.m. to 4 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trails: Open daily dawn to dusk. Parking Restrooms Universally Accessible Rest Rooms Nature Center Education Programs Camp Programs Picnic Area Gifts and Snacks for Sale Butterfly or Other Specialized Garden Information Kiosk Trail Map Boardwalk or Wildlife Blinds Snowshoeing Cross-country Skiing Bird Checklist Nature Play Area/ Discovery Trail Passport to Nature Stamp Paddling Self-guided Activities (e.g. Quests) For Your Safety Do not feed any animals Stay on trails to avoid ticks and poison ivy Do not smoke anywhere on the sanctuary Do not pick or collect plants or crops without permission Avoid Conflicts with Wildlife Do not bring pets, leashed or unleashed, on to the site Picnic only in designated areas Do not bring motorized vehicles or bicycles onto the site Hunting, fishing, or trapping are not permitted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Admission: Mass Audubon Members enjoy FREE admission. Not a Member? Join Today! Also free for Princeton residents. $4 for nonmember adults; $3 for nonmember children (2-12) and seniors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Directions: From Rt 2: Take exit 28 (Rt 31, Fitchburg/Princeton). Follow Rt 31 south for 3.9 miles to a blinking red light. Turn left at the light and follow Rt 31 and Rt 140 south for 1.8 miles to a blinking yellow light. Turn right and follow Rt 31 south for 2.8 miles to a steep hill and a blinking yellow light (center of Princeton). At the light, follow signs for Rt 62 west by crossing the intersection and bearing right (follow the road as it curves right on the far side of the common after the light). Follow Rt 62 west for 0.6 miles, and you will see the sanctuary sign on the right at Goodnow Road. Turn right on Goodnow Road, and the parking lot is 1 mile ahead on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; From Rt I-190: Take exit 5 (Rt 140, Sterling/W. Boylston). Follow Rt 140 north for 2.4 miles to the intersection of Rt 62 (blinking yellow light). Take a left onto Rt 62 west and follow it for 4.2 miles to a stop sign. Turn left on Rt 31 and go up the hill to a flashing yellow light (center of Princeton). Follow directions above from the "center of Princeton."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acres: 1011&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1325039317000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324693229000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's do a Wachusett Meadow hike to wear off those holiday deserts;-)</name><id>45362972</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324922400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/45362972/</event_url></item>