<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thursday, July 9, the Coolidge Corner Theatre will present a preview screening of &lt;br /&gt;THROWN DOWN YOUR HEART, a terrific documentary that follows&lt;br /&gt;American banjo virtuoso Bela Fleck on his journey to Africa to&lt;br /&gt;explore the roots of the banjo and record an album.  Bela Fleck&lt;br /&gt;will introduce the film and also perform on the banjo following&lt;br /&gt;the screening.  THROW DOWN YOUR HEART will continue its run at&lt;br /&gt;the Coolidge beginning July 10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fleck's boundary-breaking musical adventure takes him to&lt;br /&gt;Uganda, Tanzania, The Gambia and Mali. Along the way, he works&lt;br /&gt;with an array of musicians - from local villagers who play a&lt;br /&gt;twelve-foot xylophone, to a family that makes and plays the&lt;br /&gt;akonting (thought by many to be the original banjo), to&lt;br /&gt;international superstars such as the Malian diva Oumou Sangare.&lt;br /&gt;Using his banjo, Fleck transcends barriers of language and&lt;br /&gt;culture, finding common ground and forging connections with&lt;br /&gt;musicians from very different backgrounds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fleck's trip provides a glimpse into the beauty of Africa and&lt;br /&gt;its rich and diverse musical traditions. As Ugandan folk&lt;br /&gt;musician Haruna Walusimbi says in the film: &amp;quot;There is this&lt;br /&gt;negative thinking about Africa.  There is nothing good in&lt;br /&gt;Africa.  They are beggars, there is HIV/AIDS, they are at war&lt;br /&gt;all the time.  But that is just a very small bit of what Africa&lt;br /&gt;is.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fleck's passion for the banjo runs deep.  In his trailblazing&lt;br /&gt;30-year career, he has brought the instrument into jazz, pop,&lt;br /&gt;classical, and world music settings, and won eight Grammys&lt;br /&gt;along the way. His journey was motivated by a desire to trace&lt;br /&gt;the origins of the instrument who defines who he is and by his&lt;br /&gt;deep love of African music.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRAISE FOR THROW DOWN YOUR HEART&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;an exhilarating feast of sight and sound&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;LA Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;you don't need to know the language to be gripped by the&lt;br /&gt;force...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;vibrant and spontaneous...&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Film Threat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;a heartfelt personal journey...refreshing&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Village Voice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;both the documentary and the disc of Throw Down Your Heart&lt;br /&gt;justify their existence independently-and rather beautifully.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Time Out New York&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;demonstrates that no other language is needed when two people&lt;br /&gt;sit down with their instruments and make them sing.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Chronicle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.readyticket.net/webticket/webticket2.asp?WCI=BuyTicket&amp;amp;WCE=THROW+DOWN+YOUR+HEART,070920091900,2,130" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.readytick...&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ext/share.php?sid=93833779806&amp;amp;h=t531d&amp;amp;u=5Dd3s&amp;amp;ref=mf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jacques Pardo / Atlas Soul</member_name><member_id>7850955</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247701302000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>World Music Fans</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonWorldMusic</urlname><id>575464</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston World Music Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245588908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>THROWN DOWN YOUR HEART documentary about banjo virtuoso Bela Fleck</name><id>10699859</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247180400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonWorldMusic/events/10699859/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/e/global_9264094.jpeg</photo_url></item>