<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Western Massachusetts' Premiere Rock-n-Roll Business-Networking Keg Party&lt;br /&gt;More info: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/Scorpion-Bowl-Party" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/Sc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Co-Sponsored by the Independent Music Conference which takes place in Northampton later this month, please visit our event page: &lt;a href="http://www.IMC2010.com/facebook" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.IMC2010.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;...---------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Scorpion Bowl starts at 5pm with the ceremonial tapping of the keg and firing up of the BBQ. The scheduled music starts at 6:00pm, with Katelyn Richards, who will be doing an early acoustic set on the porch, and keeps playing throughout the night. There are always piano-room sing-alongs and jams that spontaneously occur too, so bring your instruments if you play and your voice if you like to sing and join in the fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a full assortment of meat and veggie BBQ, tortilla chips and salsa, a Polish Deli Platter from Gramp's Restaurant, plenty of delicious Paper City Dam Ale on tap, a wide variety of soft drinks, and hot Dave's Blend Coffee. If you want to drink Wine or Cocktails or eat anything else, please bring your own supplies. Guests are also welcome to bring something to share if they are so inspired, and there will be a table set up for this purpose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission is FREE! These are the IMC artists that will be performing:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carrie Ferguson and Daniel Hales perform solo and as a duo. They may join us on the porch, or perhaps Carrie will tinkle the ivories in the Piano Room!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Daniel-hales-and-the-frost-heaves/241667492692" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carrie: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=1186913102" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later, onstage we'll enjoy...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The soul, jazz, funk and groovalicious sound of local heroes, GROOVE SHOES, featuring:&lt;br /&gt;Molly Steinmark (Vocals, Soul)&lt;br /&gt;De'Angelo Nieves (Trumpet, Alto)&lt;br /&gt;Jon C Gardner (Soprano &amp;amp;Tenor)&lt;br /&gt;Pat Garland (Keyboards)&lt;br /&gt;Michael Andrew Gleason (Guitars)&lt;br /&gt;Matthew Clegg (Basses)&lt;br /&gt;Sam French (Drums)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Groove-Shoes/376854745995" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The incredibly infectious rock/jam band sounds of REMEMBER SEPTEMBER (recently opened for Train), featuring:&lt;br /&gt;Jay Schod - Lead Vocals, Acoustic&lt;br /&gt;Chris Schod - Lead Guitar, Vocals&lt;br /&gt;Eric Schod - Bass&lt;br /&gt;Gerard Awad - Drums&lt;br /&gt;Dave Savitsky - Sax, Vocals&lt;br /&gt;Mary Albano - Vocals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Remember-September/257771498860" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The funky, jazz, blues, swingalicious sound of Turner's Falls' own GHOST QUARTET, featuring:&lt;br /&gt;Sam French-Drums&lt;br /&gt;Zack Holmes-Guitar, composer&lt;br /&gt;Hilary Graves-Vocals&lt;br /&gt;Kevin Smith-Tuba Love&lt;br /&gt;Josh Powers-Bass&lt;br /&gt;Jonas Cain- Saxophone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Ghost-Quartet/190214982139" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These and DOZENS more bands like them will be descending upon Northampton in November, be sure to check out their performances. More info on the IMC shows will be posted here: &lt;a href="http://www.IndieFans.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.IndieFans....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also on the Scorpion Bowl lineup is the amazingly sultry Katherine Kendall, and her mesmerizing Color Dancing performance art. This year we're also being blessed by a Belly Dancing performance by the beautiful Tommie Gunn (aka Ramara).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is truly a Business Networking Event, so bring your brochures and business cards and chachka giveaways (if you have any) and come prepared to meet some great people, eat some tasty food, and listen to some outstanding live musical performances. We believe that bringing together creative, intelligent people in a fun, inviting environment is always positive for both our culture AND the economy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here for the official invite: &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/Scorpion-Bowl-Party" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/Sc...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Bring a table or information to share regarding 9/11 truth. Newtorking invited!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Caputo</member_name><member_id>9333748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289777364000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289232897000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scorpion Bowl - party and networking </name><id>15378873</id><headcount>150</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1289685600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/15378873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/9/f/global_19493023.jpeg</photo_url></item>