<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>90 Drum Hill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01824</zip><lat>42.624310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-654-7990 </phone><name>Panera</name><city>Chelmsford</city><id>984022</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.362696</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>With the recent surveys of military personnel and their position on Don't Ask/Don't Dell, a lot of extremists have spoken up about what the Bible says about gays (and other fundamentalist-religious topics). At this meetup, we will discuss our favorite flaws in the Bible, the Koran, the Torah, or any other &amp;quot;scripture&amp;quot; that is the basis of believers. Some people might have a lot to share, and others might just want to learn. Bring any books or scriptures you have and share your favorite contradiction, impossible miracle, or against-the-laws-of-nature-and-everything-we-know story. It should be fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you have anything to bring up at the meeting and we'll be sure it's added to the (roughly-adhered-to) agenda. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What to expect: This monthly meeting typically begins with an introduction all around for the benefit of any first-time attendees, and discussion of any announcements, upcoming events, etc. We then move on to a topic of interest to atheists (usually) chosen beforehand. Sometimes participants bring print-outs of articles, research, or books to share on the topic, and sometimes people just come with a story or opinion to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We loosely moderate the topical discussion to give everyone a chance to participate. Then the conversation often flows onto other related subjects, sometimes in smaller conversation groups around the table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any ideas for meeting topics, please let any of the co-organizers know. We can also add announcements or &amp;quot;mini-topics&amp;quot; on the agenda if there's anything you'd like to share with the group.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the large group, some might be wearing atheistic shirts</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul S</member_name><member_id>4811434</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>5222022</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Valerie </member_name><member_id>7248057</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292891044000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lowellatheists</urlname><id>13032</id><group_lat>42.6300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3300018311</group_lon><name>Atheists of Greater Lowell</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291180372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday Morning Topical Meeting--The problem with scriptures</name><id>stgrpynqbzb</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292772600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lowellatheists/events/15604771/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/8/2/global_10991506.jpeg</photo_url></item>