<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>37 Boulder Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.581813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1434512</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.797374</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In February we'll get together at Chaibo in Fitchburg to discuss &lt;em&gt;The Guernsey Literary and Potato Peel Pie Society&lt;/em&gt; by Mary Ann Shaffer and Annie Barrows. Enjoy one of Chaibo's scrumptious grilled cheese sandwiches, a latte with lots of whipped cream, tea, or one of their many yummy desserts!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;As always we'll meet on the first set of big comfy couches by the door. This month is also the first anniversary of our group&amp;rsquo;s very first Meetup! &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Wow &amp;ndash; time flies! After book club join us for a drink at Destare (upstairs from Chaibo) to celebrate!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Below is a description of &lt;em&gt;The Guersney Literary and Potato Peel Pie Society&lt;/em&gt; from Bookmarks Magazine:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Traditional without seeming stale, and romantic without being na&amp;iuml;ve&amp;rdquo; &lt;/em&gt;(San Francisco Chronicle), &lt;em&gt;this epistolary novel, based on Mary Ann Shaffer&amp;rsquo;s painstaking, lifelong research, is a homage to booklovers and a nostalgic portrayal of an era. As her quirky, loveable characters cite the works of Shakespeare, Austen, and the Bront&amp;euml;s, Shaffer subtly weaves those writers&amp;rsquo; themes into her own narrative. However, it is the tragic stories of life under Nazi occupation that animate the novel and give it its urgency; furthermore, the novel explores the darker side of human nature without becoming maudlin. The &lt;span&gt;Rocky Mountain News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; criticized the novel&amp;rsquo;s lighthearted tone and characterizations, but most critics agreed that, with its humor and optimism, &lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Guernsey&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ldquo;affirms the power of books to nourish people during hard times" (Washington Post)&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And from an Amazon Reviewer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What a wonderful book! Having just finished this one, I am still smiling and thinking of the characters. Had I the time and money, I'd be booking a trip for Guernsey right this minute. As it is, I feel as though I've already visited and been made to feel at home.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Set in both London and Guernsey Island, this novel follows author Juliet as she becomes friends with the inhabitants of the island shortly after the end of World War 2. Told in epistolary style, Juliet learns of the occupied island and its deprivations, as well as the resounding spirit of the people who live there. As she writes, she becomes more and more intrigued with the stories of the people who survived the hard times, and she decides to create a book based on their experiences. In order to gather more information, Juliet moves temporarily to the island and soon finds herself immsersed in the culture and relationships. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; This is absolutely one of the most delightful books I've read all year. The characters are real, the relationships are unique, and Juliet is hysterically funny, as well as warm hearted and genuine. I did have a bit of trouble keeping all the characters straight in the beginning, but once I caught on, I was enthralled. The pages just fly by and while you will learn a little of what happened to Guernsey during World War 2, you will learn much more about love and friendship. Highly recommended!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1298647588000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296343699000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - The Guernsey Literary and Potato Peel Pie Society</name><id>16362020</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1298592000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/16362020/</event_url></item>