<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our wonderful member Norm often travels over an hour to go to some of our walks, so it is time that we go closer to him.  He has been generous enough to provide guidance through this stunning jewel of East Taunton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This heavily wooded park, minutes from Interstate Route 495, offers abundant beauty and many opportunities for recreation. Four lakes provide excellent fishing. Swimming for camping patrons only is available at the beach on Middle Pond. Picnicking, biking, canoeing, walking, hiking, horseback riding and cross-country skiing are popular activities. In the fall the contrast of scarlet cranberry bogs against the pines is breathtaking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Massasoit is also a favorite of trailer campers, with most of its 123 campsites provided with electrical or water hookups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Map and more information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/mass.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Things to know before you go?&lt;br /&gt;? Campground Office Hours: 8am?8pm&lt;br /&gt;? Camping Season: Late April through Columbus Day&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Massasoit State Park is located in south-eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;From Cape Cod or Worcester: Take Rte. 495 to Exit 5 in Middleborough. Take Rte. 18 South to the first intersection where there is a yellow flashing light. Turn right onto Taunton Street which becomes Middleboro Ave.. Park entrance will be on the left, about 2.5 miles from flashing light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: Take Rte. 24 south - Rte. 44 east. At first traffic light, turn right onto South St. E.. Follow to end. Turn left onto Middleboro Ave. Continue about 2 miles to Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Fall River/Providence: Take Rte. 195 East - Rte. 24 North - Rte. 44 East. At first traffic light, turn right onto South St. E.. Follow to end. Turn left onto Middleboro Ave. Continue about 2 miles to Park entrance on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On google maps:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;q=Massasoit+Park+Road+%26+Middleboro+Ave+Taunton+MA&amp;amp;sll=41.880457,-70.98597&amp;amp;sspn=0.014922,0.038581&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.88509,-70.994232&amp;amp;spn=0.00746,0.01929&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;iwloc=addr&amp;amp;om=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we will dine at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fireside Grill&lt;br /&gt;30 Bedford St.&lt;br /&gt;Middleboro MA&lt;br /&gt;508-947-5333&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180969289000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177815434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massasoit State Park</name><id>5720823</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180796400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5720823/</event_url></item>