<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>931 Ocean Blvd</address_1><state>Ne</state><zip>03842</zip><lat>42.941540</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>North Beach Bar &amp; Grill</name><city>Hampton</city><id>3228832</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.794052</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Hello everyone,&amp;nbsp; Come and join us for this beautiful ride along NH's Seacoast into Kittery, Maine.&amp;nbsp; Though boasting only 18 miles of ocean views, the Seacoast Region offers some of the most scenic and sought after cycling in all of New Hampshire.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin at Hampton's North Beach and cycle along the water past the gorgeous waterfront homes in North Hampton &amp;amp; Rye.&amp;nbsp; We will then head across to New Castle, Island, where we may stop to visit the grounds and beautiful marina at the "Wentworth by the Sea Resort" from there we will ride into Portsmouth through Historic Strawberry Bank, across the Memorial bridge into Kittery for about 3 miles..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;On the way back we will stop on Badger's Island for a bite to eat at the "Weathervane Restaurant" right on the water, where we shall have a gorgeous view of Portsmouth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Here is a link, with pictures and a menu:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.weathervaneseafoods.com/index.cfm/p/Lobster%20In%20The%20Rough" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.weathervaneseafoods.com/index.cfm/p/Lobster%20In%20The%20Rough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From there we will ride past some of Rye's prettiest homes and farms.. 
&lt;strong&gt;The total mileage of this ride is about 37 miles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we return for those that are interested we can have a relaxing beer or drink at the North Beach Bar and Grill..&amp;nbsp; Plan on spending the day.&amp;nbsp; We will probably not get back til about 4pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Again meeting time is at 10am Be ready to ride at 10:30 am.. The ride is going to be about 37 miles.&amp;nbsp; I did it this week.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;The average speed of this ride is 12-15 miles per hour. The terrain is mostly flat with rolling hills (mostly in Kittery).&amp;nbsp; If it's Windy it can be difficult to push against the wind. &amp;nbsp; Road bikes and hybrids are highly recommended, I do not recommend the use of mountain bikes on this route. Helmets are required. Please be sure to bring plenty of water, sunscreen &amp;amp; a spare tire tube.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Don't forget to bring money for lunch.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;We WILL CANCEL for RAIN!
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;*****Directions to North Beach, Hampton, NH (From downtown Boston drive time is about 50 mins)*****&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Take I-95 North or South (depending on where you are coming from) to exit 2 (Toll booth exit).&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Exit heading towards 101 east towards Hampton&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Get on 101 east for a short time stay in Right lane..&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Take first exit It will say Rte 27, Exeter/Hampton (I think it's Exit #13 could be wrong)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Take two rights off of the Exit onto Rte 27 east heading towards Hampton.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Follow Rte 27 (aka High Street) at about a mile and a half (this is not exact) you will pass through the intersection of Rte 1 (See The Old Salt on your left at the corner).&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Continue on Rte27/High Street straight through the intersection you will go straight for about another 2 miles..&amp;nbsp; Rte 27/Hight Street ends at the beach.&amp;nbsp; Park either to your right across from North Beach Bar and Grill or in the lots by the Bath House.&amp;nbsp; If there is no parking available in the lots you can park along the street on High Street or drive further south on Ocean Blvd and you should see many open parking spots.&amp;nbsp; Meet in the lot on the North side of the Bath House/Bathrooms on the beach across Ocean Blvd from the North Beach Bar and Grill.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;For those of you with GPS's use the address for the North Beach Bar and Grill up above.. 931 Ocean Boulevard, Hampton, NH, 03842.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;***Note, Depending on how many other ride leaders decide to do this ride, I will more then likely increase the # of riders I can allow on this ride... Please be sure you are capable of riding 37 miles.
   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
     &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us in the parking lot on the beach side across Ocean Blvd from the North Beach Bar &amp; Grill.  We will be on the north side of Bath House at North Beach.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cyndi</member_name><member_id>3604417</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>5</waitlist_count><updated>1315681087000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-207</urlname><id>482869</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Cycling/Outdoor Fitness Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>34</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314561294000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join us For the most scenic and sought after cycling in all of New Hampshire.</name><id>31292132</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315231200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-207/events/31292132/</event_url></item>