<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>420 Totten Pond Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397327</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-0100</phone><name>Hilton Garden Inn Hotel</name><city>Waltham</city><id>669398</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.254820</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>John Harrington&lt;br /&gt;Monday January 26, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is a CIPNE Program you must sign up on their web site: &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographer John Harrington’s business savvy has successfully brought him through two previous economic downturns. In this two-part seminar John will share insights on how to tweak your current business practices to operate more efficiently and more profitably.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In part one John starts with a discussion of the business side of photography: from pricing to negotiations, client relationships to logistical challenges. John shares actual negotiations with clients, from the back-and-forth over prices, to the final agreement and resulting images.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part two will be about learning the back-end secrets of how Search Engine Optimization can maximize your web presence and keep you at the top of “The List.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based in Washington DC for nearly two decades John has covered the world of politics, traveled internationally, and negotiated contracts along the way. His work has appeared in Time, Newsweek and Rolling Stone, and his commercial clients have included Coca-Cola, XM Satellite Radio and Lockheed Martin. He has lectured on the importance of solid business practices and published the book Best Business Practices for Photographers in 2007.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hilton Garden Inn&lt;br /&gt;420 Totten Pond Rd.&lt;br /&gt;Waltham, MA 02451&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Registration: 5:00–6:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Program: 6:00–10:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: CIPNE Members, Free; ASMP Members, $20; Guests, $35; Full-time Students, $10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-registration is required for this program. &lt;a href="http://www.cipne.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cipne.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here to register (Non-members may pay by PayPal)&lt;br /&gt;Please note: on-line registration closes January 23rd.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233277665000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231860083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wait! Don't Jump! Rise above the competition with solid business strategies</name><id>9513160</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233010800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9513160/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/a/4/global_6925700.jpeg</photo_url></item>