<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 William T Morrissey Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02125</zip><lat>42.309647</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Savin Hill Yacht Club</name><city>Dorchester</city><id>1527219</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.043594</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Brian Hancock will be answering question: &amp;quot;Can a Monohull Ever Sail Faster Than a Multihull? One of the most experienced offshore sailors in the United States with over a quarter million offshore miles logged racing both fully crewed as well as solo - Brian Hancock will share his latest project &amp;quot;Grabbing The Dream&amp;quot;. This new multimedia presentation gives Pelagic Sailing Club Members and guests a close look at what it takes to build a monohull capable of sailing faster than a same-sized multihull. A monohull that is predicted to sail at speeds consistently over 40 knots and cover 1,000 nautical miles in a single day. In 2010, Hancock created SpeedDream, the Quest to Build the Worlds Fastest Monohull. With a long list of innovative features such as a narrow, wave-piercing bow, an extreme canting keel that actually flies out of the water, to a radical leeward lifting foil, SpeedDream is set to change the way we look at sailboats, and their relationship to speed. Brian Hancock has competed in three Whitbread Round the World Races (currently known as the Volvo Ocean Race). He's a highly sought out inspirational speaker, given thousands of talks in over 15 countries, author of seven books and his book on sails and sailmaking; Maximum Sail Power, has become an industry standard. His new book, Grabbing the Dream, will be coming out in 2012. Hancock lives in Marblehead, Massachusetts. Pelagic Sailing Club meets on the second floor of Savin Hill Yacht Club in Dorchester, MA. Pizza and social hour starts at 6:30pm, meeting at 7:15pm, guest speaker at 8pm.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318903935000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313370286000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brian Hancock Guest Speaker at Pelagic Sailing Club!</name><id>29494981</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314311400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/29494981/</event_url></item>