<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A great empire, like a great cake, is most easily diminished at the edges.” &lt;br /&gt;Ben  Franklin &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theme for March is Empire. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“The enemy of my enemy is my friend”, who said this???? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nVTEqG9enEY" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can take the words &amp;quot;empire&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;imperial&amp;quot; and put another noun  before or after it and it will be something that has or does or will one day exist. That’s just a fact, go ahead and try it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Empire comes from the word Imperium which has to do with absolute a-thor-i-tay.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I got nothing – if you feel inspired to write about Empire in a funny and creative way send 400 word to me and I will consider posting it as our March meetup write-up. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be back at my place for this month. If you don’t know or remember the location in West Hartford, no worries, I will send it out a few days before the event.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>9</waitlist_count><updated>1268611499000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266023409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes March Meetup</name><id>gwhmhynfbqb</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268438400000</time><rsvp_limit>17</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/12592500/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/3/a/global_13070618.jpeg</photo_url></item>