<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>600 Main Street, Hartford, ct</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.763206</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 278-2670</phone><name>Wadsworth Atheneum</name><city>Hartford</city><id>607396</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.674088</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;Thought this might be a nice afternoon spent, lets meet at 12, wonder through the museum until 1 or so and maybe have a quick bite in the museum cafe. At 2:30 there is a tour of the Andrew Wyeth exhibit. Also of interest throughout the museum is the Fine Art and Flower show, pairing creative floral pieces with the museum exhibits.  I have been to these shows before and you will be amazed at the creative interpretations of the art pieces. Admission is $10.00 for regular admission plus an additional $3.00 for the special flower exhibits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/1/8/event_82539192.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Andrew Wyeth: Looking Beyond&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/c/4/event_73924292.jpeg" width="46" height="31" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 24-July 22, 2012.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Andrew Wyeth: Looking Beyond&lt;/em&gt; will explore the work of one of the most celebrated modern American artists.   This highly focused exhibition takes its inspiration from the three paintings in the museum’s collection: Northern Point, 1950; April Wind, 1952; and Chambered Nautilus, 1956; each defined by a distinct use of perspective.  Wyeth’s use of windows and open doors to invite viewers to look into a distant realm—be it emotional or physical—will be explored. Included among the 15-20 works will be important loans from public and private collections, including rarely seen preparatory studies in pencil and watercolor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fine Art and Flowers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrate spring with the Annual Fine Art &amp;amp; Flowers show presented by the Women’s Committee of the Wadsworth Atheneum Museum of Art. Each year the committee pairs masterworks from the museum’s collection with 60 imaginative floral arrangers and table designers, who research their assigned work and create stunning interpretations and tributes. The resulting arrangements are both beautiful and clever, lending a deeper understanding of the artist’s vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James Welling: “Wyeth”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 24 – July 22, 2012&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Profoundly affected by the work of Andrew Wyeth as a budding artist, Los Angeles-based contemporary art photographer and Hartford-area native James Welling recently reconnected to the influence of Wyeth in his work. Through a series of photographs, Welling explores some of the subjects of Wyeth’s paintings made in Cushing, Maine and Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania. A companion exhibition to &lt;em&gt;Andrew Wyeth: Looking Beyond&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;James Welling: “Wyeth”&lt;/em&gt; includes photographs that correspond to Wyeth’s most iconic paintings as well as the works in the concurrent Wyeth exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On-Street Parking&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Two-hour kiosk parking is available. The kiosks accept coins, debit cards, and credit cards. Display the printed parking receipt on the dashboard inside your vehicle. Parking is free after 6 pm on weekdays and all day on weekends. Please observe posted signs. Some areas are tow zones after 3:30 pm weekdays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discounted Rate:&lt;/strong&gt; $3 Museum Visitor Parking &lt;br /&gt;

Trumbull-on-the-Park Garage, 100 Trumbull Street &lt;br /&gt;

Monday through Friday – open all day / Saturday, 4 pm – midnight &lt;br /&gt;

Validate your parking ticket at The Museum Shop. &lt;br /&gt;

Located three blocks from the Museum, enjoy the walk along the Ancient Burying Ground and Stone Field Sculpture – or pick up the free Star Shuttle at stop #3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Located nearest the Museum:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Front Street Garage &lt;br /&gt;

Weekdays: 7 am – 7 pm &lt;br /&gt;

First Thursdays Phoenix Art After Hours to 11 pm and selected special events. Call (860) 278-2670 to confirm. &lt;br /&gt;

Daily rate: $3 first hour, $2 each additional hour. $19 daily maximum&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meet in the lobby at 12, I will be wearing that Black and white scarf with piano keys.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cathy M</member_name><member_id>6563416</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336702186000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>42</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325349970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Andrew Wyeth: Looking Beyond/Fine Art and Flowers</name><id>46074182</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335628800000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/46074182/</event_url></item>