<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Do you sometimes find it hard to communicate your best qualities to someone you're attracted to, even though you know deep down that you really are an interesting person?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;When you go out to social gatherings (such as a meetup event), do you find yourself wishing that people would see through your shyness and take the time to discover the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;real&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; you that's hiding inside?&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;If you answered &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to either of these questions, then you're going to love this.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;In this unique event, you'll learn the secrets to becoming more interesting and attractive so that you can experience the kind of effortless connections that you've been hoping for when you go out to socialize.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HERE'S A SMALL SAMPLE OF WHAT YOU'LL LEARN:&lt;br /&gt;************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The single most important ability you must develop in order to be interesting and attractive to other people.  Once you master this, you'll have a never ending supply of quality people wanting to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;My proven method for instantly make people feel closer you.  You can use this for dating, friendship, and even business, and people will find themselves making excuses to spend more time with you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &amp;quot;secret question&amp;quot; that everyone's subconscious mind is asking when you first meet them.  Once you know this, you'll be able to put people at ease and make them feel comfortable around you.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simple steps you can take right away to make yourself more physically attractive.  If you do this, be prepared to get a lot more compliments on your appearance!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;PERSONALITY FEEDBACK&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;And that's just the first part of the seminar.  Then we will go into one of the most popular activities that we do in this social skills group... personality feedback!&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;You will have an opportunity to participate in small group evaluations of other members, and you'll also get to experience what it's like to receive both positive encouragement and constructive feedback about how you come across to others.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;This is often the most revealing part of the workshop, because it's so personalized.  Some members became away of things they were doing for years that were turning people off, and some learned that they come across much better than they realized (which dramatically boosted their confidence in all social situations).&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/u&gt;  I want you to know that exercise is done very gently, kindly, and in the spirit of personal growth.  We are all there to help each other.  So if this section makes you a little nervous, don't let it.  I promise that you will find this to be one of the most educational and &lt;u&gt;enjoyable&lt;/u&gt; parts of the seminar.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;HOW TO GET INVOLVED&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The seminar is conveniently located in Harvard Square, less than 5 minutes walk from the red line.  Please plan on arriving by 3:00pm.  The first 30 minutes is used for personal networking and socializing, and then we start the seminar promptly at 3:30.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The event is limited to 40 people due to the size limitations of the classroom.  Our meetings usually sell out quickly, so here's what I recommend.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have Sunday, June 28th available.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now.  Trust me, it's going to fill up fast.  They always do.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;#3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 3:00pm for registration and personal networking.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The cost of the event is only $20, which is a bargain for the quality of training that you'll be getting.  Think about it... what else do you spend $20 that makes no difference in your social life (or love life) whatsoever?  I promise that this will be well worth your time.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Please remember to bring:&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;$20 cash&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A pen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great attitude&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;And a willingness to learn fun, new things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;I'm looking forward to seeing you there.&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost.  The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 401-359-6685&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248032128000</updated><rating><average>4.69000005722</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245480839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>How To Make Yourself More Interesting To Others + Personality Feedback</name><id>10693534</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246215600000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/10693534/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/b/global_9242459.jpeg</photo_url></item>