<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Westminster and Union</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.822727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Grant's Block</name><city>Providence</city><id>1284760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.412857</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/#!/event.php?eid=131455866943613" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook....&lt;/a&gt; (I am a fill in on the agenda and will show some pictures from a recent trip to Egypt). FREE EVENT Announcing the 29th Pecha Kucha Night in Providence! This month we take over the heart of Downtown Providence at Grant's Block (corner of Westminster and Union Streets) for the first ever Pecha Kucha On the Block. Those of you who have been to the popular Movies On the Block, the Downtown Bocce League, the Providence Art Festival or any of the other great events there know what an exciting space this is for PK. Tazza and Cornish... Associates have been kind enough to donate the space for the evening, and we are so thankful! Tazza will serve food and drinks you can take over to the block. Bring blankets and chairs, as you will want to be comfortable for this evening under the stars! The theme this month is &amp;quot;immerse&amp;quot;. The presenters include some of the following: - Leadership Rhode Island - David Fisher - Andrea Clip - The Providence Foundation - Celia Cackowski - Rosanna Ortiz Sinel - John Taraborelli If you haven't heard of this global yet unpronounceable phenomenon, Pecha Kucha is a monthly format for sharing ideas, in which presenters are allotted 20 slides and 20 seconds per slide. Put simply: 6 minutes and 40 seconds of adult-style show &amp;amp; tell. It began in Tokyo in 2003, has since spread to over 430 cities worldwide, and first landed in Providence in March of 09. ***Doors open at 7:20, presentations start at 8:20, and shmoozing goes down throughout.***&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314283692000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314025677000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pecha Kucha - downtown, outside!</name><id>30423001</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314228600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/30423001/</event_url></item>