<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>**This event has changed from Wed, July 23rd to Fri, July 25th!**&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;Shakespeare in the Park is really a lot of fun!!  Bring a blanket/pillow or short lawn chair.  Also bring wine/bevs or snacks, if you want.  RSVP here on Meetup &amp;amp; then call Bernadette's cell when you arrive (617)372-3357 to find where we're sitting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citicenter.org/shows/lists/details.php?showID=423" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citicenter.org/shows/lists/details.php?showID=423" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.citicenter...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FREE SHAKESPEARE&lt;/b&gt;, a public program of the Citi Performing Arts Center, will return for an extended run on Boston Common this summer. The popular midsummer tradition of free Shakespeare under the stars will return to the Boston Common for three weeks with Citi as the new corporate presenting sponsor for the program. Directed by Steven Maler, founding artistic director of Commonwealth Shakespeare Company, As &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You Like It will be staged at the Parkman Bandstand on Boston Common July 18 through August 3, 2008, with two dress rehearsals open to the public on July 16 and 17. Following the Boston run, the production will travel to Springfield, MA, playing in Forest Park, August 8 through 10. As well, the 3rd annual Celebrate Shakespeare Day, a program of Citi Performing Arts Center?s Education Department, will be held on Saturday, August 2, also at the Parkman Bandstand. Celebrate Shakespeare Day is a multi-faceted free event featuring workshops, performances, backstage tours, and lectures for the public to enjoy and learn more about the works of William Shakespeare.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citicenter.org/shows/lists/details.php?showID=423" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.citicenter.org/shows/lists/details.php?showID=423" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.citicenter...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please call Bernadette's cell phone: 617-372-3557</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218654781000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1211840206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Shakespeare in the Park: "As You Like It"</name><id>8014830</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217030400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/8014830/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/global_4254007.jpeg</photo_url></item>