<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>50.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Join us for an evening of channeling as Judith Grant, channels Balistar. During the 1&amp;amp;1/2 hour event, Balistar will deliver pertinent messages from The Light, then will answer questions from the audience. Balistar is a delightful being of Light from the Pleiades Star System. His group is here to help our planet to heal and raise the vibratrion. With loving support and guidance Balistar shares his love and wisdom through a unique and joyful personality. He has presented about the changes in the universe, the weather, the planet, the many challenges that we have faced in our humanity , etc., as well as answered questions that many in attendance have had for much of their lives. During the channeling session many that have been  present have been able to raise their vibration and feel the unconditional love that the guides have for us. Balistar is both playful and brilliant, yet presents with no ego. With all that is happening with the economy, and the many changes that are yet to occur, please join us to see what the guides have to say at this time. Fee for the channeling session is $50.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Judith and William will meet you there.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>William Bezmen</member_name><member_id>8774813</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235327769000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Holistic health &amp; Spiritualist</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Pathways-to-Health</urlname><id>1369837</id><group_lat>40.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-73.0100021362</group_lon><name>Pathways To Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1235003531000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Channeling Session of "Balistar" a star being of Light and Love</name><id>9771645</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235089800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Pathways-to-Health/events/9771645/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/8/global_7174024.jpeg</photo_url></item>