<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>78ee Olympia Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><lat>42.498879</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-27-DANCE</phone><name>Kadanse Ballroom &amp; Latin Dance Studio</name><city>Woburn</city><id>940071</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134075</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us for Zumba fitness classes at Kadanse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Classes are held on Thursdays and Mondays @ 7:30pm. &amp;nbsp;Each class is $10 per person. We also offer class cards...ask the studio for details:)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Zumba class is truly more like an experience...the environment is open and expressive and the workout is like no other. It is accessible to beginners, but even advanced dancers can challenge themselves in this class. Zumba is all about YOU, so enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.kadanse.com&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;www.zumba.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Zumba&amp;reg; program fuses hypnotic Latin rhythms and easy-to-follow moves to create a one-of-a-kind fitness program that will blow you away. Our goal is simple: We want you to want to work out, to love working out, to get hooked. Zumba&amp;reg; Fanatics achieve long-term benefits while experiencing an absolute blast in one exciting hour of calorie-burning, body-energizing, awe-inspiring movements meant to engage and captivate for life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The routines feature interval training sessions where fast and slow rhythms and resistance training are combined to tone and sculpt your body while burning fat. Add some Latin flavor and international zest into the mix and you've got a Zumba&amp;reg; class!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1369362882000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ballroom Dancers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-North-Shore-Ballroom-Dancing-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1441798</id><group_lat>42.4799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1600036621</group_lon><name>The North Shore Ballroom Dancing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288312679000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zumba</name><id>mztspyrhbfc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1369351800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-North-Shore-Ballroom-Dancing-Meetup-Group/events/119961702/</event_url></item>