<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>20 Ames St. - Bldg. E15</address_2><address_1>MIT campus</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>List Visual Arts Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1412527</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.088730</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Updates:&lt;/b&gt; It's looking like the weather is going to cooperate. I got an email that the tour will be led by List Visual Arts Center educator Mark Linga, and will feature new commissioned works by artists Cai Guo Qiang and Anish Kapoor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MIT has an extensive and varied public art collection, with work by artists including: Calder, Picasso, Stella, Bartlett, Di Suvero, LeWitt, and Sze. Join MIT public art curator Alise Upitis for a walking tour of the collection. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://listart.mit.edu/public_art" target="_blank"&gt;Link for more info about MIT's collection.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://listart.mit.edu/directions" target="_blank"&gt;Directions to the List Visual Art Center&lt;/a&gt; (the meeting place)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tour is free and starts at the MIT List Visual Arts Center (in the Wiesner Building, 20 Ames St., Cambridge, MA). I'll arrive @ 10:45; I'm tall and look like my picture and will send out my cell phone # as the date draws nearer. Since this is a guided tour, we won't be waiting for late-comers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come and explore this comparatively unheralded local art resource. I believe that we'll view both outdoor and indoor pieces. After the tour, we can get some lunch and discuss public vs. private art, art in urban settings, or anything else of interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to meetup Asst. Organizer Karen for the idea!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bob</member_name><member_id>2963965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289169907000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288055952000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guided Tour of MIT's Public Art Collection</name><id>15228437</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289055600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/15228437/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/e/global_19079566.jpeg</photo_url></item>