<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://blog.seedalliance.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/SPE_crowd-300x225.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;In April, our monthly &lt;strong&gt;Portland Trading Post&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;swap event turns into &lt;strong&gt;the mother of all seed and plant swaps&lt;/strong&gt;! &amp;nbsp;Bring seedlings, divisions, seeds, propagated plants ... anything at all to help each other get food going in our landscapes. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to chat in advance about what you might be bringing and/or looking for from others. &amp;nbsp;Please label your offerings as best you can and bring some extra envelopes and markers (for seed swapping) and some buckets or pots or plastic bags for getting plant material home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp;If you are a member of Hour Exchange Portland (&lt;a href="http://www.hourexchangeportland.org/howtojoin.php"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/span&gt;join here if you're no&lt;span&gt;&amp;#65279;&lt;/span&gt;t&lt;/a&gt;) consider bringing more substantial items to trade to time dollar hours! &amp;nbsp;I'll make some "I'll Trade for Time Dollars" table tents for anyone who wants to post one on her/his trading table.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main idea is that we are stepping outside of the cash economy and mutually "gifting" things to each other in a way that turns whatever we have in abundance into a diversity of goodness and good will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The only rules are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No cash changes hands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't start the swapping until everyone's there and has a chance to look around at what's on offer (usually about 15 minutes into the swap, but it's flexible)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can swap with someone or simply "gift" things to each other without taking a return item. Your choice. &amp;nbsp;Make sure you've found a home for all your stuff before you leave (or take home what hasn't been gifted).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you bring a food item with multiple ingredients, pls label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments area of this page to talk about what you might be bringing or seeking. Food/Snacks/Fiddles/Juggling/Attended Children welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a very relaxed, social atmosphere. &amp;nbsp;Even if you have nothing to trade, feel free to come by just to see what it's all about and meet some members. &amp;nbsp;We are considering combining these with short skill-shares or "show and tell" sessions, too. &amp;nbsp;These are kid-friendly events but in a "keep an eye on your child" sort of way, as the space is also a functioning business with equipment, etc. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that gifting and bartering is still something many of us are getting a handle on...it requires different thinking for our society which has been so used to "monetizing" every transaction or product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to our friends at Zero Station for hosting this event!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.zerostation.com/"&gt;http://www.zerostation.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Homa </member_name><member_id>2587064</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aaron Parker</member_name><member_id>6845673</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334500461000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>56</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328637088000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SPECIAL Portland Trading Post :: April Plant/Seed Swap Extravaganza</name><id>lccwpyqgblb</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333827000000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/51404232/</event_url></item>