<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Beacon St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.356799</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 635-4505</phone><name>Boston Common Frog Pond</name><city>Boston</city><id>795283</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066720</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Attention Attention!  The Boston Common has won at as the spot for the incubator tonight!  We'll meet up right outside of Park Street Station (literally between the two Station entrances) at 7:30 and take it from there.  Easily accessible for all your red liners and green liners plus they'll be plenty of options for after incubator munching. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey hey incubators!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know this will be a last minute affair but no BU this week, so we have a couple other options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since I'm still waiting for some phone calls while continuing to plug away at finding us a permanent new space AND given that the weather tomorrow looks amazingly gorgeous, I was thinking we rock out back to the otherside of the bridge, aka outside Porter Square T Station near our good ol' stomping grounds or we wing it and stay in Boston for a night under the lights of lovely impromptu fun in the Boston Common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll put up a pole and let you vote away.  Or if anyone else has a better idea.  I'm all ears. Shoot me an email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rock on!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason J.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;p.s.  ahh what a hectic week, thanks again for the patience from everyone.  You are all fantastic.  I send you all a peaceful and calming late summertime breeze!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Give me the top 5 reasons how you will find me at the venue??</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221466778000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Improv &amp; Performance Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cambridge-improv-incubator</urlname><id>472156</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Improv incubator</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221076929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wowzers!!! What just happened? Just a last minute Incubator tomorrow!  Awesome!!</name><id>8731262</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221175800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cambridge-improv-incubator/events/8731262/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/0/global_3414704.jpeg</photo_url></item>