<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Clinton St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360661</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.424.ROCK (7625)</phone><name>Hard Rock Cafe</name><city>Boston</city><id>746069</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.054817</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>23.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join us for The Boston Comedy Festival at the Preliminary round of a nationwide stand-up competition. Ninety-six, bright-eyed comics from all over the country compete for $10,000 dollars in prize money.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This evening is the first round of the semi finals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston International Comedy &amp;amp; Movie Festival began back in 2000 as a way to showcase New England stand-up comedy talent to bigger audiences and the entertainment industry. Given the long line of successful comedians who got their start here in Boston, it seemed to be a natural fit for such a festival. The audience agreed, and the event has grown every year. In addition to the traditional stand-up comedy routines, the festival also includes improv, sketch comedy, and one-person theatre shows, as well as the newly expanded movie portion of this festival.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Over the past seven years, we've expanded to over a week of festivities, including outdoor family-friendly events and $10,000 in prize money for the competition winners, thanks to our sponsor Vin DiBona. The addition of The Boston Park Plaza Hotel as the official host hotel and hub of the event has created a more centralized feel, and our partnerships with other sponsors have helped us to include over 30 Boston venues and to bring in such stars as Lewis Black, George Carlin, and Gallagher.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This year, over 96 comedians from around the world will compete for the prize money. Improv, sketch, and showcase acts will run throughout the week, and our film exhibition will take place at the historic Coolidge Corner theater. Check out the Calendar for more details on the event and explore the rest of our Web site for more information about how you can be here for the 2007 Boston International Comedy and Movie Festival!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Barbara</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara</member_name><member_id>6525575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222014856000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>40-plus</urlname><id>1222683</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2699966431</group_lon><name>40/50 Something Year Olds - Men &amp; Women Social Networking</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217731532000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Comedy Festival - Live from The Cavern Club Stand-Up Comedy Contest </name><id>8465263</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221777000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/40-plus/events/8465263/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/4/global_5014660.jpeg</photo_url></item>