<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>For our Novemeber meeting, we'll take a look at some &lt;b&gt;purely&lt;/b&gt; technical analysis on stocks chosen by individual members. &lt;br /&gt;The assumption will be that fundamental analysis has already been completed in accordance with the member's Trading Plan, and that their plan follows some sort of structured selection criteria like CANSLIM.&lt;br /&gt;I am asking each member to please be prepared to provide: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; At least one stock or asset symbol of their own choosing, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Those &lt;b&gt;indicators&lt;/b&gt; they would normally use on their own charts, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; The &lt;b&gt;time frame&lt;/b&gt;(s) they prefer to trade in, and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; What consitutes an &lt;b&gt;Entry&lt;/b&gt; and an &lt;b&gt;Exit&lt;/b&gt; in their terms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will then take a look at these assets with two objectives in mind... 1.) Backtesting that Entry and Exit strategy, and 2.) Whether or not &amp;quot;reading&amp;quot; the various candles preceding that Entry and Exit can help us improve our results and/or the strategy itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, bringing questions regarding a favorite stock from your own watchlists (or perhaps even a trade from the past) for a group critique is very much encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I look forward to a lively and engaging discussion, and hope all can attend (if you have friends that might like to attend, please bring them along). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this meeting is after-hours, we are free to use the Library's parking lot. Our meeting room is downstairs and just to the right of the staircase (the Peace Dale Room).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Newcomers are certainly welcome, so if you know of others who might be interested in joining us, please refer them to this site or just bring them along to the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you all there, and look forward to a lively meeting! Meanwhile...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trade Green, &lt;br /&gt;Ray&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy working the laptop &amp; projector set up.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Raymond Dreczko</member_name><member_id>4521820</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290105016000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>IBD Enthusiasts and Traders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ibd-739</urlname><id>559772</id><group_lat>41.4099998474</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286451627000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Charlestown Investor's Business Daily Forum Monthly Meetup</name><id>zjhdnynpbwb</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290034800000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ibd-739/events/15032251/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/e/2/global_8444018.jpeg</photo_url></item>