<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Old North Dana Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01355</zip><lat>42.506814</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 35</name><city>New Salem</city><id>907353</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.270399</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;Remember to call the rangers number before the hike! Bring permit, bugspray, a snack, maybe a coat, a drink, a camera if needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;Just a reminder, this is a PERMIT REQUIRED hike. Please make sure you have one!  Rangers don't take kindly to people in their reservoir after dark unless they know about them!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;This is a repeat of a previous hike. We saw no wildlife that evening. Will we this time? Or will we just hear bears in the woods???  (Using the bathroom of course!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;If you're interested in going, you MUST have a permit. Directions are listed below.  If you don't have a permit already, you may have to hand deliver the application to the Visitors Center. If you mail it in, it could take 7-10 days to get it back. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of us have hiked/biked/walked all over the beautiful Quabbin Reservoir. But how many of us have enjoyed the solitude at night? Not me... So lets change that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PERMIT NEEDED!!! SEE BELOW!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The Quabbin Reservoir is open to night access from April 14th to October 13th this year. From their information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Night Access Permits are required for access in the Quabbin Reservation and are good only for the time &lt;br /&gt;

 period April 14, 2012 to October 13, 2012. Each person entering the Reservation must have a valid permit. &lt;br /&gt;

 The permit allows the holder PEDESTRIAN ACCESS ONLY through Gates 16, 31, 33, 35, 41, &amp;amp; 43 during &lt;br /&gt;

 the period of one hour past sunset to one hour before sunrise. Prior to each use, the holder must notify the &lt;br /&gt;

 Quabbin Watershed Rangers at 413-323-0192 regarding the time and point of access. A permit is not &lt;br /&gt;

 transferable and may be revoked for failure to adhere to these requirements or DCR Rules &amp;amp; Regulations. &lt;br /&gt;

 Instructions for use and rules/regulations information will be included with the issued permits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I propose a night hike for an illuminating walk(sarcasm intended) along the shores of the Quabbin. Gate #35 is a very flat route which follows the shoreline for a couple miles. We may include a little side trip to the Beaver Pond at dusk to see if there is anything going on a dusk... This is less of a "destination" hike and more of a "wonder what this looks like in dusk/night" hike. If all goes well, we may have other night access hikes at other locations in the Quabbin!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who knows what lurks in the darkness!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to "Night Access Permit":&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/watersupply/watershed/documents/quabnightaccess.pdf"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/watersupply/watershed/documents/quabnightaccess.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anybody interested in going MUST print out a "Night Access Application" and mail (or deliver) to the provided address. Best of all, the permits are FREE! You can either provide a self-addressed stamped envelope for them to mail you your permit or it will be available 10 days after you get the application to them for pickup at the Visitors Center. As stated above, YOU MUST CALL THE RANGERS AT 413-323-0192 the day of the hike to let them know that you have a valid permit, where you are going, and at what time. Plan on doing this prior to arriving at Gate #35 as I cannot guarantee cell phone access from there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time is tentatively set at 7:00pm, but could be moved forward or back if needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1345846478000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344805935000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset hike in the Quabbin at Gate 35 (again)!</name><id>77453962</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1345590000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/77453962/</event_url></item>