<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>North Providence</address_2><address_1>16 Josephine St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02904</zip><lat>41.861110</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>401-722-5599</phone><name>Il Fornello</name><city>Providence</city><id>579748</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.423760</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>OK, after having my original choice restaurant not return 4 calls and having 5(yes 5) restaurants say no, I found a restaurant that is excited to have us!  Apparently, this weekend being close to graduation, most restaurants are pretty full.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I chose Il Fornello for this month's event because it was fairly centrally located.  I had visited this restaurant a couple of times a while ago and had very good dining experiences- as memory serves.  Their stuffed baby squash was INCREDIBLE!  The menu is full of plentiful Italian favorites and some new-age spin on some classic dishes.  You can view their menu and learn all about the restaurant at their website &lt;a href="http://www.ilfornellori.com/home.htm" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.  As an added bonus, if you find you enjoy one of their sauces, you can even take some home for a reasonable price!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will have one bill for food, which will be divided equally among members then a second bill for beverages and alcohol. This way we can order appetizers as a table and everyone can enjoy with minimal confusion and the ones who choose not to indulge in &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; won't have to worry about paying extra when just enjoying non-alcoholic drinks. Please let me know if this is a problem for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Should we fill up and you are still interested in attending, please enter a &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; RSVP and put a note stating that you want to be wait-listed. If spots open up, I will contact you in order of RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;I have ammended the attendance policy for the group.  It will be effective starting this month's event.  Please be sure to view the &amp;quot;About Us&amp;quot; page or the Attendance Policy in the &amp;quot;Messages&amp;quot; section to make sure you understand it.  Also, if you could update your profile to answer the question that you have read and agree to the policy.  If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone who has not attended previous events, please plan on bringing a dollar to help me defray the cost of posting on meetup. For everyone who has attended, I only ask that you contribute every other event.  This would be such a big help to me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks everyone!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>"See my picture- I'm the one with the red hair. ;-)"</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212416648000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>We're good people and eating out is fun!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1205947395000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Dining-Out May Meetup- Il Fornello</name><id>7563790</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212188400000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/7563790/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/4/d/global_3818381.jpeg</photo_url></item>