<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Portland, ME</address_1><state>ME</state><lat>43.672546</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Maine Day Trip</name><city>Portland</city><id>5290592</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.283958</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi all, This is an AMC Trip I've helped lead in the past. I'm going this year for fun. This may appeal to some of you who have a few days vacation to play with. Sign up with the AMC Leader, Arnold Nadler at ardnadler@aol.com if interested! Here is the AMC Trip Listing: Drive to Portland, ME on Tuesday evening for a chartered luxury bus trip from Portland, ME on Wednesday until Sunday. Enjoy some of the best, most reliable, and most extensive skiing in the East, plus European charm, style, and the great restaurants of Quebec City. Experience nature by day, and a uniquely cosmopolitan city at night. Choice of downhill/XC skiing or snowshoeing at Sugarloaf resort in Maine en route to Canada on Wednesday, or near Quebec City on Thursday, Friday and Saturday. On Sunday, choice of XC or DH skiing close to Quebec City or stay in Quebec City for brunch, museums, etc. Also possible visit to Ice Hotel. Quebec City areas include Mount St. Anne downhill/XC, Camp Mercier &amp;amp; Duchesnay XC, LeMassif &amp;amp; Stoneham downhill. One night in Portland, ME, and four nights in luxury Loews LeConcorde Hotel, Quebec City. $620/U.S. includes five nights lodging (per person double occupancy), five days chartered bus, one breakfast, one bus dinner, bus and trail snacks, and possibly some XC tickets or cash back equivalent. $900/U.S. (per person single occupancy). Register with L. Deposit required.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Barry</member_name><member_id>7898976</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330929851000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Cross-Country Skiers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Boston-Cross-Country-Skiing-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1330889</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Cross-Country Skiing and Snowshoe Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327205070000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Want to go to Quebec for Big XC Center Skiing 2/28-3/4?</name><id>49088832</id><headcount>32</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330473600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Boston-Cross-Country-Skiing-Meetup-Group/events/49088832/</event_url></item>