<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>--&gt;Look for the Brown Boat launch sign</address_2><address_1>1050 Boston Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06043</zip><lat>41.796856</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bolton Lake Boat Launch</name><city>Bolton</city><id>610200</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.428391</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok i see the weather reports, Since this rain stuff is irritating and the predictions are usually off somewhat, I am just going to choose SUNDAY now to be safe and so you can plan ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Time of 12 Noon on Sunday For a Lake BAPTISM by Reverand AL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR (Water Boarding techniques like AL-Rxxx gets when going to airport security screening).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;~~~~&amp;gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Patchy fog before 8am. Otherwise, mostly sunny, with a high near 76. Northwest wind between 3 and 8 mph.&amp;nbsp;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : medium"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT"&gt;http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ae3333"&gt;I have some spare pumps, sponges and 2 paddle floats for us to practice with but not enough junkey practice paddles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WE will be onsite till we are tired enough and when enough feel they can safely self rescue (maybe till 2 pm or so, Bring dry clothes for the Barbie-Q later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you get COLD i will bring the gas Fire Pit (or similar gas heater) for the lake area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than likely to be left alone by the DEP it will be the heater on top of the 20 lb tank and save the gas fire pit for the nature center or a real fire at my home..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;I want you and me to get in some self rescue prior to the "OCEAN EVENTS" &amp;nbsp;which start right after our Camping Weekend Event in East Lyme in July. &lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lt;~~~~~~~~&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/f/d/7/event_34628151.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(I propose the East River, (stop at CIP, &amp;nbsp;rest &amp;nbsp;or stop for the rec yaks) then Bob's Bird Islands, and both groups meet the LOVE SHACK on the return trip. Fire and BBQ at 7 Falls as our FIRST ocean event if the weather is ok) This means open water farther out than most can swim.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;For those that can't make this "practice your self rescue" on this weekend, you may have another chance when and if we go to Mansfield Hollow on July 2, but its colder water there and will be very abbreviated portion only prior to the Barbie-Q.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;You can always practice self rescue when you expect it least at real time conditions in bad situations and hope things work out, but i may just call on the emergency radio and say, "Deputy Deputy, Help Help, somebody is sinking in the Creek Mud" and paddle to the Barbie-Q since its no hope for you&amp;nbsp;any more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please ask some of us our stories we have experienced out on the water, sometimes its&amp;nbsp;miraculous&amp;nbsp;how we made it through and learned..you won't &amp;nbsp;DO THAT again , so you learned something that will be in your mind forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS EVENT DEPENDS ON THE WATER AND AIR TEMP BECAUSE&amp;nbsp;YOU WILL BE IN THE WATER FOR A FEW HOURS OF IMMERSION WHILE&amp;nbsp;PRACTISING&amp;nbsp;YOUR&amp;nbsp;SELF RESCUE SKILLS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wear some good wet water clothes. As a general rule around water - Avoid Cotton, but wear whatever you have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(You can wear what you normally wear at paddling and see if you can tollerate being in the water to learn what does work, might as well experiment.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you are done just change into some dry clothes. The larger floored &amp;nbsp;Handicapped persons POOP houses are ok for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/5/d/event_21664189.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is so you can practice your self rescue skills and help others learn them also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that summer is here, we are starting to head out to more shore areas and a bit more challenging conditions until the fall season when we return to some new and old local rivers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 If you haven't done any self rescue classes or practiced lately, you don't want to be surprised out in the deep especially when out in the ocean at a distance out more than you can swim back to shore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This is not a "formal class", we are not instructors, &amp;nbsp;but its more for us practice and for some first timers who will get a chance to try it also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am more worried about recreational kayaks on the ocean as we travel further out and much farther than we have in the local rivers to get to our destinations. Recreational yaks don't really belong out in the ocean but with care and thought along with staying close to to someone, you can go and enjoy a great day with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BUT One small wave and those recreational boats with the big opening is full of water and they have no flotation internals so plan accordingly. Self rescue is usually not easily possible with these boats but assisted rescues work pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recreational Kayaks should have Floatation Bags in them to keep you up and for someone to make it easier to empty them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what a floataiton bag looks like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.outdoorplay.com/Kayak-Float-Bags?gclid=CIjFoPjrwakCFYrb4AodHyYhPA"&gt;http://www.outdoorplay.com/Kayak-Float-Bags?gclid=CIjFoPjrwakCFYrb4AodHyYhPA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few comments:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.paddling.net/message/showThread.html?fid=advice&amp;amp;tid=1145792"&gt;http://www.paddling.net/message/showThread.html?fid=advice&amp;amp;tid=1145792&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally tried to empty a small recreational boat and simply couldn't, &amp;nbsp;it was too heavy for me to even pull up on my bow, maybe 5 gallons maybe 10+ in the pointy parts, it seemed over 40 lbs and took many minutes to pump it out. I simply tried the bow then the stern, couldn't get that thing empty, (no floatation bags to displace any water).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I may need more practice doing this with rec boats too, thus this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of us including my self have not fallen in a lot lately and we get so used to our paddling skills untill we do fall in and find because we haven't practiced..its harder than we think... im usually good for 3 attempts then i am worn out..(and just think i have practiced in the past and should know and be better, but that is a reality).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are A biginner for the first time on oe IN the water..well..you better hope there is someone to help you if you are out on the open water..(thus the reason for a whistle on your Life Jacket and are wearing the life jacket properly so it won't float up to your neck/head..) You can't put on a life jacket very well when in the water watching the wind and waves take away your boat - paddle- and the boats contents of fresh water and things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;SO IF YOU PLAN TO JOIN US ON THE OCEAN (ACTUALLY ANY TIME ON THE WATER), &lt;br /&gt;

 PLEASE LOOK AT THE VIDEO LINKS ON THE GROUPS "MAIN PAGE" OR DO YOUR OWN SEARCH TO HAVE AN IDEA WHAT TO DO PRIOR TO THIS EVENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IF YOU HAVE A PADDLE FLOAT AND PUMP BRING IT. IF YOU DON'T HAVE ONE AND YOU HAVE A YAK..YOU MAYBE SHOULD BUY THEM ESPECIALLY IF YOU EVER GO OUT ALONE... 99% OF THE TIME I HAVE MINE LOADED AND READY TO GO..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(a bail bucket, sponge &amp;nbsp;and a dry bag are chaep alternatives but not as good)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole idea of this event is not to make you an expert but for you to learn at least one technique (the paddle float self rescue) so when you on your own, you &amp;nbsp;can get in on you own on a deeper water situation.... (Or help a biginner or seasoned person in their time of need also).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember the paddle float re-entry is not the best technique compared to others (IE the Eskimo roll, "T" rescue..etc), (a paddle float &amp;nbsp;is also not a preferred method in rough waters either) but learning the other ones requires the basic knowledge of how a boat behaves in re entry and how we really need some effort to get in using the paddle float at first and even at other times in our experiences.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember: A Paddle Float re-entry is still a necessary (first) and last resort if all else fails in most situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to start somewhere and this is the best kind of technique to start with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After this self rescue event- BRING SOME FRESH WATER FOR A QUICK RINSE SHOWER if you think you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will have the Barbie-Q at Oak Grove Nature Center again. Its private enough so we will be left alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions AT BOTTOM OF PAGE:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;. &lt;span style="color : #ff9900"&gt;iF ITS ONLY 8 OF US, THEN MAYBE JUST HAVE THE BARBIE-Q AND FIRE IN MY BACK YARD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don't need to reserve any of my boats for this event, i will bring what i feel is ONE good starter boat ( The Eddyline Wind Dancer) &amp;amp; one a bit more challenging (maybe the Greenlander Pro - if you can get in that thing you are doing good).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will work with a few of you at a time that will be with us in the ocean trips. Others will help each other too so everyone will get a chance to help, practice and learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your own boat if you have one to learn your own physical&amp;nbsp;strengths&amp;nbsp;and your own boats limitations along with discovering what you can do to make it more seaworthy..IE FLOAT BAGS for (fore and aft) Some of you will im sure not look at your safe and stable feeling recreational boat the same, because they may not be.. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh i forgot : this kind of event is a good excuse to sort of swim in an area we are not supposed to and get away with it legally up to a point. &lt;br /&gt;

 --------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the Bolton Lake Boat Launch area:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Rte I - 384 heading East to Bolton Notch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (Take the left part of fork) ...rte 6 is to the right &lt;br /&gt;

 There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At The next light has the boat launch to the LEFT and a church to the right. (South street intersection) &lt;br /&gt;

 Enter the boat launch area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 PLEASE LEAVE THE LAUNCHING CIRCLE OPEN after unloading AND PARK ON THE DESIGNATED SIDE AREAS, the DEP cops show up all the time it seems. They are looking to make some money and kayakers are the rich ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need help unloading we will always help you but don't know if you need help all the time so ask anyone to help you, we do this at all events anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please as always inventory your equipment at arrival and when leaving especially when people are trying to help, things seem to be forgotten and left behind..etc..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you all soon.. &lt;br /&gt;

 al-r&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #00ccff"&gt;Oak grove nature&amp;nbsp;centre:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then its a POT LUCK BARBIE-Q NEARBY AT OAK GROVE NATURE CENTER BY THE COVERED BRIDGE AND WATER FALL, nearby in MANCHESTER,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, everyone will arrive @ the Covered Bridge&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 (locally/unofficially referred to as "Childrens Covered Bridge"&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 over Porter Brook) smoothly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THIS LOCATION CAN handle more cars but still IS nearby, There is parking on the road up by the dam and bridge too (this is where i have to park with the trailer) and room for about 6 more cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The location is just minutes from Highland Park Market (if you forgot or want something fresh) as a reference and very easy to caravan to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring some chairs, food, and your faviourite beverage for here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GPS apx 200 Oak Grove St, Manchester&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park at: Oak Grove Nature Center Parking Lot (please park in a way as to leave room for others)&amp;nbsp;if done properly it should hold 10-20 cars &lt;br /&gt;

 ------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Driving directions from Bolton Lake:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave Bolton Lake boat ramp, take a right onto rte 44 going&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;WEST&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bear left onto 384 toward Hartford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the first exit off of 384 (exit # 4)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a left onto Highland St (if going to Highland Park Market take a right)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go apx 0.5 mile and take a right onto&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;AUTUMN&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;ST&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THEN AN IMMEDIATE RIGHT onto Oak Grove St&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the first parking lot area on the right is the place..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Park tightly..use some of the areas off on the sides also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also park by the side of the dam as i will, room for apx 6 more cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will walk up into the area a bit to a nice secluded spot near the covered bridge and water fall.&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear my Bright Orange Hunting Hat and will be near the boat ramp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309205422000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306873284000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SUNDAY JUNE  26 *KAYAK SELF RESCUE PRACTICE for everyone* @ Bolton Lk &amp; BB-Q</name><id>20406241</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309104000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/20406241/</event_url></item>