<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>110 Canal Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.364371</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-897-1337</phone><name>Boston Beer Works</name><city>Boston</city><id>842989</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060299</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Sierra Club, Boston Chapter is having a Bi-annual fundraiser for their Inner City Outings program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to put this out there for our members. If you are interested in supporting inner-city youth programs and love the outdoors, this looks like a good way to support an activity that we all love. They are also looking for volunteers who would like to get involved with planning this event. The planning meeting is tomorrow, Tuesday January 18, 2011. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.bostonico.org/apps/calendar/showEvent?calID=4831155&amp;amp;eventID=112932327" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonico&lt;/a&gt;.... for more information. Read below for the actual fundraising event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Sierra Club Inner City Outings (ICO) is a community outreach program that provides opportunities for urban youth and adults to explore, enjoy and protect the natural world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Inner City Outings Program provides safe, fun, and educational outdoor experiences to youth that would not otherwise have access to these opportunities. Simply stated, we take kids outdoors. The adventures are provided at no cost to the participants, their families or the volunteers. Our program is dependent upon volunteers and charitable contributions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Welcome to Boston Inner City Outings&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Bi-annual Winter Fundraiser Party and Raffle
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Benefiting Sierra Club Boston Inner City Outings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, February 17, 5 to 8:30pm&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Join us for food, drinks and a raffle. Proceeds raised at this event will go to fund food, transportation and any activity fees incurred on future trips with Boston area youth.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonico.org/winterfundraiser.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonico&lt;/a&gt;....[/url]  &lt;br /&gt;Event location: Boston Beerworks, 112 Canal Street, Boston  &lt;br /&gt;RSVPs not necessary&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Monica Trust</member_name><member_id>4555776</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297984667000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295275048000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bi-annual Winter Fundraiser Party and Raffle - Sierra Club</name><id>16077361</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297980000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/16077361/</event_url></item>