<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1217 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.176247</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-749-8200</phone><name>Scarlet Oak Tavern</name><city>Hingham</city><id>385248</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.885380</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a Columbus Day Lunch! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.scarletoaktavern.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Scarlet Oak Tavern&lt;/a&gt; is the latest tenant in an old Colonial house that has been run as a restaurant for years. It opened fairly recently to good reviews, including one by Christine Ordway in the Patriot Ledger's &lt;a href="http://ledger.southofboston.com/articles/2007/08/22/life/life02.txt" target="_blank"&gt;Taste &amp;amp; Tell&lt;/a&gt; section. The menu offers a wide range of American standards, some with interesting twists, as well as dishes influenced by other cuisines, notably Italian.  Entrees range from $12-$30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Organizer team at SSDOMG has been wanting to throw a weekday event into our mix for quite awhile. Columbus Day is a great chance to finally do it at a time when a significant number of members should be able to attend. We are looking forward to seeing both new and familiar faces as we check out a new and promising addition to the South Shore dining scene!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Columbus Day Lunch!&lt;br /&gt;Monday, October 8th&lt;br /&gt;12:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Scarlett Oak Tavern&lt;br /&gt;1217 Main Street&lt;br /&gt;Route 228&lt;br /&gt;Hingham, MA 02043&lt;br /&gt;781-749-8200&lt;br /&gt;Handicap Accessible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Mike and Susan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: $2pp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Min/Max: There is no min or max.  Guests are welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: 6pm Sunday, October 7th ~ Any changes made after the deadline may not be seen by the Event Organizer(s) and will be considered a Last-Minute Cancellation and could be considered a No-Show.  Please remember that we are making a reservation at this restaurant, therefore, we need to know whether or not you will be attending by the deadline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The Scarlet Oak is located within sight of the intersection of Rt 228 and Rt 53 (Queen Anne's Corner). From Rt 3, take Exit 14 and head East on Rt 228 towards Hingham/Nantasket. Follow Rt 228 for 1/2 mile to the intersection with Rt 53 - this will be the first traffic light you come to. Go straight through the intersection and The Scarlet Oak will be immediately on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: Please meet outside the restaurant's main entrance as long as the weather is fair. If you should somehow miss the main group, both the name Mike and the name &amp;quot;South Shore Meetup Group&amp;quot; should be noted with our reservation.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1192409790000</updated><rating><average>4.57999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1190404090000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Columbus Day Lunch</name><id>6404336</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191861000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6404336/</event_url></item>