<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sergei Eisenstein, having already made a splash in the Soviet Union for his first film,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Strike,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;was quickly requisitioned by the Russian revolutionary leadership to make a new film that was to celebrate the 20th anniversary of the famous Potemkin uprising. V.I. Lenin had hailed this revolt as the first proof that Russian troops could be counted on to join the proletariat in overthrowing the old czarist regime - and thus a high water mark in the October Revolution.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The crew Potemkin, coming home from a war with Japan, become mutinous due to the poor quality of rations. The ship's officers - hoping to avoid a full mutiny - order the rebellious crew shot. One crew, Vakulinchuk, cries out, "Brothers! Who are you shooting at?'' The firing squad lowers its guns, but when an officer unwisely tries to enforce his command, a full-blown mutiny explodes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #003366"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Onshore, news of the uprising reaches citizens who have long suffered under czarist repression. They send food and water out to the battleship in a flotilla of skiffs. The ruling regime catches wind of this and orders its army to suppress the citizens. In one of the most famous sequences ever put on film, czarist troops march down a long flight of steps, firing on the citizens who flee before them in a terrified - and terrifying - tide. Countless innocents are killed. The massacre is ultimately encapsulated in the image of a woman shot dead trying to protect her baby in a carriage - which then bounces down the steps, out of control. News of the uprising reaches the Potemkin, which speeds toward Odessa to put an end to the massacre.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Battleship Potemkin&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;has become one of the touchstones in film history and one of the landmarks of silent cinema. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;The Coolidge has once again joined forces with the composers and musicians of the Berklee College of Music's Department of Film Scoring to present an original score for the fully restored version of Eienstein's most famous film.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The silent films scored by Berklee College of Music tend to be among the most popular events at the Coolidge. &amp;nbsp;It is strongly advised that tickets be purchased before the event as this will likely sell-out. &amp;nbsp;Please note that members get in free, so if you are not currently a member, this would be a great time to become one:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/content/battleship-potemkin"&gt;Battleship Potemkin Tickets&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We'll gather at the Panera Bread before getting into line at 6:30. &amp;nbsp;Please note that we will not save space in line, nor seats inside the theater. &amp;nbsp;As the film is 75 minutes, we might gather after to go to a pub across the street for brew and discussion. &amp;nbsp;I'll send an email before the event to make sure everyone knows how to find each other.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be at Panera Bread as early as 6:00 pm in order to Meetup before getting into line at 6:30.  This film will probably sell out, so get your tickets when you RSVP.  We may go across the street for a brew and discussion following the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324937342000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319065830000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Battleship Potemkin</name><id>38026022</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324339200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/38026022/</event_url></item>