<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Friends: Welcome www.BestMatchClub.com members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Member request! Everyone welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dynamic, fun Super Bowl party begins at 6:00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite a gentleman. Associate with other enthusiastic Patriot fans who enjoy being with other positive dynamic singles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have just found a potential companion with a common interest. Sports!These are people who want to just have fun, laugh and enjoy the excitement of a superbowl game. Singles with passion are welcome to share their joy of the sport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entry fee for this party is $25.00 and includes pizza and beer on me. You want wine? Then bring a quality bottle of wine for yourself and share it with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice the quality of people who attended the last party. I'm very happy. You will notice another higher level of quality will be achieved at this party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprise! You will observe, Continuous improvement is a process. More improvements to come. This party is for single individuals.(30-65) The mission is to have fun and meet other high integrity single people with common interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Develop friendships and possibly find a lifetime partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Values: Be positive, nice, kind, cheerful, friendly and respectful to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please invite other eligible single people. The synergistic efforts of everyone will make it truly a memorable party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;***The entry fee is $25.00 Organizer/Host - Richard&amp;nbsp;and Nancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location is in a warm, loving, supportive and relaxing environment of our home. "Dress code - "&amp;nbsp;Comfortable". &amp;nbsp;First impressions are most meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00PM - 10:00pm Sunday. Feb. 6th, 2011 Maximum attendees 60 Location and Directions My Home 36 Woodridge Road Westwood, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-551-3307&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;128-Exit 16B/Route 109 toward Westwood Go 2 miles left on Pond Street- just past the middle school on left-if you go by Dunkin Donuts on right you missed it. Go I mile left on Oak St. (google search says go right-this is wrong) Go 1.5 miles to end-right on Brook St. 100 feet take a right on Woodridge Road My home is the 3rd house on the left-cream colored- number 36 Woodridge, Westwood, MA See you on Sunday, Feb. 6th at 6:00pm----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sharp TV coverage begins at 6:00pm If you are not a member please join at www.BestMatchClub.com The best is right now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Tosti PS: Speed dating it coming soon- offering privacy and a touch of class!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Welcome you at the door with a Sincere, Friendly Smile!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297041276000</updated><rating><average>1.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Curious Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>singles-dinner-parties</urlname><id>1245686</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Singles Dinner Party</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294069073000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl Sunday Home Party</name><id>15896785</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297033200000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/singles-dinner-parties/events/15896785/</event_url></item>