<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Updated event description on 9/22/2010:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm planning to stay Hiker's Inn or Motel in Gorham one day before the hile, 10/16 since I'll be hiking at Mt Isolation on 16th.  Moreover, our meetup time for this event is very early morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the information for Hiker's Inn (Hikers Paradise) and Motel (Colonial Fort Inn). Both are owned by same person.   1 bunk in a large bunk room is $20 including tax.  Motel room for 1 person is $47 (+9% tax), room for 2 beds (2 people) costs $59. (+ 9% tax)&lt;br /&gt;Contact information is listed on below web page.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikersparadise.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikerspara...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm planning to cover all of 4K Footers at Carter-Moriah Range in White Mountains, NH on 10/17(Sun)-18(Mon).  If you haven't hiked there yet, please join me.   &lt;br /&gt;This hiking event requires you to book bunk at Carter Notch Hut (AMC Member $32 + tax, Non-member $35 + tax) on 17th night.  You can book your bunk either on-line or call AMC reservation center at (603)-466-2727. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet at the parking lot of Wildcat Ridge Trail TH on Rt 16 at 6:30AM, 10/17. (Approx 1 mile South from Pinkham Notch Lodge.)  This is the ending point of our hike.    &lt;br /&gt;We leave some cars there at 6:40AM and drive the rest of cars to the parking lot of Carter Moriah Trail TH.  We'll start hiking at 7:15AM sharp.   Here is &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=NH-16+N%2FWhite+Mountain+Rd&amp;amp;daddr=Bangor+St&amp;amp;geocode=FU4qowIdaMLA-w%3BFTo8pQIdNgzC-w&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=dme&amp;amp;mrcr=0&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=14&amp;amp;sll=44.378349,-71.165314&amp;amp;sspn=0.052022,0.055103&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=44.259769,-71.235008&amp;amp;spn=0.052127,0.055103&amp;amp;z=14" target="_blank"&gt;the google map driving direction. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;On Day-1(10/17),&lt;/b&gt; we use &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Carter Moriah Trail&lt;/span&gt; most of the time.  The total hiking mileage is approx 14 miles and we will peakbag the following mountains: [ Note: Red ones are listed mountains in AMC 4K footers ] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Mt Surprise (2194 ft) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;* Mt Moriah (4049 ft)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* North Carter Mtn (4530 ft) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;* Middle Carter Mtn (4610 ft) &lt;br /&gt;* South Carter Mtn (4430 ft) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Mt Hight (4675 ft)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;* Carter Dome (4832 ft)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After peakbagging Carter Dome, we hike out about 1.4 mile and arrive at Carter Notch Hut.  I'd like to complete Day-1 hike within 9 hours.   &lt;br /&gt;Bunk is available to stay over night, however, there is no blankets.  You'll need to bring necessary gear (sleeping bag etc) to sleep warm.  Also, we'll need to cook dinner by ourselves. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;On Day-2 (10/18),&lt;/b&gt; we'll cover all of Wildcats at Wildcat Ridge on &lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Wildcat Ridge Trail&lt;/span&gt; and hiking mileage is approx 5.3 miles.   We'll peakbag the following mountains: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;* Wildcat Mtn (4422 ft)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* B Peak &lt;br /&gt;* C Peak &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;* Wildcat D (4062 ft)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* E Peak &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll complete our hike before noon time on 10/18. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I checked sun rise / sun set estimated time at Gorham, NH on 10/17/2010.   &lt;br /&gt;It'll be 7:02AM and 5:57PM in each.  Therefore, I hope we have enough day light time for the hike, but, needless to say, bringing headlamp is required.   &lt;br /&gt;Again, there is no food service at Hut.  Please bring your own food for lunch, dinner on 17th and breakfast on 18th at least besides snacks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please read and understand &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/hiking-490/about/"&gt;&amp;quot;About&amp;quot; page on Hike/Snowshoe in Vermont Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;, before siging up on this event.   You can sign up only when you agree with it. &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;This is strenuous hike.  If you never hiked any 4K footers, this is not for your hike.  Also, if you haven't hiked several months to high elevation mountains, this is not for your hike either. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My car is Honda CR-V (Blue, VT plate)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287546054000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1284772224000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Carter Moriah Range Traverse Hike including Wildcats!</name><id>14809197</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287311400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14809197/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/3/7/global_14218663.jpeg</photo_url></item>