<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-401-8047</phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>221452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><fee><label>Requested contribution</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We hold these truths to be self evident:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fires don't bring down steel-frame buildings.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Real suicide hijackers don't turn up alive.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A third tower (WTC 7) collapsed on 9/11.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some crazy conspiracy theorists say that 19 men directed from a cave in Afghanistan were able to hijack 4 planes simultaneously, fly around the northeast corridor for 90 minutes without a fighter response and crash 2 planes into 2 World Trade Center towers in New York City - causing 3 towers to collapse - all on the say so of a lying government that directly benefited and a servant media owned by a handful of corporations who all told us Iraq had weapons of mass destruction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't be fooled!  Learn the truth!  Save our republic!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Facts you might not know:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No steel frame building has ever collapsed due to fire, before 9/11 or since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1957, NORAD has had 100% success intercepting errant airlines in minutes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WTC 7 had minimal damage and a few small fires but collapsed into its own footprint at free-fall speed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jet fuel burns at &amp;lt;1800 F, steel melts at 2800 F, and molten steel was seen on 9/11 and months after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bush is an idiot.  How could he do this?  Why?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're right.  Bush is an idiot.  He's just a puppet.  From all indications he didn't know what was going to happen that day, though he did go along with it shortly thereafter.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The real rulers of this country committed this act of treason (and many other crimes) in order to wage a &amp;quot;clash of civilizations&amp;quot; and an endless war of domination against those nations not already under their control and to create a police state for the American people.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The terrorists hate us for our freedoms?  No.  The Taliban (&amp;quot;Al Qaeda&amp;quot;) was created to wage war against the Soviets in the 1980s and have done yeomen's work for the empire ever since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9/11 provided the pretext for the boys in &amp;quot;The Project for a New American Century&amp;quot; (PNAC) and their controllers to attack any country they claim have dangerous weapons and might attack &amp;quot;the Homeland&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We The People need to awaken from this nightmare before they attack us again for another round of wars and increasing totalitarianism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop being a &amp;quot;good&amp;quot; Democrat.&lt;br /&gt;Stop being a &amp;quot;good&amp;quot; Republican.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start being a good American.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Defend our Constitution from all enemies, foreign and domestic!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston 9/11 Truth Film Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See &amp;quot;911 Mysteries&amp;quot; and more on a big screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;February 9th-11th at The Democracy Center, 45 Mount Auburn Street, Cambridge MA 02138.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday 6pm-12am&lt;br /&gt;Saturday 12pm-12am&lt;br /&gt;Sunday 12pm-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://boston911truth.org" target="_blank"&gt;Boston 9/11 Truth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonsonsofliberty.blogspot.com" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Sons of Liberty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175022146000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169860857000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston 9/11 Truth Film Festival</name><id>5428624</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171062000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/5428624/</event_url></item>