<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Christine from the CT Paranormal Society has invited &lt;br /&gt;Members of the Greater New Haven Unknown &lt;br /&gt;Zone to attend her presentation;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Journey Into The Paranormal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come spend the night with a team of Professional&lt;br /&gt;Investigators.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lecture will cover everything that is paranormal.&lt;br /&gt;From orbs &amp;amp; their many theories to exorcisms. &lt;br /&gt;Also included will be examples of actual&lt;br /&gt;private case with the traditional beginning of exorcism rites.&lt;br /&gt;All areas of the paranormal will be covered in this lecture &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;power point presentation. Bring all your paranormal questions!&lt;br /&gt;Come &amp;amp; enjoy one of your favorite topics.&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to discuss your experiences.&lt;br /&gt;Get answers to your paranormal questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coffee &amp;amp; tea will be served along with cookies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no fee for this lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only thing we ask of you is to come enjoy &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your questions with a good dose of&lt;br /&gt;curiosity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP is now closed for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;Members who are in CT Paranormal, if you RSVP Yes in CT Paranormal,&lt;br /&gt;Then I require you to also RSVP Yes here.&lt;br /&gt;If you RSVP No in CT Paranormal, then I require you to RSVP No here.&lt;br /&gt;We are aware of the count.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location of the Meet Up will be sent to some&lt;br /&gt;Members via individual e-mail only.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope that who attend enjoy themselve.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your positive energy and your paranormal questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike B.</member_name><member_id>3713716</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196728731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Conspiracists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>conspiracy-83</urlname><id>648888</id><group_lat>41.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9599990845</group_lon><name>Greater New Haven Unknown Zone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192591149000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Journey Into The Paranormal</name><id>6564153</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196555400000</time><rsvp_limit>28</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/conspiracy-83/events/6564153/</event_url></item>