<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 Main St (Rte 32)</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.483776</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Petersham Curling Club</name><city>Petersham</city><id>4030932</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.186668</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>CAD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>30.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very sorry folks, registration came up short this year and we're not able to go forward with this event!  All registration charges will be refunded.  I hope we can try again next year!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the NHL lockout there's some ice around here that's not getting used, but not at any of the Boston area curling clubs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Queen's Alumni curling event at the Petersham Curling Club is here again and there has been a good Meetup contingent for the last several years. All Canadian alumni &amp;amp; friends of Canada are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The easy format accommodates beginners and capable skips alike. Curling club members will provide some instruction, help us set up teams to play some games, and provide plenty of tactical guidance. We'll roll out a Redbones BBQ buffet for you to finish up with, or, like Bruce, you can also just stay on the ice until they kick us out. We've also got some door prizes which you'll like best if you're a Queen's alum, or willing to be mistaken for one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The club provides all the equipment you'll need to curl, which for many includes their cash bar which will be open for the duration of our visit. You should wear comfortable, warm, and flexible clothing, and clean shoes, i.e. not the ones you walked in on. Don't forget the "warm" part: even if it's unseasonably nice out, it will still be freezing on the ice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Registration is $30 (Cdn) which covers everything mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately we aren't including transportation to Petersham, which is a charming 75 mile trip west of Boston just off Rt 2. I am coming from Cambridge and could bring 2 but will need to arrive quite early and leave a bit late for set up. Anyone who'd enjoy helping provide rides can post here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get to the online registration with the link below. RSVP on Meetup after you have paid and registered at the Queen's site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.queensu.ca/alumni/networking/branches/usa/boston/eventCurling.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.queensu.ca/alumni/networking/branches/usa/boston/eventCurling.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Stokes</member_name><member_id>7363758</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1354483830000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Expat Canadians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Canucks-in-Boston</urlname><id>29048</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Expat Canadian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353828536000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Good Curling!</name><id>92698602</id><duration>14400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1354469400000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Canucks-in-Boston/events/92698602/</event_url></item>