<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 Wheelbarrow Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06513</zip><lat>41.329034</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Haven High School</name><city>East Haven</city><id>1426780</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.832210</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newhavenchorale.org/" target="_blank"&gt;The New Haven Chorale&lt;/a&gt; is an auditioned, professionally conducted, 100-member community of vocal musicians dedicated to bringing beautiful choral music to the Greater New Haven community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Joy! Concert will include Mozart's Spatzenmesse (Sparrow Mass) in C, Bach's Missa Brevis in G Major, and sing-alongs of holiday favorites including selections from Handel's Messiah, with spirited orchestral accompaniment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;The CCCC (&lt;a href="http://www.ccccnh.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Coordinating Council for Children in Crisis&lt;/a&gt;) is the beneficiary of this year's concert. CCCC works to prevent abuse, neglect and victimization across the life span and to serve those affected by providing home visiting and outreach, parenting education, family strengthening activities, counseling and advocacy to children and adults.  Please feel free to visit their website (above) and of course feel free to &lt;a href="http://www.ccccnh.org/donate.php" target="_blank"&gt;donate&lt;/a&gt; to this important organization serving the New Haven community for over thirty years through multiple programs and initiatives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Tickets:&lt;br /&gt;Adults $20&lt;br /&gt;Seniors $15&lt;br /&gt;Students free with ID&lt;br /&gt;Childen under 12 are free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**Tickets must be purchased ahead of time from me** THe CCCC's has special tickets with a different color, and will only receive proceeds from those tickets &lt;i&gt;which are used by attendees.&lt;/i&gt;  (The reasoning for this is that they don't want people to buy tickets but not attend, leaving empty seats.) If you cannot make the concert but are moved to volunteer or donate to the CCCC, please feel free to do so : )  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think it makes the most sense for us to meet outside (ok, nevermind that sounds cold... &lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;meet in the lobby/area outside the auditorium&lt;/span&gt;) and I can give you your tickets, and you can give me cash for the tickets.  Feel free to call my cell if you can't find me, are going to be late, or are a &amp;quot;maybe&amp;quot; and decide to come (so that I can look out for you). Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My contact number will be in my RSVP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327350054000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289503033000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fundraiser for local non-profit - New Haven Chorale’s Joy! Concert</name><id>15417542</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292189400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/15417542/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/8/global_19550904.jpeg</photo_url></item>