<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>795.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;HAPPENINGS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Retreat opens at 6 PM Thursday, July 1st, with a quiet, meditative ritual, creating spiritual space and setting intentions. Opening ritual is followed by a delicious candlelight dinner, overlooking the sunset over the pristine clear lake and tranquil wooded hills. However you arrive to this magic secluded place, within the very first hours you will find yourself relaxed and open for a gentle but powerful transformation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Retreat opening night is concluded with the first Transformational Breathwork session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, Saturday and Sunday mornings start with meditation and group work, followed by Transformational Breathwork sessions. Free time in the afternoons is allocated for personal reflection, meditation, journaling, swimming or canoeing in the warm, welcoming waters of the spring-fed lake, enjoying sun on a private deck or a hammock, hiking, relaxing in the privacy of surrounding woods, communing with trees, fun and soulful connections with old and new friends. We may even be blessed with a visitation by a bald eagle, bear, foxes, swan, or deer. Nights are busy with exquisite dinners, talent offering show, powerful rituals. On the last night of the retreat everything comes together in a ritual of release and empowerment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;LEARNING AND EXPERIENCING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deep inner group work focuses on ego and projection, on using relationships as a laboratory for personal growth, learning and exercising non-egoic modalities of relationships, balance of energies, techniques of awareness, relationship with the Source and authentic use of inner power.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Group work and processing is complemented and expanded by four Transformational Breathwork sessions, where surfaced emotions, suppressed memories, traumas, hurts, outdated cultural and personal misperceptions, inner conflicts cluttering our psyche and bodies are released and transmuted within the powerful space of spiritual energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;TEACHER AND PRACTICES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teachings developed by Christian de la Huerta are uniquely connected to the essence of the world spiritual traditions, linking traditions of east and west, with the most powerful yet simple and clear application to everyday challenges of being and living fully in the world. Practices, tools and techniques experienced at the retreat give you a mighty spiritual boost for personal growth and for personal relationship with the Divine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://soulfulpower.us/aboutus/" target="_blank"&gt;Christian de la Huerta&lt;/a&gt; is a spiritual leader and master breathwork practitioner, writer, inspirational speaker, retreat and group facilitator for the past 20 years. He is founder of the Mastery of Breath, a school, program and system of training based on the principles of Transformational Breathwork.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The spiritual space held and facilitated by him at retreats is known for its intense healing energy, clearing, evoking one's essence, exquisite spiritual experiences and positive life-changing effects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://soulfulpower.us/testimonials/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Read testimonials from our retreats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;LOCATION&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The wonderful retreat venue in New Jersey is only 40 min drive from Manhattan, yet it feels like another reality. This tranquil and peaceful, custom-built magnificent home is surrounded by the lake and reminds one of Frank Lloyd Wright, with a touch of Zen. There isn't a square room in the house. The lake is constantly replenished by the underground springs which you can feel when swimming. A hot tub just steps outside the house is a perfect place for stargazing and nighttime meditations. Food is healthy and delicious, and you are welcome to participate in the meal preparation. All dietary requirements and preferences are respected and accommodated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional services, such as Transformational bodywork enhancing your energy flow and experiences, are offered at retreat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;WHO IS PARTICIPATING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soulful Power retreats are open and inclusive of all religious and spiritual paths and traditions, system of beliefs, genders and love orientations. Retreat graduates often return to be part of new retreats, advancing in their own process of growth and transformation. The work itself evolves continuously; every next retreat creates yet more powerful elevated space and builds more connected spiritual community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;LOGISTICS AND TRANSPORTATION&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most participants from mid-Atlantic states and the northeast drive in. From the West Coast and elsewhere, you may either take a flight or a train to Newark, where you will be picked up and brought to retreat location, and then driven back on Sunday. There is also a bus from midtown Manhattan to the nearest town of Bloomingdale, where you will be picked up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;More detail and pictures from the Lake House&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;              &lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;You may register via this meetup, or by sending email to info@soulfulpower.us, &lt;br /&gt;or via &lt;a href="http://soulfulpower.us/lakeretreats/" target="_blank"&gt;http://soulfulpower.u...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Insturctions will be provided</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christian de la Huerta</member_name><member_id>11469589</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287708875000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Breathwork</urlname><id>1299646</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>Breathwork</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275961292000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Soulful Power -- Annual Independence Day Retreat. July 1-4, in the Lake House.</name><id>13731654</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278021600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Breathwork/events/13731654/</event_url></item>