<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>159 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.377552</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Historical Society</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12883772</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.134193</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;A FABULOUS NATIVE PLANT SALE: Buy plants with the expert advice of horticulturalists and landscape professionals-- all while enjoying delicious food, wine, and light jazz music. Every plant sold is native to New England and guaranteed to add ecological value to your garden. Our experts will help you choose the best species for your garden. A great selection of books on ecological gardening will also be for sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND MORE: Tour a native plant garden to see the beauty of these plants in the landscape. This event is also an annual fundraiser to support Grow Native Massachusetts. It includes a silent auction with great garden-related items available for bid: a granite bird bath, outdoor planters, professional tree services, nursery gift certificates, silk scarves, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admission includes all food, wine, music, and programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Live Jazz Music by the Silverwood Duo— on Sax, Flute, and Guitar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase tickets by April 18 and you can pre-order the plants you want! We will be sourcing these plants from three different nurseries and having them delivered for your pick-up at the sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets: $28 Members / $35 Non-members &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="https://co.clickandpledge.com/advanced/default.aspx?wid=65721"&gt;https://co.clickandpledge.com/advanced/default.aspx?wid=65721&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More event information at: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.grownativemass.org/programs/festivalfloralia"&gt;http://www.grownativemass.org/programs/festivalfloralia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367786522000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366142515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Festival Floralia: A Native Plant Sale and Celebration of Spring</name><id>114663432</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367776800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/114663432/</event_url></item>