<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>147 Princeton Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01863</zip><lat>42.633003</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-251-1500</phone><name>Princeton Station</name><city>North Chelmsford</city><id>991231</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.376991</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>hi everyone,&lt;br /&gt;making an executive decision...lol.  no, really the heavier votes went to Princeton Station.  Sorry for those who wanted to go to NE Seafood, but if people still want to meet up at NE Seafood, I'll be happy to post it, when I come home from Foxwood today with all that money, but someone should be the point person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have to deal with doing small groups to eat, and splitting smaller bills, that's my only suggestion.  I'll try and be there by 8-8:30 pm, as I probably won't have a date afterall, that way I can do some introductions.  If you get there when the band goes on, you're out of luck, I'll be on the dance floor :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One week PS got it right and gave us all separate bills, I was quite impressed, but then the bottom fell out last time.  So, you all MUST insist on separate bills if you're going to eat.  We can always spring out the meetup signs, and combine tables, after eating is done :)&lt;br /&gt;I'll def be there to boogie but in case I get a date, someone will have to hold the fort and keep the troops in line before I get there (Richard?).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;suz&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281321052000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280860091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rock City at Princeton Station :)</name><id>14306489</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281139200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/14306489/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/3/0/global_15205072.jpeg</photo_url></item>