<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The workshop will begin with delving into the mystic path of Sacred Sexuality. We will learn about Sexuality&amp;#146;s expressions through the different spiritual traditions across the ages. Topics include Daoist and Hindu forms of Tantra Yoga, foundational concepts, different approaches -- restrictive and expansive and a taste of what tantric practices are all about. We will inspect how various religions differ in their innate outlook ...of life and sexuality, including masturbation, brothels, orgasms, penis size and so much more. Diving into Tantra, Introduction Lecture This portion of the workshop is mostly talk, we might be able to touch on a few simple practices but it is given as a conceptual introduction to the practical workshop we will be holding on Saturday morning. In continuation to our introduction on Friday night, we'll be delving deeper into the meditations, practices and techniques used by Tantrikas to heighten their awareness and redirect their attention inwards. We'll be working through numerous processes used to connect us to one another, and work with the body towards awakening our dormant Kundalini energy. Kundalini and Tantra go hand in hand, and our practices will cover both. We'll be covering the issues of self acceptance, pleasure and pain, relationships, the short history of human sexuality, the origins of sin, neo-tantric perspectives, the dangers of the Tantric teachings and it's various teachers and much more. This workshop is directed toward serious and truly curious seekers, wanting to explore their own perceptions and understand why we do what we do and yet take a conscious choice, a leap of faith into themselves. Diving into Tantra Our Kundalini practice will end with holding a Tantric `Yab-Yum` ceremony or practice, and the workshop will end with an empowerment Puja, held in recognition and glorification of the divine mother or divine feminine within us. This event is recommended for individuals and couples alike, but we would love to have preregistrations in order to try and ensure a proper gender balance for our Saturday workshop. What should I wear? Do I need to bring anything? --------------------------------------------------------------- For the Friday event, there is no requirement for special attire, for joining the Saturday workshop it's recommended to wear comfortable clothes which would fit for light movement exercises (similar to a Yoga class). For the ending Puja celebration bring some kind of an offering such as flowers or fruit. For those coming from Boston or NYC or any other distance...we are opening up the co-op space for those interested for an overnight stay for any additional $30 - will include an all organic breakfast &amp;amp; morning yoga with Imani. Bring your own mattress pad &amp;amp; bedding. Please email Imani@themamalution.com to reserve your spot! For more info, visit -- &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/3p9t47m" target="_blank"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/3p...&lt;/a&gt; See More&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316282174000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314398096000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Diving into Tantra</name><id>31088671</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316214000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/31088671/</event_url></item>