<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>College Street and Frontage Road </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.303593</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Yale</name><city>New Haven</city><id>9464722</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.931442</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Yale University imprisons over 150,000 animals including primates, dogs, cats, sheep, pigs, ferrets, rodents, and others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yale experimenters have cut holes into the skulls of animals, forced them to consume dangerous drugs including cocaine, and have subjected them to electrical shocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is almost no end to the myriad of ways that animals suffer in Yale labs before being killed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yale considers this to be a humane and responsible use of animals. Experimenters document their abuses in academic papers that boost their careers and earn big money for this, usually funded by millions of taxpayer dollars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Government documents indicate that Yale University currently locks up over 150 nonhuman primates such as the rhesus macaque in the photo to the left. Under the guise of "research" and often with taxpayer dollars, these animals are subject to range of cruelties such as being forcibly addicted to dangerous drugs and having debilitating diseases such as Parkinson's deliberately inflicted upon them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yale's own website also indicates the University does business with the notorious Florida-based company PRIMATE PRODUCTS which has gained national notoriety after photos of horrific abuse leaked from their facility. Primate Products both breeds animals and sells the instruments use to torment them in laboratories such as those at Yale University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please join us in exposing these Ivy League abusers and in standing up for animals!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leaflets and signs will be provided, but feel free to make your own signs if you prefer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please rsvp here: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/426459044058260/" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/426459044058260/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1349652728000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-386</urlname><id>279146</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1348607156000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>National Primate Liberation Week Protest</name><id>84062622</id><duration>5400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1349555400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-386/events/84062622/</event_url></item>