<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>165 Brainard Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06114</zip><lat>41.734776</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-244-3311</phone><name>Chowder Pot IV</name><city>Hartford</city><id>219703</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.659450</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>You are cordially invited to the wedding of the year...The Godfather's Meshuggener Wedding @ The  Chowder Pot in Hartford.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The nuptuals of the Godfather's daughter To Bernie Goldberg is taking place and you will be part of it all! This very funny, very entertaining dinner show is back for a repeat performance. Everyone has heard about it...really hilarious wedding where the two cultures collide. If you have seen it, come back for the fun. If you have not, come and laugh until your face hurts!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full meal is included with your ticket price of $39.95. Dancing, food and laughs...what can be better! We will be getting a table and enjoying the evening as a group...we would love to have you join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must call The Chowder Pot box office (860-244-3311) to purchase your ticket by credit card. The dinner choices are Stuffed Chicken or Stuffed Shrimp. You will be asked your choice when you call. Please tell them that you want to be seated at Chuck Quint's table (as the reservation is in his name).&lt;br /&gt;Once you have made your reservation, you MUST email me to let me know in order to ensure a seat at our table. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This show ALWAYS sells out way in advance...so don't wait. If you want to be in on the fun, do it (make your reservation) sooner than later in order to avoid the disappointment of a sold out show! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is being done in conjunction with Eat, Laugh and Be Merry in West Hartford (Chuck's group). Join us and LET'S HAVE FUN!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for  Terri or the Meetup Sign...cell is 203-808-5829</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1300630159000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>This is the wedding of the year...lol!!!!!!!!!!!</why><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294695082000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>You Are Invited To A Wedding...The Godfather's Meshuggener Wedding!</name><id>15997939</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300575600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/15997939/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/7/global_20733095.jpeg</photo_url></item>