<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Trotting Park Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.655754</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lowell-Dacut-Tyngsboro State Forest </name><city>Lowell</city><id>1581120</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.370743</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Claire P. &lt;br /&gt;

 RAIN CANCELS THIS EVENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weather permitting, I think it would be fun to go hiking on the trails at Lowell-Dracut-Tyngsboro State Forest. Please know that my intent is to enjoy the view of the area, and to chat along the way. This event is meant more to have fun than to get a workout. I thought that we would enjoy nature for about two or three hours, with a few breaks/stops along the trail. This park is just full of beautiful views, so come and enjoy some fresh air, beautiful views, and all this while in good company of friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will meet at 2&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/8/9/2/event_211354962.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;:00 pm at the end of Trotting Park Rd in Lowell MA, which is the parking area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECTIONS: From Route 3, take exit 32, to Drum Hill Rd. Go 5 sets of lights. Drive over the bridge, take left at set of light, then next set of light take a right on Old Ferry Rd. Go to stop sign, tak a left on Varnum Rd, drive about ½ mile, take a right on Trotting Park Rd, drive all the way to the end. OR From Route 113 in Lowell, take Old Ferry Rd (street alongside JJ Boomers), go to stop sign and take a left on Varnum Rd, drive about ½ mile and take a right on Trotting Park, go all the way to the end of the road, this is where the trails start. Look for the meetup sign or my white Toyota Corolla.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to bring plenty of fluids and to dress in layers so that you will be comfortable the whole time we are out on the trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone cares to, we can then go grab a bite to eat or enjoy a hot chocolate, at a restaurant nearby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is at no cost. I hope to see you there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP or call my cell @ 603-247-0897&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Lowell-Dracut-Tyngsboro Forest Park&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a white Toyota Corolla</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Claire P</member_name><member_id>7906902</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364250214000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>fun folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dance-342</urlname><id>462174</id><group_lat>42.75</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4899978638</group_lon><name>Dance &amp; Activities Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362528439000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking or Snowshoeing at Lowell-Dracut-Tyngsboro State Forest</name><id>107800712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364148000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dance-342/events/107800712/</event_url></item>