<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>83 Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.352554</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-338-8158</phone><name>Chau Chow City</name><city>Boston</city><id>669028</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.060160</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>No website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross streets: Chauncy and Edinboro&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nearest T stop: Park Street, or;&lt;br /&gt;Green line: Boylston&lt;br /&gt;Red line: Downtown Crossing&lt;br /&gt;Orange Line: Chinatown&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside at 12:45 for a 1:00 reservation. If you arrive late, we'll be on the 3rd floor (the dim sum floor).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My favorite, lazy way to celebrate New Year's Day is by going out for Chinese and then seeing a movie. You, too? Then join friends for a festive, yet relaxed lunch in this three-story, award-winning favorite in Chinatown. We'll dine on the third floor (the dim sum floor) where, in addition to dim sum, we have our pick of the entire menu, including a huge variety of seafood (like squid, oysters, sea conch, lobster, crab, abalone) and the usual crowd-pleasing dishes (Sweet and Sour Pork, Kung Pao Chicken, etc.). I'm partial to noodle and veggie dishes myself, so if you're a vegetarian, come sit by me! :) Afterward, we'll take the five-minute stroll over to Loews Boston Common and take in a 3pm-ish flick. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We don't all necessarily have to see the same movie. On Friday December 28, I posted a new discussion on the message board and sent out an update to all &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; RSVPs with a link to the movie theater's schedule so you can give some thought to what you might want to see, and we can have some discussion about who's seeing what. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That's as much organizing for that portion of the day's event that I'm going to do, except for strongly recommending you buy your ticket in advance either from Fandango (or whatever agency you use) or in person that afternoon before you arrive at the restaurant, because the theater will be crowded and films WILL sell out.  (I don't know about you, but for me, standing in a long ticket line for a half hour, only to finally reach the counter and be told that the movie I wanted to see has sold out, is not the way I want to start off the new year!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If folks are interested, we can gather afterward and wind up the day by grabbing coffee/drinks or dessert. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*********************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events &lt;br /&gt;run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while &lt;br /&gt;sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving &lt;br /&gt;promptly. &lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and &lt;br /&gt;tax. &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event &lt;br /&gt;and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO- &lt;br /&gt;SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than twenty- &lt;br /&gt;four hours from the the event you are counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if &lt;br /&gt;you've NO-SHOWED. &lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the &lt;br /&gt;group. &lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, to those on &lt;br /&gt;the wait list, to the organizer, as well as the restaurant, whose &lt;br /&gt;staffing numbers are based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-four hours from the event and you are not &lt;br /&gt;able to attend, you MUST call or text Tonya at (617) 445-7549. An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than &lt;br /&gt;twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected &lt;br /&gt;courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other &lt;br /&gt;unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO &lt;br /&gt;with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO &lt;br /&gt;with a comment to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and &lt;br /&gt;venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barring a blizzard, we'll meet outside at 12:45 for a 1:00 reservation. If you arrive late, we'll be on the 3rd floor (the dim sum floor).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200001043000</updated><rating><average>4.55999994278</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>29</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196433356000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Year's Day Lunch and a Movie</name><id>6830000</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199209500000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6830000/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/3/4/global_2870100.jpeg</photo_url></item>