<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>New Years Eve Dance&lt;br /&gt;Friday Dec. 31st. 8 pm. to 1 am.&lt;br /&gt;The Castleton&lt;br /&gt;Rt 111 off of exit 3 on rt.93&lt;br /&gt;Winham NH 03078&lt;br /&gt;Host: Steve Obermiller 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can be bought &lt;br /&gt;Price $20.00 Through December 1st&lt;br /&gt;$25.00 Through December 26 th&lt;br /&gt;$30.00 12/27 to end of event date&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.togethernh.com/singlesevents.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.togethernh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Please join Steve O. and about 55 + friends out of the 300 to 400 + attending this event. Also, we are doing a dinner before at a different location. So, please look for that event and  RSVP for the two of them. If you wish to join us for both. If not, just come and dance. If you get there as close to 8 pm. as possible? ( the doors open at 7:30)  Steve O. will introduce you to everyone at our talbles. After 9 pm. it get difficult to introduce people. Because there is no one at our tables. They are all up dancing.&lt;br /&gt;The Together Dance director wrote:&lt;br /&gt;These Dances always have new people in attendance, no two dances are ever the same. They have in attendance 300-450 quality single adults of all ages at every dance. The clientele, top notch - easy to find location, the fun, excitement and energy all add up to an unbeatable evening out. The dances are a great way to meet and mingle with other area singles in a great setting. Feel free to come solo, bring a friend, or bring a crowd - your bound to have fun.&lt;br /&gt;All parties are SMOKE FREE and start at 8pm sharp and end at 1:am, good idea to arrive early.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROPER DRESS PLEASE, NO JEANS NO SNEAKERS, NO HATS.&lt;br /&gt;Complimentary hors d'oeuvres until 8:30 pm.&lt;br /&gt;Cash bar, free parking, door prizes&lt;br /&gt;Professional D.J. - Takes requests and plays the music you want to hear and danCE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join In To Bring In The New Year!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE PURCHASE YOUR TICKETS IN ADVANCE OF THIS EVENT, EARLY PURCHASE STRONGLY SUGGESTED. LAST YEARS PARTY AND PREVOUSE SOLD OUT EARLY. PRE PURCHASE YOUR TICKETS AND SAVE WHILE GUARANTEEING YOUR ADMISSIONS, RESERVE YOUR TABLE WITH SEATING IN BLOCKS OF 10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All pre-purchased tickets allow early entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ticket Purchase - you may purchase on line- togethernh@msn.com (1-800-688-5644 Questions)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price $20.00 Through December 1st&lt;br /&gt;$25.00 Through December 26 th&lt;br /&gt;$30.00 12/27 to end of event date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Meet Up was suggested by many people who live within this area, but remember have a happy and fun New Year where ever you go, safety!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you respond please let me know that you purchased your ticket.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where&lt;br /&gt;Castleton&lt;br /&gt;RT.111 &amp;amp; RT.93 exit 3&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call us at anytime 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293844947000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291239216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Years Eve Dance</name><id>15612333</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293840000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/15612333/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/4/8/global_4195352.jpeg</photo_url></item>