<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mount Carmel Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.399429</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>510-828-5439</phone><name>Sleeping Giant</name><city>Hamden</city><id>101161</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Woo-hoo! Looks like as gorgeous a day as yesterday so we are go go go!&lt;br /&gt;HEY! All you Maybes! Its &lt;b&gt;Novermber 2nd.&lt;/b&gt; Exactly how many more warm sunny days do you think you're gonna see?!?&lt;br /&gt;Everyone please shoot to meet there at 11:45 so we can start hiking at 12:00. Some people need to get back early so we may do trails and/or split up depending on turn out and interest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**REMEMBER THE CLOCKS WERE TURNED BACK***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hey Gang!&lt;br /&gt;     I want to see if we can get in a Sleeping Giant hike on Sunday before the season's done altogether.&lt;br /&gt;There's some terrific foliage out now and I bet it looks great from up there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lets meet in the parking lot by the main gate off Mt. Carmel across from Quinnipiac at noon. Last I checked, there's a $7.00/car entry fee for the lot, but you can park on the nearby street for free.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Dogs are welcome!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail lengths and difficulty will be determined when we get there based on who shows and what they're up for.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather forecast for Sunday is currently completely sunny, though a brisk 49 degrees. You may want to dress in layers and wear hats, gloves, etc. There's a couple places near there where we can stop for food after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll update this Sunday morning if the weather is questionable. If its raining, its cancelled, but assume its on unless I post otherwise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you Sunday!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008 (unavailable from 10am-11am Sunday morning, but any messages will be returned shortly after 11.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225819728000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225402635000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sleeping Giant Hike</name><id>9063306</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225645200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/9063306/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>