<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's celebrate spring and get out and take an advanced/walk hike.  The walk in unlimited but lunch at my mom's house will be limited to 10 people.   Please email me directly if you would like to join us for lunch even if you don't want to walk/hike. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wachusett Mountain is about an hour's drive from Boston. Please note the walk to the top is not especially difficult but could be more challenging than other walks.  My plan is too walk/hike for about 2.0 hours so please bring some snacks and plenty of water.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LUNCH: My mom is cooking Easter Dinner so please bring something to share. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3,000-acre Wachusett Mountain State Reservation surrounds the summit and offers a wealth of natural and recreational resources. The Reservation's natural resources include forests, alpine meadows, ponds, streams, fields, and even a perched bog. Recreational opportunities abound at the reservation including hiking, nature study, hawk watching, picnicking, and skiing. The Reservation offers 17 miles of hiking and walking trails, including 3.9 miles of the Midstate Trail, which runs from Ashburnham to the Rhode Island border. Mountain Road stretches to the John Hitchcock Visitor's Center at the summit, a short distance from the Wachusett Mountain Ski Area, which is the largest in eastern Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/central/wach.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in front of the visitor center.  If you are lost or can't find me my cell is 508-472-7900.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206459297000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203639516000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wachusett Mountain state reservation and potluck</name><id>7381668</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206286200000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/7381668/</event_url></item>