<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;* INVITE AND BRING EVERYONE YOU KNOW! EVERYONE (21+) IS WELCOME! * LIR IRISH PUB IS GRACIOUSLY DONATING APPETIZERS FOR US!!! * Learn more about my run at www.howardsimpson.com/marathon , contribute, and cheer me on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In THREE WEEKS from today, I will be taking on my first marathon. I have been training hard, including running over 100 miles in January, overcoming a toe injury in February, and getting myself back on track (pun intended) in March. I have raised nearly $800 so far as well. The goals are simple. Run 26.2 miles (in under 4.5hrs) and raise awareness and support for the Gay Men's Domestic Violence Project, an organization that provides a 24-hour crisis hotline, emergency safe-housing, and free legal counsel to survivors, regardless of their sexual orientation or gender identity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested $12 "cover" at the door includes appetizers, but please contribute at any level you feel comfortable. Can't wait to see you there, and thanks again to everyone in TMIRCE for all the inspiration and support that makes this effort possible!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332808146000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Llama's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonruns</urlname><id>502534</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Informal Running Club: Home of TMIRCE:BOS</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1331827216000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Run Howard Run, Drink Howard Drink! Bar Night for Survivors of Domestic Violence</name><id>56470452</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332802800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonruns/events/56470452/</event_url></item>