<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of 133 and 1A</address_2><address_1>26 Main St </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01969</zip><lat>42.707548</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stephanie's Village Pancake House</name><city>Rowley</city><id>862761</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.881822</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trees are getting bare and the weather is getting cold.  Let's head indoors for an awesome breakfast!!  Stephanie's Village Pancake House has a mouth watering breakfast just waiting for us to sink our teeth into!  So grab that appetite and Meetup with us for a morning of great food, conversation and lots of laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will not be seated until everyone is there, so please arrive on time, I have the Meetup time set for 10:45 but we won't be sat until everyone is there AND the room is available for us, please note that we may NOT be seated exactly at 11:00, but the restaurant will do their best to sit us when the room is ready for us, please be patient when waiting for the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read this entire write up, as there are a few things that you need to know before you RSVP!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event has a few special rules, please read below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For those of you that have had breakfast with us before you know what to expect.  If the last time we went for breakfast here didn't work for you then please take that into consideration when RSVPing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We may not all be sitting at the same table, if there is enough of us we may get out own room, but different tables in the room, who knows you may be sitting next to your new best friend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please bring plenty of smaller bills and some change to pay for your bill, remember one dollar bills are your friends, lol.  I have a new way for everyone to keep track of what you have eaten and paying your bill, at the end should be easier to pay (should be).  Work with me here this will be the 1st time we will be using it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have RSVP'd for any past event and you were a no show, then you may not be able to get into this event.  This event is very popular and I really want everyone to be able to come.  But IF you have been a no show in the past, and want to come to this event then send me an email: msdondon2003@yahoo.com telling me that you plan on showing up at this event. Remember that this is a popular event and everyone wants to come, don't take up a spot that someone else could have had.  If you don't email and tell me that you are coming, then I may remove you from this event.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will be scheduling this on my 2 Meetup sites, so there may be more people going to this event then you see.  IF you are on both sites (Our Circle of Friends and Connections &amp;amp; Friends) then please only RSVP on 1 site.  If you end up putting in your yes on both sites be looking for an email from me, explaining which group I took you off of which will be my choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have put a minimum amount of people that can attend this event, I will probably change it as the date gets closer, so be watching that you were taken off the waiting list and on the coming list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a minute now and put the Meetup phone into your phone, that way if you are are running late, can’t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, you already have it in your phone:  978-304-2811, please note this phone does not accept text messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it time for you to pay your dues?  Please look at your profile page where it states “Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer” You can pay your dues at any event.  Thank you in advance for paying your dues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snow may cancel this event please remember to check back to see if we are still going to this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a courtesy to everyone in the group come back to the event page and change your RSVP if your plans change or call me/send a message through the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you at Stephanie's&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be on the porch as you walk into the restaurant if we are not there, then come on in and you should see us right there in the waiting area</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353449571000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>A-Circle-of-Friends</urlname><id>1421257</id><group_lat>42.8100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8799972534</group_lon><name>A Circle of Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350100844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's breakfast time!</name><id>86782572</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353253500000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/A-Circle-of-Friends/events/86782572/</event_url></item>