<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.349530</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-536-5400</phone><name>Boston Public Library/ Rabb Lecture Hall</name><city>Boston</city><id>401397</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.079430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lecture Series: &amp;quot;Shaping the 21st-Century City&amp;quot; with Anthony Flint&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The author of &amp;quot;This Land: The Battle over Sprawl and the Future of America&amp;quot; describes how concern about global warming and the growing appeal of urbanism are converging to shape the 21st-century city. This presentation is co-sponsored by the Loeb Fellowship Program at the Harvard Graduate School of Design.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This Land&amp;quot; tells the untold story of development in America--how the landscape is shaped by a furious clash of political, economic, and cultural forces. It is the story of burgeoning anti-sprawl movement, a 1960s-style revolution of New Urbanism, smart growth, and green building. And it is the story of landowners fighting back on the basis of property rights, with free-market libertarians, homebuilders, road pavers, financial institutions, and even the lawn-care industry right alongside them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The free lecture begins at 6:00 pm and is open to the public. These lecture series are very popular and can fill up. I recommend you come early if you can, which is why I set the time at 5:45 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterward, let's go next door to Sólás (710 Boylston Street) to discuss the lecture or just socialize. Here is the website for Sólás: &lt;a href="http://www.solasboston.com/solasboston/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.solasbosto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet just outside the doors to the lecture hall. Look for me: I will wear a name tag.&lt;br /&gt;If you miss the lecture just meet us at Solas around 8:00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199660064000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Design Build Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonarchitects</urlname><id>696342</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Architecture Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194566757000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Architecture December Meetup: Lecture and Discussion</name><id>6705297</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198104300000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonarchitects/events/6705297/</event_url></item>