<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>439 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.346640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 338-8884</phone><name>Masa </name><city>Boston</city><id>668968</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.069084</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's expected to be freezing Sunday, so let's go South, to the South End that is, to bask in the warmth of the Southwest. If you you love a bargain and a delicious one at that, join us for Masa's Brunch Fiesta.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this time this is open to members only....you're not allowed to invite a guest. If you include a guest in your RSVP, your RSVP will be updated to zero (0) guest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://masarestaurant.com" target="_blank"&gt;Masa's Web Site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://masarestaurant.com/menus/masa_menu_brunch.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Masa's Brunch Menu&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Driving from I-93: &lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 18 to Mass Ave. Take a right onto Mass Ave. Go under the Boston Medical Center and continue through 3 traffic lights. At the 4th light take a right onto Tremont Street. Masa is 1 mile up on the left. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MBTA directions: &lt;br /&gt;The Arlington stop on the green line is the closest Subway station. Exit the station onto one-way Arlington St. Follow the flow of traffic for 5 blocks past the castle and over the bridge. At the Tremont St intersection look to your right to see Masa. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following MEMBER GUIDELINES were developed so our events run smoothly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly. &lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend. &lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event &lt;br /&gt;and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO in less than twenty-four hours from the the event you are counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation. &lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the event and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must text or call me at (617) 445 -7549.  &lt;br /&gt;An email from you to Tonya explaining your absence or less than twenty-four hour RSVP change from YES to NO, is an expected courtesy.  &lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other  &lt;br /&gt;unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO  &lt;br /&gt;with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list.  &lt;br /&gt;If this event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be placed on wait list.  &lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated, so please rate the event and venue by completing the surveys after the events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196782386000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196222609000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Masa Brunch Fiesta</name><id>6816008</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196609400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6816008/</event_url></item>