<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Shaw Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02905</zip><lat>41.776336</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Edgewood Yacht Club</name><city>Cranston</city><id>1305073</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390270</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ever wonder what a &amp;quot;Yacht Club&amp;quot; is like? Wonder what Narragansett Bay looks like south of the oil drums and the J&amp;amp;W Campus? Have you been thinking about learning to sail, but Newport is a haul? Here's your chance to check it out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: royalblue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SOCIAL MEMBERSHIPS ARE $85 FOR THE SEASON AND THE APPLICATION FEE IS WAIVED (FOR THIS YEAR)!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edgewood Yacht Club is a really great yacht club. It's historical, low-key and no one is snobby. Its entirely run by the members and the club dates back to the late 1800's so there's a lot of history. After many years in the planning the Darby Room (member's social room) is being renovated and demolition has already started. Uncovered after many years of hiding behind ugly wood paneling is the spactacular and original field stone fireplace with the keystone dated 1908. There's a story behind THAT one! Construction will be finished by Opening Day in May!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you didn't know it already, sailing on Narragansett Bay is the best sailing on the East Coast and it can be affordable - yes, you can buy a boat for less than a used car! EYC is holding an Open House this Sunday between 1-4pm, so I'm posting it as an FYI. The members will be there (as will I), so if you've ever thought about checking out the sailing scene in the area this is a great place to see. They also have a sailing school! The only other sailing opportunity in Providence is through Community Boating at India Point. I learned to sail at EYC as an adult (they have an adult sailing program) and if you take lessons and graduate from the school the one-time application fee is waived to become a member. So if you're the slightest bit curious, come on down and check it out! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edgewood Yacht Club is located 10 minutes south of Providence in the Edgewood section of Cranston off Narragansett Boulevard on Shaw Ave. at the foot of the hill (you can't go any further or you'll end up in the water). You can see the building to the left when you drive south on Narragansett Boulevard. Basically if you take Allens Ave. south and keep going (past that industrial section and the Johnson &amp;amp; Wales Campus) Allens Ave. turns into Narragansett Boulevard when you cross into Cranston. Pawtuxet Village is also in this area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing the silver scarf!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268158665000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267221125000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Edgewood Yacht Club Open House -  Sunday, March 7, 1-4pm!</name><id>12719337</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267984800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/12719337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/c/d/global_7564301.jpeg</photo_url></item>