<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Reincarnation, posited by great spiritual and philosophical traditions including Hinduism, Buddhism, the Kabbalah, Pythagoreanism and others, is backed by circumstantial evidence that is not easily discounted. How does one explain memories of past living persons that have been supported by meticulous research?  Or how do young children suddenly begin speaking foreign languages or languages that are no longer spoken? Or the phenomenon of many people's night dreams and daydreams that so clearly reference other times and places, often giving that person a greater sense of life purpose and meaning in the universe?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the outright rejection of past lives reflects scientific dogma, it is equally dogmatic to take a completely non-skeptical approach.  Every memory “recalled” in a past life regression may not be the recollection of persons who have actually lived.  The subconscious mind has long been thought of as being the seat of creativity and imagination as well as the link to spiritual and psychic dimensions (e.g.. Thomson Jay Hudson, The Law of Psychic Phenomena, 1892.)  If the subconscious does in fact have this dual role then it would not be unreasonable to suppose that creative imagery and past life memories might at times become confused or intertwined.  It is possible that past life regressions may reflect information about both actual past lives and creative solutions to difficulties and challenges of the current life.  Ultimately, does it matter whether the past life &amp;quot;memory&amp;quot; is real or only creative fantasy?  In either case, information is being uncovered that has profound importance to the hypnotic subject who is experiencing a past life regression.  Even if the PLR recollections are sometimes imaginary they can be the ultimate life reframing experience and give profound new meaning to a person’s life.  And, in this respect, there is a clear suggestion that past live regression work and dreamwork are closely interrelated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting will begin with a short introduction about the nature of past life regressions and will then be followed by free flowing discussion.  In the middle we will have a short demonstration of group hypnosis that will provide an experiential taste of a past life regression.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Arthur Schwartz&lt;/b&gt; is director of Integral Hypnosis, a hypnotherapy and philosophical counseling practice located in Newton.  In addition to conventional hypnotherapy such as for weight, smoking cessation, correcting bad habits, improving motivation and reducing anxiety he uses his background in philosophy to help clients discover the deeper meaning behind the issues that lead them to his office. Past life regression work is a special aspect of Arthur’s practice, and philosophical counseling may be employed to help unravel and better understand the karmic lessons uncovered by the PLR session. For more information visit &lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.integralhypnosis.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.integralhy...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is welcome to attend and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/suggestion/" target="_blank"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 25 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions and other information about Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel, please visit &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.swedenborg...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263570945000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1261112053000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Past Life Regression and Hypnosis</name><id>12108520</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263340800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/12108520/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/7/1/global_12289137.jpeg</photo_url></item>