<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note the time change: I'll be at the theater by 6:15 p.m.; the movie starts at 7:05 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, December 15: I just learned that Charlize Theron has been nominated for a Golden Globe Award for her role in &lt;em&gt;Young Adult&lt;/em&gt;. I was already looking forward to seeing this movie, but this news makes it a little more interesting.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The previews promise lots of laughs for &lt;em&gt;Young Adult&lt;/em&gt;, which opens on Friday.&amp;nbsp;I have seen very funny clips on late-night talk shows, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****From the theater website:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the comedy/drama &lt;em&gt;Young Adult&lt;/em&gt;, Academy Award winner Charlize Theron plays Mavis Gary, a writer of teen literature who returns to her small hometown to relive her glory days and attempt to reclaim her happily married high school sweetheart (Patrick Wilson). When returning home proves more difficult than she thought, Mavis forms an unusual bond with a former classmate (Patton Oswalt) who hasn't quite gotten over high school either.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Young Adult&lt;/em&gt; reunites director Jason Reitman and Academy Award winning screenwriter Diablo Cody (of &lt;em&gt;Juno&lt;/em&gt; fame).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*****&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more about &lt;em&gt;Young Adult&lt;/em&gt; at the theater website: &lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheaters.com/"&gt;www.landmarktheaters.com/&lt;/a&gt;. If you click on the link for "Boston" on the left, then scroll down on the right to find the movie, you will also find a link for the movie's website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will purchase my ticket at about 6:15 (maybe earlier), then wait at the foot of the stairs in the theater lobby. I&amp;nbsp;don't know if the theater will be crowded at this new time, so my plan is to arrive&amp;nbsp;early, just in case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for me and my red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; At about 6:40, I will move into the theater auditorium (can't miss the previews, although the last movie I saw had no previews or ads -- amazing!) You can find me in the theater auditorium if you are late. &lt;strong&gt;The movie starts at 7:05 p.m.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movie, I will wait in the theater lobby near the foot of the stairs to gather everyone. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for the red backpack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please RSVP if you plan to attend this event so I know who to look for.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the red backpack. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324860464000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323749509000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Young Adult (the movie)</name><id>44281902</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324163700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/44281902/</event_url></item>