<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Updates: The movie starts at 5:15 PM and its a 3D show. So request all of you to come by 4:30 PM. Again if anyone running late call me in advance and can book you a seat. My number is &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;980-939-2107&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First we will watch the movie Clash of the Titans at Buckland Mall, Manchester and then hit out to Texas Roadhouse. We shall meet at the lobby by 4:30 PM. If any of you get late you can call me and  I shall reserve a ticket for you. My number is 980-939-2107 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please check back for the actual timings of the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location of the movie theater is &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Showcase Cinemas Buckland Hills &lt;br /&gt;99 Redstone Road &lt;br /&gt;Manchester, CT 06045 &lt;br /&gt;(800) 315-4000  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;br /&gt;I-84 &amp;amp; Buckland Street, On Red Stone Road, directly across from 99 Restaurant &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Clash of the Titans &lt;br /&gt;In &amp;quot;Clash of the Titans,&amp;quot; the ultimate struggle for power pits men against kings and kings against gods.  But the war between the gods themselves could destroy the world.  Born of a god but raised as a man, Perseus (Sam Worthington) is helpless to save his family from Hades (Ralph Fiennes), vengeful god of the underworld.  With nothing left to lose, Perseus volunteers to lead a dangerous mission to defeat Hades before he can seize power from Zeus (Liam Neeson) and unleash hell on earth.  Leading a daring band of warriors, Perseus sets off on a perilous journey deep into forbidden worlds.  Battling unholy demons and fearsome beasts, he will only survive if he can accept his power as a god, defy his fate and create his own destiny. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film will be presented in 3D wherever possible, making the gods even more formidable, the creatures even more fearsome, and taking audiences even deeper into the mythological realm of Perseus quest. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://clash-of-the-titans.warnerbros.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://clash-of-the-t...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Texas Roadhouse &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Texas Roadhouse Story is simple. Legendary Food, Legendary Service®!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hand-cut steaks, award winning ribs, fresh-baked bread and made from scratch side items are the standard at Texas Roadhouse. All of our food is created from scratch with only the highest quality-freshest ingredients. We combine large portions and great value to give you Legendary Food at a reasonable price. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But we're not just about steaks. With great ribs, chicken dishes, fish, salads and lots more, we can satisfy almost any appetite. We guess that's why you all voted us #1 in both Menu Variety and Value in the 2004 Restaurant &amp;amp; Institution Magazine's Choice in Chains Guest Survey. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Legendary Service for every guest and Legendary Fun with our employees, are also main ingredients in our recipe for success. At Texas Roadhouse, our team has an incredible sense of pride in everything we do. We want our guests to have such a good time they'll want to come back again tomorrow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.texasroadhouse.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.texasroadh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Prem</member_name><member_id>5450086</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270500322000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269109908000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clash of the Titans + Dinner at Texas Roadhouse</name><id>12941444</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270326600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/12941444/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/c/global_2456236.jpeg</photo_url></item>