<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rte. 6A, Brewster</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02631</zip><lat>41.741430</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Nickerson State Park</name><city>Brewster</city><id>477594</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.015175</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This event is also listed on both the wlking and the hiking meetup sites. 10 campsites have been reserved so we will be  alarge group. Its going to be a lot of fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Camp Friday and Sat. nights at Nickerson State Park. The park is located right&lt;br /&gt;on the Cape Cod Rail trail, near its center. We will ride for a couple of hours&lt;br /&gt;each day, doing the western end on Saturday and the eastern end on Sunday. ***&lt;br /&gt;Both rides will begin and and in the parking lot at the entrance to Nickerson.&lt;br /&gt;The Staruday ride will begin at 1:00 since many people will be arriving from&lt;br /&gt;Boston. The Sunday ride will begin at 10:00.*** You may join us for any portion&lt;br /&gt;of the weekend.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nickerson State Park&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rte. 6A, Brewster&lt;br /&gt;508 896-3491&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travel the road to the upper campgrounds in Nickerson State Park and you may think for a moment that you have been magically transported to the Berkshire Hills or the piney woods of the Carolinas. Nowhere in sight are the sand dunes and salt marshes usually associated with Cape Cod. Instead, you are surrounded by woods that slope down to the banks of eight crystal clear fresh water ponds. Yet, if you walk or bicycle through the woods, you will find no rivers or streams feeding the ponds. These are ?kettle ponds,? among more than 300 formed as glaciers retreated from the Cape over 10,000 years ago. Completely dependent on groundwater and precipitation, the water level in the ponds fluctuates from season to season and year to year.&lt;br /&gt;Nickerson's 1900 acres offers more than 420 campsites, including yurt camping, an amphitheater, eight miles of roads, hiking trails, an eight mile bike path that connects to the 25 mile Cape Cod Rail Trail, and ponds stocked year-round with trout. Cape Cod Bay is within walking or bicycling distance. You can swim and canoe at Flax Pond; birdwatch or catch-and-release fish at Higgins Pond, or participate in the many seasonal interpretive and recreational programs offered by park staff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/nick.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park Directions&lt;br /&gt;Nickerson State Park is located in southeastern Massachusetts on the mid-Cape, near Brewster.&lt;br /&gt;From Boston: take Rte. 3 south to the Sagamore Bridge, then Rte. 6 to exit 12 in Orleans, turn left off the ramp onto Rte. 6A West towards Brewster. Continue for about 2 miles. Park Entrance is on left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cape Cod Rail Trail &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Cape Cod Rail Trail follows a former railroad right-of-way for 22 miles through the towns of Dennis, Harwich, Brewster, Orleans, Eastham and Wellfleet. Its paved surface, few hills, and well-marked automobile crossings make it ideal for cyclists. The trail has a wide unpaved shoulder on one side to accommodate horseback riding, walkers, and runners.&lt;br /&gt;There are many opportunities to get off the trail and visit a beach. Food and water are also readily available and public restrooms can be found at Nickerson State Park, Salt Pond Visitors Center at Cape Cod National Seashore and the National Seashore Headquarters. If you do not have a bike, bike rentals are available at many points along the way. For people with disabilities, a limited number of hand-cycles are available for rent at specific bike concessions. For more information call Nickerson State Park at 508-896-3491.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/ccrt.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/trails/print/ccrt.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217804540000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Leisure Bicyclists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bike-235</urlname><id>527341</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Boston Leisure Bicycling</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200268206000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Cod Cycling &amp; Camping weekend</name><id>7107252</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217631600000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bike-235/events/7107252/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/4/1/global_1549089.jpeg</photo_url></item>