<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hillary and I went last year it was a Chocolate dream and it was all free - Willy Wonka move over :-) ---&lt;br /&gt; Chocolate and love songs.  What better combination for you and your loved one on Valentine’s Day weekend? One of the highlights of Romantic Willimantic’s 7th annual Chocolate Festival brings those two sweet things together at the Chocolate Lovers’ Soiree and Cabaret on Saturday, February 12, at the Capitol Theater on 896 Main Street, Willimantic. The lobby doors open at 6:30 p.m. where you can sample some chocolate treats before heading into the beautifully renovated theater at 7 p.m. to enjoy love songs of all styles, performed by the Windham Performing Arts Alumni and friends.  After the show enjoy a gourmet chocolate reception including imported chocolate, truffles, fudge, hand-dipped fruit, cakes, and cookies, and …the Italian barista will return by popular demand.The soiree and cabaret caps off the first day of Romantic Willimantic’s 7th Annual Chocolate Festival.  Earlier on Saturday downtown streets will be bustling with folks taking the Chocolate Chip Stroll.   Over 30 businesses will open their doors and invite families to sample all types of chocolate goodies and entertainment from 11 a.m. to 3 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;“It’s such a great way to spend the day and to support Willimantic,” said Lynn Duval, organizer of The Romantic Willimantic Chocolate Festival.  “Take your family to the Chocolate Chip Stroll, perhaps eat at a downtown establishment, then enjoy a wonderful evening with friends or take your sweetheart on a date at the Chocolate Lovers’ Soirée and Cabaret.”&lt;br /&gt;Tickets for the Chocolate Lovers’ Soirée and Cabaret are $15 per person or $25 per couple and may be reserved by calling 860-450-0918 or purchased at Potpourri, 860-456-4476, or at the box office the night of the event.  Seats are limited and will sell out.  For a complete listing of the Romantic Willimantic Chocolate Festival, visit www.romanticwillimantic.org. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Romantic Willimantic Cupid will be crowned on Monday, February 14 at the Windham Town Hall at 10 AM. Join us to see who it will be.    &lt;br /&gt;#   #   #&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Brown</member_name><member_id>10321540</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297611708000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Winos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup</urlname><id>593834</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven  Wine and Dining  Meetup Group,</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295561722000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cupid's Chocolate Delight  " Willimantic's 7 th Annual FREE Chocolate Festival"</name><id>16124219</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297526400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Wine-and-Dining-Meetup/events/16124219/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/7/d/global_2165245.jpeg</photo_url></item>