<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>William J Day Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02127</zip><lat>42.330878</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Castle Island</name><city>South Boston</city><id>714718</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.030659</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Leslie S. will be your host for this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not your average Thursday night…spend this one viewing the amazing vistas this park has to offer. Only 2 miles off Route 93 via either Columbia Rd. or down Summer Street from South Station, you will have 2 choices- a 2 mile walk along the waterfront taking in views of the Boston Harbor islands, city skyscrapers, and Bunker Hill on a paved and boardwalk path, all with flat terrain OR a climb up one level to the open air observatory of Fort Independence where you can see forever while watching the sunset over the Harbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will reconnect at the end and for those who would like, we will mosey down the street into Southie for a drink or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will convene in front of Sullivan's Take-Out at the entrance to the park and reconnect back at the same point. At the conclusion, those who would like can mosey down the street into Southie for a drink or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This location offers plenty of free parking and great summer take-out fare if you would like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please call Leslie at 617 848-8802 when you arrive (or if late) so we don’t leave anyone behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event will be rescheduled if it rains. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>call Leslie at 617 848-8802</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>4094202</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>leslie seabury</member_name><member_id>12064134</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342838667000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Active "People" people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1425</urlname><id>1283834</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Sitzundjibers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340487719000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Tour of Castle Island and Fort Independence Observatory</name><id>70438042</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342736100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1425/events/70438042/</event_url></item>