<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><lat>42.407211</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Innovation Center</name><city>5th Floor - Havana room</city><id>11853672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.382439</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/"&gt;http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for tickets and more info. The cost is $10 per ticket. People who have purchased tickets a minimum of 24 hours prior to the event will receive preprinted name badges. Refreshments will be served.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We would like to thank O'Reilly Media for sponsoring this event!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://strataconf.com/rx"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/2/2/8/event_231401512.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://strataconf.com/rx2013/public/content/home"&gt;O'Reilly Strata Rx conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, happening September 25-27, 2013 in Boston, MA, brings together the diverse communities driving innovations in big data analytics for health care. At Strata Rx you'll discover how data experts are successfully using big data to advance personalized and predictive medicine; realize significant cost savings; and conduct research that points to entirely new products and markets. This is a rare opportunity to take a fresh and deep look at how to acquire, analyze, and use big data in your own organization. Pain Points in Healthcare members can save 20% on any conference pass with discount code H2BOS .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets for this event will be on sale after May 8th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearly half of the health IT professionals queried believe mobile technology will "substantially impact healthcare delivery" in the years ahead, while 16% of respondents said mobile technology will dramatically change the future of healthcare delivery, according to&lt;a href="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/"&gt;the survey&lt;/a&gt;. HIMSS looked to IT professionals from major U.S. hospitals and had approximately 180 participants who answered questions regarding mobile use in their organizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Let's learn from the experts who are advocating or building Mobile Technology solutions for Healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speakers Bio &lt;strong&gt;QMedic - Sombit Mishra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/uploads/1/1/0/3/11038074/2038574.png" alt="Picture" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Sombit Mishra is the Founder and CEO of QMedic (www.qmedichealth.com), a smart wearable sensing platform that passively monitors physical activity, sleep, and falls in the home.  Sombit brings over 8 years of experience in Web/Mobile strategy, product management, marketing, and business development to QMedic.  Since its launch, QMedic has received numerous awards and recognition for its work in behavioral measurement, machine learning, and ubiquitous computing.  The company was selected from over 2,500 companies as a "Big Data" finalist for the Amazon Web Services Global Startup Challenge, was a finalist for AARP's startup award, and is the recipient of an SBIR contract from the National Cancer Institute and National Institutes of Health.   In 2013, Sombit was selected as a TEDMED Innovation Scholar as well as 1 of 14 Global Emerging Innovators by American Express and the Ashoka Foundation.  While in graduate school at MIT, Sombit was awarded the Patrick J. McGovern Prize for outstanding contributions to the student community, which included raising over $1M in sponsorships for MIT startups across health, software, and clean technology.  He continues to serve as a business mentor to hundreds of executives through the MIT Trust Center for Entrepreneurship and Sloan Fellows programs.  Sombit completed his MBA from the MIT Sloan School of Management, an MSc from the London School of Economics, and a BA from Northwestern University. You can follow Sombit/QMedic on Twitter at @sombit and @qmedichealth, or connect with him on LinkedIn at&lt;a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/sombitmishra" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.linkedin.com/in/sombitmishra&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Healthcare Experience - Mohan Venkataramana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/uploads/1/1/0/3/11038074/3884710.jpg" alt="Picture" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Dr. Mohan received his bachelors degree from Indian Institute of Technology and his Doctorate degree from MIT.  &lt;br /&gt;

Dr. Mohan has over 25 yrs of Software development experience and has worked for AT&amp;amp;T Bell labs, Microsoft, Amazon and Fred Hutchinson cancer center developing applications and solutions. He is experienced in converting innovative ideas from concept to market.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

He is passionate about helping businesses succeed by mentoring and coaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RxApps - John Moore III&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/uploads/1/1/0/3/11038074/7679140.png?173" alt="Picture" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;John is a reformed molecular biologist, trading in his pipette for his inbox to found RxApps, a system to enable better care management and collaboration in the treatment of chronic illness. After conducting genetics research at two fantastic facilities at MGH and then Novartis, John decided that pursuing a PhD no longer excited him as much as it once did. He made the transition to entrepreneurship working at the Partners Healthcare Research Ventures and Licensing practice and Mass Medical Angels. He decided to pursue healthcare IT as the best means to enact change after a consulting project showed him the potential that the HITECH Act and PPACA had to truly enact change. He recently completed the Rock Health accelerator and is currently working with a team of health innovators to launch HealthSpark, a new community focused on enabling innovators in this very difficult space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/"&gt;http://www.painpointsinhealthcare.com/&lt;/a&gt; for tickets and more info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368061918000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Healthcare-IT-Professionals</urlname><id>1467042</id><group_lat>42.5099983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1999969482</group_lon><name>Boston Healthcare IT Professionals</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367361470000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mobile Technology Innovation in the Healthcare Industry</name><id>117033652</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368050400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Healthcare-IT-Professionals/events/117033652/</event_url></item>