<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>35 White Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.388901</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Porter Square Shopping Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>12742462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119186</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear BA Members,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come hike with fellow BA members! Meet in the Shaws parking lot near the Porter Square T stop. Contact me at 857-236-5631 if you can't find us. Remember your bag lunch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for drivers for all those who wish to attend this trip, so post a message if you are available to drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Monadnock is a popular hiking destination for many who live in New England. It is a moderately challenging hike with typical New Hampshire terrain (rocky and steep) and close enough to Boston for a day trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Monadnock It is one of the most frequented high peaks in New Hampshire and part of the White Mountain range, noted for its varied hiking trails and great views (e.g., &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/IesTwk"&gt;http://bit.ly/IesTwk&lt;/a&gt;). And for the benefit of beginners and novice hikers, the summit is just under 4,000 feet. For more details on the &lt;span&gt;White Dot Trail&lt;/span&gt;, please visit &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/riC5mk"&gt;http://bit.ly/riC5mk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check out the weather report in the following link for Mount Monadnock before attending this hike. This page will help prepare you for the weather conditions you will face and the type of clothing, footwear, and gear you will need. &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://monadnocktrails.com/weather.trails.php"&gt;http://monadnocktrails.com/weather.trails.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the Mt. Monadnock weekly report for updated information on weather and trail conditions &lt;a class="linkified" href="http://blog.nhstateparks.org/monadnock-weekly-report-04-05-13/"&gt;http://blog.nhstateparks.org/monadnock-weekly-report-04-05-13/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chances are there will be some snow and ice still on the trails&lt;/strong&gt;. Also, it's a New England spring, aka still winter weather conditions on the mountain, so that means bringing hats, gloves, an extra pair of hiking socks, hiking boots, gaiters, microspikes or crampons if you have them, layers, warm jacket, rain jacket, two liters of water, lunch, snacks, first aid kit, trail map, and compass if you have one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a one day trip with the sole purpose of hiking to the summit of Mt. Monadnock.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; At a minimum, we require that anyone signing up have a basic fitness level &lt;em&gt;comparable&lt;/em&gt; to walking 3 miles daily or running 3 miles three times per week. The hike will be 4 miles round trip and take an estimated 5-6 hours on the trail, including lunch. This trail is often busy with hikers and rated a 3 out of 5 in difficulty, meaning it can be noticeably steep at times, you’ll be breathing in deeper and faster, and you’ll probably need to step up onto or over rocks, tree roots, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We will be hiking at a moderate to brisk pace, and we will want to keep all members together for the safety of all our hikers. So, cooperation to this end is important.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***Note: For safety, anyone in not wearing hiking boots or similar footwear and not carrying water will not be allowed to carpool with the group to Mt. Monadnock.  &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Need To Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 All summits are potentially hazardous due to high winds and unpredictable weather. Please bring appropriate provisions and hiking gear in preparation. Note it tends to be colder than average New England temperatures at the summit. &lt;strong&gt;Think winter weather conditions when prepping for this trip.&lt;/strong&gt; Please be sure to bring the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: Monadnock State Park day use fee&lt;/strong&gt;: $4 per person, $2 for children aged 6-12, children 5 and under are free and New Hampshire residents over 65 are also free. &lt;br /&gt;

 A season pass is available for $60.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking Equipment&lt;/strong&gt; recommended by Hike Safe: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;2 Liters of Water&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hiking boots &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt; No vibram 5-fingers or barefoot/light footwear as trails are expected to be wet and potentially snowy/icy. Wet/ cold feet mean turning back to the car &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sweater or Pile Jacket &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long Pants (wool or synthetic)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hat (wool) &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bag lunch (we will be on a mountain and driving for 8-9 hours, so bring lunch and snacks)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;extra socks &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt;(a welcome treat for the feet at mid-hike, or if you inadvertently step in a stream or snow. They also double as mittens…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flashlight or Headlamp &lt;strong&gt;(required)&lt;/strong&gt; Dark falls quickly below tree-line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gloves/ mittens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;high energy lunch and snacks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;winter jacket and shell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Aid Kit/Repair Kit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whistle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rain/Wind Jacket &amp;amp; Pants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pocket Knife&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hiking poles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;map&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;compass&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Notice&lt;/em&gt;: Pets are not allowed on the mountain! &lt;br /&gt;

 No Camping or Fires except at campgrounds!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Text/ call me at 857-236-5631 if for some reason you have trouble locating us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;NOTE: HIKING HAS INHERENT RISKS. DO NOT ATTEND THIS MEETUP IF YOU ARE UNSURE IF YOU ARE ADEQUATELY PREPARED. AS A GROUP WE CAN DECREASE RISK BY BUDDYING UP AND LOOKING OUT FOR EACH OTHER BUT NOBODY IS LIABLE FOR YOU. THIS IS A VOLUNTARY HIKE. IF YOU ATTEND, YOU ARE ASSUMING THE RISK.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Porter Square parking lot in front of Tags and Shaws- Text Emilie at 857-236-5631 if you can't find us</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Emilie</member_name><member_id>4710889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367977204000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365398558000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mount Monadnock!</name><id>113239112</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367758800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/113239112/</event_url></item>