<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;GREENING OF AMERICA - The Conversion Of Bio-Agriculture, Bio-Energy,  and Bio-Products To Eco-Sustainable Businesses&lt;/b&gt; :&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last summer we saw the impact of peaking global production of fossil hydrocarbons in the massive price increase for our fuels. Even more devastating was the impact to the agriculture sector for food production, processing and transportation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Bio-economy is emerging with bio-agriculture, bio-energy, bio-products taking on new emphasis in our national quest for energy independence and sustainability. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Chad Kruger of WSU identified, this “Triple Bio” involves three interwoven tracks of:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * bioagriculture to produce food and feedstocks in an environmentally and energetically sustainable way. It is a suite of concepts, practices and technologies which capitalize on biological processes to maximize resource conservation and resource-use.&lt;br /&gt;    * bioproducts research and development to process raw biological feedstocks into useful and higher value materials. This refers to refined, value-added materials derived from biomass, such as industrial, biological, medical and nutraceutical products.&lt;br /&gt;    * bioenergy to reduce our reliance on fossil fuels for transportation fuels, electricity and heat. It refers to both power (electricity and heat) and liquid fuels derived from biomass.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tonight the EntreTech panel of business, technology and investment professionals who are contributors, supporters and participants in the emerging bio-economy will emphasize businesses and technologies that present eco-sustainable activities for this “Triple Bio” play.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderator: &lt;br /&gt;Gary Patterson, &lt;a href="http://fiscaldoctor.com/" target="_blank"&gt;FiscalDoctor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Panel:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dennis R. Costello, Managing Director, &lt;a href="http://www.braemarenergy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Braemer Energy Ventures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Patrick J. Govang, President and Co-founder, &lt;a href="http://www.e2ematerials.com/" target="_blank"&gt;e2e Materials, LLC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;William &amp;quot;Jeff&amp;quot; Marshall, Chairman and CEO, &lt;a href="http://www.getg.com/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Green Earth Technologies, Inc.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donald W. Crookes, Sr., President and CEO/ Founder, &lt;a href="http://www.hy-syence.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Hy-SyEnce, Inc.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meeting Organizer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry Grumer, &lt;a href="http://www.taacorp.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Technology Associates &amp;amp; Alliances&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://theentretechforum.camp7.org/" target="_blank"&gt;REGISTER ONLINE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;websites of interest:&lt;br /&gt;Green Fuel Technologies pick up speed in 2008 -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn16343-green-fuel-technologies-pick-up-speed-in-2008.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newscienti...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.masshightech.com/stories/2008/12/29/daily33-DOE-has-200M-for-biofuels-development.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.masshighte...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The U.S. Department of Energy announced $200 million in new funding opportunities for the development of pilot and demonstration-scale biorefineries including the use of feedstocks such as algae and production of advanced biofuels such as bio-butanol, green gasoline and other biofuels.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter </member_name><member_id>6855667</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237333124000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225198354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>GREENING OF AMERICA - Conversion of Bio-Agriculture to Eco-Sustainable Business</name><id>9046400</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234913400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/9046400/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_4560057.jpeg</photo_url></item>