<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>475 Moody St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02453</zip><lat>42.367938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 894-8755</phone><name>Little India</name><city>Waltham</city><id>739937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.237468</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Our first book will be The Space Between Us, by Thrity Umigar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazon.com&lt;br /&gt;The Space Between Us, Thrity Umrigar's poignant novel about a wealthy woman and her downtrodden servant, offers a revealing look at class and gender roles in modern day Bombay. Alternatively told through the eyes of Sera, a Parsi widow whose pregnant daughter and son-in-law share her elegant home, and Bhima, the elderly housekeeper who must support her orphaned granddaughter, Umrigar does an admirable job of creating two sympathetic characters whose bond goes far deeper than that of employer and employee. &lt;br /&gt;When we first meet Bhima, she is sharing a thin mattress with Maya, the granddaughter upon whom high hopes and dreams were placed, only to be shattered by an unexpected pregnancy and its disastrous consequences. As time goes on, we learn that Sera and her family have used their power and money time and time again to influence the lives of Bhima and Maya, from caring for Bhima's estranged husband after a workplace accident, to providing the funds for Maya's college education. We also learn that Sera's seemingly privileged life is not as it appears; after enduring years of cruelty under her mother-in-law's roof, she faced physical and emotional abuse at the hands of her husband, pain that only Bhima could see and alleviate. Yet through the triumphs and tragedies, Sera and Bhima always shared a bond that transcended class and race; a bond shared by two women whose fate always seemed to rest in the hands of others, just outside their control. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Told in a series of flashbacks and present day encounters, The Space Between Us gains strength from both plot and prose. A beautiful tale of tragedy and hope, Umrigar's second novel is sure to linger in readers' minds. --Gisele Toueg&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Space-Between-Us-Novel-P-S/dp/006079156X/ref=pd_bbs_sr_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;qid=1219087803&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.amazon.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Grey Tshirt with a large Om symbol on the front, and book on the table!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dorothy Drennen</member_name><member_id>2879015</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224347162000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indian Bookwalas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-1439</urlname><id>1261834</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Indian Food, Indian Fiction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219087471000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indian Fiction, Indian Food September Meetup</name><id>8570542</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221321600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-1439/events/8570542/</event_url></item>