<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>291 Ocean St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02050</zip><lat>42.091411</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 837-2722</phone><name>Haddad's Ocean Cafe</name><city>Marshfield</city><id>751868</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.645430</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Greetings once again, fellow diners! Our popular Letter Series continues!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Representing &amp;quot;H&amp;quot;, this month's letter, is Haddad's Ocean Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the Brant Rock section of Marshfield, Haddad's typifies the sort of no-frills, fried seafood restaurant that can be found up and down the South Shore. There are, however, fried seafood places and fried seafood places, and the recommendations of our members and the online community concur in placing Haddad's among the gems of its genre.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A couple quotes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From &lt;a href="http://www.hiddenboston.com/Haddads.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hidden Boston&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;Haddad's Ocean Cafe...may just be one of the best--and most authentic--seafood restaurants south of Boston.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And from psc109 on &lt;a href="http://chowhound.chow.com/topics/311120" target="_blank"&gt;Chowhound&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;quot;The decor has seen better days but you can't beat the quality or price.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us as we wet a line in Brant Rock and hope to reel in a golden, not to mention flaky, culinary experience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Haddad's Ocean Cafe&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;291 Ocean Street&lt;br /&gt;Marshfield (Brant Rock)&lt;br /&gt;(781) 837-2722&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 13 @ 6:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizer:&lt;/b&gt; Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; None at this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; Up tp two per member.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; S2.00 per person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Friday, Sept 12 @ 5:00 PM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special Note:&lt;/b&gt; SSDOMG's usual policy of paying in cash is even more important at this venue. Haddad's does &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt; accept credit cards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions From Route 3:&lt;/b&gt; Take Exit 12 (Route 139) and head &lt;b&gt;East&lt;/b&gt; on Route 139. You will remain on Route 139 essentially the entire way. The road passes through both business and residential areas. Go straight through any traffic lights that you come to, remaining on Route 139. Businesses that you will pass include a Wendy's on your left and a Roche Brothers supermarket on your right. If you watch house numbers as you drive, you should notice before long that Ocean Street is actually running concurrently with Route 139.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will know that you've almost arrived when you see that Route 139 is running &lt;b&gt;parallel to the water, which is on your left&lt;/b&gt;. Just after you pass Victory Baptist Church on your right, Route 139 takes a hard right turn, while Ocean Street continues straight. Note that you cannot simply keep driving straight to remain on Ocean Street (you will see a &amp;quot;Do Not Enter&amp;quot; sign directly in front of you) but must rollow Route 139 as it curves right, then take an immediate left to get back onto Ocean Street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you turn back onto Ocean Street, you will see a row of buildings on your right, and parking spaces on your left. Haddad's is the second or third building on your right and is clearly visible.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both Mike and South Shore Meetup Group.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1222537160000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220330602000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"H" is for Haddad's!</name><id>8668085</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221343200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8668085/</event_url></item>