<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This idea was submitted by one of our members, and definitely worthy of officially being on our calendar. I love that PARL will be benefiting. Please note that this is not being run by our group, so you Must buy tickets on the website below.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 1st Annual Vegan Holiday Meal, Raffle for Charity and Cookie Swap is on sale! Go to www.like-no-udder.com/veganholidaymeal.html to purchase tickets, see the menu and check out raffle prizes. The extravaganza will take place at 2pm on Sunday, December 12th in Warwick, RI. Limited seating, so don't miss out on your chance to indulge. &lt;br /&gt;     PARL will receive raffle proceeds, and prizes have been donated by all local vegan friendly businesses.  The vegan holiday cookie swap will be as big as you make it.  The more the merrier.  Live entertainment by Lindsay Adler is also part of the afternoon! &lt;br /&gt;     This event is hosted by Karen Krinsky, owner of Like No Udder and husband  Chris Belanger, Kripalu Yoga Teacher and Laughter Yoga Leader. Both vegans, they wanted to share a cruelty free event with friends, new and old.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292339343000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289676099000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Catered Vegan Holiday Meal and more</name><id>15436610</id><headcount>85</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292180400000</time><rsvp_limit>90</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/15436610/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/f/global_12060127.jpeg</photo_url></item>