<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Organizer - Michael Blair @ (978) 808-1932&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mt Shaw is the highest peak in Ossipee Range @ 2,990 feet and is one of the peaks on the New Hampshire 52 with a View list.  It affords excellent views north towards the White Mountains and to other mountains towards the east.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will follow Mount Shaw Trail, Black Snout Trail, and High ridge Trail to reach the summit and then return following the same route in reverse. This roundtrip will cover about 7.0 miles and climb a combined total of about 2,300 feet. According to the AMC it should take an average hiker about 6.0 hours to complete. This hike is considered MODERATE to STRENUOUS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU MUST DRESS FOR WINTER CONDITIONS WHICH MEANS NO COTTON CLOTHING. YOU MUST ALSO HAVE WATERPROOF WINTER HIKING BOOTS ALONG WITH SNOWSHOES AND SOME FORM OF TRACTION DEVICE TO PARTICIPATE. Traction devices include Stabilicers, MICROspikes, or Crampons (No Yak Trax).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While Cold Weather Backpacking (&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.c..." target="_blank"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;) is intended for multiple day trips, it provides useful information to prepare for hiking in winter conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This hike is being offered to both The New England Hiking + Adventurers Group and The Random Group of Hikers. I realize that many of you are members of both groups - you only need to RSVP to this event from one group or the other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at 9:00 AM at the Mount Shaw Trailhead. The trail begins (there is no sign) as a road on the north side of NH 117, 3.9 miles east of the junction of NH 109 and NH 171 and 9.7 miles west of the junction of NH 171 and NH 28. The trailhead is just east of the bridge over Fields Brook and nearly opposite Sodom Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In an effort to coordinate ride-sharing please indicate in your RSVP if you are able to give a ride or if you are looking to get one. All RSVPs must be updated by noon of the day before this event. A MAYBE will be changed to a NO at that time so that others have the opportunity to participate. Changes or cancellations will be posted on the calendar by 6:00 PM the night before the event and those members who responded YES or MAYBE will also be notified via email.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please contact me if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a dark green Toyota Highlander.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204034888000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1200191811000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt. Shaw</name><id>7100786</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203861600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/7100786/</event_url></item>