<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>727 East Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.857951</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401.305.5255</phone><name>LJ'S BBQ</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>1354315</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390662</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Here's something fun for the Rhode Island Atheist Society to try.  Let's go to LJ's BBQ in Pawtucket on Saturday, September 25th.  When we're finished with brunch we can walk over to Lippitt Park for the wonderful Farmer's Market and the Open Market Art Fair!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LJ's BBQ is one of the favorite bbq spots in the Providence area.  They will be serving both the brunch and lunch menus when we are there.  To get more specifics of the menu check them out here: &lt;a href="http://www.ljsbbq.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ljsbbq.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards we can wander over to the Hope Street Farmers Market.  If you've never been it is amazing!  There are dozens of vendors selling veggies, fruits, flowers, cheeses, etc.  Find them here:  &lt;a href="http://www.farmfresh.org/food/farmersmarkets_details.php?market=11" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.farmfresh....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an added bonus...the Providence Open Market Art Fair is also being held at the same time.  You can purchase handmade goods and art and meet the artists making and selling their wares.  For more specifics on the Art Fair go to: &lt;a href="http://www.providenceopenmarket.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.providence...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've made reservations for us but I need to give the restaurant a head count.  If you have any questions let me know and hope to see you there!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285507970000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Atheists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Atheist</urlname><id>12929</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282487002000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rhode Island Atheist Society - Brunch at LJ'S BBQ &amp; Farmer's Market </name><id>14500861</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Atheist/events/14500861/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/0/global_13237216.jpeg</photo_url></item>