<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389782</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Arts for the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>11294002</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.105949</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IN THE CERVENA BARVA PRESS STUDIO&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;At The Arts for the Armory&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Basement, Room B8&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;191 Highland Avenue&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Somerville, MA &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

CERVENA BARVA PRESS READING SERIES &lt;br /&gt;

SATURDAY APRIL 13th, 7:00PM &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Featuring: Nina R. Alonso | Jennifer Jean | Enzo Silon Surin &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Nina Rubinstein Alonso's poetry has appeared in Ploughshares, The New Yorker, the New Boston Review, Ibbetson Street, etc. and her book This Body was published by David Godine Press. Her stories are currently in the Southern Women's Review. She edits Constellations a Journal of Poetry and Fiction, (&lt;a href="http://constellations-lit.com/" target="_blank"&gt;constellations-lit.com&lt;/a&gt;) and teaches at her ballet school in Cambridge (&lt;a href="http://freshpondballet.com/" target="_blank"&gt;freshpondballet.com&lt;/a&gt;). She's been involved in meditation for years (&lt;a href="http://srcm.org/" target="_blank"&gt;srcm.org&lt;/a&gt;) and her daughter is a junior at UVM in Vermont. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Jennifer Jean has published two poetry collections, In the War and The Archivist, and the multi-media chapbook FISHWIFE. She's released Fishwife Tales, a collaborative CD comprised of art songs and accompanied recitations. Her work's appeared, or is forthcoming, in: Poetica, Drunken Boat, Tidal Basin, Caketrain, Denver Quarterly, Poets/Artists, and The Mom Egg. She blogs for Amirah, a website addressing human-trafficking issues, and she teaches at Salem State University. Visit: &lt;a href="http://www.fishwifetales.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fishwifetales.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Enzo Silon Surin is a Haitian-born poet, writer, playwright, speaker, advocate and the author of Higher Ground (Finishing Line Press, 2006), a collection of poems for urban uplift, which was nominated for the Massachusetts Book Award. He is also the author of A Different Kind of Love, an eBook of inspirational writing. His poems have also appeared in Tidal Basin Review, Reverie: Midwest African American Literature, Freshwater, The Caribbean Writer, Soundings East, among other literary journals. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Admission is $3.00. Refreshments served. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Directions: &lt;br /&gt;

The Center for the Arts is located between Davis Square and Union Square. Parking is located behind the armory at the rear of the building. Arts at the Armory is approximately a 15 minute walk from Davis Square which is on the MTBA Red Line. You can also find us by using either the MBTA RT 88 and RT 90 bus that can be caught either at Lechmere (Green Line) or Davis Square (Red Line). Get off at the Highland Avenue and Lowell Street stop. You can also get to us from Sullivan Square (Orange Line) by using the MBTA RT 90 bus. Get off at the Highland Avenue and Benton Road stop. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Inside the Armory: &lt;br /&gt;

Go inside main doors and walk straight ahead about 30 feet, look for the door on the right to the stairs down to the basement. (There is an elevator just after the stairs.) Once in the basement walk through the basement lobby straight ahead about 20 feet, first door on the right is the Cervená Barva Press Studio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Chenevert</member_name><member_id>76210242</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365905819000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364489246000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CERVENA BARVA PRESS READING SERIES</name><id>111505222</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365894000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/111505222/</event_url></item>