<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Johnny Cupcakes Presents: GHOSTBUSTERS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Movie starts @ 7:30 pm on Mon, Oct 12 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$9.75 All Seats. Student Members get 2 for 1 admission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each month, local T-shirt impresario Johnny Cupcakes emerges from his super secret T-shirt laboratory to screen some of his all-time favorite childhood movies here on the Coolidge's GIANT screen. Not only is Mr. Cupcakes himself here in person to host and inspire movie-related mischief, he also comes armed with groovy limited edition Tees to sell that are made just for each show -- get 'em while they're hot!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we screen GHOSTBUSTERS, the 1980's cult classic that practically raised every 80's baby!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special spooky secret screening before the feature!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After being kicked out of their university, due to lack of funding, parapsychology professors Spengler, Stantz and Venkman decide to go into business for themselves by trapping and removing ghosts from New York haunts. Armed with proton packs and promising never to cross the streams, the Ghostbusters strike fear into the translucent hearts of the reluctantly deceased. When a local high-rise apartment building becomes the landing pad for an ancient evil spirit named Gozur, it's up to our heroes to prevent the destruction of the world; as brought about by a giant marshmallow man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For tickets and information: &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/node/2463" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For directions: &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I strongly encourage you to buy your ticket in advance if you're planning on attending this, my gut tells me this one might sell out before the day of the event. Also, you probably want to get here before 7:00 to get a good seat! I'll try to get here early so we can get seats together.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the guy with a Red and White Meetup sign, or just call me on my cell (617-899-8445).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom "spot" Callaway</member_name><member_id>2590946</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256241602000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254923433000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>[MOVIE] Johnny Cupcakes Presents: Ghostbusters (Coolidge Corner Theatre)</name><id>11570978</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255388400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/11570978/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/9/global_8154265.jpeg</photo_url></item>