<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 - 24 School St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02119</zip><lat>42.313031</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.557.7188</phone><name>Borders Books</name><city>Boston</city><id>13545</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097122</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The inimitable Tuesday Night Study Group, of recent (somewhat dubious, but nonetheless FABULOUS) fame, will meet tomorrow evening from 6:30-8:45 in the Borders Bookstore Conference Room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Conference Room is located on the first floor of the bookstore, in the back room.  Upon entering, head towards the rear of the store.  You will see set of about 3-4 stairs; after you climb them, turn immediately to your left.  Keep along the wall, and you will see the tall wooden conference room doors after just a few steps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have difficulty finding the Conference Room, please ask any Borders Bookstore or Cafe Employee!  Minasan ni aete totemo tanoshimini shiteorima~su!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)  A maximum of 20-25 people can be accommodated in the Conference Room.  If any Members beyond this limit attend, Cafe seating is welcome, but not guaranteed available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2)  There will be NO outside food or beverage allowed at this location.  All such purchases must either be consumed and all trash disposed of prior to entering Borders, or stored in a bag or backpack (no visible food or beverage containers).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3)  Purchases from the Borders Cafe are strongly encouraged.  To view a representative menu (which may include items not available at this location), please visit  &lt;a href="http://www.seattlesbest.com/#/coffee/prepared-drinks/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seattlesbe...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4)  At the close of this Meetup, an envelope will be passed around for the collection of tips for the Cafe Staff.  A minimum contribution of $1-2 per person is strongly encouraged.  Whole dollars only please, no coins. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Suzanne</member_name><member_id>1732576</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>yuuszmi</member_name><member_id>3618501</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264721839000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1264482659000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>*~The FABULOUS Tuesday Study Night Meetup!~*</name><id>12425462</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264548600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/12425462/</event_url></item>