<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Sunday, Feb 21, 2:30-6:30pm, $55/person prepaid by Mon, Feb 15, $65 thereafter &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Do you crave deeper intimacy and sensual connection in your relationship(s)?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Are you curios about integrating spirituality and sensuality?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Would you like to explore a quality of touch that nourishes not only the body, but also the soul?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this experiential workshop you will learn the fundamentals of:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Creating Sacred Space&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Cultivating the Presence, Key Attitude and Intention for an Ecstatic Energy Exchange&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Principles of Sacred Sensual Touch&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Keys to Accessing Greater Pleasure&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#9830; Chakra Breathing to Ignite and Circulate Sexual Energy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a clothes-on, non-explicit class in which we will create a safe space to learn tantric principles and practices incorporating caring, non-sexual touch. You will learn to deepen your experience of pleasure, whether giving or receiving touch. You can then take your new-found skills home to skyrocket your lovemaking to unimaginable heights of pleasure and connection!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This workshop is open to people of all genders, sexual orientation and relationship styles, whether single or partnered. You may attend alone or with a partner or a friend. No previous experience necessary. Beginners welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Please wear loose, comfortable clothing. We will be sitting on the floor. Bring a blanket and pillow, and backjack, if you have. Bring a water bottle and snack.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The location will be at a private home with a beautiful indoor Watsu pool space in Newton Center. Directions will be emailed to those who have paid.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**NEW ADDITION: Optional post-workshop &lt;b&gt;Potluck Dinner&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Watsu!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to stay to socialize over dinner, please bring a dish and drink to share with 5 people. Fridge space will be available as well as stove, oven and microwave for heating items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watsu (water shiatsu) is an aquatic bodywork technique done in 96 degree water. During a session you are held in the practitioner's arms. There is a sequence of movements involving spinal stretches, spinal twists, muscle stretches, joint release work, shiatsu points gently pressed and periods of profound stillness, all seamlessly interwoven into a dance. It is extremely nurturing and relaxing as it allows your body to move in ways it never has before in a womb-like environment. Available at $25/20 minutes. You may reserve a session in advance by emailing me (organizer). You can also decide that night. Please bring a towel and bathing suit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brynn Bishop is a Bodyworker, Tantric Educator and Intimacy Coach with over twenty years experience in the fields of Somatics, Spirituality and Consciousness Relating. Brynn assists women and men in increasing their capacity for Intimacy and Pleasure, and in accessing their full Aliveness and Passion! Her training in Massage therapy, Taoist and Hindu Tantric Practices, Body-Oriented Psychotherapy, Authentic Movement and Expressive Arts Therapy provides a uniquely integrative approach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;For more info or to inquire about Private Coaching, contact Brynn via email (organizer) or call 415-244-1652. &lt;i&gt;Free initial consultation!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;What past students of this workshop have said:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;“My soul was deeply nourished. It was a good blend of experiential and didactic. Wonderful group of like-minded souls! ”  - Laurie A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“This was a very good experience. I hope to learn more. ”  - Robert B&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“This was a very good course for anyone who knows nothing about Tantric Secrets... The group leader Brynn was fantastic. She explained things in a very simplified way and she made sure all in attendance were comfortable with the subject matter before going forward. I would recommend this seminar to anyone with a curiosity about touch and what role it plays in one's own life as well as what role it may play in your relationship with others. I am very glad I took the seminar and am looking forward to some more exploration. ” – Michelle O&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“This was a wonderful, comfortable way to learn about some of the Tantric principles. I enjoyed this very much and feel open to learning more. ” – Karen W&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; “The experiential part of the workshop felt rich, calming, enlivening, connected, and deeply nourishing.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Private home in Newton Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brynn</member_name><member_id>7976948</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266968331000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Passionate Souls</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tantric-Intimacy</urlname><id>1471990</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Tantric Intimacy</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262975078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tantric Principles of Sacred Sensual Touch</name><id>12262490</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266780600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tantric-Intimacy/events/12262490/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/a/0/global_9965280.jpeg</photo_url></item>