<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Meford Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.450626</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>503682</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.230660</lon></venue><fee><label>ticket</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>The Reel Paddling Film Festival World Tour is an international event presenting the world's best whitewater, sea kayaking and canoeing action and lifestyle films of the year on screens in 75 cities across Canada, United States, and around the world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With more than 30 paddling films short listed for the World Tour, including the eight festival category winners, audiences can expect to see hairy whitewater action, sea kayakers explore remote coastlines, monster kayak fishing, bug-infested canoe expeditions, international travel films, environmental documentaries and hilarious short films capturing the lighter side of the paddling life. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On this year's World Tour you can expect to see these great films: Threshers Yak Style, where you'll hook into a 125-pound thresher shark from a kayak; Source to Sea is expedition kayaker Ram Silwals' story about fulfilling a dream -1,350 kilometers in 19 days from the high mountains of the Himalayas to the Bay of Bengal; the documentary 49 Megawatts takes a close look at the future of British Columbia's rivers and why the government is fast-tracking hydro projects under the name of &amp;quot;green power&amp;quot;; follow six Serbian Canadians in Canoeing to the Arctic as they descend the Hood River to the Arctic Sound; Source is an action-packed, epic global kayak adventure down the world's greatest rivers, including the highest waterfall; Jon Bowermasters' Birthplace of the Wind is a sea kayak journey to five volcanic Aleutian islands rising straight out of the sea; and Lockapalooza Rodeo, a clever claymation featurette made by 11-year-old Ben Doran. Plus, local hosts can choose to play any of the other 24 films on the World Tour.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>May try  to meet at Starbucks before the film or go out for a beer/food after.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Lane</member_name><member_id>5915593</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208792359000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>hmmm, how does "Wedeln Paddlers Club" club sound?</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203648210000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Reel Paddling Film Festival - Arlington</name><id>7383053</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208469600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7383053/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/1/0/global_3292112.jpeg</photo_url></item>