<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Celebration Social! Boston Area Chapter wins the Platinum Grand Award for Excellence and Innovation!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, December 15, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Royal Sonesta Hotel, Cambridge, MA&lt;br /&gt;Social: 5:00 - 8:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In early November at the ISPE Annual Meeting in Orlando, the Boston Area Chapter was awarded the top honor, the North American/South American Affiliate Council &amp;quot;Platinum Grand Award for Excellence and Innovation&amp;quot; for the second year in a row! The Chapter was awarded this recognition by a committee of judges based on the Chapter’s prior year events and activities. Thank you to the entire 2009-2010 Board of Directors, Committee Chairs and Volunteers for their commitment to the Chapter and their extraordinary efforts during difficult times. The Chapter continued to add value to its membership by diversifying the subjects of the educational programs; increasing operating companies' opportunities for involvement at all levels; adding to the participation of women at events; beginning and hosting a CPIP study group; sponsoring events like Bio-Ball; Young Professionals Committee hosting educational events; co-sponsoring educational events with other industry-related associations, among many other achievements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come see what ISPE has been doing this past year, look at old photos, read about our accomplishments, celebrate with new friends. Enjoy complimentary hors d'oeuvres and cash bar. This event is FREE for Members and their guests. Enjoy and Celebrate the Success of YOUR Chapter! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ispeboston.org/eventcal/calendar.html?action=display_event&amp;amp;oid=151" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ispeboston...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Joshua Lang</member_name><member_id>3926861</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292461814000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Scientific Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nexusproject</urlname><id>1294865</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Nexus Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290882056000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebration Social! </name><id>15567636</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292457600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nexusproject/events/15567636/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/c/global_12600668.jpeg</photo_url></item>