<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Liberty Hotel Bar has become THE place to be in Boston on Thursday evenings, and this Thursday will not be any different!  Liberty has already become a Boston institution since opening two years ago, and for good reason!  There are few, if any, places in town that offer the sophistication, style and open space that you will find here.  You don't want to miss this on Thursday - Come out and experience why we are one of the best meetup groups in Boston! New and current members are all welcome!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;**Please arrive early in the evening, as Liberty Bar gets VERY BUSY later in the night.  This place fills up on Thursdays, so be sure to call me so you can find the group (number listed below).**&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to meet our wonderful  members and to experience one of the best scenes in Boston.  There may also be a couple of surprises on this particular night at Liberty...  come by and find out!  For some pictures of the bar: &lt;a href="http://www.libertyhotel.com/food_and_drink/liberty_bar.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.libertyhot...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DETAILS: We will meet at 6:30pm at the Liberty Hotel Bar, which is located at 215 Charles Street, off Cambridge Street by Beacon Hill.  The hotel is large - after you enter through the main doors, take the escalators up one flight, and you will see the Liberty Bar to your right.  We will initially meet by the top of the escalators, but I expect to move around as the night progresses.  &lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Please look for me to find the group, and call if you can't find the group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Cover:  No cover, but get there early!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIND THE ORGANIZER: My picture is located on the left-hand side of the site. &lt;b&gt;For help/questions, my cell: 646.541.0708.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please dress to impress as this is an upscale venue.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If traveling by T, Charles MGH is the closest T stop on the red line.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! Charlie&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Organizer reserves the right to adjust RSVPs in order to balance out group turnout.*&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>My picture is on the left hand side of the web site.  Call me for assistance: 646.541.0708.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlie - Nightlife Organizer</member_name><member_id>2175480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1253150610000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Night Life Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-nightlife</urlname><id>111392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Night Life Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248753769000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nightlife Style and Class! - Afterwork Mixer at The Liberty Hotel Bar, Thursday!</name><id>10974302</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248993000000</time><rsvp_limit>53</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-nightlife/events/10974302/</event_url></item>