<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;The Leopard (Il Gattopardo) (1963, 205 min.)&lt;/b&gt; An epic of the grandest possible scale, the film recreates with drama and opulence, the tumultuous years of Italy's Risorgimento—when the aristocracy lost its power and the middle class rose and formed a unified, democratic country. Burt Lancaster stars as the aging prince watching his culture and fortune wane in the face of a new generation, represented by his upstart nephew (Alain Delon) and his beautiful fiancee (Claudia Cardinale). Awarded the Palme d'Or at the 1963 Cannes Film Festival, The Leopard translates Giuseppe Tomasi di Lampedusa's novel, and the history it recounts, into a truly cinematic masterpiece. &amp;quot;He (Lancaster) based the character on Visconti himself--a man who acknowledged the need for change but increasingly began to regret the vulgarity of the present compared with the past&amp;quot; (The Guardian).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members, seniors, students $6; general admission $7&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the original New York Times Review:&lt;br /&gt;By BOSLEY CROWTHER&lt;br /&gt;Published: August 13, 1963&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;THE film that Luchino Visconti and his star, Burt Lancaster, have made from Giuseppe di Lampedusa's fine novel &amp;quot;The Leopard&amp;quot; is a stunning visualization of a mood of melancholy and nostalgia at the passing of an age.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sentiment and sadness whisper through it like the soft Mediterranean breeze that flutters the curtains in the windows of the palace in the stark Sicilian hills, on the outskirts of Palermo, as the unhurried story begins. They waft through the slow and stately tableaux of incidents in the stilted, baroque life of a noble Sicilian family in the mid-19th century.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They even rustle in the laughter of young people who are the inheritors of the change that the Risorgimento of Garibaldi is allegedly bringing to the land. And they hang like a softly soaking vapor over the great, gaudy end-of-an-era ball that takes up the last 40 minutes of this 2 hour and 40 minute film.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the one thing that Mr. Visconti has been able to do magnificently — and it's the only thing I imagine he figured he could possibly do with the shimmering, atmospheric material of Mr. di Lampedusa's book—is translate in terms of brilliant pictures, almost like paintings, the autumnal mood of change and decay that the onrush of social revolution brought to one family and to the spirits of one strong man.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John will be sipping coffee at 10:30 out in front of the MFA with plans to go inside at 10:50.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please notice the runtime of the film is 3 1/2 hours.  This is an epic of epic proportions.  For those able to stay for discussion afterwards, we'll go downstairs and out into the courtyard on what will hopefully be a fine and sunny day.  Look for John to be holding a red Meetup sign in the lobby outside the theater.  The discussion should be fascinating and add to your appreciation of the film.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248644166000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Films of Luchino Visconti - The Leopard (Il Gattopardo)</name><id>10962578</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249830000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/10962578/</event_url></item>