<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Broadway</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.407043</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-643-1499</phone><name>Together in Motion</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668944</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.133880</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you wonder why others are in satisfying loving relationships and you are not? Do you sometimes ask yourself, "What am I doing wrong here?" Are you frustrated with one-night stands or platonic dates, and you're looking for something much more meaningful? And finally, are you ready to create the relationship of your heart's desire? &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 If you answered yes to any of these questions, then I think you're gonna like this. Here's the scoop: My friends at the Human Awareness Institute have agreed to put on a free mini-workshop for my group, and I'd love to have you join us. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is not like a regular social skills seminar. In fact, this is totally different than what I do, but I think it's incredibly valuable, and something that honestly... most people don't know exists. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 WHAT'S IT ALL ABOUT? &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This mini-workshop is dedicated to teaching you the very necessary skills of intimacy that you need to create deep, long-lasting relationships with others. The end result? You will feel free to express yourself fully, receive others in a loving way and have the very best in communication skills (the most vital ingredient to creating lasting love!). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 We will offer a variety of ways to connect to yourself and others - in small groups, and one-one-one and with the larger group, if desired. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 THESE HEART-FELT EXERCISES ARE DESIGNED TO ASSIST YOU IN: &lt;br /&gt;

 *************************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expressing yourself in ways that draw people to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being present with yourself and others, creating an interpersonal dynamic that provides safety and love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling confident when reaching out to meet someone new.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being your authentic self and let others truly see you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discovering the power in opening up to others and sharing yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being more in touch with your feelings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning new perspectives on asking for what you want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Letting go of judgments and fears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increasing clarity, honesty, and trust in relationships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And much more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 HOW TO GET INVOLVED &lt;br /&gt;

 ************************************************* &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The seminar is conveniently located in Arlington, and there is plenty of parking. Please plan on arriving by 6:45pm so you have time to settle in and meet the other members. We start promptly at 7:00 and go until 9:30 (with a break in the middle). &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 The event is limited to 70 people due to the size limitations of the place we're renting. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Here's what I recommend you do: &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 #1 - Check your calendar right now, and see if you have the evening free. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 #2 - If you have that evening free, go ahead and RSVP for this workshop right now. Trust me, it's going to fill up fast. They always do. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 #3 - Write it in your calendar so you remember to attend, and please arrive at 6:45pm to sign in and also to meet the other members. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 There is no charge for this event, and I promise that this will be well worth your time. The only thing you need to bring is a pair of socks to wear inside the main room. It's a padded room, and we can't wear shoes in there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 I'm looking forward to seeing you there. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Warmly, &lt;br /&gt;

 Jason &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 P.S. - Take down my cell number in case you have any questions about the event or if you get lost. The venue is extremely easy to find, so you should have no problems, but just in case, my cell is: 617-901-8871.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go in the front door.  The signs will point you to the room.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>6614402</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ben Farris</member_name><member_id>11587658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1337544705000</updated><rating><average>4.46999979019</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>Social Artists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialskills</urlname><id>1110801</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Dating School</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>53</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333997065000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE MINI-WORKSHOP - Creating More Love and Intimacy</name><id>59859552</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334444400000</time><rsvp_limit>70</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialskills/events/59859552/</event_url></item>