<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;NEWER STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts at 6:40, so let's meet right inside the theater lobby doors at 6:10 and get our tickets for Up in the Air. Then we'll get goodies and go sit down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lemme know if you're going to be late or get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;NEW STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think I speak for all of us when I say that I'm saddened to the core to have heard about (and continue to learn about) the terrible earthquake in Haiti, the most impoverished country in the Western Hemisphere. With this earthquake, not only the largest and capital city in Haiti was demolished, but that also means the rest of the country has broken down. The hospital, many embassies, countless relief organization headquarters and even the prison have been demolished, killing thousands and setting free serious criminals. There are thousands dead (we may not know for another week what the real deathtoll is), and the entire country needs international help to regain any basic needs for its men, women and children (not to mention pets), including basic shelter, food and clean water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please consider joining me in supporting the relief efforts in this time of need (list of organizations below). Right now, they need monetary donations more than goods, so I'm asking each and every one of you 420 members to help me by donating money. You can hand it to me at the next meetup you attend or you can PayPal me ([address removed]), and I will make sure that &lt;u&gt;EVERY PENNY&lt;/u&gt; goes to the organization of your choice (from the list below). I say &amp;quot;every penny&amp;quot; because Paypal does charge a processing fee, but Paul and I will donate that equivalent ourselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;It gets better...&lt;/b&gt; For every dollar you spend from today -- Jan. 15, 2010 -- through Feb. 28, 2010, Paul and I will match your donation. If you give me $5, we donate $5 ourselves and your $5 becomes $10. If you decide to donate through me after Feb. 28, your money still gets where you want it to go, we just won't match it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the list from which you can choose (if you're Paypalling me, just include the desired charity in the comment field; if you don't specify, your donation will be applied to the Red Cross):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * American Red Cross&lt;br /&gt;    * Habitat for Humanity&lt;br /&gt;    * Doctors Without Borders&lt;br /&gt;    * The Salvation Army&lt;br /&gt;    * Best Friends Animal Society -- to help the animals who have been stranded or orphaned&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a case like this, every little bit counts -- so please donate what you can, whether that's $1 or $100. I know times are tough for everyone these days, but even a dollar or two will make a huge difference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks a lot, everyone. I know we can make a difference!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;OLD STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People are shouting at what a wonderful movie &lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/movie/1810062520/details" target="_blank"&gt;Up In The Air&lt;/a&gt; is. George Clooney is said to give a terrific performance. Some of you business people may really identify with his character in this movie. It may make for a wonderful conversation after the movie!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;SUMMARY:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ryan Bingham, is a corporate downsizing expert whose cherished life on the road is threatened just as he is on the cusp of reaching ten million frequent flyer miles and just after he's met the frequent-traveler woman of his dreams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;THE USUAL STUFF:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet right inside the theater ticket lobby doors and then I can buy us all discounted tickets ($8.00 each for FMM members and their guests). I also have $3 vouchers each for small sodas and small popcorns (can be used towards a larger size). Exact change makes me like you more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, guests are welcome, just be sure to include them in the RSVP so that I know who/how many to expect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your RSVP as up-to-date as possible. And please call me if you're going to be late or need to change your RSVP after I close RSVPs on the site (2 hours before we meet). My cell is: 508/308-4897. I'm also good for directions if you get lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we'll head to Fridays (I'll bring the coupons!) to chat about the movie (and just chat).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'll update the time a few days before the meetup, so keep an eye on your email!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you for Up In The Air!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--Dana&lt;br /&gt;508/308-4897&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I look like my pic!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Gillin</member_name><member_id>6519146</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264338755000</updated><rating><average>3.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262391655000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Up In The Air</name><id>12193113</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263945600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/12193113/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/4/global_3996532.jpeg</photo_url></item>