<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>560 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.340809</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 422-0224</phone><name>Gaslight, Brasserie du Coin</name><city>Boston</city><id>408332</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.067444</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's been a big mix up. The Buttery over booked the large garden area for two other large groups, one for 25 and another for 35. There is no more space available @ the Buttery for Brunch And More. They informed me of this only this morning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Would any of you be opposed to brunch @ the Gaslight? It's in the same area but over on Harrison Ave. They have a great Brunch and the space to accommodate our large party!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sorry for the sudden change of plans!! But unfortunately it was unavoidable. I feel a little like when an airline over books a flight and we're all waiting standby. But now we're about to board our next flight, The Gaslight :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gaslight Brunch Menu: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gaslight560.com/media/menus/Gaslight_Brunch_Menu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gaslight56...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More About The Gaslight:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gaslight, Brasserie du Coin, (literally brasserie on the corner) is The Aquitaine Group’s classic neighborhood Parisian brasserie. Gaslight, located at 560 Harrison Avenue in Boston’s historic South End, offers its guests French brasserie cuisine of impeccable quality and improbable value in an informal, old world, is new again setting. With its hand crafted Parisian zinc bar, reclaimed wood floors, mosaic tiles, beamed wood ceilings, nicotine stained walls and antique mirrors, Gaslight’s decor is warm and inviting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seating guests in an eclectic mix of bar, café tables, communal tables, booths and banquets, Gaslight will be open seven days a week serving lunch, dinner, late night &amp;quot;Supper&amp;quot; and brunch on the weekends. Gaslight diners can choose from a large selection of classic French brasserie cuisine prepared by Chef de Cuisine Christopher Robins. Gaslight will offer an all French wine list with over 20 wines by the glass, ½ carafe and carafe with additional 60 selections on its reserve wine list. Suitable for all occasions, and for all times of the day and week, Gaslight courts all who appreciate a great time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free Parking available nightly and all day on weekends in our adjacent lot.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257880890000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257195043000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Venue Change: Brunch @ The Gaslight </name><id>11773770</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257706800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11773770/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/c/global_11655164.jpeg</photo_url></item>