<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Well, with the writer's strike, this year's Oscars might be postponed. I am very glad to announce our first annual (?) awards party will have no such difficulties and will take place on Feb. 23rd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carmela, who is moving to Belmont,  has graciously offered to have a combo housewarming/group party. So, lets have some fun! We'll play some movie-based games and this will be a great time to mingle with  others from the group- some of whom you might not have seen for awhile (hey, I remember you- you were at so and so) and others whom you  may have never met before. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for the awards, the prestigious BAMS (Boston Arthouse Meetup Statuettes) will be based on categories and nominations  we all make up: from the straight-forward (Best Film), to the overlooked (Best Performance by an Animal- thanks Susan  for this suggestion), to the silly (Worst Hair). I'll create a Message Board posting for these Categories and Nominations and get the ball rolling with a few ideas. This is open to everyone, even if you can't make it to the party. Nominate, create categories and vote to your heart's content and our crack staff of organizer's will sift through it all in time for the big awards bash. Oops, I forgot to mention that the awards will be limited to movies the group has seen in the past year, so any event after The Lives of Others (last year's unofficial winner, which we saw on March 4) is fair game. That's about 125 movies to choose from. You can see all the films the group has seen in the past year by scrolling through the 'Past event list' which is right under the Recent Meetups on our Welcome Page. Be creative, have some fun, and drop me an email if you have any questions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carmela's new digs are 2 blocks from the Harvard bus-line which runs regularly from Harvard Sq. The address for the party as well as the bus schedule will be sent  to the attendees once we have the final party list figured out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details and information about our Award's Party Gala will be provided as we near the auspicious date. Gowns and tuxedos are of course optional.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks so much Carmela  !!!!!  for making this possible, this should be a wonderful night .&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Fay </member_name><member_id>3089505</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nicole</member_name><member_id>3185465</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>3369401</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949394000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>19</count></rating><why>This will be a fun time! Get to meet other people from the group, talk about movies- past, present and future. We'll  play some movie-based games and have our own award ceremony. The winner of the BAM for funniest movie of the year is...</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201225600000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our Own Awards Party!!!</name><id>7189843</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203811200000</time><rsvp_limit>37</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7189843/</event_url></item>