<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>98 Elm Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01952</zip><lat>42.843979</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Blue Ocean Music Hall</name><city>Salisbury</city><id>1558779</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.877045</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Update 1/22/2012: Tables we originally stated below are now all sold out. Please buy your tickets as soon as possible. The new tables we are purchasing are 66-68. The sooner you buy your tickets the less of a chance you will get shut out of sitting with the rest of the group, so buy your tickets soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;See you at Blue Ocean&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff6600"&gt;Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go out to a comedy show at Blue Ocean Music Hall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul D'Angelo is the comic on stage on this date, we have seen him before and he will keep you laughing, here is his bio:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Paul D'Angelo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who is the comedian/writer/actor that the Los Angeles Times calls: ". . . quite likely the funniest entertainer you'e never heard . .yet "? Comedian Paul D'Angelo has been headlining A-List comedy clubs around the country for 20 years, entertaining hundreds of prominent corporate clients, and opening for over 50 international stars such as Aretha Franklin, Ray Charles, The Beach Boys, Tony Bennett, George Carlin, Joan Rivers and Dennis Miller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets: Advance online purchase only. Price is $15.00pp . In order to sit together, please reserve your spot at the following tables: 47, 39 or 40.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blue Ocean does have food and drink service and we will also be posting a dinner event prior to the start of the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The show starts promptly at 8pm, so please try to arrive prior to that time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not paid your dues for this year, please consider paying one of the organizers at this event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bad weather will only cancel this event if the show itself is cancelled by Blue Ocean Music Hall. If Blue Ocean cancels the show the organizers will post that message to this site as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember to take the Meetup Cell phone number (978-304-2811) with you in case you are running late, get lost or can't find us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you can join us at this event and share some laughs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Janet &amp;amp; Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for our assigned tables</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328467031000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326678498000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Comedy Show at Blue Ocean Music Hall</name><id>48243862</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328402700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/48243862/</event_url></item>