<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366467</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kendall Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1924141</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091454</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Adrien Brody is in the latest from Woody Allen. That fact alone was enough for&amp;nbsp;me to&amp;nbsp;see &lt;em&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;Kathy Bates is also one of the cast members and another good reason to see it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie stars Owen Wilson and Rachel McAdams. (And Adrien Brody!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're a fan of Woody Allen's, you won't need much more information to go see &lt;em&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/em&gt;, his forty-first movie according to the Boston &lt;em&gt;Phoenix&lt;/em&gt;. I do miss the comedy of his earlier films. &lt;em&gt;Annie Hall&lt;/em&gt; was hilarious. So was &lt;em&gt;Bananas&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;combines fantasy and comedy, and that sounds good to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of the reviews that I have started to read warn about giving away the surprises in the plot, so I'll leave it right there. I *did* read a little farther, I have to admit, but I wouldn't have found out about Adrien Brody otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll buy my ticket, then wait at the foot of the stairs from 6:30 to 6:45 p.m. We're going to the 7:00 show. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/em&gt; shows on 3 screens at the Kendall Cinema; be sure to buy your ticket for the 7:00 show.&lt;/strong&gt; Look for my bright red backpack. If you're late, you can find me in the theater watching the previews before the movie or the credits afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm reading the credits for this one. If you don't want to wait in the auditorium, we can gather everyone in the theater lobby after the movie. Look for my bright red backpack, no matter what.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If people who sign up for this event want to go out afterward for tea, food, and conversation, we'll go to the Friendly Toast (&lt;a href="http://www.thefriendlytoast.net"&gt;http://www.thefriendlytoast.net&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kendall Cinema is part of the Landmark Theater chain. Go to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.landmarktheaters.com/"&gt;http://www.landmarktheaters.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information about the theater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the Kendall Cinema!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marianne&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for my bright red backpack. See the event description for more details.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307133348000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306612451000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Midnight in Paris (Woody Allen's new movie)</name><id>20083991</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307053800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/20083991/</event_url></item>