<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>79 John F. Kennedy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.371391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Kennedy School - Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>10300462</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121384</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crisis Management and the Social Sector&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;with&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Herman B. (Dutch) Leonard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Frontline with Faculty Seminar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All Frontline with Faculty seminars are open to the public.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, Mar 7 | 4:15 – 5:15 pm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Belfer, Weil Town Hall, Lobby Level, Harvard Kennedy School&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In responding to and recovering from large, complex disasters (like Katrina, the Haiti, Chile, and Japan earthquakes, Irene, and Sandy), we argue that a decentralized, “fast and light” response will outperform a more centralized response. What are the implications of this for the social sector, which plays a key role in providing resources and expertise in the aftermath of disasters?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Herman B. (Dutch) Leonard is Eliot I. Snider and Family Professor of Business Administration at the Harvard Business School and the George F. Baker, Jr. Professor of Public Sector Management at Harvard University’s John F. Kennedy School of Government. In addition, he serves as co-chair of the HBS Social Enterprise Initiative. He teaches extensively in executive programs at the Business School and the Kennedy School and around the world in the areas of general organizational strategy, governance, performance management, crisis management and leadership, and corporate social responsibility. His work on leadership focuses on innovation, creativity, effective decision-making, and advocacy and persuasion. His current work in leadership and management is focused on the relationship between governance, accountability, and performance, and emphasizes the use of performance management as a tool for enhancing accountability. He has also worked and taught extensively in the area of crisis management and on issues related to corporate social responsibility. He is the co-editor of Managing Crises (2009), the author of Checks Unbalanced: The Quiet Side of Public Spending (1984), of By Choice or By Chance: Tracking the Values in Massachusetts Public Spending (1992), and (annually from 1993 through 1999) of The Federal Budget and the States (an annual report on the geographic distribution of federal spending and taxation). For Professor Leonard’s full bio and publications, click here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frontline with Faculty video recordings: Video recordings of Frontline with Faculty sessions will be available on the Hauser Center’s Vimeo channel approximately one week after the session date. Please click here to access the recordings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Frontline with Faculty Series is a venue for Harvard faculty affiliated with the Hauser Center to share their work and research with faculty colleagues, as well as students in an informal setting that will allow for spirited discussion, debate and exchange. The seminars link faculty experts from Harvard Schools and beyond on a wide range of topics.  The Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations at Harvard University seeks to expand understanding and accelerate critical thinking about civil society among scholars, practitioners, policy makers and the general public, by encouraging scholarship, developing curriculum, fostering mutual learning between academics and practitioners, and shaping policies that enhance the sector and its role in society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362702245000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357588170000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Crisis Management</name><id>98410862</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362690900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/98410862/</event_url></item>