<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 112</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03818</zip><lat>44.003360</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Chocorua - Champney Falls Trailhead</name><city>Conway</city><address_3>11.5 miles from Rte 16 in Conway</address_3><id>334382</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.240859</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Chocorua via Champney Falls Trail&lt;br /&gt;Hike Rating: Level 5&lt;br /&gt;Minimum gear requirements are:&lt;br /&gt; Snowshoes, micro-spikes or crampons, headlamp and no cotton clothing.  Trekking poles are strongly suggested.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must read and agree to the terms of the waiver and liability waiver on this Website.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All attendees must also know there own abilities.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Chocorua is one of the most beautiful mountains in New Hampshire.  At 3500', Chocorua isn't a big peak, but enjoys a bare rocky peak with spectacular 360 degree views and is one of the most popular peaks in the White Mountains. The trail up is mostly in the woods and sheltered; but when you emerge onto the rocky summit, the views are great! We will be hiking this mountain from the north side (Kancamagus Highway). &lt;br /&gt;Roundtrip is about 7.6 miles and estimated time to hike will be 8 hours, and has 2250' of elevation gain. Due to this being a winter hike, I am rating it an advanced hike. There is also a side trail loop on the way up at around 1.5 miles that provides a nice side trip to Champney Falls and Pitcher Falls. We will follow the left fork to the falls, and then we will regain the main trail in about 0.4 miles.&lt;br /&gt;From the parking lot, we will follow Champney Falls Trail which ascends the northern flank of Mt. Chocorua. &lt;br /&gt;We will pass over Twin Brook on a footbridge. At 0.1 mile going straight to remain on Champney Falls Trail (Bolles Trail veers off to the right). At about 0.4 mile, Champney Brook will appear on our left and will run roughly parallel to the trail for the next 1.4 miles. At 1.4 miles Champney Falls Trail forks. The trail rejoins 0.3 mile later (following the right fork) or 0.4 mile later (following the left fork). &lt;br /&gt;We'll follow the left fork which will take us past Pitcher Falls and Champney Falls. Pitcher Falls is a narrow stream of water spilling over the side of a narrow gorge. Champney Falls is a series of cascades tumbling down 200 feet. This section of trail tends to be slippery in all seasons. This may be where your traction device we'll be put to use. At 2.4 miles there is a good outlook to the north, just before the switchbacks and steeper climbing begin. At 3.1 miles, we'll turn left to follow the Champney Falls Cutoff (Champney Falls Trail continues straight). After 0.3 mile on Champney Falls Cutoff, that trail ends as it meets up with Middle Sister Trail. We'll turn left and follow Middle Sister Trail to the summit of Middle Sister in 0.1 mile, and then from there continue to the summit of Chocorua. Return via the same route.&lt;br /&gt;Trip Summary: 7.6 miles, 2,250 feet elevation gain, estimated book time 8:00 hr &lt;br /&gt;Directions to the trailhead: &lt;br /&gt;Champney Falls Parking Lot on Route 112 in Passaconaway. The large parking area for the Champney Falls Trailhead is situated on the southern side of the Kancamagus Highway (Rte 112). From the west (Rte 93 side), it is 24.3 miles east of exit 32 on Interstate 93. From the east (Rte 16 side), it is 11.4 miles west of the junction on New Hampshire Routes 16 and 112. There is a large sign at the kiosk that reads Champney Falls Trail, and the parking area is quite large. From Boston, I-93 to exit 32, left on Rte 112 drive east for a half hour. Total driving time from Boston, approximately 2.5+ hours.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dianne and I will be in a black four door Toyota Echo with Maine plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237210784000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236774784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT. CHOCORUA VIA THE CHAMPNEY FALLS TRAIL</name><id>9930380</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237037400000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9930380/</event_url></item>