<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>The Hunt Room</address_2><address_1>2 Court St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.763014</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(603)589-4600</phone><name>Nashua Public Library</name><city>Nashua</city><id>744622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.464680</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Since 1993, the Stroll has served as Nashua’s official kick-off to the holiday season. Each year, close to 30,000 people from across New England visit downtown Nashua to enjoy this FREE holiday event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening kicks off with a candlelit walk of thousands down to Railroad Square where the City's official Christmas tree is lit.  Much of the downtown is closed to traffic for the evening, allowing Strollers to wander to different artistic and cultural performances, sample offerings from street vendors, dine in downtown’s fine restaurants and do holiday shopping at our unique specialty shops and boutiques. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Entertainment - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over 25 venues will host a variety of performers this year in addition to the costumed characters and entertainers on the street.  Program guide to be posted on website by November 6th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to food concession stand, several of your favorite downtown restaurants will be serving menu items outside in front of their restaurant.  Try food from Fody's Tavern, Vietnam Noodle House, San Francisco Kitchen, Vietnam Noodle House, Collins Brothers Chowder, the Sausage King of Nashua, and Villa Banca.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Silent Auction - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New this year!   The Stroll is Great American Downtown's largest fundraiser!  Stop by our Silent Auction to bid on FABULOUS prize packages with great items such as:  Chunky's Cinema &amp;amp; Pub movie passes, Pat's Peak ski passes. gift certificates to downtown shops and restaurants, hotel stays and more!  Auction location:  tbd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beer Garden -&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New this year!  In 2008, we introduced an outdoor Beer Garden but this year, we're ramping it up BIG TIME! Instead of a simple outdoor set up with draft beer available, the 2010 Beer Garden wil lnow feature live music, more beverage options, and fun activities! In fact, there will be a jam packed schedule of entertainment for the entire night!  All ages are welcome, HOWEVER wristbands are required for all attendees who are 21+ (valid ID required). We are partnering with Community4Productions to make this all possible! Are you ready to ROCK THE STROLL? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:  High Street (Located on Main Street, in between Bank of America &amp;amp; Scontsas Jewelry)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hours:  5- 10 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spirit of Giving/Nonprofit info. area - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL non-profits will be located in front of Citizens Bank.  Strollers can drop off items such as canned goods, disposable diapers and new, unwrapped toys for local charitable organizations. Check back soon for specific items that are needed for the organizations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking/Free shuttle rides - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Offered between 4:30pm and 10:30pm.  Park at Holman Stadium or Rivier College.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Courtesy of First Student and Nashua Transit.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.downtownnashua.org/stroll" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.downtownna...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet in front of the library.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291036428000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289690060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>17th Annual Winter Holiday Stroll</name><id>15438234</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290894300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/15438234/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/0/global_5981968.jpeg</photo_url></item>