<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22-24 Clinton Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.360752</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hard Rock Cafe Boston</name><city>Boston</city><id>10185452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055504</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;LIVE MUSIC SHOWCASE at The Hard Rock Cafe!! All details are below.  PLEASE REMEMBER to go to the EventBrite link to purchase your ticket to this event! A MeetUp RSVP will NOT get you admission to the show.  Limited tickets at the door, advance tickets are recommended.  One tix will get you admission for all 4 artists/bands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://bostonsoulexperience.eventbrite.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;http://bostonsoulexperience.eventbrite.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;The Boston Soul Experience - 4 artists / bands at Hard Rock Cafe, featuring Sheila Raye Charles, the daughter of legend Ray Charles, performing his music and her own!  The show will be a night of music that touches and liberates the soul. The artists of all four handpicked acts  - Sheila Raye Charles, Lucia Marie, Gold Blood &amp;amp; The Associates, Aisling Peartree - stand out for their unique talent and sound. They'll bring various flavors and experiences of music with the underlying continuity of soul - performing pop soul, soul rock with a Motown flair, R&amp;amp;B soul and some classics! A percentage of ticket sales will be donated to Music Drives Us (musicdrivesus.org). Show sponsors and artist profiles below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;7:15pm VIP "Behind The Scenes" Meet The Artists event will give VIP ticket holders ($10 additional at checkout) early entry plus a behind the scenes experience before the show! They'll get an opportunity to meet the artists performing also incl headliner Sheila Raye Charles. There will be photo opportunities, the ability to purchase all artists' merchandise incl books and CDs from Sheila Raye, autographs, book signings and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;TICKETS: Online advanced ticketing thru Nov 14: $18/$13 student w/student ID.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;Day of the event, tickets $20/$15 student w student ID at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; TICKET ADD ON'S: "Seating (Limited)" $15 additional *; "VIP 7:15pm MEET SHEILA RAYE &amp;amp; All Artists" - $15 additional&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;SPONSORS &amp;amp; CHARITY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;** Berklee Internet &amp;amp; Radio Network (thebirn.com)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;** Revere Hotel Boston Common&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;** Motives Cosmetics (Independent Distributor at info@beyondintent.com)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;** A percentage of ticket sales will be donated to Music Drives Us. For info: musicdrivesus.org.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;** Produced by Beyond Intent Music Group and featuring several independent Conquer Entertainment artists. Owner is an independent distributor/Certified Artist Developer and Certified CAD trainer with Conquer Entertainment. She is also a nationwide CAD recruiter and talent scout. CONTACT:&lt;a href="mailto:info@beyondintent.com" style="color : #8d0000"&gt;nina@beyondintent.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;ARTISTS/BANDS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; SHEILA RAYE CHARLES will sing the songs of her legendary father Ray Charles as well as her originals. Sheila Raye creates her own distinct sound while delivering her intensely inspiring message of hope and love.  As a talented singer/songwriter, she has found her voice in acoustic jazz and R &amp;amp; B with lyrics that deliver the personal journey of her own life and her relationship with her father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; LUCIA MARIE is a Boston-based pop soul artist who will perform her originals from her latest CD as well her renditions of classics such as "Midnight Train to Georgia" and a Donna Summer tribute mix. Lucia Marie's music resume includes 2 music videos, inclusion in 2 Feature Film Soundtracks with speaking roles in each the movie, a first self-titled album and numerous performances. She'll be accompanied by top dance professionals who liven up a crowd!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; GOLD BLOOD AND THE ASSOCIATES is a powerful New England 7-piece band bringing their unique Soul Rock sound with a flavor &amp;amp; flair reminiscent of Motown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; AISLING PEARTREE is a Boston area soul &amp;amp; R&amp;amp;B singer/songwriter who will sing a mix of her originals and covers we all love. Her first performances were as a child in the gospel musical "Black Nativity" when she was 10 and 11 years old. She hopes her music will give her the opportunity to be an advocate for social change, especially on issues that affect women, children and people of color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;=========================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;The Hard Rock Cafe is located near Faneuil Hall, within walking distance of Haymarket (Orange and Green Lines); Government Center (Green and Blue Lines) and about a 10 min walk to Park Street (Green and Red Lines).  Everyone is responsible for their own food and drink. PLEASE MAINTAIN A SEPARATE TAB OR PAY AS YOU GO!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color : #362e2c ; text-align : left ; font-size : 13px"&gt;Hope to see you there!  -Isabel&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Details to be emailed closer to date.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Isabel Bourelle</member_name><member_id>8394555</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353036853000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352215690000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LIVE MUSIC - The Boston Soul Experience at The Hard Rock Cafe</name><id>90206982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353024900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/90206982/</event_url></item>