<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hey Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ted will be guest hosting this meetup. His actual address will be emailed to Yes RSVPs 24 hours before the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions about this meetup event, please message Ted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For all soccer fans and those who just love to party it's...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Manchester United vs. Barcelona. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 2009 UEFA Champions League Final. For those less familiar with the sport, this is the Super Bowl of Europe; a one-off game to determine the champion of European soccer for the 2008-2009 season. This year's match up is a titanic one; two of the biggest clubs in the world going head to head for all the marbles. English grit against Catalan style! Featuring the two greatest players in the world; Cristiano Ronaldo vs Leo Messi! Who's better? Theyll decide for themselves on the pitch at Rome's Stadio Olimpico on the 27th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.uefa.com/competitions/ucl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.uefa.com/c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be watching the match at Ted's apartment on the East Side of Providence, where we succesfully hosted the Inauguration Party back in January. There won't be the giant screen and projector this time but Ted's own fairly sizabe TV will have to do. And since the match kicks off at 2:45 PM Providence time, while most of us are at work, we will be watching the playback of it starting around 7:15 PM. It's up to you to stay away from the result, but if you do know the score on the day and still want to come, please respect those who want to watch the match as if it were live. So in other words, NO SPOILERS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you're not really a fan of the sport of just have casual interest, it will hopefully be a fun night with friends and a good game by two of the world's most exciting clubs. Ted will be putting out the basics: snacks, chips, crackers, soda, etc but please feel free to bring along whatever you'd like to snack on. And you are more than welcome to drink, it is a soccer match after all, but it will be BYOB. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ted will be hosting this event</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244207381000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241786303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Soccer Party - UEFA Champions League Final</name><id>10367394</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243465200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/10367394/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>