<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Nashs Mill Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01301</zip><lat>42.604650</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Greenfield Swimming Area</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>1125824</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.617836</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/2/7/6/event_19645206.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This is a walk and socialize meetup; not really so much a hike as a romp by the river! The Greenfield Swimming Area closes to dogs after Memorial Day Weekend, and re-opens in early November thru the winter. There are trails by the river. Lots of room to play for everyone! There is another trail on the opposite side of Nash's Mill Road that follows the Green River.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions are to take Route 91 and head towards Greenfield. &lt;span&gt;Take exit &lt;strong&gt;26&lt;/strong&gt; for Greenfield rotary which is the exit for routes 2West and 2A East.  Get off the rotary at the exit for route 2West towards NorthAdams and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;immediately get into the right lane&lt;/span&gt;.  (From north of exit 26, this will be the first exit off the rotary.  From the south of exit 26, this will be the 3rd exit off the rotary.)  At the 1st traffic light, take a right onto Colrain Road and go 1.4 miles.  Pass a 99 Restaurant on the right.  Pass Greenfield Community College on left.  Nash's Mill Road will be on the right. Greenfield Swimming Area will be on the left and we will meet in the parking lot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As of today, Jan 6, 2013, there is approximately a 6 inch snow base on the ground.  The bridge to cross over the river has been shoveled but the paths have not been plowed - foot traffic of the 2 and 4 legged kind has stamped down the snow.  The parking area has been somewhat plowed but not the entire parking lot.  The other trail across the street is the Franklin County Bike trail but no bikes will pass on this at this time since the snowbase is in the same condition.  Oh well, at least this is a workout!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359827247000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357481169000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greenfield Swimming Area</name><id>98176262</id><headcount>10</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358004600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/98176262/</event_url></item>