<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Macedonia State Park has been on my list for a while.  This is a 2,300 acre park comprised of rugged trails and rock scrambles.  The views from the west ridge offer the Taconic Range and the Catskill Mountains.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a 6.7 mile loop around the perimeter of the park.  The terrain is rugged and the distance long.  This is NOT a beginner hike due to distance and climbing.  If you do not know what a rock scramble is or how to get up one, this is not the place for you.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spring is here and warm weather.  You will need a day pack, water, snacks (lunch), insect repellent, sunscreen, waterproof boots.  It is already tick season so light colored pants and trail gators if you own them would be helpful.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are a hiking group.  That means we start together and we finish together and are only as fast as our slowest hiker.  If this system does not appeal to you then do not come.  &lt;br /&gt;As always with me.....No Dogs, No Children.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:  From route 7 in Kent, turn onto Rt. 341 west, after 1.7 miles right onto Macedonia Brook Road.  This will turn into the park entrance.  The trail heads are near the bridge.   &lt;br /&gt;Mapquest directions:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Kent&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=1+Macedonia+Brook+Rd&amp;amp;zipcode=06757-1018&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;latitude=41.74272&amp;amp;longitude=-73.499429&amp;amp;geocode=ADDRESS" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park info and trail map:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dEP/cwp/view.asp?a=2716&amp;amp;q=325234" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dEP...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== &lt;b&gt;Legal Stuff&lt;/b&gt; ===   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274111572000</updated><rating><average>4.94000005722</average><count>16</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269999358000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Hiking Macedonia State Park, Kent CT</name><id>13043542</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273932000000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/13043542/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/7/b/global_2859963.jpeg</photo_url></item>