<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Prime 16&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This place is so amazing that I'm even in love with the veggie burgers - and I am a complete meat and potatoes kind of gal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;20 beers on draft (selection changes often); 40 bottled beers. (Surprisingly well chosen group of scotch/whiskey as well; wine by the glass was yummy too)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a quote from the Play article on the food:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The secret, Farber explains, is in the beef itself. &amp;quot;We get our meat from a company out of the midwest called Meyer Beef, the cattle are vegetarian fed... it's all natural, Angus beef.&amp;quot; Farber says what Meyer Beef is all about: &amp;quot;It's 250 family farms that raise it just for this company, so it's traceable, it's sustainable. There's no hormones at all, so water content is really low. The burgers are stamped, they're humanely slaughtered, and approved by the ASPCA- it says it right on the package.&amp;quot;....For those who prefer their burgers meatless, Farber- who was a vegetarian for quite a while- also offers a world-class veggie burger. &amp;quot;I make them myself,&amp;quot; he grins. &amp;quot;I add a little lemon zest, and grind I some sprouts into the other mixture, which is sweet potato, your standard mirepoix of vegetable, and some chickpea and some other whole-wheat ingredients and mix it together.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They also have a three-cheese grilled cheese with avocado and sprouts that is delicious. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The amazing (and beautiful!) manager Char has offered us these specials:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6-7pm:  ALL DRAFTS HALF PRICE!!&lt;br /&gt;7pm-??? Kill the Keg night - most drafts for cheap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dev is your contact; number in RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.&lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235336622000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>28</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231812389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Prime 16 Happy Hour!</name><id>9510161</id><headcount>29</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234220400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/9510161/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>