<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>298 Stage Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03269</zip><lat>43.540527</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-286-8191</phone><name>ULCS Clinic</name><city>Sanbornton</city><id>947760</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.609424</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;While concurrently planning to live self-sufficient lifestyles, going "back to basics", conserving energy and our natural resources, we need to expand our level of awarness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cosmic energetic changes arriving in 2012 will affect us in ways that we must understand NOW, before it is too late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn the details about unavoidable energy changes&amp;nbsp;which will otherwise mutate&amp;nbsp;our DNA encoding.&amp;nbsp; The consequences of ignoring this information are extremely serious, since failure to do the essential energy shielding and healing&amp;nbsp;techniques in time can not be remedied later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Since&amp;nbsp;the encoding&amp;nbsp;for all levels of our multi-dimensional bio-spiritual anatomy is encrypted&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;the DNA, it is essential to protect against the devistating frequencies which will otherwise permanently mutate our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contemporary society takes for granted the notion that the soul and spirit can never be destroyed, and will always survive the death of the physical body.&amp;nbsp; This is true only when the orginal organic DNA encoding, upon which the gestalt of the soul is defined, remains in-tact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the intensity of the noxious energies arriving in 2012 will&amp;nbsp;further mutate&amp;nbsp;the DNA of unshielded planetary inhabitants.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This will forever destroy&amp;nbsp;our potential for spiritual survival, including&amp;nbsp;our original ascension capability to return to God-Source in a state of wholeness&amp;nbsp;with all our memories in tact. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure to do the necessary techniques in time&amp;nbsp;affects much more than the DNA encoding governing our physical bodies.&amp;nbsp; This will&amp;nbsp;irreversably mutate the encoding of our&amp;nbsp;higher level spiritual&amp;nbsp;anatomy (soul and beyond).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To understand&amp;nbsp;cosmic, galactic, intergalactic and inter-dimensional structure and energetics,&amp;nbsp; please&amp;nbsp;view&amp;nbsp;the U-Tube presentation on the link below. Technical diagrams are presented during the 3 interviews with Ashayana Deane which will make it much easier to understand the DVD which will be viewed at this Meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each of the 3 interviews lasts about 2 hours, so allow sufficient time and take notes.&amp;nbsp; Bring a list of questions to the Meetup.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.krystalspiral.com/CamelotInterviews.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT:&amp;nbsp; The level of detail presented at the Meetup itself&amp;nbsp;requires viewing the above U-tube presentations as a prerequisite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, grasping what will be presented at the Meetup itself will be extremely difficult.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Meetup adjourns at 9:00 PM. Please bring your own refreshments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for meetup sign at end of first driveway.  Enter through front door, which has another meetup sign.  Do NOT park in second driveway with the ULCS Clinic sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306373470000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>SURVIVAL 101: We must wake up to the BIG PICTURE!  We need to protect much more than or physical bodies and planetary lifestyle. We must understand what is encoded in our DNA and how to protect against devistating mutations from 2012 cosmic energies.</why><group><who>Co-Creative Planetary Stewards</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Back-to-Basics</urlname><id>1438479</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Back to Basics: Sustainable Self-Sufficient Healthy Living</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297832947000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Survival 101: Limited Opportunity to Protect Against  2012 Cosmic Energy Changes</name><id>16583736</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1300226400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Back-to-Basics/events/16583736/</event_url></item>