<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 12-13 miles round-trip &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Easy to moderate (some hills, dirt and old paved roads) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Estimated 4.5 hours plus lunch &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Price to park @ swimming:&lt;/strong&gt; $5? (The DCR website doesn't say, but &lt;strong&gt;usually&lt;/strong&gt; you pay at &lt;em&gt;state parks&lt;/em&gt;. It's not consistent, but if there's a fee, it should be $5 per car.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are welcome to join us at the park whether or not you join the hike! I am guessing we'll be there between 2-2:30pm depending on the group's pace.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/e/3/e/event_120367742.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Photo: shoreline between Dana Common and Soapstone Hill)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HIKE DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll visit two historic villages in Dana, one of four Massachusetts towns disincorporated to build Quabbin Reservoir. Highlights include cellarholes of old homes, a schoolhouse, and the Dana Town Hall, plus more homes and mills in Doubleday Village. Between, we'll pass the summits of Whitney Hill (1,017 ft) and the "other" Rattlesnake Hill (832 ft).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our travels, we'll visit Quabbin Reservoir's shores twice (north and west of Doubleday Village), near to Soapstone Hill and Leveau Island, respectively. We will not be far from Mount Zion, Quabbin's biggest island, at 4 miles long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plenty to drink (1-2 liters).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lunch and/or snacks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunscreen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Deep-woods"-type repellant with DEET, or repellant with Pemethyrin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light-colored clothing/long pants (easier to see ticks).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera highly recommended!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rules of Quabbin Reservoir:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming or wading (public water supply).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No animals allowed (same reason).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please take trash with you when you go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove anything from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are outhouses with sanitizer at the beginning and at Dana Common.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS TO GATE 40 @ QUABBIN RESERVOIR &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take 32A north off Route 9 on the West Brookfield/Ware town line. Gate 40 is in Petersham, MA, north of the Hardwick/Petersham line on Route 32A. Pass through the town of Hardwick and continue on a long, rural stretch. Gate 40 is on the southbound side (the left), about 1 mile north of Dana Road, and about 1/10 mile north of Old Valley Rd (maybe Glen Valley Rd on some maps). The GPS coordinates are good, we've used them before:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N42 degrees 26 minutes 45.3 seconds by W 72 degrees 12 minutes 57.0 seconds.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you are coming from the north&lt;/em&gt;, take Route 2 to 202 south, 122 south (in New Salem), and 32A south (in Petersham). Gate 40 is roughly 4 miles south, on the southbound side (the right), 1 mile before Dana Road. If you enter Hardwick, MA, you've gone too far!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not park in front of the gate.&lt;/strong&gt; We can fit at least 8 cars.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TO LAKE WYOLA, 94 LAKEVIEW RD, SHUTESBURY&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;(Estimated 25-minute drive from Gate 40)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the north/northwest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Gate 40, drive north on 32A about 4 miles. Turn left on 122 north and continue about 10 minutes (9-10 miles). Turn left onto 202 south.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 202 south &lt;em&gt;(about 5 minutes to pass 122 if coming from Route 2)&lt;/em&gt;. Continue south about 9 miles into Shutesbury, MA. There is a sign for "Lake Wyola" on the right; turn right onto Prescott Road. After about 1 mile, turn right onto Wendell Road. The lake appears to be about 4 miles up, but it's surrounded by three roads. Stay left at the fork after about 3 miles to take Locks Pond Road. Follow it to the end and turn right onto Lakeview Road. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I haven't been here yet, so above all, follow the signs!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (You could drive either way around the lake, really.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the south/southwest:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 east or west as needed. Take Route 202 north about 16 miles (15+ minutes). Look for the "Lake Wyola" sign on the left, and follow directions as from north, above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the east:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 122 north. (Take 31 or 140 south to get to 122 if needed.) Continue through Petersham, MA, and into New Salem, MA. Take Route 202 south and follow directions as from north, above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I may not see morning emails. I also leave my house about 1 hour before the hike. If you have questions, please post them at the bottom of this event; I will check it before leaving the house.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340574874000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340082630000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 40: Dana Common and Doubleday Village</name><id>69781662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340283600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/69781662/</event_url></item>