<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Due to the advanced and strenuous nature of this event it is not suitable for beginners **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Prior experience with travel during winter conditions is required **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Crampons &amp;amp; Snowshoes are required **&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** All cancellations will be posted by 11 a.m. on Saturday morning **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are hiking to East Osceola (4156') with the option of continuing on to Mt Osceola (4340'). A fine, scenic, forest hike with challenging trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Lincoln Woods Visitor Center/trailhead. From here we will carpool to the Greeley Ponds parking area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hike 1.30 mi/+337 ft on the Greeley Ponds Trail to Mad River Notch. At Mad River Notch we then take the Mt. Osceola trail for 1.5 mi/+1851' to the summit of East Osceola (4156'). The Mt. Osceola trail which leads to the east summit from Mad River Notch is steep and rough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we choose to continue on to Mt. Osceola (4340') there will be a &amp;quot;chimney&amp;quot; section that will need to be bypassed or ascended directly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To East Summit only -&lt;br /&gt;Distance 5.60 mi&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +2390 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To East &amp;amp; Main Summits -&lt;br /&gt;Distance 7.60 mi&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain +3232 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Headlamps, Crampons &amp;amp; Snowshoes are a requirement for this hike. We will likely encounter ice and possibly unbroken trails between the two summits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hike time will vary with the pace of the group. &lt;b&gt;This hike has a higher rating of difficulty due to the elevation gain.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain cancels. The weather will be reviewed on Saturday Dec 6th. Any cancellations or adjustments will be made by 3 p.m on Saturday Dec 6th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;a href="http://www.fs.fed.us/r9/forests/white_mountain/recreation/roads_status.php"&gt;check the status of forest service roads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Milton</member_name><member_id>4294409</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1229263232000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226274421000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Osceola East (with option for Osceola Main)</name><id>9128034</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228656600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9128034/</event_url></item>