<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Oh, the pressure! My guests keep asking for coffee and I just didn't have the equipment or product to provide. But that is the past! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have acquired excellent coffee brewing equipment, old school no little packets and electronic gadgetry for me.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then I set off on my quest to find fresh roasted coffee in the Hartford area that was good enough to serve; remember folks I am from San Francisco and we fog-bound northern west coasters take our coffee very seriously. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Success!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jose' Rene' Marinez Onofre, owner of &lt;a href="http://www.jrenecoffee.com/#home" target="_blank"&gt;J. Rene' Coffee Roasters&lt;/a&gt; is a practicing Ct attorney who roasts outstanding coffee in West Hartford and runs the &lt;a href="http://www.makrismidtowndiner.com" target="_blank"&gt;Makris Midtown Diner &lt;/a&gt;in Wethersfield.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Such a busy guy can't do everything at once so coffee roasting is only done on Saturdays and the facility is only open to the public from 10 to 1 on Saturdays. He has agreed to give our group a coffee roasting seminar after they close on Saturday, March 13.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This won't be a long event, so plan on an hour or so. Plenty of time to do other things that afternoon and evening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because space is limited  in the roasting facility, I am limiting this event to 10 cooking club members (no guests). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wake up and smell the coffee!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am the one that looks like me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268678360000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266687760000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wake up and smell the COFFEE</name><id>12656341</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1268505000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/12656341/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/f/global_13207231.jpeg</photo_url></item>