<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Be a part of the Big Picture campaign and help build the grassroots base President Obama needs to turn the tide on climate change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;President Obama sees the Big Picture. A few weeks ago his administration took great strides toward securing our clean energy future and addressing global warming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are a critical piece of the Big Picture and our country's clean energy future!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come to the Massachusetts Chapter  House Party on Climate change and get the latest on national legislation while meeting other environmentalists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us, chat and socialize, and participate in a Nationwide Sierra Club conference call and discussion with Sierra Club leaders on how we can move forward towards clean energy and averting climate change.  The call begins at 8:00.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BYOB and a snack to share.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Also get to see Jamaica Plain Cohousing, a &amp;quot;new old-fashioned neighborhood&amp;quot; (a condo development with plenty of common facilities and a community-oriented spirit) completed and moved into in 2005. See the energy-saving features and community-encouraging architecture, and meet some of the residents.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Greeting People at the Door</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mary Ann!</member_name><member_id>618637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245273191000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Environmental Activists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Sierra-Club</urlname><id>229402</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Greater Boston Sierra Club Environmental Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243463117000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Big Picture Energy and Climage Change House Party</name><id>10507802</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243981800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Sierra-Club/events/10507802/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/3/global_7614675.jpeg</photo_url></item>