<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Tripyramids Slide Trails - Advanced/Strenuous Hike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North Tripyramid - 4140' and Middle Tripyramid - 4110'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tripyramids have three summits, but only the North and Middle peaks count as official 4000 footers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are multiple approaches to these peaks. One of the most challenging hikes in the Whites is to hike the slide trails. But these are only suitable for dry weather conditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So we'll hike the slide trails &lt;b&gt;if the weather is dry&lt;/b&gt;, starting from the Livermore Trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the event of wetter conditions, we will instead ascend via Sabbaday Brook and/or Pine Bend Brook trails which are off the Kancamangus Highway (I will modify the meetup details if this happens).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both options afford us an 11 mile hike.......the first will be much more strenous and therefore this hike will be listed as Advanced-Strenuous. All participants signing up will be required to answer a few short questions to ensure the hike is suitable and safe for all. Safety is the most important.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we are doing the slide trails, we will start at the Livermore trailhead, near the center of Waterville Valley. The first 3.6 miles are on the Livermore Road which is gated at the trailhead. The Mount Tripyramid Trail climbs up the north slide a steep, bare slide that is difficult and dangerous in bad weather.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tripyramids consist of three peaks: North Tripyramid (4,140 ft.), Middle Tripyramid (4,110 ft.), and South Tripyramid (4,090 ft.). They form the eastern wall of Waterville Valley in New Hampshire's White Mountains. Many people hike all three peaks on the same trip starting at Livermore Road and using the slide trails, which form a loop. The North and South Slide Trails are actual rock slides and offer a challenging hike because of their steepness and slipperiness. It is generally recommended to hike up the North Slide Trail, traverse across Middle Tripyramid, and then down South Tripyramid. This is because the slabs of stone on the North Slide Trail are so steep it is easier to go up them than down them. The Osceolas, Waterville Valley, and Tecumseh can be seen to the west.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The north slide was created in 1885 during a heavy rain, the south in 1869. The best views are from near the top of the north slide, with some nice views near the summit of Middle Peak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details for this hike:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance  11.10 miles round trip &lt;br /&gt;Book Time 7 hr 23 min &lt;br /&gt;Elevation Gain 3214 ft &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The loop begins with the gentle and wide Livermore Trail. At 2.6 miles there is an intersection for the south end of Mount Tripyramid Trail. Continue on Livermore Trail for one additional mile to the north end of the Mount Tripyramid Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From here, the real hiking begins, ascending a steep, rocky, and mostly exposed 1.2 miles to the summit of Mt. North Tripyramid. From this summit, the final 3.7 miles of the Mount Tripyramid trail tags the remaining two summits, descends another rocky slide below the south summit, and finally links back to the Livermore Trail at the southern end. A lollipop!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an advanced hike with steep sections. Please be prepared to &lt;br /&gt;hike at book time or less. Pace will be 1.5 - 2 MPH. If you have any &lt;br /&gt;doubt please contact me. If you are up to it, it will be a great &lt;br /&gt;hike with fantastic views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross posted with North East Adventures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a condition of attending this meetup you agree to release, hold &lt;br /&gt;harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group &lt;br /&gt;from any and all claims for property damage, injury, and/or death, &lt;br /&gt;including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. You also &lt;br /&gt;agree to assume all risk associated with this meetup and agree to know &lt;br /&gt;and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;br /&gt;www.hikesafe.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michele</member_name><member_id>9237839</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279593367000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277501583000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tripyramids Slide Trails</name><id>13912069</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279367100000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/13912069/</event_url></item>