<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Per Ms. Wells the Outreach Coordinator or the W. Hartford REI store, those wishing to volunteer are to give Ms. Wells a telephone number and email address so that she can can communicate one last time to everyone directions and a reminder of appropriate clothing and footwear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you contact Ms. Wells directly, please state that you are with The Greater Hartford Adventurers Meetup Group (this event is cross-listed with Hartford Area Hiking). Ms. Wells' telephone and email address are below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event listing with REI:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/stores/store_event_detail.jsp?pid=A40A02B082DCCA9B24FA0CBE88E964E9&amp;amp;template_id=30&amp;amp;template_family=webDetail&amp;amp;ignore_cache=1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/st...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will clean the ravine near Windsor Avenue/Main Street entrance and improve a trail by opening a former roadway for bicycle and pedestrian use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Participants will receive REI Volunteer tee-shirt, coffee, water, and a snack will be provided. Meet 10:00 am at the golf course in Keney parking lot. (REI's website, &lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/stores/105" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/st...&lt;/a&gt; ). Rain or shine. Please pre-register with Outreach Specialist Jenna Wells, &lt;br /&gt;jewells@rei.com, 860-233-2211, x 203.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Service Project at Keney Park, Windsor Ave/Main Street Entrance to Park:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: &lt;br /&gt;* Take 91 South to Exit 34.&lt;br /&gt;* Take 159 Exit and Turn Left on Main Street. &lt;br /&gt;* Cross Under highway Park Entrance on your left. &lt;br /&gt;* Enter Keney Park follow park road until T intersection Take a right&lt;br /&gt;* Follow road until you find the golf course parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I95 North to Exit 34.&lt;br /&gt;* Take 159 Exit.&lt;br /&gt;* Take a left at the end of the exit and then an immediate right onto Main Street.&lt;br /&gt;* Keney Park entrance will be immediately on your left.&lt;br /&gt;* Enter Keney Park follow park road until T intersection.&lt;br /&gt;* Take a right follow road until you find the golf course parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Keney Park, Hartford, CT &lt;br /&gt;Contact: Jenna Wells Outreach Specialist &lt;br /&gt;Cost: Free &lt;br /&gt;Registration Required. Please pre-register by calling 860-233-2211 x 203.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keney Park Home Page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.keneyparkhartford.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.keneyparkh...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REI Store, West Hartford, Local information page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rei.com/stores/store_events.jsp?store=105" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rei.com/st...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Sven Pihl (http://adventurers.meetup.com/167/members/2672127/ ) is the leader on this one! He is leading via his Meetup: Greater Hartford Adventurers (http://adventurers.meetup.com/167/ )</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1213020133000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Volunteering for Trail Days is a noble cause.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212632037000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Service Event: CT Trails Day (Keney Park, Trail Improvement/Cleanup - Hartford)</name><id>8081889</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212847200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8081889/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/5/e/global_2859934.jpeg</photo_url></item>