<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Foster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.265118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 755-6800</phone><name>DCU Center</name><city>Worcester</city><id>732028</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.798937</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Worcester Sharks Hockey Click and Shoot Event&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;April 11, 2009 - Fan Appreciation Night&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at 4:45 PM  We are going to need everyone to meet outside of Door 5.  This is a security entrance that will bring you guys down to ice level.  Door 5 is off of Major Taylor Boulevard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost $12.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;MUST PRE PAY (normally these tickets are $17.25)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We met with the folks over at the Worcester Sharks this week to discuss having a click and shoot at one of the games. Looks like we have a real good opportunity not only to witness the game at a group rate discount but we got some serious benefits offered as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s the scoop!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you sign up and pay for this event by April 3rd, all photographers will be given “full access credentials” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;– So what does this mean? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will get a full tour of the facilities.&lt;br /&gt;Then during the game have access to the entire arena. &lt;br /&gt;Including the catwalk above the ice, the tunnel where the players line up, and after the event - access to photographing the players signing autographs on the ice. (Please note however that the Locker Rooms are OFF LIMITS – no one goes in there. Period.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We’ll also meet the current photographer for the sharks, Jason Morneau. You can ask him questions about his experiences photographing for the Sharks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also have excellent seats if you want to sit and watch the game. If you have a family member or a friend who would like to attend the game they will get the same price on the tickets and can join you in the stands. The seating section we have reserved is in the 100 Level seating section of the arena. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In exchange for the all access passes we have been asked by the Sharks to please share our photos with them. They would love to use them for the photo gallery section of their web site. Which is the most frequently visited section of the site. You can have your © Name listed on the photos. So if you agree to the all access passes – you’ll be asked to give Donna Dufault a cd of your images as Jpegs to share with the Sharks. The deadline for this is April 13th. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We asked about “Model Release” issues – Turns out there is a statement on every ticket- and it is the policy of the Venue (DCU Center), that if you attend any function in their facilities you automatically agree to being photographed and have a “release on your likeness” by simply entering the building. So we are covered!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Photo Ops:&lt;br /&gt;The Fans &lt;br /&gt;The pre game events&lt;br /&gt;Action shots of the players&lt;br /&gt;The arena and all its glory&lt;br /&gt;The Ice&lt;br /&gt;Crew members&lt;br /&gt;Tunnel Line Up&lt;br /&gt;Shark Pit&lt;br /&gt;Autograph session&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Game Time is 7-9PM &lt;br /&gt;But we have to meet ahead of time to hand out tickets, get the tour, get set up with credentials, and sign wavier forms. So you MUST meet us at 4:45 at Door 5 – it is off of Major Taylor Boulevard and we will need to go in as a group. Please do not be late, or you will miss out!!! No refunds!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We think this will be an incredible evening of fun and an excellent chance to get cool photos. We hope you’ll join us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please get us your money via cash or check by April 3rd... you can mail it to us at:&lt;br /&gt;380 Bridle Path&lt;br /&gt;Worcester, MA 01604&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or bring it to the MeetUp event on March 26th.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;Donna and Scott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/cool.gif' border='0' alt='cool' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the person organizing and rounding folks up at the head of the line.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240002264000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237298525000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Worcester Sharks Hockey Click and Shoot Event</name><id>9972332</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239482700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9972332/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/5/global_7716469.jpeg</photo_url></item>