<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 Bloomfield Ave</address_1><state>Co</state><zip>06117</zip><lat>41.797863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>200 Bloomfield Ave</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>11857202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.718033</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Register at &lt;a href="http://www.eoct.org/"&gt;www.eoct.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eoct.org/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Registration Begins at 12:15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start Time: 12:45&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The University of Hartford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wilde Auditorium (Lower Level)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;200 Bloomfield Avenue, West Hartford, CT 06117&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EO Members, Uof H faculty and students – FREE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside guests - $50&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cameron Herold Bio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For over 20 years, Cameron Herold has been coaching, speaking to, and helping entrepreneurs on five continents build their companies. He started BackPocket COO to be able to coach and mentor young, fun companies, and help them make their dreams happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cameron Herold is one of the country's most innovative business leaders and was a leading force behind one of the most successful new business ventures of the last decade, 1-800-GOT-JUNK?. He was Chief Operating Officer for nearly seven years and his innovative business leadership helped enable the company build a presence in 46 states, 9 provinces, and 4 countries while being ranked the “2nd Best Company to Work for in Canada” by Canadian Business Magazine and “the #1 Company in BC to Work for” twice by BC Business Magazine. During his tenure, numerous MBA programs studied the company, including the prestigious programs at Queen’s University and Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cameron helped the leading edge company grow from $2 million to $105 million in revenue in six years with no debt or outside shareholders, an awesome achievement by any standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to this, he was VP, Corporate Development at &lt;a href="http://ubarter.com/"&gt;Ubarter.com&lt;/a&gt;, a division of a 900-person firm with a $900 million market cap based in Seattle. He was also President of Barter Business Exchange in Vancouver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From October 1994 to March 1998, Herold was VP, Franchise Development for Coast-to-Coast Franchise Services (Boyd Autobody &amp;amp; Glass).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, he’s accumulated 20 years of real life experience since starting his first real company at 21. His successes (and yes, the occasional failure) have given him insights into tried-and-true systems that work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cameron has been an integral part of the sale, branding and integration of 450+ franchise locations with three franchisors. He’s worked on the development and deployment of e-commerce and Internet strategies, negotiation of corporate acquisitions and development of numerous strategic partnerships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has a unique understanding of growing companies, having led business areas from Operations, Marketing and Public Relations to Strategic Alliances, Sales and Call Centers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His work has helped companies be featured in the Associated Press, Bloomberg, USA Today, New York Times, Wall Street Journal, Fast Company, and Fortune, as well as TV shows like Donny Deutsch, Oprah, and Dr. Phil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building a successful brand and hyper-growth business isn’t about personality or luck. It’s about having the right systems. Cameron can give you the framework and proven solutions that will accelerate your revenue, build your profitability, and help you avoid costly problems. It really is like having a COO right in your back pocket!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Wide Auditorium (Lower Level)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362089856000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>startupcafe</urlname><id>1540019</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Startup Cafe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361452241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>EO: A day with Cameron Herold</name><id>105671182</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>17100000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362071700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/startupcafe/events/105671182/</event_url></item>