<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Remote Objects with Pyro -- Allen Downey&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pyro is a network communication module for Python -- it provides an&lt;br /&gt;easy-to-use form of remote method invocation.  In many cases you can&lt;br /&gt;take existing objects and make them available for remote access with&lt;br /&gt;a few lines of code.  When you invoke a method on a remote object,&lt;br /&gt;Pyro marshals the arguments, sends them to the remote object, then&lt;br /&gt;marshals the return value (or exception) and sends it back to the caller.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this presentation Allen will show a few simple examples that use Pyro,&lt;br /&gt;we will write a server together, and then participants will write a&lt;br /&gt;client that talks to it.  If possible, please bring a laptop with&lt;br /&gt;Python and Pyro installed.  If you use Ubuntu, you can install the&lt;br /&gt;package named pyro, and optionally pyro-doc, pyro-examples and&lt;br /&gt;pyro-gui.  Otherwise you can get it from &lt;a href="http://pyro.sourceforge.net/" target="_blank"&gt;http://pyro.sourcefor...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The talk will be accessible to intermediate Python programmers --&lt;br /&gt;if you are familiar with inheritance, that should do it.   If you can't bring a laptop,&lt;br /&gt;don't worry -- if we have one laptop for every two people, that will be plenty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions about Pyro or anything you would like Allen to&lt;br /&gt;cover, send him email: downey@allendowney.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ned Batchelder</member_name><member_id>1824278</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253145320000</updated><rating><average>4.90000009537</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Pythonistas</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonpython</urlname><id>469457</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Python User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245283527000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Cambridge Python July Meetup: Remote Objects with Pyro</name><id>10676152</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpython/events/10676152/</event_url></item>