<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>301 Congress Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.661304</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cathedral Parish - Guild Hall</name><city>Portland</city><id>1552780</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.253456</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come join the Maine Buddhist Gathering for Buddhist Movie Night, featuring the Japanese film, DEPARTURES.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the movie: The featured film, "Departures" follows Daigo Kobayashi, a devoted orchestral celloist, who is suddenly left without a job. Daigo decides to move back to his hometown and accepts a job as a "Nokanshi", a Buddhist funeral professional who prepares bodies for burial and entry into the next life. The film follows his profound and sometimes comical journey with death as he uncovers the wonder, joy and meaning of life and living. Winner - Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film, 2009. In Japanese with English subtitles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Maine Buddhist Gathering is a collection of different sanghas, meditation groups and individuals throughout the state who practice in the Buddhist tradition. Those who are unaffiliated with a group or a center, are new to practice, or have an interest in meditation practice are warmly welcome to attend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film begins at 7, however, you are encouraged to come early to socialize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film is offered free of charge. Your donation of a snack or dessert to share is appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please contact Maggie Miller at maggiemiller513@gmail.com for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348396996000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Mindful Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-703</urlname><id>1270329</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Mindfulness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347402262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Buddhist Movie Night </name><id>81950362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348353000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-703/events/81950362/</event_url></item>