<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 Locust St #1</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01830</zip><lat>42.774986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-912-7136</phone><name>Nichiren Buddhist Sangha</name><city>Haverhill</city><id>753460</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084330</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Beginners' Workshop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Nichiren Buddhist Sangha of Greater New England is proud to offer a fun and engaging full day workshop for anyone interested in learning basic Buddhists concepts and experiencing the rich traditions of this Japanese school of Buddhism. Nichiren Shu Buddhism is a Mahayana Buddhist practice based on the Lotus Sutra and the teachings of the 12th century Japanese monk, Nichiren Shonin. Nichiren Buddhism is the second largest school of Buddhism in Japan and has been in the United States for over one hundred years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop is designed for those who want to learn about basic Buddhism and experience the practice of Nichiren Shu Buddhism at the New England temple in Haverhill, MA. Through lecture, discussion, and experiential activities, we’ll explore the supportive theories and practices behind this 2500 year old religion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The facilitator, Reverend Ryuoh Faulconer, has been a Nichiren Shu minister since 2001. Prior to leading the New England temple, he was the resident minister at the Portland, OR Nichiren Shu Temple for four and a half years. He has specialized training in Buddhist iconography, Reidan, Shomyo and Reiki and is deeply passionate about teaching the Dharma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The workshop is held monthly on Saturdays from 9:00 am to 4:30pm.  A small fee covers materials and lunch. See the MeetUp calendar for future dates. There is a registration deadline. The workshop will be canceled if no one is registered by the deadline. Payment can be made upon arrival on or using Paypal. The MeetUp page does not always show the number of people registered as we use several methods of enrollment for our events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information: &lt;br /&gt;

Nichiren Buddhist Sangha of Greater New England &lt;br /&gt;

15 Locust Street, #1 Haverhill, MA 01830 &lt;br /&gt;

Temple phone: 617-314-7782 &lt;br /&gt;

Email Reverend Ryuoh Faulconer: &lt;a href="mailto:ryouh@comcast.net"&gt;ryouh@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandbuddhist.org"&gt;www.newenglandbuddhist.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryuoh Faulconer Shonin</member_name><member_id>7835520</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365885473000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Buddhists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>buddhism-616</urlname><id>1275091</id><group_lat>42.7799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Haverhill Buddhist Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361212669000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beginners' Workshop</name><id>105189872</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>27000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365858000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-616/events/105189872/</event_url></item>