<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Amity Road</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06524</zip><lat>41.402840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Graduate Institute</name><city>Bethany</city><id>1346914</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.002243</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Awakening the Dreamer* Symposium is a profound inquiry into a bold vision: to bring forth an environmentally sustainable, spiritually fulfilling, and socially just human presence on Earth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Symposium invites all participants to understand what is happening in our global culture, and to discover how we can all play a part in creating a sustainable world for future generations. By using a workshop format, the Symposium incorporates inspiring videos, up-to-the-minute facts and &amp;#64257;gures, and dynamic group interactions. Some of the world's leading experts will contribute their views on many important topics -- including the current state of the Earth's biodiversity and the reality of socio-economic disparity throughout the world. Participants will leave the Symposium empowered to take clear steps to embody their vision for a better world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are ready to explore what this vision means for you, we invite you to attend our upcoming Symposium: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, September 12th, 1 to 6:00 pm &lt;br /&gt;Chris Robedee and Elaine Lengyel, Facilitators &lt;br /&gt;The Graduate Institute &lt;br /&gt;171 Amity Road, Bethany, CT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A suggested donation of $15 will be collected at the door &lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meetup is also being hosted through &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/VisionaryThinkers/"&gt;Visionary Thinkers&lt;/a&gt; meetup group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The Awakening the Dreamer, Changing the Dream Symposium is an initiative of The Pachamama Alliance, a San Francisco-based non-pro&amp;#64257;t organization whose mission is to preserve the Earth's tropical rainforests by empowering the indigenous peoples who are its natural custodians, and to contribute to the creation of a new global vision of equity and sustainability for all. The vision of the initiative is to generate widespread awakening at the grassroots level that leads to a transformation of our worldview, such that humanity becomes committed to restoring and protecting the environment and moves towards social justice and spiritual fulfillment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284315597000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281981805000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Awakening the Dreamer</name><id>14439507</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284310800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/14439507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/e/global_17244878.jpeg</photo_url></item>