<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hallo zusammen!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ja, ja...der langersehnte Filmabend ist endlich geplant!! Wer hat Lust auf einen guten Deutschen Film? Ich habe eine Befragung gestellt, mit der man waehlen kann, welchen Film man am liebesten sehen wuerde. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wir sind grosse Fans von &amp;quot;Pot luck&amp;quot; Essen. d.h. Wir machen ein Paar Pizzen (vegetarish und mit Fleisch) und geben ein paar Flaschen Wein aus. Dann kann jeder Beilagen oder ein anderes Hauptgericht oder Dessert mit und was zu trinken. Gell? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Da wir nicht so viel Platz haben und die Sitzmoeglichkeiten knapp sind, beschraenken wir den Abend auf 10 Leute. :-(. Also beeilt euch :-)!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wir freuen uns Euch zu sehen!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam &amp;amp; Hanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.  Ich habe die Befragung in der letzten Zeit geaendert. Bitte noch mal waehlen!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, yes... the long-awaited German Film Night is finally here!! Who wants to see a great German flick? I created a poll so that people could vote on which film they would like to see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're big fans of pot-luck dinners. That means that we'll make a couple of pizzas (probably one veggie and another with meat) and we'll have a couple bottles of wine. Then everyone else can bring a main or side dish and something to drink.  Ja?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately since we only have so much space at our place, we have to restrict this to 10 people. So join quickly!!! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you all!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam &amp;amp; Hanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P.S.  I had to change the poll recently. Please vote again!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Maps, GPS, memory</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Samuel Shirley</member_name><member_id>1090509</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1223831162000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Language &amp; Culture Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>language-63</urlname><id>531356</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence German Language Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219937101000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>German Movie Night</name><id>8640088</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221262200000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/language-63/events/8640088/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/5/4/global_1943460.jpeg</photo_url></item>