<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Wayside Commons Mall</address_2><address_1>Cambridge St (Rte 3A)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01803</zip><lat>42.509998</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>(if carpooling) LL Bean Parking Lot</name><city>Burlington</city><id>260804</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.199997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>What:  5-6 mile walk at the Audubon Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When:  Saturday, April 14, 11am  (if carpooling meet at 10:20am at LL Bean Parking Lot, Burlington MA - see details below)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where:  Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary,  87 Perkins Row, Topsfield, MA 01983 978-887-9264 ($4 entrance fee or $3 for seniors) Free for Audubon members&lt;br /&gt;ipswichriver@massaudubon.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Optional Late Lunch:   after the hike we will go to a late Lunch at about 3pm at the Starboard Gallery in Newburyport (15 minutes north of Sanctuary). Location: in the heart of charming Newburyport.  Window views of the River !&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, April 14th... Walking Trails at the Audubon Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary. Meet at 11am at the Ipswich Sanctuary Parking Lot or you can meet for Carpooling at LL Bean Parking Lot in Burlington MA at 10:20am (Exit 33A off of Rte 95 North).  Contact Sharon if you need additional information or have questions about carpooling for the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's get outside and breath some fresh air and see some majestic scenery !! Sharon will lead the 5-6 mile walk on these beautiful trails starting at 11am.  Some of us will continue the day by driving to Newburyport 15 min up on Rte 95 and eating at a local seafood restaurant there overlooking the Merrimack River.  Ipswich River, Mass Audubon's largest sanctuary, offers more than 10 miles of interconnecting trails that invite you to explore the forests, meadows, and wetlands. In April, listen for the chorus of American toads and pickerel frogs. Watch for river otters, painted turtles, and great blue herons at various times throughout the year. Climb the drumlin and esker, landscape features created by a glacier 15,000 years ago. Huge rocks and exotic trees and shrubs that were part of a former arboretum provide an adventurous walk along the Rockery Trail.   (FYI - This walk is very flat and EASY).   NOTE: in your reply please RSVP to both the Walk and Late Lunch or just the walk.)  Be sure and bring a water bottle &amp;amp; snack bar.  Cost is $4 fee for the Sanctuary entrance fee or $3 for Seniors.  Please use map quest for directions to the site or email SharonAnderson777@yahoo.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Address of Ipswich Sanctuary is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary -  walk starts at 11am&lt;br /&gt;87 Perkins Row&lt;br /&gt;Topsfield, MA 01983&lt;br /&gt;978-887-9264&lt;br /&gt;ipswichriver@massaudubon.org&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy K</member_name><member_id>3926599</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1176815117000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1176162318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Audubon Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary Walk</name><id>5653715</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1176562800000</time><rsvp_limit>22</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/5653715/</event_url></item>