<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Boston, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>02109-3502</zip><lat>42.360081</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Dewey Square Parks</name><city>Boston</city><id>3740072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.056808</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/170087583089872/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook....&lt;/a&gt; December 15 is Bill of Rights Day and the ACLU of Massachusetts is hosting a protest of the National Defense Authorization Act of 2012. Join us as we try to we appeal to left-leaning independents. We will try to persuade them to see that Ron Paul is the only candidate i...n either party who would preserve our civil liberties. more info on left outreach here: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/bluerepublican" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt; here's the event invite: CAN THE BILL OF RIGHTS SURVIVE 2011? On December 15 the Bill of Rights turns 220 years old. And it has never been more endangered. Both Houses of Congress have voted to authorize the military to indefinitely imprison civilians &amp;#150; including American citizens &amp;#150; without charge or trial, based on suspicion alone. A final vote could take place at any time, gutting fundamental Bill of Rights protections that guarantee due process and a fair trial. Join us to demand that Members of the Massachusetts Congressional delegation oppose the National Defense Authorization Act of 2012 if it contains this dangerous provision &amp;#150; and that President Obama use his veto to defend the Bill of Rights. When: Thursday December 15, 12:15 &amp;#150; 1:30 PM Where: 12:15 &amp;#150; Meet at Dewey Square (near South Station in Boston) 12:30 - March to the JFK Federal Building (Government Center) 1:00 - Rally and Speak Out BRING SIGNS AND BANNERS, A PAN AND A WOODEN SPOON, A WHISTLE OR A DRUM!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323973290000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Blank The Ballot Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot</urlname><id>504022</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Election 2012 -  BLANK THE BALLOT!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323450461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Blue Repub Outreach at Indefinite Military Detention Protest</name><id>43937492</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323968400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Election-2012-Blank-The-Ballot/events/43937492/</event_url></item>