<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Given the rousing success of this past game weekend – 16 people in house with up to four games going at once – I thought I'd do it again on Saturday, June 27 and Sunday, June 28, starting at noon on Saturday and running until 6 pm or so on Sunday. (Admittedly Sunday turnout was minimal, with only three people on hand to game, but we still played a couple of good games.) We have a cot and lots of floor space for anyone interested in sleeping over.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A friend of mine, Lorien Green, has been working on a board game documentary, and she might attend during this weekend to film people while playing, ask them about their interests, and invite speculation on the winner of the 2009 Spiel des Jahres, the German Game of the Year award that will be announced on Monday, June 29. I have four of the five games in house for those who want to play and compare. Lorien's blog: &lt;a href="http://boardgamedoc.blogspot.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://boardgamedoc.b...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seung Chan is interested in holding a Tichu tournament, and failing that, he will play the game with any willing bodies. Yes, I think he's addicted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP with an arrival time if you plan to attend, and feel free to suggest games that you want to play. Hope to see you here!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the host of the house</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric Martin</member_name><member_id>1979558</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249074089000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Concord-NH-Boardgame-Meetup</urlname><id>1400736</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Concord, NH Boardgame Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1245115050000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Game weekend in Concord, June 27-28</name><id>10659683</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246118400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Concord-NH-Boardgame-Meetup/events/10659683/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/8/e/global_7561166.jpeg</photo_url></item>