<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Lansdowne St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.347279</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bill's bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>5302272</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.095016</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you like live music? Do you like puppies?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us as for our fundraiser to benefit the Doggy Fun Run and the Boston Volunteers. Joining Social Fun Group... &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/106563812/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/106563812/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 In our partnership with the Animal Rescue league of Boston the real winners of this celebration will be the dog survivors of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is made possible to you by a generous performance by a local popular band, The Faux Farwell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who is the Faux Farewell:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Faux Farewell is a Boston-based rock band that is quickly gaining attention in Massachusetts. Hailing from Northeastern University, The Faux Farewell features a driving rhythm section, soaring lead vocals,and tight vocal harmonies. The lineup includes Ben Mallare on vocals, Emma Kurman-Faber on keys and vocals, Sam Hanson on drums, Will Baker on guitar, and Jason Smith on bass. After coming together in early 2013, the Rock/Pop quintet has performed both contemporary covers and original compositions written largely by lead vocalist Ben Mallare. After a debut show at Northeastern AfterHOURS that received fantastic support, the band is gearing up for multiple performances in the Massachusetts area over the next few months. Additionally, the members are working on an original album that will be released later this year. The Faux Farewell is ready to “say hello” to the Boston music scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about The Faux Farewell: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/TheFauxFarewell" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/TheFauxFarewell&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn more about their newest music: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/thefauxfarewell" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/thefauxfarewell&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 This event is a $15 cover. Because the club is small, there are a limited about of tickets. This benefit is also a popular Facebook event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the proceeds will benefit the Doggy Fun Run and the Boston Volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We just got permission from the Mayor today for our Doggy Fun Run. &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn more: What is the Doggy Fun Run (not yet announced)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Bonus for you: Bring four or more friends with you and YOU get in for FREE. Must RSVP +4 (or more) and simply show up together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Live music. Good times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't miss this popular benefit! :) &lt;br /&gt;

 Josh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Boston Volunteers &lt;br /&gt;

 Big enough to deliver, small enough to care &lt;br /&gt;

 Learn more: www.BostonVolunteer.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Casey Dinneen</member_name><member_id>71254452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364513901000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364223262000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Live Music to help Homeless Dogs of Boston</name><id>110942762</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364504400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/110942762/</event_url></item>