<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1525 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.955864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-666-3688</phone><name>The Great Buffet</name><city>Manchester</city><id>435491</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.435875</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is our second monthly video screening in Manchester. We'll have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; &lt;b&gt;2nd Tuesday-Manchester&lt;/b&gt;; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesday-Plymouth. If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, maybe we'll have a Truth Party somewhere!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;When we first started the Merrimack Valley 911 Truth group, our first act was to host Michael Berger (in Concord) to a showing of his new film, Improbable Collapse. We've decided to show it again after almost 2 years to our Manchester viewing crowd. His video talks about the 3 different government reports about the collapses of the WTC towers and touches on the WTC 7 tower. His video contains some footage of the WTC7 rubble that has not been seen anywhere else, since it was shot clandestinely by someone who was in that secured area with a video camera rolled up in a newspaper under his arm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A great and engaging video. If we have time, we'll show a couple of shorts, as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-------------------------&lt;br /&gt;We'll also go over how each attender can become more involved and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll have free DVD's and DVD's and books for sale. Everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We've developed a collection of books for sale at these various meetings. We hope that each of you will be able to donate $5 to help us build our collection of supplies, but please come anyway if you cannot afford that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Please arrive at 6:30 if you can, in order to get your dinner and beverages from Tom's fine buffet, sushi bar and stir fry bar. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and then on to the video showings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is plentiful in the lot out in front of the Great Buffet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &lt;a href="http://mv911t.erideshare.com" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online at eRideShare.com&lt;/a&gt;. Carpooling arrangements can now be made by clicking on the link above to go to the online ridesharing group. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, donations for the ride-sharing are appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You'll see me fiddling with the TV and DVD player</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218753492000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218404060000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Manchester - Improbable Collapse; The Demolition of Our Republic</name><id>8516820</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218580200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/8516820/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/f/0/global_5105360.jpeg</photo_url></item>