<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>corner of Sargent Ave and Manchester St.</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.771756</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Volleyball area</name><city>Nashua</city><id>984819</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.470365</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Wimp Volleyball under lights&lt;br /&gt;Wedensday, Sept. 29th., 6:00. or any time before to 8 pm. &lt;br /&gt;At the lighted tennis courts on &lt;br /&gt;Sargent Ave between &lt;br /&gt;101a Amhurst St. and Manchester St. &lt;br /&gt;Nashua NH. 03061 &lt;br /&gt;Nashua Parks &amp;amp; Rec. permit #19606 &lt;br /&gt;Steve O. ob@tds.net 603-491-1962&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF IT RAINS OR SNOWS THIS EVENT IS CANCELED. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      We will be asking for a $1.00 donation to help play for the equipment. But please remember, your attendance is more important than the your money. We would rather you play than pay. The money is only to help pay for the Group expenses and maintain the equipment. Thank you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;       Please join Steve O. and friends at anytime for evening of fun and easy exercise, or just come to watch. Wimp Volleyball is a noncompetitive games. Totally for the fun of moving around trying to hit and return the ball. We will be following the rules. But, having fun and learning, will be more important than winning. We count the laughs, not the score. We work on keeping the volley going. Rather than trying to end it. The winners are those who sides hurt from laughing to much. We usually have a larger number attending. So, we will rotate everyone through. If we have enough of those people who must win, and play exactly to the rules. We will have another net to set up for them. So, bring your friends and kids, an your drinks to keep cool and hydrated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will also have another event going at the same time, Wimp Volleyball Chatting &amp;amp; Cheerleading. This event requires a lawn chair and the ability to chat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warning: You are responsible for anything you bring to an event. The Organizer and the Ass. Organizers are not responsible for danage or loss of your things.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call us at anytime 603-491-1962</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285801975000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285260397000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wimp Volleyball under Lights!</name><id>14871423</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285797600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/14871423/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/c/global_18179964.jpeg</photo_url></item>