<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is the 1st of 2 meetups this month (the other will be Tuesday Jan 22 in Portland (still deciding between 2 topics for that one...).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter &amp;amp; Michael have generously offered to host the group at their home and open up their DVD library for a viewing of the film &lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;What a Way to Go: Life at the End of Empire&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt; which is sure to inspire discussion and, hopefully, energy toward action.  The film features interviews with Daniel Quinn, Derrick Jensen, Jerry Mander, Richard Heinberg, William Catton, Paul Roberts, Chellis Glendinning, Thomas Berry, Richard Manning and Ran Prieur.  It looks head on at our present global predicament, as oil depletion, climate change, species extinction and population overshoot converge in a ?perfect storm? of cataclysmic dimensions.    &lt;a href="http://www.whatawaytogomovie.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.whatawayto...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/b&gt;:  See detailed directions from Winter below and/or use the mapping link that meetup.com provides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CARPOOLING&lt;/b&gt;:  It's about 30 minutes to Michael &amp;amp; Winter's place.  If you wish to carpool, PLEASE POST a message in carpool message thread on our message boards, including a contact phone number so you can coordinate with others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;POTLUCK&lt;/b&gt; Supper to start, as always!  Potluck 6:30 to 7:00 or 7:15 followed by the film promptly at 7:15pm.  Discussion to follow (or at least the start of it) with additional discussion if needed during the potluck portion of our January 22 meetup in Portland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Potluck breakdown: &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with A-G main or side dish to share&lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with H-M bring salad or veg or dessert &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with N-S bread or beverage &lt;br /&gt;Last name starting with T-Z bring whatever you want&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don't forget to bring your own potluck kit of plate/bowl/cup/utensils/cloth napkin - we're trying to move away from disposable or even compostable stuff!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Directions from Winter:&lt;br /&gt;149 Simpson Road, &lt;br /&gt;Buxton, Maine 207.929.6960&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From South (or North on turnpike):&lt;br /&gt;Maine Turnpike  North to Exit 36 (Saco/Old Orchard Beach)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take first off-ramp to Industrial Park Road&lt;br /&gt;Left on Industrial Park Road (follow signs to Rt. 112)  Right at stop light (from this point, travel 3.7 miles to Simpson Road on your left.  3.7 miles (no mistake) to 149 Simpson Road.  Our driveway will be on your left, mailbox with 149 on your right.  (There is a large green telephone on the telephone pole over the mailbox.)  Note: you will be traveling through two towns, do not follow mailbox numbers...they can be very misleading.  Follow mileage.  Our home is a cedar cape that sits back in the woods.  There may be a white goose and/or chickens in the yard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alternative route from Portland:&lt;br /&gt;Congress street extended to Rt. 22 past O'donals nursery.  Follow 22 for about 15 minutes until Rt.22 veers right at a 3-way stop.  There is a white church on one corner and a home on the other. Go straight.  At the stop light, Route 202, turn left.  Go about 2.3 miles to Rt.117, there is a blinking light here and you will be at a bridge that crosses the Saco River.  Do not cross the river.  Turn left on 117.  Go .3  miles to Simpson Road.  Right on Simpson Road for .7 miles.  Our driveway will be on the right and the mailbox on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cell phones do not work well out here. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1200008039000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Come together with like-minded people to learn more about what we are facing as a community/planet and re-energize your commitment to becoming part of the solution in 2008.</why><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1194466515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>1st of 2 January Meetups:  "What a Way to Go" Film &amp; Discussion</name><id>6696600</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199835000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/6696600/</event_url></item>