<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a VISIT (not participating till a later day) to the pool where the ACA and ConnYak members (others invited also) do a lot of their practicing for the up-coming season. They know that if you want to learn to save yourself, it isnt a good idea to be learning when your mouth is full of water and a shark is biting your.... ok you get the message. Just observing for a few minutes gives you an idea of what its supposed to help you accomplish. I like meeting the people of these organizations and as the season starts to go kayaking with them also. Another benifit for me is to have not only me to save you (i might be distracted by a blondie on the beach (or another kayak)waving a bathing suite) but someone closer to you that can be like a hand fom God is to your benifit. I think recreation kayaks are like toys and no enough people knowing the dangers, especially if i have an event in an area with currents or shore line areas with difficult shores to reach might be a real adventure.&lt;br /&gt;The ConnYak session is from 9am to 1 pm in Wallingford&lt;br /&gt;The ACA session is from 2pm to 4pm in Kiingworth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Charlies hike is pretty good, not sure if im going yet.&lt;br /&gt;There is enough time after to just stop at Wallingford to observe and meet the folks..or hike a simple pace in Wallingford/Meriden area later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If its the one in Killingworth, observe, meet...and can walk in a few parks near there( Seven falls/other Haddam places...)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now i need some feedback on your interests or i will just go to the closest one to me and meet the Yakers there.&lt;br /&gt;in the near future i will schedule another event when i actually bring my yaks and enjoy my own learning along with a few of you interested future experts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting there and more info:&lt;br /&gt;See ConnYak website&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.connyak.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.connyak.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look at the calendar of events tab and look at the specific events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh i forgot... Im planning to link with a lot of AMC events also as the new season starts. They and the others require you to know how get back in from out in the deep water. I am supposed to also have forms for my own liability reasons here on meetup, but im really poor so i never have anyone sign libality relases, dont need to, thats how i feed and fatten up the sharks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1168360319000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1167762978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pool Practice Observation</name><id>5359080</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1168187400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5359080/</event_url></item>