<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>2589 N. River Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03106</zip><lat>43.041414</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(800) 668-1249</phone><name>Southern New Hampshire University</name><city>Manchester</city><id>1088085</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.451606</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The June 24 meeting of the Manchester Adobe User Group will feature a presentation on Adobe’s Lightroom by Kent Messamore.  Lightroom is a software program released by Adobe in Feb. 2007.  It was a complete departure from Adobe’s Photoshop and was designed specifically for Photographers.  Photoshop is an image editor while Lightroom is an image database.  Lightroom has modules for asset management (the Library), image development, Slide Shows, Printing, and Web creation.  Lightroom is not a replacement for Photoshop.  It integrates with Photoshop very well.  The current release of Lightroom is 2.7.  Lightroom 3 beta is available for free download and the production version is expected to be released in June or July.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Kent:&lt;br /&gt;Kent Messamore has been a member of the Manchester Adobe User Group since its inception.  He is retired from 44 years in the computer service industry.  Photography is primarily a hobby but Kent has been successful in local camera club, Regional (NECCC), and in international (Greater Lynn), photo competitions. He is a member of the Manchester Camera Club and the RiversEdge Photographic Society.  He has worked with Adobe Photoshop since its inception in Feb. 1990 and has a high skill level in its use.  He teaches Digital Photography at Manchester Community College and Photoshop, Lightroom, and Studio Lighting classes for camera clubs, local Photographic studios, and does tutoring commercially.  His forte is enhancing photographs to increase their impact and restoration of old photographs (thus the name of his company - &amp;quot;Enhanced Images&amp;quot;).  He prints his images on an Epson 2400 Printer using fine art papers and does his own matting and framing.  His primary interest is black and white prints.  He administers two Web sites, his own (&lt;a href="http://www.kmessamore.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.kmessamore...&lt;/a&gt;) and the Manchester Camera Club (&lt;a href="http://www.manchestercameraclub.org)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.manchester...&lt;/a&gt;.  If you are interested in viewing Kent's images go to &lt;a href="http://www.Enhanced-Images.biz" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.Enhanced-I...&lt;/a&gt;.  Recently he acquired the Adobe Master Suite with plans to expand into video with Premier Pro.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Webster Hall Room 106, check in lobby for the meeting sign to verify</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Penny Savage</member_name><member_id>10532962</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279977580000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ManchesterAUG</urlname><id>1532602</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>Manchester Adobe User Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1275921218000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>June Manchester Adobe User Group Meeting</name><id>13723636</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1276812000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ManchesterAUG/events/13723636/</event_url></item>