<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>South End, Boston</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.339375</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Carlton Park</name><city>Boston</city><id>589197</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.075810</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Carlton Court Dog Park, South End&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description: Carleton court dog park in the south end is an excellent  dog park. It's fenced in and right on the southwest corridor. There are refuse bags available, you can bring toys and there's a mulch elimination area. Its a great park, there are usually at least a few other dogs enjoying the space, please keep in mind there may be a few larger breeds there when we meet...it is a public space so I can not ask them to leave!!!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The park is located at the intersection of Carlton and Holyoke Street at the Southwest Corridor.&lt;br /&gt; There is typical visitor parking located on the corners of the streets in and around the south end.&lt;br /&gt; Holyoke, Braddock Park street and as well as plenty of meters on Columbus Ave..... Also, a extremely short walk from the Green line, Pru or Copley stop as well as back bay station! If you can take mass transit it's the best choice. The 39 and 55 bus also have stops at the Pru.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of the neighborhood regulars  will be there early in the morning and after 5 pm. &lt;br /&gt;Hopefully, 1-3pm we will have the place to ourselves! I would like to test this out to see if we can meet here this summer as our &amp;quot;outdoor location meeting spot&amp;quot; I know many people wanted to to let their animals go off leash in the common but this is no longer allowed, so if this works. Perhaps, Carlton court will be a great alternative!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212426295000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209139379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup at Carlton Court Park, South End</name><id>7810777</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212253200000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/7810777/</event_url></item>