<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>some of you may want to check this talk out. most of us are strongly opinionated when it comes to issues that pertain to foreign policy and economic policy. this is a fact. how many of us want to become more comfortable when speaking in public. try researching the event speakers history to see if you find something you disagree or agree with them on then try creating a relevant dialogue. anyone want to experiment video taping these interactions so you can find out how to make great youtube videos? this is a great opportunity to see how to best get your point across to a crowd. soon enough when the school year starts back up again we will have numerous opportunities at public forums and lectures. we need to document our questioning and confrontation of the stale logic of the mainstream train of thought. the question i pose is who wants to get involved? if you want to become more confident when attempting to convey a message this may be a perfect venue to attend as a confidence building trial run. i may not attend if people dont reach out to me or take matters into their own hands. research the various youtube videos &amp;quot;We Are Change&amp;quot; chapters have made for ideas and inspiration. the We Are Change Boston youtube channel is here: &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/WeAreChangeBoston/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt; please subscribe comment and add us as a friend to help spread the word. if anyone has ideas for events lectures confrontations or anything else please share. help put the We in We Are Change! -mark 617 652 0121 -------------------------------------- THE COMMUNITY CHURCH OF BOSTON SUMMER SPEAKERS &amp;amp; COMMUNITY DISCUSSION SERIES: &amp;quot;Capitalism, Imperialism &amp;amp; the Current Global Crisis: Theory vs. Reality!&amp;quot; On August 28th, CCB will be hosting the FINAL event in a summer series of weekly topical discussions. We will gather at 11:30am, to share brunch. The speakers will begin presenting on our chosen topic of interest at 12:15pm. Q &amp;amp; A and community discussion will follow. CCB members, friends, and anyone interested, are welcome to all of these summer events. Our final topic in this weekly summer series will be on &amp;quot;CAPITALISM, IMPERIALISM, &amp;amp; THE CURRENT ECONOMIC CRISIS - THEORY VS. REALITY!&amp;quot; Our presenters are Mary Lynn Cramer and John Macleod. Mary Lynn has published several articles and editorials related to the subject to be addressed. She has degrees in the history of economic thought and clinical social work, as well as over two decades of experience as a bilingual clinical social worker. In the 1960's, while participating in organizing and initiating of the nation's first Women's Studies Program, at SDSU, she also published articles on Women and Economics. For the past 6 years, she has been deeply involved in &amp;quot;economic field research&amp;quot; among elderly women and men dependent upon social security, Medicare and food stamps, living in subsidized housing projects. Her most recent writings can be found in on-line journals such as Countercurrents, Counterpunch, Axis of Logic, and DissidentVoice. Mary Lynn will kick off our discussion with a look at the economic ideology and myths (i.e., theory) that leave so many of us confused and frustrated as we attempt to understand the causes and solutions to repeated economic crises. For a sneak preview of her perspective, you can find one of her recent articles linked to the CCB website below (&amp;quot;The Limits of Liberal Rhetoric; Profits vs. Jobs&amp;quot;). John MacLeod is an activist with an Abolitionist perspective, and a member of Community Church of Boston, the Park Street Committee for Peace and Human Rights, and other groups. John states that his first political activism was anti-capitalist, and in opposition to Euro-US weaponized diplomacy. John will address the &amp;quot;reality&amp;quot; aspect of today's topic. He has found some inspiration for today's presentation in the words of Frantz Fanon's Wretched of the Earth: &amp;quot;Two centuries ago, a former European colony decided to catch up with Europe. It succeeded so well that the United States of America became a monster, in which the taints, the sickness and the inhumanity of Europe have grown to appalling dimensions.&amp;quot; (If you would like to read the entire Chapter 6 from which the above is quoted, you can find it on-line at &lt;a href="http://www.marxists.org/subject/africa/fanon/conclusion.htm)" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.marxists.o...&lt;/a&gt;. Please bring a wholesome, nutritious, savory something to contribute to our brunch table. Coffee, tea &amp;amp; juice will be provided! ========== DIRECTIONS/PARKING The Community Church is located at 565 Boylston Street in Copley Square, between Dartmouth and Clarendon Streets. Parking is available on Sunday mornings at the Back Bay Garage (entrances on Clarendon Street or St. James Ave.). We do not provide a sticker for discounted parking during the summer series; therefore, you would have to pay the regular fee (around $20 for three hours). However, public transportation is dependable and you can take the Green line to Copley or take the Orangeline to Back Bay station. Community Church is a 2-minute walk from either station. ========== A PEACE AND JUSTICE CONGREGATION SINCE 1920 The Community Church of Boston is a free community united for the study and practice of universal religion, seeking to apply ethical ideals to individual life and the democratic and cooperative principle to all forms of social and economic life. ========== FOR MORE INFORMATION, PLEASE CONTACT US: Community Church of Boston 565 Boylston Street Boston, MA 02116 (617) 266-6710 info@commchurch.org www.communitychurchofboston.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314552623000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314320434000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>8/28 *Read Details* Capitalism Imperialism &amp; the Current Global Crisis.</name><id>30970851</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314548100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/30970851/</event_url></item>