<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>265 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.361805</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-253-5927 </phone><name>MIT Museum </name><city>Cambridge</city><id>777893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.097664</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This lecture is from this year's Fall Series at the MIT&amp;nbsp; Museum: "Life in the Universe: Are We Alone?". Tues. 10/25, Wed. 11/9, Tues. 11/15, Tues. 11/29.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: Life in the Universe: Are We Alone? Part&amp;nbsp;4 of 4: Finding Intellegence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: 6:00 pm to 7:30 pm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: MIT Museum&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Free&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the lecture, from the MIT Museum site:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2011/alone.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2011/alone.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"The search for intelligence in the universe is among the most controversial endeavors in astrobiology. Do we even know what we are looking for? To better understand what 'they' might be like, we need to know what is meant by 'intelligence.' &lt;a href="http://www.iq.harvard.edu/people/richard_wrangham"&gt;Richard Wrangham&lt;/a&gt;, Harvard Professor of Biological Anthropology and author of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Catching-Fire-Cooking-Made-Human/dp/0465020410/ref=sr_1_sc_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1318376335&amp;amp;sr=8-1-spell"&gt;Catching Fire: How Cooking Made Us Human&lt;/a&gt;, is renowned for his lucid explanations of the evolutionary origin of humanity, so he will help us explore what it means for animals to evolve intelligence, and how common this event is in the universe. &lt;a href="http://www.physics.harvard.edu/people/facpages/horowitz.html"&gt;Paul Horowitz&lt;/a&gt;, Harvard Professor of Physics and Electrical Engineering, is the Principal Investigator in Harvard's SETI (Search for Extra-Terrestrial Intelligence) program and an expert in custom instrumentation (such as a 3-beam, 250- million-channel radiofrequency Fourier spectrum analyzer performing an all-sky transit survey at the university's 84-foot radio telescope (!)). Professor Horowitz joins the final session of the series to talk about what it takes to search for intelligent civilizations in outer space, looking for, or at, human life on planet Earth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;T.J. Maher will be waiting inside the MIT Museum starting at 5:40 pm. He is guessing that they will have round tables set up that five or six people can sit around. He will be attempting to grab a few and save them for the group. If he can manage to save a block of seats, look for the red MEETUP sign table tents. The area is so small, the MIT Museum staff frowns on him saving too many tables for Nerd Fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a "Hello My Name is T.J." nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;After the lecture, let's grab dinner so we can talk about the lecture. T.J. will be holding up a large red MEETUP sign outside the Museum after the lecture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About this year's theme: "Life in the Universe: Are We Alone?"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2011/alone.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/museum/about/pr/2011/alone.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Are We Alone? That question has perplexed humanity for centuries. Perhaps scientists are getting closer to the answer; come find out during four evenings of discussion as biologists, astronomers, chemists and anthropologists talk and share their insights with you as they explain some of their latest research about life on other planets, as well as on our own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Moderated by MIT Museum Director, John Durant, and Museum Education Coordinator Erika Reinfeld, this special evening series will give audiences both a historical overview and insight into current research about the search for life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;" 'Is it really the case that we are the only place where there is life?' asks John Durant. 'The debate has taken place for centuries, and it's intriguing that we don't know the answer.' Join Harvard and MIT Professors for 4 evenings beginning at 6:00 p.m. for this series about the origins of life; meet top scientists in their fields, and leave with a deeper understanding about what it means to be human. All discussions take place at the MIT Museum, 265 Massachusetts Ave. Cambridge, MA 02139".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to the MIT Museum:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/museum/visit/directions.html"&gt;http://web.mit.edu/museum/visit/directions.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"The MIT Museum is located near the north shore of the Charles River Basin in Cambridge, MA, a few blocks from the central part of the MIT campus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"The MIT Museum is accessible via public transportation, and is within three miles of two major interstate highways. The Museum is approximately a 30 minute walk from downtown Boston or from Harvard Square.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"Take the Red Line to either Central Square Station (a 10 minute walk to the Museum) or Kendall Square/MIT Station (a 15 minute walk to the Museum).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;"From Central Square: Walk down Mass. Ave. toward Boston and the main MIT campus. The Museum is on the left at the corner of Front St".&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>13</waitlist_count><updated>1322781690000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319121895000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Life in the Universe: Are We Alone? Finding Intellegence @ MIT Museum</name><id>38088782</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322607600000</time><rsvp_limit>36</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/38088782/</event_url></item>