<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Guest fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person per night</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Here are the details  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday Jan 18 - Arrive at Wedeln  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Jan 19 - Come join us skiing or riding at Wildcat (our personal favorite)! Or you can try any of the other 5 mountains close by Cranmore (5 min), Attitash (15 min), Black (15 min), Bretton Woods (45 min), Sunday River (60 min). Join us for apres-ski activities  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday Jan 20 - Most of us will do more skiing and riding!  If you want a change of pace, you can x-country ski in the beautiful New England village of Jackson, NH. (15 min). Join us for apres-ski activities  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday Jan 21 - Maybe get a final run in the AM, then get some outlet shopping done before you head home!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you plan to attend, please rsvp here and you must e-mail me at membership@wedeln.com by Tuesday, January 15 at 11 PM.  Please include your full name, the names of your guests, your actual e-mail address, and cell phone number so I can get back to you. &lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For dining options, none are currently offered, but that may change as we get closer to the event. You can always bring food and drink and use our great communal kitchen.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All social events are optional but encouraged. Details will be sent after you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions, issues, or concerns by sending me an e-mail at membership@wedeln.com. With all inquiries, please include your full name, actual e-mail address, and cell phone number so I can get back to you.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regards,  &lt;br /&gt;Jonathan  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;membership@wedeln.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BTW - If you are new to skiing and snowboarding, we want you to come join us!  All of the mountains have great learn to ski or ride programs with rentals included.  Or if its been a while, come rent the latest equipment and take a lesson. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4353463</member_name><member_id>4353463</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tara</member_name><member_id>4521773</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>5121941</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie Ochse</member_name><member_id>5135141</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Audra</member_name><member_id>5480374</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201027731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><why>Our guest fee is only$20 per person per night. We would love to see you come up and join us out on the mountain for a weekend of skiing or riding and then joining us afterward for some apres-ski activities.</why><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199793309000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MLK Jr. weekend at Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name><id>7061574</id><headcount>40</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200708000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/7061574/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/f/e/global_2109326.jpeg</photo_url></item>