<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/a/a/4/event_87375012.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This month is all about the number two and we are going to get in on it with some one-on-one action. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to prove to your significant other who the better half is? Want to show your best friend who's boss? &amp;nbsp;Want to finally take down your personal gaming rival? &amp;nbsp;Well come join us as we have a day specifically for &lt;strong&gt;2-player games&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;This will be a daytime event in case things start to heat up and people want to leave at night for a private gaming session. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your favorite game designed specifically for 2 players only and/or come see what others have brought so we can showcase some of the best games you can use to face off against another person. &amp;nbsp;This is an all genre event which means we will be featuring 2 players games that fall under any category (card, strategy, word, etc.) so come prepared to play anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Important note:&lt;/span&gt; You don't have to be part of a "pair" to sign up. &amp;nbsp;All are welcome. &amp;nbsp;And in fact, the rule for today is that if you come as a pair, you won't be allowed to play with each other. &amp;nbsp;Gotta try new experiences. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mini-Meetup&lt;/strong&gt;. Anyone can sign up, but I would please ask that you&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;allow new or previously inactive members get a slot if they are on the waiting list since there is limited seating. &amp;nbsp;Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;See this&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/messages/boards/thread/9907478"&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food theme:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme for this event will be "things that just go together". &amp;nbsp;Please bring a food item to share with the group that fits that theme. &amp;nbsp;Interpret that however you want, for example, strawberries and chocolate, chips and salsa, peanut butter and jelly etc.. &amp;nbsp;I will try to have also generic, healthy snacks on hand for all diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;

 This event will be hosted at a private residence,&amp;nbsp;conveniently&amp;nbsp;located at the intersections of Route 1 and Route 95. &amp;nbsp;If you need directions, just ask. &amp;nbsp;This is a housing complex, so please do NOT park in any numbered spaces. &amp;nbsp;There are no animals on the premises and the property should be child-friendly. &amp;nbsp;Look for Unit 901 since Meetup doesn't display addresses correctly! :-(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Unit 901</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ryan</member_name><member_id>8995629</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1329157353000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327172564000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mini-Meetup: Face-off</name><id>49045172</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328986800000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/49045172/</event_url></item>