<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>cross street Center between Chapel and Crown</address_2><address_1>76 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304688</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> (203) 562-2511</phone><name>Bentara</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1077533</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.924828</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello - So when I originally decided to do the Christmas Eve happy hour, people warned me that no place would be open.  Pshaw! Said I - who closes then?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Um... everyone :) (I'm so used to NYC lol) After calling a bunch of restaurants this week, I felt about as rejected as a lonely tin of anchovies on the supermarket shelf.  I had asked around for suggestions after this process, and the places that people suggested were all closed, or they didn't pick up the phone (grrr).  (So, attentive members who made suggestions.... that's why I didn't choose your location lol)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, originally I had decided that I had to do either a really Christmasy thing, or a completely secular (possibly oriental-themed) thing.  So.... I've decided on Malaysian! Bentara is a delicious Malaysian restaurant with an impressive wine list.  I think it will be just the relaxed, classy thing everyone might need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bentara.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bentara.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Devorah is your contact 203-314-4329&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Based on good suggestions, I've made the time earlier than usual (5pm - when Bentara's opens) so that people can go on to family events, if they so choose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be there until 6.  If anyone wants to be the contact after that, let me know :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, stay late... nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hour, not even Christmas Eve!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah</member_name><member_id>3741637</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198770120000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198206667000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>12/24 Monday Happy Hour - Bentara</name><id>6947953</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1198533600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6947953/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/8/c/global_351724.jpeg</photo_url></item>