<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Living As Monks For God In The World of The Senses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a seminar with Mother Clare Watts&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, November 13 • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jesus said that the path to life is narrow and there are few who walk it. In the past, those who have walked it have been called monks or monastics and have lived secluded lives. Well, it is now a new age and a new millennia and the Order of Christ/Sophia has the way for individuals wanting a life of devotion and love for God, while being in the world, but not of it. Communities now exist in fifteen Centers of Light around the country where young and old as well as those raising families and single live the experience of a devoted and communal life. In this age of decadence, there is still a way back to innocence, and the Order of Christ/Sophia has found the way. Come and spend the evening with co-founder Mother Clare Watts, who spent years in yoga ashrams and Sufi schools, searching for the most direct path to God and found it in Christianity. Undoubtedly, you will be amazed!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We're just around the corner from the Stony Brook T-stop on the orange line.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226795725000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Mystics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spiritual-mystic</urlname><id>302540</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Spirituality &amp; Mysticism Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223568102000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: Living As Monks For God In The World of The Senses</name><id>8930420</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1226622600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spiritual-mystic/events/8930420/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/7/global_5804807.jpeg</photo_url></item>