<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;DO NOT FORGET TO WEAR A BRIGHT ORANGE HAT - IT IS HUNTING SEASON! Those bright orange gloves would be nice if you happen to have some but a hat is probably the most visible item and essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will venture to the East [3620'] and Middle [3480'+] peaks of Scar Ridge on this trip. The start is a hike on the East Pond Trail of approx 2.5 miles, followed by the main event. It is worth mentioning that the West peak [3774'] is the one on the AMC list but we will NOT be climbing that on this trip.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please understand these types of trips are not hand holding excursions. You are expected to be ready to rise to the challenge of bushwhacking. If you don't know too much about navigation, that's fine all you have to do is follow, but the way through is rarely easy .. or even visible. &amp;nbsp;:-) The distance covered off trail is slow, demanding, and intense.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not attempt to list milage or times as these rough estimates and of little use. Just expect to be out all day - the raw milage is nothing that a seasoned hiker should be concerned about. If you have any questions please contact me via email to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing and Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the minimum required clothing and equipment to participate in this event. DO NOT rely on others to have extra clothing or equipment to share with you once we are out on the trails. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Footwear&lt;/span&gt;: Insulated boots, this is a requirement due to snow/ moisture. You will get wet feet on this bushwhack. Gaitors very highly recommended. Some form of light traction (e.g. MICROspikes) is required. We probably won't need snow shoes yet, but we will reassess before the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clothing&lt;/span&gt;: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring insulating layers such as a fleece jacket/wool sweater. Warm hat and gloves. ABSOLUTELY NO COTTON&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Outerwear&lt;/span&gt;: Waterproof/windproof rain shell with hood and shell pants. We will be very up close and personal with the trees so you need something to stay dry but be advised clothing takes a beating on these trips!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Food and Water&lt;/span&gt;: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/span&gt;: Hat, 2 pairs of gloves, handwarmers. Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it before the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;******&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will find you</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew B</member_name><member_id>4803051</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321317609000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1319682064000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Scar Ridge East/Middle   NH100 bushwhack</name><id>38880052</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1321102800000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/38880052/</event_url></item>