<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>906 Washington St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02184</zip><lat>42.202822</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 848-1151</phone><name>Sintra Restaurant</name><city>Braintree</city><id>1182910</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.005078</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join SSDOMG Members, Former Members, and Guests as we celebrate 5 years of South Shore Meetups and the SSDOMG's 5th Anniversary!&amp;nbsp; This will be a fun event you do not want to miss.&amp;nbsp; We will be dining at Sintra in South Braintree Square and order off the regular menu.&amp;nbsp; We will be seated at 2 tables with equal seating.&amp;nbsp; (Please note the previous two items have been updated as of Sunday morning.)&amp;nbsp; As is our Anniversary Dinner custom, the Organizer Team will pay for one appetizer for each table from the Event Fees you have been paying throughout the year.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a fun night for all to share in the SSDOMG's 5th Anniversary as we continue our summer celebration of 5 years of South Shore meetups.&amp;nbsp; So, catch-up with old friends, make new friends, enjoy dinner at a fantastic South Shore restaurant in Braintree and enjoy the night out with your SSDOMG friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SSDOMG 5th Anniversary Dinner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday, August 18th @ 7pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sintra Restaurant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;906 Washington Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;781-848-1151&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href="http://www.sintrarestaurant.com"&gt;www.sintrarestaurant.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Meeting Place&lt;/em&gt;: Our tables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Please Note&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. We&amp;nbsp;will be separated into two tables of fairly equal numbers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Each table will receive their own bill.&amp;nbsp; It will not be broken down individually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. One free appetizer per table will not appear on the table's bill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. A 20% gratuity will be applied to the bill.&amp;nbsp; Plan to pay 126.25% of your food and drink total which is a 20% gratuity plus 6.25% tax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. We will have&amp;nbsp;one dedicated server depending on the size of our Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Organizers&lt;/em&gt;: Angela and the SSDOMG Organizer Team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Event Fee&lt;/em&gt;: FREE for ALL ATTENDEES.&amp;nbsp; $5 to become a 2011 Annual Member ($1 savings) TONIGHT ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: No minimum. There is a maximum of&amp;nbsp;16 people *as of Tues 8/16 @ 6:30pm.*&amp;nbsp; One caveat: Whatever the number of Yes RSVPs is as of 8/12 is the minimum we need to have in attendance in order to guarantee our seating area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;:&amp;nbsp;One per member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;RSVP Deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 6pm on Tuesday, August 16th as we have to call in our final RSVP count that evening. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer prior to the event and will be considered No-Shows unless you email Angela directly with a valid excuse.&amp;nbsp; *No new RSVPs will be allowed after 6pm on Wednesday night.**&amp;nbsp; 6pm on Wednesday is the FINAL RSVP DEADLINE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the bill including drinks, food, shared food, tax, and tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Directions&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sintra is located on 
&lt;strong&gt;Washington Street&lt;/strong&gt; in 
&lt;strong&gt;South Braintree Square&lt;/strong&gt;; quite close to Exit 17 off Route 3 and an easy drive for most of our members. We are providing directions from Route 3 in order to guide members who may be coming from a distance and also because the Union Street Rotary is a well known local reference point.&amp;nbsp; These are also great walking directions from the T.&amp;nbsp; (Total distance from the Rotary is just under 1.5 miles, if that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;From Route 3:&lt;/strong&gt; Take 
&lt;strong&gt;Exit 17 (Union St)&lt;/strong&gt;. This is the Union St. Rotary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take the 
&lt;strong&gt;Union St/South Braintree/Brain 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; tree exit from the rotary. This will bring you immediately to the traffic light at Ivory St. (The entrance to The Marketplace at Braintree, where Borders and Big K are located, will be on your right.) Go 
&lt;strong&gt;straight&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; through this light keeping the T on your left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next light is the intersection of Union St. And Washington St. Turn 
&lt;strong&gt;left&lt;/strong&gt; onto 
&lt;strong&gt;Washington Street&lt;/strong&gt; (as you can only go left or right) 
&lt;img src="http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/clear.gif" width="0" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go 
&lt;strong&gt;straight through&lt;/strong&gt; the 
&lt;strong&gt;next two lights&lt;/strong&gt; (Central Ave. and JFK Memorial Dr.) keeping the Fire Station and Thayer Public Library on your left and Town Hall on your right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will shortly pass St Francis of Assisi Church on your left, then immediately see a 
&lt;strong&gt;CVS on your left&lt;/strong&gt;. The CVS is on the near corner of Holbrook Ave. Turn 
&lt;strong&gt;left&lt;/strong&gt; onto 
&lt;strong&gt;Holbrook Ave.&lt;/strong&gt;, then immediately turn 
&lt;strong&gt;right&lt;/strong&gt; into the 
&lt;strong&gt;parking lot behind Sintra&lt;/strong&gt;, which is shared with Giovanna's Salon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sintra has a rear entrance that opens onto this parking area, or you can walk around to the front and enter from Washington St.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the loft upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison </member_name><member_id>9429931</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315669081000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308364637000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SSDOMG 5th Anniversary Dinner Celebration</name><id>22624091</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1313708400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/22624091/</event_url></item>