<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello, my name is Dale Massicotte. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This note is for everyone who has signed up for the Russian Language Meetup group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Anderson (a.k.a. Buck) is the Meetup organizer, and he has missed the past couple of meetings as he is temporarily living away from Connecticut.  In his absence he has made me an assistant organizer for the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am no expert on Russia or the Russian language, but I have a strong desire to learn all I can.  People join the Russian Meetup group for different reasons.  In my case, it was to expand my Russian speaking ability.  What’s yours? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I have recently decided to donate some resources online in order to help others who are attempting the same goal ... to expand their Russian language speaking ability!   You have to see and experience it to believe it.  The web site is a work-in-progress that is up and running, but will continue to be built on and enhanced over time.  This online reference (exclusive only to Hartford Russian Meetup members) will soon be password protected and only accessible by verified username and password. The web site even offers English to Russian speakers!  How’s that for savvy?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: firebrick"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The purpose of the group is to get acquainted, speak some Russian, learn about Russian culture, but most importantly – to have fun. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So come to the meeting and find out how to access this invaluable resource.  Hope to see all of you on Tuesday evening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dale &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS. &lt;br /&gt;Andrew's email is anderson06143@yahoo.com &lt;br /&gt;Dale's email is dmassicotte@premierexpress.net &lt;br /&gt;The website for the Wood-n-Tap is www.woodntap.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andrew Anderson</member_name><member_id>1738935</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dale Massicotte</member_name><member_id>5951349</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242169595000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Russian Speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordrussianmeetup</urlname><id>723352</id><group_lat>41.7900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>The Hartford Russian Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236730431000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Russian Language April Meetup</name><id>9927185</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239750000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordrussianmeetup/events/9927185/</event_url></item>