<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Again, from the polls, the next read is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blind Woman, Sweeping Willow by Haruki Murakami&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from: &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?isbn=9781400096084" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Publisher Comments:&lt;br /&gt;From the bestselling author of Kafka on the Shore and The Wind-up Bird Chronicle comes this superb collection of twenty-four stories that generously expresses Murakami's mastery of the form. From the surreal to the mundane, these stories exhibit his ability to transform the full range of human experience in ways that are instructive, surprising, and relentlessly entertaining.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are animated crows, a criminal monkey, and an iceman, as well as the dreams that shape us and the things we might wish for. Whether during a chance reunion in Italy, a romantic exile in Greece, a holiday in Hawaii, or in the grip of everyday life, Murakami's characters confront grievous loss, or sexuality, or the glow of a firefly, or the impossible distances between those who ought to be closest of all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again, to the statue!  John Harvard's that is, in the yard.  Again, to the stairs on the right if tons of tourists, again the Au Bon Pain if it rains :-)&lt;br /&gt;And, again, my apologies, slim chance you'll have a surrogate leader:-)  But will definitely keep you posted:-)  If not, cell phone will be delivered so we all find each other:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then!!&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Pink comforter in tow :-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248630863000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243940773000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:  Blind Woman, Sweeping Willow by Haruki Murakami</name><id>10553442</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248130800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/10553442/</event_url></item>