<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you are interested in amping up your fields for Advanced Energy Healing, you'll discover that there are proven techniques available which do exactly this!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When Keylontic Science techniques were mentioned at the last meetup, one member requested more info on these.  Some members are currently trying out a technique which shields against disharmonic frequencies in the environment, and I look forward to hearing reports on their experiences at the next meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But there are additional Keylontic Science techniques which do much more!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These can be used to amp up for Advanced Energy Healing, strengthening ones fields and shields, as well as increasing the energy-holding capacity of one's multi-dimensional bio-spiritual energy template. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be a VERY interesting meeting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't know what Keylontic Science is, check out the definition on this web-page:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;keylonticdictionary.org/Words/K/Keylonta.htm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to first insert the prefix &lt;a href="http://www" target="_blank"&gt;http://www...&lt;/a&gt;.  before attempting to bring up the web-page.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the lady with long black hair and a BIG smile!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aalia Kusmis</member_name><member_id>7978464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247350591000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bio-Spiritual Healers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BioSpiritualWellness</urlname><id>1275951</id><group_lat>43.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6200027466</group_lon><name>Bio-Spiritual Wellness</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241709611000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Amping up for Advanced Energy Healing Technologies</name><id>10360403</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244329200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BioSpiritualWellness/events/10360403/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/e/5/global_5403045.jpeg</photo_url></item>