<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/3/0/event_63378992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;I knew there was good wine made in Massachusetts and fabulous cheese made in Vermont, but I hadn't realized until recently that wine and cheese is being made in all of the New England states. There's even a vineyard on Nantucket!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A "locavore" is one who prefers to eat food that was not transported great distances to market. It generally refers to fresh produce and meat, but let's apply it to wine and cheese as well and explore what our region has to offer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring at least one wine or cheese that was made in one of the New England states. More than one would be more than welcome, especially if there is a particular pairing you are interested in. In the locavore tradition, we will also enjoy some locally made breads and hors d'oeuvres that feature ingredients from farmers' markets. Your $5 RSVP fee will go towards the cost of these as well as other basics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To ensure no duplications and a balanced amount of wine and cheese, please notify us of which&amp;nbsp;one&amp;nbsp;you plan to bring when you RSVP. If you give us some details of what you want to bring (i.e. "Vermont goat cheese" or "a rose from Rhode Island") that would be very helpful as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Address and directions will be sent to attendees</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Harold</member_name><member_id>5109349</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>irisZ</member_name><member_id>8194464</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319456121000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Gourmet Gurus</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>gourmetgurus</urlname><id>1277459</id><group_lat>42.4199981689</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1100006104</group_lon><name>Gourmet Tasters Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318552373000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Locavore Wine and Cheese Tasting</name><id>37330352</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319236200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/gourmetgurus/events/37330352/</event_url></item>