<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>245 Whiting Farms Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01040</zip><lat>42.175727</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Holiday Inn at Ingleside</name><city>Holyoke</city><id>906244</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.641467</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Finding new success in a changing world:&lt;br /&gt;Learn the new skills needed to beat the odds and boost your profits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attend and learn more about the new skills needed to beat the odds and boost your profits in a changing world. Most importantly, learn how to navigate your way to greater success by using inclusive leadership strategies and developing a culturally-relevant mindset. It is time to turn the challenges of a tough economy into the new opportunities of a dynamic and diverse marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Janine Fondon, President and CEO of UnityFirst.com. and Co-founder and Publisher of Unity First News, has been referred to as an 'information age griot’ for sharing news and information across the U.S. and world. Janine and her husband Tom have established two of the best diverse, national news services -- UnityFirst.com and African American/Diversity Newswire – as well as  publishes a local magazine Unity First Online News, covering Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the founding of Unity First some 10+ years ago, Fondon has inspired hundreds of diverse businesses and encouraged collaborations to empower communities to achieve excellence. She has been recognized for her multicultural marketing outreach on behalf of top corporations as well as and her communication consulting for senior leaders and diversity professionals.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allison Biggs</member_name><member_id>10438666</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271506866000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance</urlname><id>1525453</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>Women Business Owners Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269919122000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Breakfast Meeting: Finding new success in a changing world</name><id>13033102</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271331900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Womens-Business-Owners-Alliance/events/13033102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/5/global_14019093.jpeg</photo_url></item>