<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>69.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/0/4/c/event_64845132.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Due to overwhelming demand and a waiting list, Mark has agreed to repeat his one-day seminar on Sunday for those who didn't get in on the Saturday session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=====&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are fortunate to be joined by farmer and soils guru Mark Fulford for a very special one-day seminar in Portland this January. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Gardeners and farmers alike, regardless of experience level, will come away from this day with a deepened and renewed&amp;nbsp;understanding of the complexity of soil as our primary life support entity&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;and of the interactions of plants &amp;nbsp;and soil life as energy converters between the soil and atmosphere. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will not only understand the living nature of soils as experienced and studied by a farmer who has worked &lt;em&gt;with&lt;/em&gt; his soils for decades, but you will also become acutely attuned to the connections between (continuum of) soil-food-human health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who have only caught Mark's short talks at fairs and conferences, this is your chance to go "down the rabbit hole!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soil .....&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No durable peaceful civilization has ever thrived without the foundation of good soils and watersheds within its boundaries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No culture that&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;honors all its members&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;forgets its earth-bound wisdoms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those that &lt;em&gt;do&amp;nbsp;forget&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;the part of humanity that is soil, water, atmosphere, plants and animals...invite conflict over resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To build soil with people is to rebuild&amp;nbsp;communities strong enough to withstand sweeping economic, social and environmental changes. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nourishment is the common denominator we share with all life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/5/7/1/event_50953681.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;We will cover both basic and complex understandings of soil function (aka: How soil nutrition becomes our nutrition)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The vessel of the rhizosphere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Biota, and the atmosphere under the ground&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chemistry and energy of the rocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The "Barterville" of the soil system (Plants and microbes are running the show)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the dinner table of life, the "microbes eat first, plants eat second, and we eat last."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;nbsp;Sunday January 29th 8:30 am to 4:30 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to bring: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;A notebook (there will be alot to capture!), your potluck kit (plate/bowl/utensils/napkin/cup or mug), a healthy dish or beverage to share for our potluck lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Portland Location TBD based on response. &amp;nbsp;Space is limited for this seminar so that we can give full attention to all attendees and their questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snow Day: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;In the event of bad weather, this will be held the following day; please plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;$69&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coffee, tea and snacks provided throughout the day. &amp;nbsp;Handouts provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-----------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;More about Mark Fulford:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;Mark has been operating Teltane Farm in Monroe Maine with his wife, Paula Fulford, since 1979. &amp;nbsp;He is a well-known &lt;strong&gt;independent farm consultant and educator&lt;/strong&gt; whose expertise includes transitioning from conventional to organic and biological agriculture; soil, crop and forage nutrition; preparing agriculture and growers for peak oil, climate change and economic drift.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;Mark also teaches combinations of &lt;strong&gt;minimum tillage techniques, permaculture principles, intensive cropping skills and simultaneous soil-building&lt;/strong&gt; with practical experience. &amp;nbsp;He facilitates learning on other specialties such as non-electric water technologies, organic orcharding, organic no-till methods, biological crop production, commercial and small-scale composting as well as fundamental rural skills and small farm food preservation. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;Mark's current work also includes developing &lt;strong&gt;custom-blended and field-specific soil amendment recipes&lt;/strong&gt; for organic and nutritionally-focused farm operations. &amp;nbsp;These customized recipes are meant to simplify and improve the cooperation between consultant, farmer, supplier and organic certifier. &amp;nbsp;Mark draws on recent discoveries and new understandings of the soil and plant worlds combined with improved methods in order to allow for the widest variety of inputs and skills to meet client goals. &amp;nbsp;In this way farmers and consumers are assured of the best quality possible in their custom blends. &amp;nbsp;The service is made possible in cooperation with Lancaster Ag Products due to their wide range of abilities to service the ag communities of the Eastern US. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mark's work in Mexico, China, Australia and the Philippines has &lt;strong&gt;enhanced the scope of his&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;soil and crop insights and has contributed to the evolution of techniques that can be applied to agricultural challenges here in the US.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;Selected consulting and/or educational clients:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span&gt;MOFGA,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;NOFA MASS,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;NOFA NH,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;NRCS,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;University of Maine Extension,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;New Forest Institute,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Portland Permaculture Group,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lancaster Ag Products of PA,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Biomatrix Water- Forres, Scotland,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Heart of Maine RC&amp;amp;D,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;DownEast RC&amp;amp;D,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;City of Rockland ME,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Troy Howard Middle School, Belfast, ME,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;North Branford High School (CT),&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Washington County Soil &amp;amp; Water Conservation Service,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inland Fisheries &amp;amp; Wildlife plus dozens of private farm and orchard clients throughout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;New England, the US and abroad.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3e4f2e ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Park on Stevens Ave, walk onto campus to left of the big church-like bldg (Ludke). Then you will be in a little courtyard. Enter Blewett thru door marked "Parker Pavillion." Take a left &amp; go downstairs for Rm 015.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328401106000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325271839000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Unlocking the Renewable Wealth of Our Soils...with Mark Fulford (Repeat)</name><id>45981802</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327843800000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/45981802/</event_url></item>