<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>181 State St.</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04101</zip><lat>43.652788</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>One Longfellow Square</name><city>Portland</city><id>1287118</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.266561</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A screening of &amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;Meet Your Farmer&lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, October 27th at 7pm, One Longfellow Square&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A crowd of over 350 people delivered a standing ovation to filmmakers Jason Mann and Cecily Pingree, and to the farmer &amp;quot;movie stars,&amp;quot; on the evening of the Meet Your Farmer Premier in Rockland. In the weeks after, Maine Farmland Trust received statewide requests to show these eight short documentaries of Maine farms in local theaters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Doors will open at 7pm, and the films will start at 7:30, followed by a panel discussion with local farmers.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   Both evenings are open to the public, and a good portion of the admission fees ($10 per person) will go directly to Maine Farmland Trust to support farmers and farmland preservation.  &lt;br /&gt;Prior to screening the films, Maine Farmland Trust's event coordinator Anna Abaldo, will offer a few remarks to help put the films into context. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    &amp;quot;After years of decline, the number of farms in Maine is growing, as more and more consumers demand local farm products,&amp;quot; explains Maine Farmland Trust's Executive Director John Piotti, &amp;quot;If we are smart, we can position agriculture to have a very strong future in Maine.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  Maine Farmland Trust is a statewide membership organization that works to support farming through various programs.  Since its creation in 1999, the Trust has worked with over 200 farmers and farmland owners. Maine Farmland Trust has worked with numerous land trusts throughout the state, such as the Cape Elizabeth Land Trust and Scarborough Land Conservation Trust. In 2009, Maine Farmland Trust received the coveted Dirigo Award from the Maine Association of Non-Profits, as one of the best-run organizations in the state.   &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alastair</member_name><member_id>4963124</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288275625000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>TT'rs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>TI-Portland</urlname><id>1233823</id><group_lat>43.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2900009155</group_lon><name>Tohidu Transition - Portland Maine</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287975325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Screening of "Meet Your Farmer"</name><id>15217111</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288220400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/TI-Portland/events/15217111/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/a/global_4989194.jpeg</photo_url></item>