<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Seaport Lane</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02210</zip><lat>42.349241</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 385-4000</phone><name>Seaport World Trade Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>801495</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.041775</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>At this month's Meetup, we will meet at the New England Boat Show which has moved to the beautiful new Boston Convention &amp;amp; Exhibition Center in South Boston. This show promises to be a huge show with much more space and with masts raised high. What a great opportunity to meet fellow sailors and see the latest in sailboats, gear, and opportunities to get on the water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet on Monday, February 19 which is President's Day. This should allow you time to see the show as well as attend the Meetup. Tickets are $12 for adults, but SailTime Boston will provide 1/2 price discount tickets to those attending the Meetup. (Note that these tickets are good only for Monday and you must contact Doug, the meetup organizer, to secure your ticket.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet in the Hunter Marine booth, which is in the middle of the sailing section of the show. We'll meet under the Hunter 45, which is the further boat toward the rear with it's mast and sail raised. We'll take a tour through the different sailing manufacturers and discuss our favorite models and gear. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 16327</member_name><member_id>16327</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1172100918000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1167786254000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Sailing February Meetup</name><id>5360119</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1171927800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/5360119/</event_url></item>