<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Donna,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you post something in the Meetups for us...an FYI if you will.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're having a 7HCC meeting-  This is happening next week, Wednesday the 18th, 7PM at the 7HCC meeting at 6 Institute Road (Merimman Hall, United Congregational Church). It's going to be about tabletop photography and we'll have different setups (black light, macro, etc.) for folks to check out. I got the attached email from Digital Silver Imaging and I put two and two together. I invited Eric Luden to come to our meeting. He's getting a table and will chat up with folks all about the B&amp;amp;W services this Belmont company provides.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I met one of their reps at last Fall's PPANE convention and their work was pretty interesting. The specialize in B&amp;amp;W from digital images. I was thinking that many of our Meetup crowd might benefit from this. They don't have to attend the whole meeting, but could stop in to chat with Eric. There's no specific schedule for the tabletop work. It's sort of a random round-robin kind of thing. So, Eric would be available throughout the evening to talk to anyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Casey&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1237988858000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236805107000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>7 Hills Camera Club - Tabletop photography and Black and White Printing</name><id>9933613</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237417200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/9933613/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/8/0/global_7636736.jpeg</photo_url></item>