<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Joy Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357903</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>AMC's Cabot Auditorium</name><city>Boston</city><id>1487529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065125</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This past fall Steve Cohen spent ten days rock climbing in the Dolomites using steel cableways permanently bolted to the mountain side.&amp;nbsp; This form of climbing, a.k.a. klettersteig, allows experienced hikers to enjoy the thrill of rock climbing without the weight and technical difficulty of ropes and pitons. In this forty-five minute slideshow Steve, who had never done serious rock climbing before, will share pictures of his trip as well as thoughts on his first exposure to klettersteig.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the area: The Dolomites are in the northeastern Italian alpine region that borders on Austria. This region, chosen as a UNESCO Heritage site, is in the words of John Murray (1840) &amp;#147;unlike any other mountains and are to be seen nowhere else among the Alps.&amp;nbsp; They arrest the attention by the singularity and picturesqueness of their forms&amp;#133; sometimes rising in pinnacles and obelisks, at others extending in serrated ridges teethed like the jaw of an alligator.&amp;#148; These mountains are surrounded sometimes by stark moonscapes and at other times by vast expanses of alpine meadows and forests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
See photos at &lt;a href="http://www.tinyurl.com/feb8slideshow" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.tinyurl.com/feb8slideshow&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doors open @ 6:15 PM - potluck @ 6:30 PM then show @ 7:15 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you have any questions, please contact Julie at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a&gt;AMCBostonSlideshows@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potluck Info:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;For those who wish to participate in the potluck at 6:30pm, feel free to use the following guidelines: Last names beginning with K-Z bring a main dish,&amp;nbsp; A-J bring an appetizer or side dish. Homemade dishes are welcome, store bought goodies &amp;amp; takeout are equally welcome:) Plates, bowls, cups, cutlery, napkins and drink pitchers will be supplied. The auditorium has a kitchen if you need to do any re-warming or prep (w/stovetop, oven, microwave, sink &amp;amp; fridge). Please bring your own cooking pots if needed for stovetop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subway Directions:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Take the MBTA to Park Street Station. Walk through the Boston Common uphill towards the State House on Beacon St. To the left of the State House is Joy St; follow Joy St uphill to the AMC Auditorium Building (brownstone), #4 Joy St on the left hand side. Map:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap"&gt;http://tinyurl.com/4JoyStMap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parking:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nearby parking is available at the Boston Common Garage, located underneath the Boston Common. Access is off Charles St, between the Public Garden and the Boston Common.&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;We offer $6 parking tickets at the slideshows (a savings of $5).&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;More info about the Garage is here:&lt;a href="http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html"&gt;http://www.mccahome.com/bcg_dir_map.html&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the event of a schedule change or cancellation, an email will be sent out to those who RSVP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Don't miss a show, get on the list and receive reminders and updates about future slideshows: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows?hl=en"&gt;http://groups.google.com/group/amcbostonslideshows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Julie</member_name><member_id>4471089</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363462593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1323877461000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Do What? Where? Klettersteig in the Dolomites (Potluck &amp; Slideshow)</name><id>44436922</id><headcount>35</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328743800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/44436922/</event_url></item>