<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>8 Central Square</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03222</zip><lat>43.590864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6037443210</phone><name>Ivy's Spice of Life</name><city>Bristol</city><id>831418</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.735903</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Please forward this announcement around to friends you think would be interested!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our 4th Tuesday venue is in Bristol&lt;/b&gt; at Ivy's Spice of Life restaurant in Central Square. It's a Tex-Mex and American fare restaurant and the owners are open to exploration of the truth.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month we'll show a video that reports on the work of the Citizens Investigation Team in Washington, D.C. The believe they have found the first known accomplice to the horrible attacks on 9/11 and you won't believe who it is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To be involved in setting our future meetings, you might want to view &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Our_video_collection/"&gt;our catalog&lt;/a&gt; and choose one you haven't seen yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have screenings every Tuesday&lt;/b&gt; somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: 1st Tuesday-Nashua; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; &lt;b&gt;4th Tuesday-Bristol.&lt;/b&gt; There's a 5th Tuesday this month, so we'll have a special meeting!&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Getting to the truth is left to us!&lt;/b&gt; Let's measure up to the task.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We'll have free DVD's&lt;/b&gt; and DVD's and books for sale. Everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We've developed a collection of books for sale at these various meetings.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donations&lt;/b&gt; - we ask for you to buy a drink or dinner to help support our hosts. If you are able to donate, it will help us to continue to build our library of books, DVD's and other materials. Please come in any event if you can't afford to donate.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive by 6:30 PM&lt;/b&gt; to order appetizers, dinner or drinks, and we'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin shortly after that.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking&lt;/b&gt; is on the street in front of the restaurant.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Newspaper&lt;/b&gt; - For an interesting paper which covers 9/11 Truth issues and other topics of concern, visit the &lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.com"&gt;Rock Creek Free Press&lt;/a&gt; out of Washington, D.C.&lt;br /&gt;Other interesting papers or journals are listed on &lt;a href="http://9-11.meetup.com/307/pages/Newspapers_and_Journals/"&gt;this page on our Meetup site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpooling&lt;/b&gt; - Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online at &lt;a href="http://mv911t.eRideShare.com"&gt;http://mv911t.eRideSh...&lt;/a&gt;. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride. As always, &lt;b&gt;donations to the driver&lt;/b&gt; for the ride-sharing are appreciated to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your friends!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239141404000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237386409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bristol - The First Known Accomplice</name><id>9980162</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1237933800000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/9980162/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/8/5/global_4632389.jpeg</photo_url></item>