<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>700 Hartford Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06517</zip><lat>41.357674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>USNH</name><city>Hamden</city><id>180814</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.897446</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Our July monthly meeting features a return visit from member Gregory Shenk, who earned his Ph.D. in the Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology at the University of Connecticut. He teaches at the Greater Hartford Academy of Mathematics and Science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his (in)famous attempt to forge (some would say “force”) a connection between biology and the social sciences, E. O. Wilson used Sociobiology, a term coined 30 years earlier by John Paul Scott as the title of his book about the adaptive origins of human behavior. Scott coined the term to propose an “interdisciplinary science which lies between the fields of biology (particularly ecology and physiology) and psychology and sociology.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some scholars have hinted that the timing of Wilson’s book can explain the hostile reception that it received. Time has healed some of the wounds that Wilson was accused of inflicting on scholarship in the social sciences and humanities, but much of the potential that the field of sociobiology proposed 66 years ago by Scott and again by Wilson 36 years ago has yet to be realized. This talk will highlight its successes along with the promises that remain to be filled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll start with thirty minutes of coffee and conversation at 7:30 p.m. The talk will follow brief announcements at 8:00 PM.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will most probably be in the Social Hall near the main entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>richard.s</member_name><member_id>1140524</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Siddall</member_name><member_id>1140632</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342492354000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>cthumanist</urlname><id>80394</id><group_lat>41.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9300003052</group_lon><name>The Humanist Association of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340491960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monthly Meeting: Greg Shenk on Sociobiology at Sixty-Six</name><id>70443662</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342481400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/cthumanist/events/70443662/</event_url></item>