<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>350 Roberts Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.768691</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-289-7212</phone><name>Margaritas</name><city>east hartford</city><id>966812</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.621508</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What a great way to enjoy your Friday night after work and start your weekend off right. We can always meet-up later as well for a night on the town. Some of the clubs have ladies night like NV and of course pigs eye and pour house are always free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Margaritas does an event on every full moon night. This is what their website says:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every month at Margaritas, on the night of the full moon, we throw a really big party and crazy things can happen. Throughout the evening our lounges are piled high with giveaways, contests, flavorful specials and lots of fun and excitement. Even better, 5% of the evening's gross lounge sales are donated to a local charity. Area businesses, organizations and distributors get in on the fun by supplying fantastic prizes and throughout the night. You could win anything and everything—t-shirts, gift certificates, ski passes, skydiving and rafting trips, snowboards and more! You have to see it to believe it. Join us for our next Full Moon Margarita Madness and see what all the excitement is about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy hour goes until 7pm with some good app and drink specials. Free salsa and chips plus $1 chimis' and taquitos, $2 mexican beers, and $4-6 drinks specials for the adventurous. I'll get a table in the lounge area when I arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh P.S. Make sure to get your free raffle tickets when you arrive-Who doesn't like a free prize? &lt;br /&gt;

Hope to see everyone there!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346460326000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Socialites</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialitesofconnecticut</urlname><id>1063500</id><group_lat>41.6100006104</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8700027466</group_lon><name>The Socialites of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1345510899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Full Moon Margarita Madness plus Bday celebration</name><id>78629532</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346448600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialitesofconnecticut/events/78629532/</event_url></item>