<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 Parrott Avenue</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.073605</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-427-1540</phone><name>Portsmouth Library</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>494523</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.757782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;This event is from 1pm - 4pm at the Portsmouth Public Library.  We ask that you reserver as there is a limited number of seats (45) available.  There is no cost for this, however a $5 donation to the &lt;a href="http://donate.nhliberty.org/" target="_blank"&gt;NHLA PAC&lt;/a&gt; would be greatly appreciated.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The future of NH depends 100% on who gets elected to our State House. NH is unique! Ordinary people who love freedom *can* and *do* get elected to our State House. Whether you are running yourself, or you just want to help good people who are running, come on out this Saturday afternoon and join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consider how many close House votes there are on important issues:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Just a few weeks ago, HB1661 repealing the LLC tax failed to pass by a margin of less than 2 dozen votes and has been put in &amp;quot;interim study&amp;quot; instead&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In 2009, the &amp;quot;State Sovereignty&amp;quot; bill HCR6 failed by just under 3 dozen votes. I know we can find 3 dozen liberty-loving people in New Hampshire!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Also in 2009, a seat belt law passed the House of Representatives by just 9 votes (we killed it -- just barely -- in the State Senate)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;In 2007, medical marijuana was defeated in the NH House by a margin of 5 votes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Margins of less than 2 dozen happen over and over for issues like seat-belt laws, home schooling, jury nullification, taxation, state sovereignty, and regulation of all kinds. A few hours of your time at election season can provide the &amp;quot;swing votes&amp;quot; on all these issues for two solid years. And if you can run for State Rep -- and win -- you can be one of those who casts those critical votes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a non-partisan event for pro-liberty activists who want limited government lower spending, and expanded personal freedoms. It is for candidates as well as campaign managers and volunteers interested in local and state races.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**********&lt;br /&gt;This session will be the one-and-only Seacoast-area training session for State Rep candidates.&lt;br /&gt;We'll be going over the basics:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;what does it take to become a State Rep?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;legal/paperwork/technical details &lt;a href="http://www.nhliberty.org/sites/default/files/becoming_a_rep.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;commitment in terms of family, time, energy, etc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;how to get started now so as to have the best chance of winning primary challenges &amp;amp; the general election&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;running as a Republican vs. Democrat&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;getting together your team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;how to be most effective for Liberty once you're in the State House&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The session is aimed at people who:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;intend to run&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;are thinking about running&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;just want to help get pro-liberty people elected&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The NHLA will be continuing with more individualized, monthly training sessions, starting in May. They will be held in Manchester going forward.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denis Goddard</member_name><member_id>3101530</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1270487887000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269909504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NHLA Campaign Training</name><id>13031213</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270314000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/13031213/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>