<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The Brettl-Hupfers will be at our lodge in Bartlett, NH the weekend of March 6 – March 8.  We are about 2 miles from Attitash and close to Wildcat, Bretton Woods, Cranmore, and Black Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of us are planning to snowshoe for the day but there will be plenty of others heading to one of the many nearby mountains.  If you are interested in snowshoeing please indicate so in your RSVP and additional information will be forwarded.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday night we will be hosting an Après Ski social at our lodge from 9PM-1AM featuring rocking tunes by the band, Dank Jankum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A full turkey dinner with all the fixings and dessert will be offered.  A vegetarian option will also be available.  Please indicate in your RSVP if you are interested in dinner ($15) and specify veggie option if that is what you prefer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come up and join us for the weekend.  Guests are welcome for $20 per night guest fee.  A Brettl guest pass and invite ($12) required for entry to the evening social.  The Après Ski evening social is not optional if you are staying at the lodge.  Once you RSVP full directions and information will follow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Members and guests must be 21+&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be at the club by the fireplace - come on in!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Min</member_name><member_id>5150181</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>dan</member_name><member_id>8253363</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238567918000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Guests</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club</urlname><id>1342211</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1500015259</group_lon><name>Brettl-Hupfers Ski &amp; Sports Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234318449000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Weekend at the Bretts, March 6 - 8</name><id>9717723</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236391200000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brettl-Hupfers-Ski-Sports-Club/events/9717723/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/7/5/global_6726629.jpeg</photo_url></item>