<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>472 Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06877</zip><lat>41.283108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 438-2282</phone><name>Ridgefield Library (Dayton Program Room)</name><city>Ridgefield</city><id>395867</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.498480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Richard Land has reserved the Rigefield Library for an informative meeting on Thursday, February 19th on how money comes into existence...something we never learned in school. The library seats about 80 people and is located in the heart of Ridgefield on Main Street across from CVS. The bad news is that Richard is recovering from hip replacement surgery and we hope he is feeling much better. The good news is we could still pull off this event with a little help. The original idea for this meeting was to be the first in a series of meetings to educate citizens on pertinent issues that are challenging our nation. For the first meeting we agreed to focus on the creation of money. We planned to use &amp;quot;Money as Debt&amp;quot; or the &amp;quot;Money Changers&amp;quot; as the main educational tool. If anyone has a copy of these videos and can be responsible to work the DVD equipment at the library, that would be much appreciated. As we try to pull this off, we have some questions such as: (1) How many of the Meet-up group can attend? (2) How can we get the word out to other concerned citizens? (The library may sponsor an ad for this event, but this is not confirmed). (3) Any other ideas would be greatly appreciated. The time is certainly ripe to spread the bad news of a fiat currency about to implode.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Barbara Costello&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ronpaul.meetup.com/384/calendar/9573749/"&gt;http://ronpaul.meetup...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235518665000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232748394000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ridgefield Library Event </name><id>9587908</id><headcount>45</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1235088000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/9587908/</event_url></item>