<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This moderate to high-moderate hike on the eastern portion of the Mattabesett Trail will be a total of about 5.5 miles in a thru-hike style and take about 4 hours with sightseeing included. This hike will be in portions of the Millers Pond State Park and the Cockaponset State Forest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start off at the Millers Pond parking area and hike by Millers Pond where many Indian artifacts have been found. One hiker even found a 4,000 year old spear tip in the footprint of his leading hiking buddy. No gaurantees we'll find anything but the potential is exciting for those with a sharp eye. We'll ascend steeply for a little bit up onto cliffs and then rolling trail among steep knobs. We reach Bear Rock (cliff, altitude 660') with great views at about 2.2 miles. We descend from Bear Rock via a steep rocky cleft and passing the massive rocky overhang of Bear Rock (if weather is bad we may have to bypass this feature for safety). At 4 miles we pass a small picturesque gorge. At 4.5 miles we'll take a 700 ft. side trail to Pine Knob Overlook. Then we'll reach Coginchaug Cave at about 4.8 miles. I expect the cave to be some sort of overhang feature but we could be surprised. Then we'll ascend steeply along a cliff and descend while crossing several small streams to the end at 5.5 miles at Old Blue Hills Rd. parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet up at the Old Blue Hills Rd. parking area which is the endpoint of the hike (see link below)  at 8 am. There is limited parking here on the shoulder. We'll then shuttle to the starting point of the hike by 8:15 am at the Millers Pond parking area in Millers Pond State Park (see link below). Some assistance may be needed in shuttling hikers to the starting point. Assistnce will be needed (one volunteer driving) in getting those driving shuttle back to their vehicles at the starting point. The endpoint of the hike should be reached by about 12:50 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may want to bring a headlamp or flashlight to check out the cave, just in case. Remember at least a quart of water and good hiking shoes/sneakers to hike in. It'll likely be cold so dress warmly in layers so you can shed some as you warm up. A day pack is advisable to stow shed clothing, water, and any trail snack. Rain gear (rain poncho or jacket) stowed in your pack may be a good idea for this time of year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to *meetup location* on Old Blue Hills Rd. (limited parking along road, look for Kevin S's dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=142+old+blue+hills+rd.&amp;amp;city=durham&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Textual directions to Old Blue Hills Rd.:&lt;br /&gt;* From junction of Rte. 17 &amp;amp; 79 in Durham, go south on Rte. 79 for .8 mi.&lt;br /&gt;* Turn left onto Old Blue Hills Rd. for about .6 mile.&lt;br /&gt;* Limited roadside parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to Millers Pond State Park parking area (hike start point):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=399+Foot+Hills+Rd.&amp;amp;city=durham&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is available from Kevin S's dark blue grandcaravan from the Hartford area. Please arrange with Kevin S as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195477564000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193244860000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on Mattabesett Trail (+ Coginchaug Cave) in Durham CT</name><id>6609405</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195304400000</time><rsvp_limit>19</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/6609405/</event_url></item>