<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West Branch Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>43.965270</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Livermore Trailhead</name><city>Waterville Valley </city><id>12988072</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.513540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Please take a moment to answer the RSVP questions when responding. It's for safety reasons this information be provided. Failure to furnish the requested information may result in removal from the activity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Introduction:&lt;/strong&gt; This should be a good hike, but be warned: it may be &lt;em&gt;scary&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;dangerous&lt;/em&gt;. This is thought to be "&lt;em&gt;one of the most exciting and challenging hikes in the White Mountains&lt;/em&gt;," as per the text in the book The 4000-Footers of the White Mountains. Having hiked the north slide (on the northern leg of the Mt. Tripyramid Trail loop), I'm inclined to agree. Put it this way, this hike isn't about the views, it's about conquering the two slides. And of course, a little peakbagging doesn't hurt: I'll get #43 and #44 of my 2013 NH48, two more grid peaks, one Trailwrights 72 peak (south summit), as well as a Terrifying 25 list trail (south and north slides). Maybe you need these, too. For more information about these mountains, please refer to the AMC's White Mountain Guide or The 4000-Footers of the White Mountains. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you (in the cold winter months this can be particularly dangerous for the entire group if we have to wait around, getting cold). Please read the entire TRIP SUMMARY, below, before you RSVP. It is important, not only for your safety, but that of the entire group.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;TRIP SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This is a MODERATELY-paced, INTERMEDIATE-distance 11 mile hike, with an ADVANCED 3000-feet of elevation gain. The approximate hike time is around 7 hours based on "book time" math, but it may take more or less time depending on trail conditions and how well we handle the slides. Always plan for spending more time on the mountain than expected. We will be taking the Livermore Trail to the second or northern junction of the Mt. Tripyramid Trail and ascend the infamous and slab-rocked north slide to the summit of North Tripyramid. (&lt;em&gt;Note: If we expect wet rock conditions we may opt to continue on Livermore Trail and take the safer Scaur Ridge Trail.&lt;/em&gt;) The majority of our elevation gain will happen on the north leg of the Mt. Tripyramid Trail and it doesn't mess around in this 1.2 mile segment. We will continue on the same trail heading south covering all three summits. From there we will descend via the same trail down the less infamous scree covered south slide. Once down the slide we will travel the rest of this 2.3 mile segment until we encounter the Livermore Trail again. From there we will travel back to the lot. Trail conditions will hopefully be dry on the rock with a good chance of a monorail on the ridge. We shall see. We will hopefully be hiking bareboot, maybe carrying light traction like Microspikes. As we get closer to the date I'll know better as to what specific conditions we'll likely encounter and what you'll be expected to bring or able to leave behind and I will be in touch. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Environment:&lt;/strong&gt; Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions so be prepared. If conditions will be or become dangerous on the trail (i.e., elevated likelihood of lightning, blizzard, dangerous winds, downpour, or dense fog, especially above treeline, if applicable), I will cancel or terminate the hike - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. I will also assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. While reaching the summit(s) is always our goal, we will not succumb to "summit fever" and risk our well-being in the process. The mountain will still be there another day. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Weather:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php&lt;/a&gt;, also check out &lt;a href="http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Tripyramid-New-Hampshire" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Tripyramid-New-Hampshire&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Gear Info:&lt;/strong&gt; This gear can be critical in the shoulder months, depending on the day and conditions at elevation. Like winter, there is no cheating here. If you mess up you could put everyone in danger. Below is a list describing the minimum required items to participate in this event (though you may be advised to leave some items behind just before the hike). Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to. Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear:&lt;/strong&gt; Proper, well-soled fall/spring-rated hiking or mountaineering boots with medium weight synthetic or wool socks with a spare pair in your pack, gaiters to keep snow/mud out of your boots, and Microspikes/Hillsounds. You should also be prepared to bring crampons in case steep ice floes are present and full-crampon steep ascent snowshoes (talk to your EMS/REI rep) if we except deeper snow. This stuff is essential. That said, as previously stated, I'll know better as to what specific conditions we'll likely encounter and what you'll be expected to bring or able to leave behind and I will be in touch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hands and Head:&lt;/strong&gt; A synthetic or wool cap that covers your ears and warm, non-cotton waterproof gloves as well as warm liners are critical. Maybe even mittens if your hands are prone to getting cold. Your rain gear/shell, should feature a hood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Face and Eyes:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;If&lt;/em&gt; the hike is above treeline: A face mask, balaclava or some other form of face protection may be needed. And for the eyes, glacier glasses with blinders and/or goggles with lightly tinted lenses (I find yellow is a good compromise color). I suggest splurging on "TurboFan" goggles (ESS is one brand) as the integrated fan effectively keeps fogging at bay. Also on the topic of eye protection, I find a pair of shop glasses in the pack a good addition in case we encounter an unexpected bushwhack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing:&lt;/strong&gt; Dress in layers with "wicking" synthetics next to the skin and wool over to easily regulate body temperature (clothing designed to deal with sweat during exertion and insulate even when wet). Also, it can be colder and windy at higher elevations so please be prepared. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON! While cotton is a great insulator when it's dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly conducts heat away from the body. Also consider bringing an extra layer in your pack just in case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear:&lt;/strong&gt; Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) as well as windproof/waterproof pants. Again, also consider bringing an extra layer like a down or synthetic "puffy" just in case conditions above treeline warrant it, if applicable. Otherwise a fleece layer is still a good idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water:&lt;/strong&gt; Bring high-energy snacks making sure you have plenty of salts and sugars (this will help you make better use of your water), your choice of food for lunch, and pack extra just in case. Again, bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip (2-3 litres is what I suggest, even when it's cold). Use at least two Nalgene bottles or a hydration bladder to carry your water. If using a hydration bladder like a CamelBak or Platypus, and &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; the weather is very cold this day, and especially if the tube is uninsulated, you will need to clear the tube after drinking, also pinching the valve while upright, "twanging" it, and keeping the bite-valve in your shirt. I also know of other trail remedies that can save your day, but do consider bringing spare some water in another container (&lt;a href="http://nhtramper.wordpress.com/2013/02/12/using-a-hydration-bladder-in-the-winter/"&gt;more info&lt;/a&gt;). It's a good idea to have a hearty meal the night before followed by a good night's sleep. Also, try to begin the hike well hydrated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter:&lt;/strong&gt; Be prepared to spend a night in the woods if you have to. Minimal options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces). A pad or some way to get off the ground is also highly recommended (though pine boughs can work). This is true at any time of year!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear:&lt;/strong&gt; Map and compass: don't just bring them, know how to use them (&lt;a href="http://nhtramper.wordpress.com/2013/03/31/wilderness-compass-navigation-primer/"&gt;here's some info&lt;/a&gt;). Also, a plastic whistle, headlamp with spare batteries, a first aid kit containing any medications you may need personally (please let me know if you have any applicable allergies, medical conditions, and special medications you may be carrying), a small knife or multipurpose tool, matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter, a toiletries kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items), sunscreen, lip balm, sunglasses, and a waterproof pack cover.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items:&lt;/strong&gt; Stowable trekking poles (recommended) and camera.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailhead:&lt;/strong&gt; Take Exit 28 off of I-93; Rte 49 for 10.3 mi. (toward ski area); left at ski area access road; go 1.2 mi.; right onto Tripoli Rd.; go .6 mi.; right onto W. Branch Rd., cross bridge; look for large parking area on left. Elevation: 1580' &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #808080"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; You agree not to hold the Organizer, Event Organizers, Assistant Organizers, or any other members responsible for any injuries, mishaps, or any other situation that may happen at a planned event. You are responsible to research the event, know the area, and bring the proper gear and agree to know and follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at &lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.hikesafe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Take Exit 28 off of I-93; Rte 49 for 10.3 mi. (toward ski area); left at ski area access road; go 1.2 mi.; right onto Tripoli Rd.; go .6 mi.; right onto W. Branch Rd., cross bridge; look for large parking area on left.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike Cherim</member_name><member_id>46806602</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368839907000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366640229000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North, Middle, and South Tripyramid</name><id>115565382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368705600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/115565382/</event_url></item>