<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Brookside Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02130</zip><lat>42.313457</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Our Lady of Lourdes Parish Center Old Church</name><city>Boston</city><id>10174922</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.103371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for the launch of the Egleston Farmers Market!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opening day will feature children’s activities, music, local artists, and a free coffee corner. Shoppers will be able to purchase local produce, meat, eggs, cheese, fish, bread, baked goods, and prepared foods made in the Crop Circle Kitchen right next door. SNAP and Bounty Bucks are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Egleston Farmers Market is a community-led initiative to make fresh, healthy, locally-grown food accessible throughout the year, bring people from all parts of Jamaica Plain together, and support the local economy. This indoor seasonal market will be open on Saturdays from 11am-2pm on Nov 10 &amp;amp; 17, Dec 8 &amp;amp; 15; and weekly in January &amp;amp; February. Located next to the Brewery complex and near the Stonybrook MBTA station, the market has plenty of free parking. &lt;br /&gt;

The market is managed by a volunteer committee and is a collaborative project of Egleston Main Street and JP New Economy Transition. &lt;br /&gt;

 Vendors: Buckle Farm, Foxboro Cheese Co., Great Cape Baking Co., John Crow Farm, Red’s Best Fish, Seta’s Mediterranean, Stillman’s at the Turkey Farm, Stillman’s Farm, Urban Hydr-O Farmers, Vianne Chocolat, Yard Birds. &lt;br /&gt;

 Contact: Kate Peppard, Market Manager &lt;br /&gt;

617.942.0194 or eglestonfarmersmarket@gmail.com &lt;br /&gt;

Website: www.eglestonfarmersmarket.org &lt;br /&gt;

Facebook: www.facebook.com/eglestonfarmersmarket &lt;br /&gt;

Twitter: @EglestonFarmMkt&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mindy</member_name><member_id>6980975</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352574556000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Urban-Homesteaders-League</urlname><id>1466080</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Urban Homesteaders' League</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352156443000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Egleston Winter Farmer's Market -OPENING DAY! Jamaica Plain. Yay!</name><id>90122572</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352563200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Urban-Homesteaders-League/events/90122572/</event_url></item>