<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.748052</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-297-2544</phone><name>Cinestudio </name><city>Hartford</city><id>742268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.693215</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Great way to end the summer.  Another place to see Paul Lynde.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1963/2009) Directed by George Sidney. Screenplay by Irving Brecher, based on the Broadway musical. Songs by Charles Strouse and Lee Adams. Cast: Janet Leigh, Dick Van Dyke, Ann-Margret, Jesse Presser, Paul Lynde. Fans of Mad Men are sure to flip for the studio archive Cinemascope restoration of a musical that serves the pre-Beatles 60s up right: cocktails, cigarettes and pearls, along with the delusion that rock and roll and the social changes it implied could be easily contained. When teen heartthrob Conrad Birdie gets drafted his income tanks, until his agent's secretary (of course!) gets a brainstorm: a contest in which one girl will share One Last Kiss with Birdie on the Ed Sullivan Show. Luckily, that one girl is spitfire Ann-Margaret, pink toreador pants, sky-blue princess phone and all. A Tony Award-winning, deliriously campy swan song for an era, released just months before the assassination of JFK. &amp;quot;If a 1963 issue of MAD Magazine had been made into a movie, this would have been it.&amp;quot; Marshall Crenshaw 112 min.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be outside or in the lobby, glasses, still a ponytail and a smile.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252625861000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251772158000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bye, Bye, Birdie</name><id>11253636</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252452600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/11253636/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/5/8/global_5698696.jpeg</photo_url></item>