<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Top-10 Economic Predictions for 2009 by Dr Nariman Behravesh, Chief Economist, IHS Global Insight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Behravesh heads the staff at America's top economic consulting firm - Lexington's IHS Global Insight. He is our most distinguished speaker ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Predictions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul type="1" class="fakeOL"&gt;&lt;li&gt;The U.S. recession with be one of the deepest—if not the deepest in the postwar period.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The downturn will be the worst in Europe over the last couple of decades and the worst in Japan since 1998.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Growth in emerging markets will decelerate dramatically.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Federal Reserve and other central banks will keep easing monetary policy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;More fiscal stimulus in the pipeline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Commodity prices will remain at depressed levels for much of next year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflationary fears will be replaced by concerns about deflation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global imbalances will improve markedly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The dollar will remain relatively strong as long as the financial crisis continues.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The single biggest risk facing the U.S. and world economies is a timid response to the crisis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The U.S. and world economies are about to suffer through some of the worst recessions in the postwar period. Most measures of economic and financial activity look like they fell off a cliff in September and October, and have been deteriorating at an alarming rate ever since. The United States is now officially in a recession that started in December 2007. Japan and many European countries are in the same boat. At the same time, growth in most emerging markets is faltering. IHS Global Insight now believes that, at best, global growth next year will be 0.2%, compared with 2.5% in 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We expect the U.S. economy to shrink at least 1.8% in 2009. Meanwhile, we anticipate GDP declines of 1.0%, 1.3%, and 2.0% for the Eurozone, Japan, and the United Kingdom.  As a result, GDP growth in most emerging markets during 2009 will be roughly half the rate of 2007 and early 2008. For example, the Chinese economy, which enjoyed 11.9% growth in 2007, is likely to expand only 6.9% in 2009.     &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Bio: Nariman Behravesh, IHS Global Insight Chief Economist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email: nariman.behravesh@globalinsight.com&lt;br /&gt;Phone: +1 (781) 301-9101&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Nariman Behravesh is Chief Economist and Executive Vice President for IHS Global Insight and author of the recent book &lt;u&gt;Spin-Free Economics: A No-Nonsense, Nonpartisan Guide to Today's Global Economic Debates&lt;/u&gt; (McGraw-Hill). Directing IHS  Global Insight’s entire forecasting process, he is responsible for developing the economic outlook and risk analysis for the United States, Europe, Japan, China and other emerging markets. He oversees the work of 325 professionals, located in North America, Europe and Asia, who cover economic, financial, and political developments in over 200 countries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Behravesh and his team were #1 in USA Today’s 2004 ranking of top economic forecasters, and in Reuters' 2004 survey of major currency exchange rate forecasters. In 2008, he was ranked #2 by USA Today.  In The Wall Street Journal annual ranking of U.S. forecasters, he was ranked #3 (out of 56) for 2006, and was the only forecaster to place in the top six for 2003, 2004 and 2006.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As IHS Global Insight's chief spokesperson, Dr Behravesh is quoted extensively in the media on such topics as the outlook for the US and global economies, oil prices, exchange rates, the budget deficit, the trade deficit, globalization, country risk, and emerging markets crises. He is cited frequently in leading business publications such as the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, Financial Times, USA Today, Investor's Business Daily, Business Week, Newsweek, Fortune, Forbes and U.S. News and World Report. He appears on national radio and television programs including BBC World Business Report, NBC Nightly News, CNN Headline News, The News Hour with Jim Lehrer (PBS), Fox News, CNBC, Bloomberg TV and Radio, and All Things Considered and Market Place on National Public Radio. He was the host of the PBS television series &amp;quot;Inside the Global Economy.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before IHS Global Insight, Dr Behravesh was chief international economist for Standard &amp;amp; Poor's.  He was president and CEO of Oxford Economics U.S.A., Inc. He held a number of positions, including group senior vice president, during ten years with WEFA. Early in his career Dr Behravesh worked at the Congressional Budget Office and the Federal Reserve.  He has covered the global economy for over 30 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Behravesh holds Ph.D. and M.A. degrees in economics from the University of Pennsylvania, and a B.Sc. from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. He has lived in Europe and the Middle East, and is fluent in several languages. He travels extensively to Europe, Asia, Africa, and Latin America.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Roberts</member_name><member_id>856777</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233191205000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>24</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>124</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228859784000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guest Speaker Meeting: Dr Nariman Behravesh, IHS Global Insight Chief Economist</name><id>9310123</id><headcount>124</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232582400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/9310123/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/9/9/global_4808969.jpeg</photo_url></item>