<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>203 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743826</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860.246.5700</phone><name>Alchemy Cafe</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1141371</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689455</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Imani &amp;amp; Kristy host a free talk, Why Detox?, at 7pm in The Alchemy Café (next door to the Growing Green Wellness Center). They will give an overview on the importance of detoxification, and  simple, yet powerful techniques you can use to eliminate toxicity from your body. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our bodies naturally detoxify everyday as part of a normal body process. Detoxification is one of the body’s most basic automatic functions of eliminating and neutralizing toxins through the colon, liver, kidneys, lungs, lymph and skin. Unfortunately in this day and age, with the pollution found in the air, water and food we eat, our bodies have a hard time keeping up. Our chemicalized diet with too much animal protein, too much saturated and trans fats, too much caffeine and alcohol radically changes our internal ecosystem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Detoxification through special cleansing diets, spa therapies and colonics is the best way to assist your body’s natural self-cleaning system. It is especially important for immune-compromised diseases like cancer, arthritis, diabetes and chronic fatigue. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find out more about how to detoxify, join Imani and Kristy for this important and free discussion and find out how making conscious choices in all aspects of your life can purify your body/mind and support optimal health. This workshop is designed to assist you in choosing what is best for your health.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Imani</member_name><member_id>7960334</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263514027000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260726885000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Why Detox?</name><id>12076034</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263340800000</time><rsvp_limit>11</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/12076034/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/a/9/global_12216681.jpeg</photo_url></item>