<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Filmgoers,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This movie will be hosted by Susan.  For those who love a mystery, this might just be your thing.  Here's a plot synopsis form the allmovie.com website:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plot Synopsis by Andrea LeVasseur &lt;br /&gt;Robert Montgomery is the director and star of the film noir mystery Lady in the Lake, adapted for the screen by source novelist Raymond Chandler. Montgomery plays detective Philip Marlowe, a private eye who just wants to publish his own crime stories. Kingsby Publications editor Adrienne Fromsett (Audrey Totter) meets with Marlowe, but offers him a job as a detective instead of a writer. She wants him to find the missing wife of her boss, Mr. Kingsby (Leon Ames). (Adrienne wants them to proceed with their divorce so she can marry Kingsby herself.) Marlowe accepts the job and goes looking for clues at the home of the wife's sometime lover, Chris Lavery (Dick Simmons). When Marlowe gets knocked out and picked up for drunk driving, he decides to drop the case. He is drawn back in, however, when Adrienne suggests that Kingsby's wife is responsible for the murder of a mysterious lady in the lake. Lloyd Nolan and Tom Tully play two police detectives also on the case. Lady in the Lake is remembered as being filmed with a subjective camera ? almost entirely from Marlowe's point of view ? and subsequently hyped by an MGM ad campaign.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want more info from this site, here's the page link:  &lt;a href="http://www.allmovie.com/cg/avg.dll" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.allmovie.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This movie is being shown as a double feature with &amp;quot;Murder My Sweet.&amp;quot;  I'm planning on seeing the first showing of &amp;quot;The Lady&amp;quot; at 1:00 pm.  The first time for &amp;quot;Murder&amp;quot; is at 3:15.  I don't know yet if I can stay for the second feature.  If I don't, I'll go for a discussion with anyone who also needs to leave after the first movie, and those who stay for the second one can discuss together.  Both movies are also being shown at other times that day:  7:30 for &amp;quot;Murder&amp;quot; and 5:15 and 9:30 for &amp;quot;Lady.&amp;quot;  I look forward to seeing you there.    Susan&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1186506301000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186088003000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Lady in the Lake at the Brattle</name><id>6116334</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186333200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6116334/</event_url></item>