<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>244 Central St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01906</zip><lat>42.468127</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(781) 233-0050</phone><name>Saugus Iron Works </name><city>Saugus</city><id>706104</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.009072</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt; June 22, 2009 at 10AM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where:&lt;/b&gt; Saugus Iron Works National Historic Site&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Address:&lt;/b&gt; 244 Central Street, Saugus, MA 01906&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admission:&lt;/b&gt; Free&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;  Parking area &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;i&gt;Saugus Iron Works National Historic Site&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the place where European iron makers brought their special skills to a young Massachusetts colony. Three hundred year old artifacts, working waterwheels, and mill machinery help to tell the story of a business failure destined to be a National Park.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The blast furnace, forge, rolling and slitting mill, warehouse, and dock area are all reconstructed on original sites and are based upon extensive archaeological excavations done between 1948 and 1953 by Roland W. Robbins. Hundreds of court records, inventories, and accounts of the original iron works were also consulted to produce a full-size (albeit, conjectural) model of the seventeenth century iron works. The &amp;quot;Iron Works House&amp;quot; is a timber framed, 1680s mansion house, still standing on its original location. It was constructed about a decade after the iron works ceased production.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between 2005 and 2008 the historic site underwent significant renovations. The 1917 museum building (a chicken coop, turned, blacksmith shop, turned museum) underwent major restoration work and new exhibits were installed during the winter of 2006-2007. Most areas reopened in fall 2007 or spring 2008.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seven operating waterwheels set reconstructed mills to motion.  Walk the scenic one-half mile nature trail consisting of marsh and woodland trails. Follow the path from the visitor contact station to the blacksmith shop and down along the east bank of the Saugus River.  The Saugus Iron Works National Historic Site is officially designated an Essex National Heritage Area Visitor Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Interstate 95 northbound or southbound take the Walnut Street exit, number 43. Drive east towards Lynn and follow the brown National Park Service signs for 3.5 miles to the Iron Works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 1 northbound take Main Street Saugus exit and follow the National Park Service signs east through Saugus Center to the Iron Works. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 1 southbound take the Walnut Street exit (East) and follow the National Park Service signs 1.5 miles to the Iron Works.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to Bring:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Water Bottle&lt;br /&gt;Comfortable Shoes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpool Information:&lt;/b&gt;  With ever rising gas prices carpooling is a great idea.  If you're interested please post a message stating whether you can offer rides, or need a ride, on the group &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/643/boards/"&gt;message board&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; $1  Money collected from event fees goes directly to paying for and supporting the group meetup.com website.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the parking area, just look for the group with all the cameras!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Beth</member_name><member_id>5251554</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214316432000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>CAPE Group members are friendly, helpful, and engaging, not to mention a lot of</why><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CAPEGroup</urlname><id>729767</id><group_lat>42.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.6200027466</group_lon><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion (CAPE) Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199636329000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cape Ann Photography Excursion Group June Meetup </name><id>7044655</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214143200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CAPEGroup/events/7044655/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/7/1/global_4330721.jpeg</photo_url></item>