<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5774 Main St. Putney</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06614</zip><lat>41.228775</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-381-2046</phone><name>Boothe Memorial Park</name><city>Stratford</city><id>384659</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.123161</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Ladies and Gentlemen --&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, they've done it again!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The US House of Representatives passed the Waxman-Markey &amp;quot;Cap and Trade&amp;quot; bill on Friday night WITHOUT HAVING READ THE BILL.  In fact, a 300 page &amp;quot;amendment&amp;quot; was added to the bill at 3:09 a.m. Friday morning and the entire 1,200 page bill was voted on at 6 p.m. that day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * To many of us, not reading a bill before voting on it the very definition of irresponsible and dangerous governance.&lt;br /&gt;    * This bill raises taxes on energy production and use, empowers unelected bureaucracies and takes power away from your local and state government and hands it to Washington DC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8 Republicans supported the bill and 44 Democrats voted against.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are a Democrat or a Republican or Libertarian, the behavior of this Congress should appall you.  The bill has NOT YET become law but action from concerned citizens can make a difference. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The upcoming July 4th Tea Party in Stratford will give you the information you need to make your voice heard in Washington.  At this Tea Party you will find out how you can impact your legislators on this issue and others.  You can make a difference.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't already, please RSVP your attendance.  Yes, it is a holiday that you might be spending with your family but remember the final line of the Declaration of Independence that encapsulated the spirit of our founding fathers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We mutually pledge to each other our Lives, our Fortunes, and our sacred Honor.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please find the time to join us for an hour or so on the 4th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tea Party starts at 10:00 a.m. July 4th in Boothe Memorial Park (near the &amp;quot;Sikorsky Bridge') at 5774 Main St. Putney (Stratford), CT 06614.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Boothe Memorial Park &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM RT. 15N ( MERRITT PARKWAY )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 53; at end of ramp take a right; bear right (almost immediately) at next intersection onto Main St. Putney; follow ¼ mile and Boothe Park will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM RT. 15S ( MERRITT PARKWAY )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 53; at end of ramp take a left; bear right at next intersection onto Main St. Putney; follow ¼ mile and Boothe Park will be on your left.&lt;br /&gt;FROM I-95N&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 33 and follow signs to RT 110; stay on RT 110 (East Main St.) one mile to traffic light at intersection of East Main St. and Main St.; take right onto Main St. (still RT 110); take 3rd left by bearing onto Main St. Putney (pond on left); follow for approx. ½ mile and Boothe Park will be on your right.&lt;br /&gt;FROM I-95S&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take exit 38 to Merritt Parkway RT 15S and follow directions above from RT 15S.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See it on a map, and get directions right from your door!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Questions?  Please e-mail me at mttaylor1959@gmail.com .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Taylor&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Azzola</member_name><member_id>5949757</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246889584000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246285853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stratford Tea Party !</name><id>10759578</id><headcount>999</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246716000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/10759578/</event_url></item>