<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As we look ahead to the forthcoming leadership transition from a Zak-tyranny to something more like a democratic oligarchy (and from social association to a community group with nonprofit status), it is important that the steering committee convene before the end of the year to discuss the whats and wherefores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The composition of the steering committee has been, over the past eight years, anyone with an interest in helping to guide the development of our group. Five years ago, our committee members decided to table the question of non-profit status until we reached the 1,000 member mark. We hit that mark, right on schedule, this summer. Now, comes Phase Two: the appointment of an interim BA president to oversee the transition; the formalization of a nonprofit proposal; and the planning and implementation of officer elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to join this conversation, please send an email to me at info at bostonatheists dot org, whether you are a recent addition to the group or have been part of the community for years. The meeting will take place in Kenmore Square; I will share the location with anyone who contacts me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first objective of this meeting is to form a quorum to select an interim president, and to agree upon a course of action for officer elections and board appointments to take place in the first weeks of 2013. An agenda will be distributed next Monday evening, to all persons who have contacted me.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355361470000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1354796438000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Steering Committee Meeting: Leadership Transition</name><id>94302742</id><duration>3600000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355356800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/94302742/</event_url></item>