<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>446 Broad St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06095</zip><lat>41.845562</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-925-6869</phone><name>Raw Food Central</name><city>Windsor</city><id>1084119</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.647430</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;“Nothing will benefit human health and increase chances for survival of life on Earth as much as the evolution to a vegetarian diet.”  ~ Albert Einstein&lt;/i&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we are truly what we eat then why are we so often living to eat instead of eating to live? During this unique 3 hour class you'll learn step by step how to create simple, yet delicious meals that are designed to bring quality health and nutrition to your body.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make it your New Year's Resolution to learn more about the Raw Food Revolution!  Even if you're not a vegetarian, join other like-minded people for some delicious food and important health and nutrition tips! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Long term raw food educators Curt and Kristin Griffing will provide a fun evening of education followed by a delicious, nutrition packed feast!  During and after the food preparation they will cover a variety of topics.  (Questions are ALWAYS welcome and encouraged!) Also, the recipes for everything prepared this evening will be distributed to everyone participating.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Demonstration and dinner will consist of a 5 course raw meal including fresh, organic juice, soup, salad, entree and dessert.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;Cost is $35.00/person and we need a definite commitment from at least 10 people to attend!  Please send your check to: Raw Food Central, 446 Broad Street, Windsor, CT 06095  (Advance payment is required)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;MENU&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;~ Appetizer ~ &lt;br /&gt;Fresh Sweet Organic Carrot Juice   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Salad ~ &lt;br /&gt;The Raw Food Central Big Six Eating to Live Salad with Creamy Craves Cashew Un-Ranch Dressing. This Salad has 6 or more fresh vegetables in it. Organic Romaine lettuce or mixed baby greens, kale, red pepper, cucumber, carrots, and broccoli dressed in a delicious creamy ranch dressing which is entirely dairy free.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Soup ~ &lt;br /&gt;Creamy Corn Soup ~ A simple yet tasty way to make fresh homemade corn soup that’s so filling and easily hits the spot on cool winter days by using only a few simple ingredients and a blender.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Entree ~ &lt;br /&gt;Two for One Collard and Marinated Cabbage Wrap ~ Shredded cabbage marinated in a light cold pressed olive oil with choice herbs and spices rolled into a beautiful green collard wrap. A great two for one recipe that teaches simple technique for FAST raw food that is ever so satisfying as a meal in a variety of simple ways.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~ Dessert ~  &lt;br /&gt;Stuffed Almond Date Balls ~ a simply delightful dessert made from soft, fresh dates and raw almonds with marinated or spiced fresh organic fruit.  Easy, healthy and oh so yummy! &lt;/center&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;We will be demonstrating the recipes using a variety of techniques that require the use of a knife,  cutting board, food processor that can be purchased anywhere (although we do have recommendations for anyone that is looking for either quality or budget friendly options) and a Vitamix blender. (The recipes made in this session can be made using a traditional blender if some of the ingredients are soaked prior to putting the recipe together though results may vary depending on each individual blender.)&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294605295000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>People Interested in Dining Out</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-271</urlname><id>258190</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Ethnic Dining Enthusiasts Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293047301000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Food Preparation Class &amp; Feast! (1/8/10)</name><id>15800681</id><headcount>24</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294524000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-271/events/15800681/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/0/f/global_20419551.jpeg</photo_url></item>