<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>69 Norman St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02149</zip><lat>42.407853</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-387-7625</phone><name>MetroRock Everett</name><city>Everett</city><id>669182</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.066201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Climbing MeetUp at MetroRock Gym in Everett. Toprope, sport leading, and bouldering available, including some tall walls up to 55 feet. Whether you're a new or experienced climber, join us for a fun and solid workout! We usually have people at all levels. Gym meetups are also a great way to make more friends for outdoor climbing. If you'd like to lead climb, don't forget to bring your rope :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*** If you are new to MetroRock Gym and/or climbing, please see the FAQ below. ***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet at the picnic tables ("round" table if available) by the cubbies and bouldering area from 7 - 7:10 PM.  If arriving later, just come find us on the walls.  Hopefully you can recognize me, the "Event Host" (see RSVP list) from my picture.  And/or check the small Whiteboard near the bathrooms and water fountain, for a description of what I'm wearing that day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If interested in starting earlier, give us a heads up in your RSVP comment.  Some sort of face/head picture in your profile helps us recognize you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full-access Day Pass $18. Bouldering-Only Pass $15.  Mondays are Women's Night: Women's Pass $10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info and directions: &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock.com/"&gt;http://www.metrorock.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions for Newbies&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q)&lt;/strong&gt; How do I get to the gym?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A)&lt;/strong&gt; See website for directions: &lt;a href="http://www.metrorock.com/"&gt;http://www.metrorock.com/&lt;/a&gt; If you're driving here for the first time, it can be tricky to find MetroRock Everett, especially in the dark! Use a GPS if possible. MetroRock is in a building opposite Boston Coach.   If you don't have a vehicle, the gym offers a shuttle service from nearby Wellington T Station; call them for schedule details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q)&lt;/strong&gt; I've never climbed at MetroRock Gym before, what do I need to do?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A)&lt;/strong&gt; You'll need to take and pass a belay test for rope climbing. There is a separate test for toproping and sport lead climbing. For toproping, if you are not confident you can tie a re-threaded figure-8 knot and double fisherman's backup knot and safely belay a climber using an ATC device, it is highly recommended you take the Level 1 Safety class. They will not allow you to climb on ropes without passing a belay test. Call MetroRock in advance to reserve your spot in the class, and ask them about any discounts or special prices they are offering. Also, you can rent basic climbing gear (harness, shoes, belay device, etc), if needed, at the gym.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the picnic tables ("round" table if available) next to the cubbies and bouldering area (on your right as you enter the gym).</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Brian Postow</member_name><member_id>5519047</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350387444000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Climbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonrocks</urlname><id>406080</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Rock and Ice Climbing Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349828252000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MetroRock Monday</name><id>qjnzfdyqnbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350342000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonrocks/events/86278212/</event_url></item>