<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>30 Alexander Ave</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02914</zip><lat>41.822292</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>United Methodist Elder Care</name><city>East Providence</city><id>5283222</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.364792</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;You know I post things from time to time that might be of interest to the group, and here's another one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've heard of Toastmasters, and always wondered about it. If you have too than this might be a good way to check it out. Whoever wins this club contest will go on to compete at Toastmasters International Area Speech Contest in April.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;East Bay Toastmasters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toastmasters members will compete against each other in a club speech contest &lt;strong&gt;Thursday, March 15, at 5:30 p.m. at United Methodist Elder Care on Alexander Ave, East Providence.&lt;/strong&gt; The winner will go on to compete in the area contest, which includes several counties in Rhode Island, next month. The event is open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every year Toastmaster clubs all over the world hold club contests to find representatives to advance and compete against Toastmasters from several different clubs in their area&amp;rdquo; says East Bay Toastmasters Club President, Shae McWilliams. &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s contest includes a diverse group of individuals speaking on a wide range of topics.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lynn Potter, a Warren resident, is the contest chair&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating in the contest will be &lt;strong&gt;Chuck Potter, Joseph Nunes, Paul Airozo, and Robert Chappell&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers will deliver five- to seven-minute presentations on wide-ranging topics, and are judged on content, organization and delivery.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The East Bay Toastmasters club meets the 1st and 3rd Thursday of the month at 5:30 p.m. at Linn Health Care, 30 Alexander Ave, East Providence. For more information about the club, please visit &lt;a href="http://9556.toastmastersclubs.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://9556.toastmastersclubs.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About Toastmasters International&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toastmasters International is a nonprofit educational organization that teaches public speaking and leadership skills through a worldwide network of clubs. Founded in October 1924, the organization currently has more than 270,000 members in 13,000 clubs in 116 countries. Each week, Toastmasters helps more than a quarter million people of every ethnicity, education and profession build their competence in communication so they can gain the confidence to lead others. For information about local Toastmasters clubs, please visit www.toastmasters.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Jeanne is hosting this one! Please look at her picture and RSVP so she knows who to look for!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeanne</member_name><member_id>14127779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332117990000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327769636000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Bay Toastmasters Speech Contest!</name><id>49995102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331847000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/49995102/</event_url></item>