<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will deviate from our plan of reading Kant's Critique in 5 segments, it is getting as difficult to read as we thought it could. Probably this is the main reason for lack of attendance in the last two meetings. For this reason we plan this, possibly last meeting on Kant's epistemology (the Prolegomena and the Critique of Pure Reason). There is no text selected for this meeting just attend if you would like to take part in a discussion about Kant. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to read about Kant then our usually suggested web sites can be very helpful:&lt;br /&gt;The Philosophy pages:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.philosophypages.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.philosophy...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Internet Encyclopedia of Philosophy:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.utm.edu/research/iep/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.utm.edu/re...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://plato.stanford.edu/contents-unabridged.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://plato.stanford...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we do not alter our future plan more substantially then we will read Hume's  An Enquiry Concerning the Principles of Morals before moving on to Kant's ethics (Groundwork of the Metaphysics of Morals and the Critique of Judgment). This would take one meeting. It is an option to bring forward some of the text the we planned to read between Kant and Hegel: Burke, Paine, Federalist/Anti-Federalist Papers ... If we choose this option then we will have some easier readings before moving on to Kant's ethics.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for the philosophy group from the staff.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228437426000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226254321000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kant's Critique of Pure Reason IV (possibly last meeting on Kant's epistemology)</name><id>9126130</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227225600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/9126130/</event_url></item>