<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>3.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Birds, a Bridge, Burgers, and Beer!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike the Audubon Sanctuary, feed the birds, and head to historic Choate Bridge Pub.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/8/4/event_89914692.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Mass Audubon's Ipswich River Wildlife Sanctuary in Topsfield, MA offers more than 2200 acres and 10 miles of interconnecting trails. There are forests, meadows, and wetlands to explore. Watch for river otters, painted turtles, and great blue herons at various times throughout the year. Climb the drumlin and esker landscape features created by a glacier 15,000 years ago. Huge rocks and exotic trees and shrubs that were part of a former arboretum provide an adventurous walk along the Rockery Trail. Eight miles of the Ipswich River run through the sanctuary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you bring bird seed, the sparrows and chickadees will eat out of your hand!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.choatebridgepub.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/1/2/event_89915602.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;The Choate Bridge Pub in Ipswich, Ma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; sits on the oldest arched stone bridge in America, built in 1764. The pub is a local favorite with legendary burgers, onion rings, &amp;amp; Ipswich Ale. &lt;strong&gt;Cash only.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pets are not permitted in the sanctuary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;leaves&lt;/span&gt; at 11:10 AM from the Portsmouth Bus Station 185 Grafton Ave. &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Meet in the back of the overflow lot&lt;/span&gt;, further up Grafton, farthest lot&amp;nbsp;from the bus depot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/7/e/8/event_89914792.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sanctuary is a 43-minute drive from Portsmouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll hike for about 3 hours on mostly level terrain before heading to the pub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring microspikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt; from the north: I-95 south to exit 53A. Then follow Rt 97 south. At the junction of Rt 1 and Rt 97 in Topsfield, stay on Rt 97 south and take the third left onto Perkins Row. Follow Perkins Row for 1 mile. Sanctuary is on the right. Admission: $4 adults/$3 seniors. 87 Perkins Row, Topsfield, MA 01983.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO&amp;nbsp;hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, snow sports, alcohol consumption, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time and location are subject to change due to weather and other factors.&amp;nbsp; Always check email &amp;amp; this listing for updates before leaving&amp;nbsp;home.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/6/4/e/event_78574382.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Blue Subaru Outback</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328532885000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>13</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327939068000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ipswich Audubon &amp; Choate Bridge Pub!</name><id>50225162</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328374800000</time><rsvp_limit>27</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/50225162/</event_url></item>