<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>22 Flutie Pass</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.301989</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508)875-6151</phone><name>AMC Framingham 16</name><city>Framingham</city><id>1004539</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.390307</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: The movie starts at 7:50. Please meet at the theater at 7:20. If this affects your ability to attend, please update your RSVP prior to Sunday at 7 pm. If you need to reach me the night of the meetup, my number is 978-857-3734.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The time will be updated closer to the meet up. Please check back for changes and update your RSVP as needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone will be responsible for their own ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the movie:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A widowed lawyer travels to a secluded village on an important assignment, and encounters a vengeful ghost with mysterious motives. After losing his beloved wife, Arthur Kipps (&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/danielradcliffe/filmography/p299899"&gt;Daniel Radcliffe&lt;/a&gt;) was nearly consumed by grief. When an important client of Arthur's dies, he pulls himself out of mourning to settle the man's affairs. But in this town, everyone has a secret. Something horrible once happened here, and it seems that the locals are determined to ensure Arthur never finds out what it was. Now the more time Arthur spends in his client's crumbling estate, the more aware he becomes of a presence that isn't quite human. In this house dwells a woman's ghost. In life she lost something precious, and now in death she'll do whatever it takes to get it back. Until she does, anyone who dares enter this house is doomed. ~ Jason Buchanan, Rovi&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet in the lobby to the right of the ticket booth.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle</member_name><member_id>2132838</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328581777000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327752943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Woman in Black</name><id>49968072</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1328573700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/49968072/</event_url></item>