<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>755 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02216</zip><lat>42.349100</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-424-8311Bosotn</phone><name>Vox Populi</name><city>Boston</city><id>669009</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.080950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Tickets are nearly sold out. Please update your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a joint-meetup with the Red Sox Natives,The Wine Meetup and Social Fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Celebrate the 5th anniversary of Boston Uncorked at a Wine Party at Vox Populi on Friday, March 26 from 7- 9 pm and beyond. You get the whole second floor of the Vox as a private enclave to sample wine, and it is a great place to hang out afterward for an after party among friends old and new.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taste from a large selection of reds, whites and ports from around the world. Enjoy tasty hors d'oeuvres from the Vox kitchen. Special features include a fifth wine table and chocolaty treats by Sugar Me Cookie Dough. And get a little Uncorked with Jay, Rob, Susan, Hillary, Vincent and Jen. and launch the start of Boston Uncorked 6th year of hosting intriguing and educational wine events throughout Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been attending their events since the beginning and they are a must attend for all. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everything that you need to know about the event is on the Boston Uncorked website.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To purchase tickets go to &lt;a href="http://www.bostonuncorked.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Please buy your tickets early as over 90% of their events sell out, some within days of posting. This event takes place on a Friday night so no excuses not to attend. Cost is $39.00. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Frank &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>On the Second floor</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>6893072</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269831995000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267716086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Uncorked 5th Anniversary Wine Party at Vox Populi</name><id>12781540</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269644400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/12781540/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/c/8/global_6854760.jpeg</photo_url></item>