<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Have you resolved to do more for justice in 2010? Get started by connecting with like-minded progressives at SoJust's biggest event of the year!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With over 1200 members and 3+ years of creating a diverse cross-issue community in Boston, Socializing for Justice is the best place to find a way to make your resolution happen while putting the SOCIAL back in social justice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always we'll help you meet all the great people in the room - so no worries if you're new to SoJust, plus we'll have &amp;quot;looking for&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ask me about&amp;quot; tags to make it even more likely you'll find the right connections. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Want to cross-promote your events and campaigns? Looking for like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston?  Are you new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in? Are you psyched about building strong cross-issue coalitions? Join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;YES, WE MEAN YOU.&lt;/b&gt; We've got members of all ages, races, genders, sexual orientations, levels of activism and professions. We hope you see someone like yourself and meet someone you otherwise wouldn't have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HEY ORGANIZERS!&lt;/b&gt; If you're involved with a group or project and want to spread the word bring flyers for the free lit table - and there'll be lots of opportunity to schmooze and network!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The venue 18+ and is wheelchair accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue.&lt;br /&gt;Lir is across from the Hynes Convention Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wanna know more about SoJust?&lt;/b&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Spread the word by inviting your friends to the facebook event:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=190598309395"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Join the SoJust Facebook group:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/group.php?gid=8770189934"&gt;http://www.facebook.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow SoJust on Twitter:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust"&gt;http://www.twitter.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cans for the Brookline Can Drive. Special thanks to SoJust member &amp;amp; Pita Pit owner Jessica Green for coordinating SoJust's participation. Everyone who donates gets a Pita Pit coupon, entered into a raffle and of course the great feeling of supporting over 200 local families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Items to donate include non-perishable foods such as pasta, soups, canned tuna &amp;amp; meat, cereal &amp;amp; powdered milk, and toiletries.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>45</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265037710000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>20</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>86</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259527227000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecting for Justice</name><id>11975037</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264719600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/11975037/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/1/3/global_11324323.jpeg</photo_url></item>