<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Main Floor-North Entrance</address_2><address_1>404 Wyman Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02454</zip><lat>42.410244</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>1-781-895-1234 </phone><name>IBM Innovation Center</name><city>Waltham</city><id>893122</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.256317</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Been meaning to check this out for a while now... let's go see what's what.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://massinnovationnights.com/event-rsvp" target="_blank"&gt; -&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;RSVP HERE&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;-   as well as there -&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;from the website&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;It’s going to be a fun Mass Innovation Nights.  We’re back at the Waltham IBM Innovation Center and, in addition to our usual assortment of new and innovate products, we’re hosting a cluster of green and/or clean products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   1. Check them out — visit their websites,what are they talking about on Twitter, on Facebook, etc.&lt;br /&gt;   2. Scroll down below the descriptions to vote for your 4 favorites.  The top vote-getters each receive a 5 minute presentation slot (all the companies get a table) at the live event.&lt;br /&gt;   3. RSVP and we’ll see you on July 14 so you can check out the companies in person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acquia Drupal Gardens – SaaS version of Drupal, site + community management tool&lt;br /&gt;BuySellAds.com – Private label ad network software.&lt;br /&gt;CleanJourney -  Clean Tech Business Networking Platform&lt;br /&gt;Difra, Inc. – Residential architectural design technology&lt;br /&gt;Episend -  Rich Media Messaging and Sharing&lt;br /&gt;Leslie Reichert, The Cleaning Coach – Coaching people to Green their Cleaning&lt;br /&gt;Miss Pinup Power 2011 — Renewable Energy Pinup Calendar (Website coming soon!)&lt;br /&gt;Real Cool TV – Marketing content dev &amp;amp; video &amp;amp; web technology&lt;br /&gt;Pietzo Hybrid Electric Bike – Sustainable transport to speed your commute  &lt;br /&gt;Yankee Barn Homes – Energy Efficient Timber Frame Homes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mass Innovation Nights (MIN) is a website and organization created to provide innovators with ways to connect with the social networking world, the main stream media, the marketplace and each other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Held once a month (usually the second Wednesday of the month, registration and networking at 6:00 p.m., presentations start showing at 7:00 p.m., the Experts Corner team has one-on-one conversations with start-ups and entrepreneurs and with an after-party at a nearby bar at 8:30 p.m.) and open to the public, the live MIN events allow companies to show off Massachusetts-based innovation.  The events are free although our nonprofit partner, the Charles River Museum of Industry and Innovation, always welcomes volunteers and donations to help keep the museum going!  We also ask that attendees and exhibitors help out by using the power of social media to help spread the word about cool new products they see at the events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MassInnovationNights.com allows product developers, product managers and marketers to showcase their new products online to an audience of social media enthusiasts, mass and industry media, influential bloggers, potential customers and prospective partners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors to the site RSVP for the monthly live events and can peruse the list of already committed attendees in order to make plans for connecting live. MIN is also great for connecting job hunters, job seekers and recruiters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather</member_name><member_id>74173</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>10</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279235927000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1277915998000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mass Innovation Night</name><id>13960725</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279146600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13960725/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/d/global_2274701.jpeg</photo_url></item>