<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Welcome to Focaccia the best kept secret on the north shore of Boston. Focaccia has been providing great Italian cuisine to their loyal guest for years. Focaccia feeds everyone from the local regulars, professional athletes, movie stars, corporate clients, and new guest everyone is treated like part of the family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As Peter says it best &amp;quot;Try us once and you will always come back&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether it's a casual dinner, Live music in the lounge or a private function, Focaccia and the DePesa family promises a truly memorable dining experience. (please RSVP if you plan to eat so I can reserve tables).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress is casual, will meet say 7:30 grab a bite to eat, then dance it off in the lounge which is seperate from the restuarant, and they have plush couches for your comfort, and smaller tables to relax in between sets. To find me look for the Meet Up sign posted at the table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Band : Four on the Floor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:Closest Major Intersection: &lt;br /&gt;Exit 38 off of route 93 &lt;br /&gt;- coming south take a left off the ramp two miles on &lt;br /&gt;the right hand side&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- coming north take a right off the ramp two miles &lt;br /&gt;on the right &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>eva</member_name><member_id>4457040</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Natalie</member_name><member_id>5909042</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292195678000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun loving peeps</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>realestatefordummies</urlname><id>458442</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Fun in So. NH and Merrimack Valley</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1290521323000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dinner, Drinks and Dancing to "Four on the Floor"</name><id>15535825</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292115600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/realestatefordummies/events/15535825/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/c/7/global_7118503.jpeg</photo_url></item>