<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>200 High St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02110</zip><lat>42.356583</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-350-5555</phone><name>Revolution Rock Bar</name><city>Boston</city><id>669018</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052190</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>8.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Join us this Tuesday, May 1st for a special Salsa Fundraiser.&lt;br /&gt;ALSO!  Help us bid our assistant organizer Ana Budin (she's the one always taking pictures!) a safe trip back to Croatia, as she leaves Boston this month.  :(&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to hang out, meet new people, and get a little dancing in, all while supporting charity.  I will be there at 9pm.  You can find me at the bar where we can do a little talking before heading on the dance floor.  I'll have my hair pulled back in a bun, jean shorts, and orange shoes!  Yay!  Make sure you come and introduce yourself if you're new to the meetup group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ana :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;==========================================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DANCE LOCALLY, ACT GLOBALLY:&lt;br /&gt;A SALSA DANCEATHON TO BENEFIT VOLUNTEERS AROUND THE WORLD&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, May 1st, 9:00-12:00 midnight, strictly dancing, get there early.&lt;br /&gt;At Revolution Lounge Downstairs, 200 High Street, Boston, State Street/Aquarium area (easy street parking on week nights)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$8, ALL PROFITS GO TO CHARITY (see below for more info)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also: Going away party for Ana B., who is returning to Croatia (and is terribly sad to have to say goodbye to everyone) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DJ Travis, 100% salsa out of control &lt;br /&gt;*****See attached flyer, in our meetup group files links*****&lt;br /&gt;*****Please forward information to friends!*****&lt;br /&gt;*****This is a charming and trendy venue with a great floor and atmosphere!*****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.revolutionrockbar.com/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.revolution...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Revolution is on High St between Batterymarch and Atlantic Ave, across the street from International Place Towers and Boston Harbor Hotel .&lt;br /&gt;The nearest T stop is Aquarium on the Blue Line. Go to Atlantic Ave (facing Faniuel Hall) and take a left (toward the Boston Harbor Hotel ). Once at the Boston Harbor Hotel Arch: Take a right onto High Street. The place is on the right hand side on the first block. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Questions? 617 230-0956&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;==========================================&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--What the donations will support &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;VSO (Voluntary Service Overseas) is an international development charity that works through volunteers in developing countries in Africa, Asia, Eastern Europe and Latin America. Instead of sending money, food or clothes, the organization engages skilled people from a variety of professions to live and work in the communities during a two-year service commitment. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;- examples of what some of around 4,000 VSO volunteers around the world do:&lt;br /&gt;Pediatrician in Uganda&lt;br /&gt;Occupational therapist in Sri Lanka&lt;br /&gt;Science teacher in Guyana&lt;br /&gt;Accountant in Pakistan &lt;br /&gt;Math teacher in Namibia &lt;br /&gt;Biomedical scientist in Ethiopia&lt;br /&gt;Eco-tourism advisor in Vietnam&lt;br /&gt;Social worker in Kazakhstan&lt;br /&gt;Nurse in Kenya&lt;br /&gt;IT trainer in Ethiopia&lt;br /&gt;Pharmacist in Cameroon&lt;br /&gt;Marine biologist in the Philippines &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1178595390000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1177616642000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>May 1st Salsa Meetup Event!</name><id>5713029</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1178067600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/5713029/</event_url></item>