<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! As you may or may not know the group will be taking a 2 week break to allow people to catch up on any meetups they missed and so nobody gets burnt out from the non stop economics. Before we get back in the swing of things I figured we could all get together for a bar crawl. The conversations we have won't necessarily always be economics matters (though I'm sure some will!) so feel free to invite whoever you want! If you own any Austrian Economics related t-shirts or other apparell, please wear them! We will start the crawl at 4pm at Cityside Bar and end at 12am at The Common Ground. We will be walking from bar to bar and spending an hour at each establishment, so if you show up at a bar and we aren't their it means we have moved on to the next one. Here is the schedule:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cityside Bar (1960 Beacon St Brighton) 4pm-5pm &lt;br /&gt;

Roggie's Sports Bar (356 Chestnut Hill Ave Brighton) 5pm-6pm &lt;br /&gt;

Harry Bar and Grill (1430 Commonwealth Ave, Brighton) 6pm-7pm &lt;br /&gt;

Joshua Tree (1316 Commonwealth Ave Allston) 7pm-8pm &lt;br /&gt;

Wonder Bar (186 Harvard Ave Allston) 8pm-9pm &lt;br /&gt;

Tavern In The Square (161 Brighton Ave Allston) 9pm-10pm &lt;br /&gt;

Sunset Grill and Tap (130 Brighton Ave Allston) 10pm-11pm &lt;br /&gt;

Common Ground (85 Harvard Ave Allston) 11pm-12am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone needs time to sober up after the crawl, we will head back to my house because we don't need anyone driving drunk. Hope to see y'all there! &lt;br /&gt;

 x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1365290193000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Libertarians</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>libertarian-349</urlname><id>593245</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Libertarian Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364246688000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Austrian Economics Bar Crawl</name><id>111021602</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365278400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/libertarian-349/events/111021602/</event_url></item>