<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Bhakti and Beyond with Mike Cohen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover answers to questions about Kirtan in this fun &amp;amp; informative one-of-a-kind workshop coming to  Hartford CT on November 20, 2010. Teachings include the Dieties, mantras, Bhatki &amp;amp; Shatki, the Dattatreya approach to Kirtan and lots and lots of chanting. All workshop participants receive a 30 page handout titled 'A Bhakti Yoga Perspective on Kirtan'. This workshop deepens chanting practice while enriching knowledge. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an experiential workshop, the teachings allow you to connect your understanding with personal experiences. And together, we will chant in harmony, raise energetic vibrations and share uplifted consciousness as a community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike Cohen leads Kirtan in a manner that blends Eastern spirituality and Western musical influences. Eastern spirituality is represented by Sanskrit mantras that calm minds and opens hearts and Western musical sensibilities are represented by musical influences such as funk, soul, rhythm and blues, jazz and rock.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This incredible workshop will be happening one day only so please register to secure your spot. Mike will also be available for somatic bodywork sessions Nov 17-21st.  Email Imani@thegreenvibration.com to sign up for a session or to register for the workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bhakti and Beyond&lt;br /&gt;Saturday November 20 from 1-4 pm&lt;br /&gt;Growing Green Co-op and Alchemy Cafe&lt;br /&gt;#203 New Britain Avenue, Hartford CT&lt;br /&gt;Cost $45 - or bring a friend for a $10 discount&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;To register and/or buy tickets in advance:&lt;br /&gt;Email imani@thegreenvibration.com or call her at 860-983-5276.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets can also be purchased before Nov 20 at the Growing Green Coop and Alchemy Cafe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a yoga teacher or studio director …&lt;br /&gt;Enroll 3 of your students in the workshop and attend FREE of charge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a form of collective spirituality, in Kirtan we bring our voices and intentions together to cultivate Shakti (Divine energy), allowing each participant to bring more love, freedom and creativity into their life. Kirtan is fun and easy, and no prior experience is necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kirtan with Mike Cohen is an invitation to sing, clap, meditate and dance together to create deep connection to the secret places of your soul.  : )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y7ISwq00Erc" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;You Tube Video of Mike &amp;amp; Friends&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike's music is an expression of the Dattatreya lineage of Swami Kaleshwar and Shirdi Sai Baba as transmitted through the teachings of Philip Lipetz, author and one of Sri Kaleshwar's most senior Western students.  Mike currently tours internationally with vocalists Joni Allen and Allie Stringer, tabla wizards Jim Feist and Andy Skellenger, bassists Mark Gorman and Patrick Hammond, as well as many other top musicians from today's Kirtan scene. His debut album, Om Dattatreya: Journey to the West was released August 2009 and has garnered rave reviews in Chicago Yoga and LA Yoga Magazines. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://xa.yimg.com/kq/groups/8294359/homepage/name/homepage.jpg?type=sn" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290344815000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>energy healing members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>holistic-energy-healing</urlname><id>449005</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>Energy Healing &amp; Holistic Health</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287937543000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bhakti and Beyond</name><id>15211015</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290276000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/holistic-energy-healing/events/15211015/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/d/global_19002349.jpeg</photo_url></item>