<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>23 Depot Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03032</zip><lat>43.018082</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Parking Lot Just Past</name><city>Auburn</city><id>2785171</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353149</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This should be an easy hike unless simply walking 5 miles is an issue for the shape you are in.  This will be a loop hike around both the Clark and Tower Hill Ponds.  Although there is some elevation gain and loss it is not all that significant.  There will be a few road crossings where there could be traffic so be sure to bring a leash if your dog doesn't do a good heel when crossing a road with traffic.  Anyone interested in doing so could catch a bite to eat after the hike at Milley's Tavern, 500 North Commercial Street,  Manchester, NH 03101.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any adult guest you want to bring should sign up on the meetup site as a member so they will be covered by the liability waiver. A minor would need a written waiver signed by a parent or guardian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judi-Judi-Judi</member_name><member_id>7477606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357866631000</updated><rating><average>3.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355623511000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Birthday Hike (Don't tell Dave) Clark Pond/Tower Hill Pond - 5 miles.</name><id>95502092</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357484400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/95502092/</event_url></item>