<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>633 Maple Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03229</zip><lat>43.205753</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ohana Yoga</name><city>Contoocook</city><id>3028691</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.707375</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #990000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to expect&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The evening of Kirtan begins at 7pm. You can sit on the floor or on chairs. We provide blankets, yoga mats and blocks and a few chairs. Hand outs are provided so it is easy to follow along. We chant together all night, so you can join in when you feel comfortable. Wear whatever you will feel comfortable sitting in and be aware that the temperature does vary. We provide tea and water to drink.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #990000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to bring&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;A cushion to sit on, your own cups and water bottles to help reduce costs and save trees, offerings of flowers or snacks, your willingness to participate and be present.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Please feel free to bring an Offering of Prasad (snack food usually sweet) to share with the group. This food is placed on the altar as a symbolic offering to the Divine. It is blessed and charged by the energy during Kirtan. Afterward the food is passed around for everyone to enjoy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #cc0000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What is Kirtan?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The purifying power of the Name of God is mentioned in almost every spiritual tradition. In Yoga, Kirtan is the practice of singing and repeating the Name of God (in both male and female aspects), as well as using descriptive phrases or Divine attributes. The word kirtan comes form the Sanskrit root "kirt" which means "to name, to communicate, to celebrate, to praise, to glorify." Bhajan, another form of spiritual music in the yogic tradition, usually refers to singing prayers or hymns rather than the repetition of God's name. Its root, "bhaj" means "to worship, to revere, to love." &lt;br /&gt;

Kirtan is a Devotional Chanting practice and an important aspect of the path of Bhakti Yoga, the yoga of Devotion. In the Ashtanga Yoga system, kirtan is categorized as pratyahara (methods which draw the mind inward). Kirtan can be seen as a bridge between our outer and inner selves and an expression of our desire to know and love God within. &lt;br /&gt;

Concentration with one pointed focus on the different Sacred Names and Mantras, or the ragas (melodic structures) increases the depth of the kirtan. For some, finding out the translation and meaning of the Chant enhances concentration and devotion, while others prefer to dwell on the Name itself or on the raga. Concentration and focus are important aspects of singing kirtan. To this end, closing ones eyes, clapping, and listening intently both to the chant and to changes in rhythm can help. Rhythm carries the energy of the kirtan; if the group is in sync, kirtan is enhanced and the atmosphere becomes charged with spiritual energy. &lt;br /&gt;

Kirtan Chanting, then is a method of attuning ourselves with God, whatever inner meaning that has for each of us. As in any spiritual practice, what we bring to kirtan will determine what we receive from it. If concentration, aim, feeling, rhythm, and repetition of the name of God combine, kirtan can be raised to a level that may carry the minds of all involved to a higher place, where communication becomes Communion, an offering and a True Prayer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>7474519</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1370740168000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Yogis</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Yoga-Safe-Haven</urlname><id>1527369</id><group_lat>43.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.6699981689</group_lon><name>Yoga Safe Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1369139820000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kirtan w/Rudra Devi</name><id>qvlvxdyrjbtb</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1370732400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Yoga-Safe-Haven/events/120463882/</event_url></item>