<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This meetup will be an Liam Neeson Double Feature (Both NEW films) at the Kendall Sq theater. Come to One or Both. Exact starting time of each picture will be posted when the theater posts them! First Liam Neeson is one of the greatest actors of our times, obviously with the loss of his wife, to a skiing accident resulting in her death, he has been trying to stay busy! With this event make Liam even more of an emotional actor?

The Other Man: 
In this gripping suspense thriller, Liam Neeson stars a man obsessed with uncovering the truth surrounding the disappearance of his wife (Laura Linney). After stumbling across clues that take him to the streets of Milan, he tracks down his wife’s charismatic lover (Antonio Banderas) and is determined to exact his revenge. In a shocking twist, however, he discovers a labyrinth of secrets and a side to his wife that he never knew existed. Written and directed by Richard Eyre (Notes on a Scandal, Stage Beauty, Iris). Official Web Site


Starring: Liam Neeson, James Nesbitt, Anamaria Marinca, Niamh Cusack, Conor MacNeill
Director: Oliver Hirschbiegel
Written by: Guy Hibbert
Type: Drama
Length: 1:30

Five Minutes of Heaven:
The idea of reconciliation between two men from opposite sides of a life-and-death struggle is perhaps impossible or even incredibly naïve. Five Minutes of Heaven, a film that tracks the lives of two men from the same town but different sides of the Irish political divide, is unlike any other on this subject. One man, Alistair, is a killer; the other, Joe, is the brother of the man he killed. One feels he dare not ask for forgiveness; the other feels incapable of giving it. And so the scene is set in this masterfully conceived drama, written by Guy Hibbert (Omagh) and perfectly directed by German filmmaker Oliver Hirschbiegel. The leads are Liam Neeson and James Nesbitt, and they are both superb. But the film’s careful construction is what transforms this from predictable to transcendent. This isn’t a work of expiation or guilt; neither does it seek a simplistically dramatic finale. It is, like its subject, the portrait of a process; and the hatred and trauma that are its foundation are such that their genesis took years. Five Minutes of Heaven is replete with an almost-exquisite sensitivity and quest for understanding. It is perhaps impossible to erase the past, but we are better off for encountering it with the kind of passion and insight emanating from a true work of art.
&lt;xobject width="470" height="264"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/tzyZ3e_yt88&amp;hl=en&amp;fs=1&amp;" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="470" height="264" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Boogie D in lobby</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264954050000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1248277661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Five Minutes of Heaven/ The other Man Confirmed for Cambridge Kendall Sq Theater</name><id>10932715</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253919600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/10932715/</event_url></item>