<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>191 Highland Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02143</zip><lat>42.389535</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Arts at the Armory</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1046137</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.106069</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest, a Local Lovefest of All Things Good and True&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Date: Saturday, June 16th, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

Time: 3PM-6PM, Session 1; 7PM –10PM, Session 2 &lt;br /&gt;

Where: The Armory, 191 Highland Ave, Somerville &lt;br /&gt;

Cost: $30 per person, per session&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than 20 craft Brewers and Vintners, local food producers, some of Boston’s best local bands and hundreds of New England brew fans will gather at The Armory for SBN's Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest on Saturday, June 16, 2012. The Brewfest is promoting local craft beer, wine, mead and cider and highlights product made with local ingredients. The local lovefest is a must-attend event in this summer season for serious foodies, nano-brewers, craft brew enthusiasts, and localvores. It will be the first time local Breweries such CBC, Mystic, Notch, Peak Organic, Slumbrew, Rapscallion, and many more get together to present their best collections of brews featuring local ingredients. Another first will be the opportunity to purchase fine bottled wine from local wineries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the Brewfest, you will be able to meet Brewmasters Caitlin Jewell of Slumbrew, and Chris Lohring Notch Brewing and Vintner Frank Zoll of Zoll Winery to hear first-hand what they are doing to support the local food industry in the sourcing of local ingredients for their products. Attendees will also have a chance to take a glance at rare grains, malts and other local ingredients made with locally sourced ingredients such as hops, barley, wheat, fruit and many other local items used for flavoring- herbs, teas, flowers, coffees, chocolates, honey and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest will raise funds to support Sustainable Business Network’s (SBN) Boston Local Food Program including Boston Local Food Festival! Admission is $30, which gets you tastings of all the beverages over a 3-hour period. Delicious brew-inspired local eats will be available for purchase for $5 or less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SBN is offering $5 OFF each ticket for the first session through May 1st. Use promo code: CRAFTCREW5 when you buy your tickets online at: &lt;a href="http://hyperlocalbrew.eventbrite.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://hyperlocalbrew.eventbrite.com/&lt;/a&gt; . This is a limited offer and we encourage you spread the word, count your friends in and get your tickets now!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340058981000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1335152900000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hyper-Local Craft Brewfest at The Armory </name><id>61716212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339873200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/61716212/</event_url></item>