<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>246 Market St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.644695</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-970-5000</phone><name>Lowell National Historical Park Visitor Center</name><city>Lowell</city><id>704436</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.313107</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Lets go see the Boott Cotton Mills Museum.  We will start by meeting at the Visitors Center at 11:00 AM and seeing the award-winning multi-image video program, “Lowell: The Industrial Revelation” at 11:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Visitor Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Begin your visit at Market Mills, the former Lowell Manufacturing Company mill complex, one of the city’s original textile mills. Market Mills houses the National Park Visitor Center, where you can make reservations for tours, explore exhibits, visit the Children’s Corner, and view the award-winning multi-image video program, “Lowell: The Industrial Revelation” every half hour 9:00 AM - 4:00 PM Also on view at 4:00 PM is “Lowell Blues,” a film by Henry Ferrini about author Jack Kerouac and his native city. (Due to special programs, times may vary occasionally). General information on area lodging, cultural institutions, and dining is also available. Also in Market Mills: the Visitor Center Bookstore, and the Brush Art Gallery and Studios. 246 Market Street, Lowell, MA. Limited free parking is available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the video, will will go to the Athenian Corner for lunch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Athenian Corner:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of downtown Lowell, Massachusetts, part of the Historic District, the Athenian Corner brings you the largest variety of fine Greek food in New England.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since 1974, the Panagiotopoulos family has been proudly serving quality dishes and generous portions at affordable prices.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop by for daily luncheon specials, mouth watering dinner entrees, or take it to go. If a night on the town is your pleasure, the Athenian Corner offers live entertainment Thursday through Saturday evenings. Dance the night away to the Greek and Middle Eastern music of the Fred Elias ensemble, and let one of our enchanting belly dancers captivate your heart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atheniancorner.com/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.athenianco...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After lunch we will go to the Boott Cotton Mills Museum.  We will then end the day back at the Visitors Center to see  “Lowell Blues,” a film by Henry Ferrini about author Jack Kerouac and his native city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Boott Cotton Mills Museum&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss the roar of a 1920s weave room with operating power looms! The Boott Cotton Mills Museum includes the weave room plus interactive exhibits and video programs about the Industrial Revolution, labor, and the rise, fall, and rebirth of Lowell. Adults, $6.00; Seniors, $4.00 (62+); Youths, 6-16 $3.00; Students (16+ with ID), $4.00; Children 5 and under, free. 115 John Street (formerly 400 Foot of John Street), Lowell, MA. Parking is available for a fee at city garage, or on street metered parking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also at the museum, check for daily happenings at the Tsongas Industrial History Center, Lowell Historical Society, and shop at the Museum Store (reduced hours in winter - call for details) for a large selection of mill-related books, cloth from our weave room, books for kids, and other mill-related items.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visitors Center - Free&lt;br /&gt;Boott Cotton Mills Museum - $6.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Direction:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/lowe/planyourvisit/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/lo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231776797000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1228952657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boott Cotton Mills Museum</name><id>9317046</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231603200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/9317046/</event_url></item>