<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1000 Chapel St.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>New Haven Green</name><city>New Haven</city><id>411509</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Chipin link to donate to this event:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ronpaulforpresidentnewhavenct.chipin.com/the-new-haven-ron-paul-halloween-pumpkin-event" target="_blank"&gt;http://ronpaulforpres...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From: New Haven Ron Paul Meetup: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Saturday, October 27, 2007, 12:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;    Where:&lt;br /&gt;    New Haven Town Green&lt;br /&gt;    1000 Chapel St.&lt;br /&gt;    New Haven , CT 06510&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Description:&lt;br /&gt;    This will be a great, family friendly opportunity to talk with New Haven voters about registering and voting for Ron Paul in the Presidential Primary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    We'll advertise by asking businesses near the New Haven town green to allow us to put signs up in their store windows. We'll put up flyers along the children's Halloween parade in down town New Haven which will take place on the Thursday before this event. And, on the morning of the event we'll walk around the city and pass out &amp;quot;FREE PUMPKIN&amp;quot; tickets. Press releases will go out to local news papers and to Channel 8 news by the end of this week to allow for local news coverage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Starting at noon there will be a Ron Paul booth on the green and a pumpkin patch of small sugar-pumpkins. We'll redeem the FREE-PUMPKIN-Tickets for a free pumpkin and have painting kits on-hand for anyone, young or old, who wants to paint their pumpkin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    A pumpkin patch on the New Haven town green will give us quite a photo opportunity for local news coverage as well as allow us to attract potential voters and convey the message of Freedom, Prosperity and Peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Please volunteer to help staff the booth on Saturday or to help with promotion efforts in the week and morning before the event. Please put the times you would be available in your RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Please also consider &amp;quot;sponsoring&amp;quot; a number of pumpkins. They will cost about $1 each and will help make a lasting impression on one New Haven voter, and perhaps an entire family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    I'll be posting more details as this event approaches. If you have any questions or need anything, please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Go Ron!!!&lt;br /&gt;    -Bryan Tracy&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Earl L.</member_name><member_id>4314674</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1193881042000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ct4liberty</urlname><id>525277</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-72.4599990845</group_lon><name>CT for Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193351596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ron Paul-o-ween in New Haven</name><id>6617378</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1193500800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ct4liberty/events/6617378/</event_url></item>