<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>96 Winthrop Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372364</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-864-0655</phone><name>Tommy Doyle's Irish Pub</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>969478</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm putting together an event at Tommy Doyle's in Harvard Square this Wednesday 6/20 at 7:00pm. It's free, and anyone who Checks-in at the event will get a free sample pour of any of the 5+ Watch City beers on tap &amp;amp; cask. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://watchcitycrimson.eventbrite.com"&gt;You'll need a free ticket to get in, so grab it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There will be paired food specials, a few door prizes (gift cards and SWAG), and the beer list is fantastic:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/Hops-Explosion-IPA/11989/"&gt;Hops Explosion IPA (IPA, 6.2 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Pine and Citrus flavors, with plenty of floral aromas and bitterness to go around. As Watch City says, "this beer would keep on interplanetary expeditions" but remains well balanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/ClockWork-Summer-Ale/12549"&gt;ClockWork Summer Ale (Kölsch, 5.1 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Orange, tangerines, and lemon zest. Whoa, can you say major summer beer? I've never had this one, but I'm looking forward to trying what sounds like an ultimate summer refresher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/Chocolate-Thunder-Porter/39"&gt;Chocolate Thunder Porter (Robust Porter, 5.6 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - This is a no brainer if you enjoy chocolate, porters, or basically anything delicious. 60 POUNDS of Belgian Chocolate added to the brew! This one's exceptionally smooth, with plenty of velvety Belgian chocolate flavors. I know what I'll be going for a free sample of...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/Senchual-Green-Tea-IPA/23579"&gt;Senchual Green Tea IPA (Specialty IPA, 5.2 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Beer is basically tea for awesome people, so I love tea-beer combos, and this is a particularly fantastic example. Brewed with sencha green tea from Shizuoka, Japan, the green tea is a subtle flavor in an otherwise earthy, malt-forward beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/BitchLden-Wheat-Lager/23578"&gt;BitchLöden Wheat Lager (Spiced Summer Lager, 4.6 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Bitchloads of wheat malt and Indian Neelam mangoes, with just a touch of Garam Masala and lemongrass. I'm often bored by summer beers, but this seems to me to be all kinds of interesting, but still has the malt build of a sessionable summer wheat beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.pintley.com/beer/Watch-City-Rescue-One-Klsch/23577"&gt;Rescue One Kölsch (Kölsch, 4.8 ABV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Feel good about buying this one: It was brewed with the Worcester Fire Department and proceeds from every sale will be donated to the Jon Davies Children Memorial Fund in honor of fallen Worcester Firefighter, Jon Davies who perished in the line of duty in December 2011. It's a traditional Kölsch that's subdued maltiness gives way to the light fruit flavors and aroma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch City Cask&lt;/strong&gt; - There's going to be a cask, and I have no idea what's going to be in it. But I bet its going to be awesome. Mystery Cask!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Meetup Group should all meet inside The Crimson Lounge (downstairs of Tommy Doyle's) at the entrance to the room at 7:30pm. You can look for me, as I'll be right there wearing a black and white houndstooth fedora - impossible to miss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll be doing events like these with different brewers all summer long at Tommy Doyle's. The staff is great, there will always be some free samples, and the prices are some of the lowest I've seen in Boston for Craft Beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to drinking some beers with you guys!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Find Rich, wearing a black and white Houndstooth Fedora at the front of The Crimson Lounge at 7:30pm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich DiTieri</member_name><member_id>12427807</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340288575000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>beer buffs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CraftBeerCrew</urlname><id>1469154</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Craft Beer Crew</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340055796000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drink Watch City Beers (Including free samples) at Tommy Doyles!</name><id>69723362</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340233200000</time><rsvp_limit>150</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CraftBeerCrew/events/69723362/</event_url></item>