<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Elm St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03101</zip><lat>42.988332</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Verizon Wireless Arena</name><city>Manchester</city><id>764594</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463048</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>2010 International Fantasy Hair Competition&lt;br /&gt;When: Thursday, April 22, 2010 &lt;br /&gt; 7:00 P.M. &lt;br /&gt;Where: Fashion Show &lt;br /&gt; Verizon Wireless Arena &lt;br /&gt; 555 Elm St., &lt;br /&gt; Manchester, NH, 03101 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: General Admission: $35.00 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Websites: www.nhfoodbank.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Detail info:&lt;br /&gt;We're looking to informally meet outside of the Verizon Arena at 5:30. If you're looking at the arena, the lighted marquee for future shows will be on the left side. We'll meet outside at the left corner of the arena next to the box office entrance (about 40' from the marquee). The tickets for the event will be $35/ea. I inquired about a group discount but that is no longer being offered. The tickets are general admission, so the sooner we get in the better. Once inside you're free to find the seats that you think will get you the best shots. I would suggest seats that are 5-10 seats up from the floor so as to be at eye-level with the models as they come down the runway. You should also bring a tripod and the longest lens you can find. You might be able to take photos of the models after the show so packing a 17-55 might be good as well. After the show, we will be meeting at Murphy's Taproom for drinks/food, feel free to come over after for some post-shoot chat. The Taproom is located at 494 Elm St (1/2 block south of the Verizon) If you have any other questions, feel free to contact Dan&lt;br /&gt;(This event is organized by Dan Pinard).&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>ichi</member_name><member_id>6271486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272150304000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Photographers, Models &amp; MUA</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonportraitphotographers</urlname><id>830833</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Portrait Photographers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266816594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2010 International Fantasy Hair Competition</name><id>12670145</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271977200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonportraitphotographers/events/12670145/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/7/global_14316375.jpeg</photo_url></item>