<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Cushing Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01420</zip><lat>42.583423</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-449-7916</phone><name>Chaibo</name><city>Fitchburg</city><id>1285089</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.802296</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;In July we're doing some light summer reading and will discuss Jen Lancaster's My Fair Lazy: One Reality Television Addict's Attempt to Discover If Not Being a Dumb Ass Is the New Black, or, a Culture-Up Manifesto. I know I love me some good reality TV (and probably need to stop watching so much), so I think this will be a great discussion! Everyone loved Chaibo, so we’ll be meeting there again this month. They have plush comfortable seating areas and serve coffee, tea, fondue, Paninis and cheesecake. Yum!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a description of the book from an Amazon reviewer:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Life as we know it? Average. Life as Jen Lancaster knows it? Hilarious. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;MY FAIR LAZY is Jen's foray into self-enlightenment. She wonders if it is time to get off the couch, away from TV Reality Shows and venture into the world of culture. At the same time, she has a reflection that perhaps if she were a &amp;quot;kinder, gentler&amp;quot; Jen she might have more success, or at least not piss off quite as many people around her. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a great premise for her to explore with her wit and sarcasm. For anyone not familiar with her work, she is a bit like an &amp;quot;bitter Seinfeld&amp;quot; and her observations on life and all the people surrounding her are truly entertaining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During Jen's explorations she makes some great strides in &amp;quot;culturing up&amp;quot; as she puts it, and gains some insight regarding her personality, most importantly without losing her Fabulous self. I think one of her friends says it best at one point in the book, telling her that it might not be about what she is saying...but about what she is listening to. A lesson we could ALL learn, grudgingly, as she does. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I most definitely recommend following Jen as she leaps off the couch and into the &amp;quot;real world&amp;quot;!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Heather M</member_name><member_id>2005368</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280530077000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>literary critics</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing</urlname><id>1551608</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Reading, Sharing and Laughing</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278423735000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Discussion - My Fair Lazy by Jen Lancaster</name><id>14014799</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1280444400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Reading-Sharing-and-Laughing/events/14014799/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/2/1/global_11643361.jpeg</photo_url></item>