<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>844 Grand Ave.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.307671</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-785-9085</phone><name>Center of Light</name><city>New Haven</city><id>342022</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.916888</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hello everyone! &lt;br /&gt;   I almost forgot to post this! We are having a weekend of spiritual seminars led by Master Teacher Mother Clare Watts. There will be three seminars this weekend, on Thursday and Friday evenings, and Saturday morning. Mother Clare is an amazing speaker and a teacher of real integrity. Come and meet her and learn!&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;FEAR: Why We Are Afraid &amp;amp; the Path to Fearlessness&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, October 30 • 7:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Donation: $25&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a world of self confidence, clarity, and peacefulness how does fear creep in so easily? It is the seed of anger, confusion, and war. Fear creatively gets us to think we are helpless, alone, isolated, and cut off.  But when the truth comes in you know differently; come to this seminar and learn to fearlessly walk the way of freedom from all that has held you from becoming your self.  &lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;about Mother Clare:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mother Clare is a mystic; ordained priest; Master Teacher of Christian mysticism; and co-director of a mystical Christian Order, a school with 15 Centers of Light in cities across the country. She holds a Master's Degree in Counseling Psychology, with extensive post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis, is a Certified Professional Midwife, and has enjoyed successful careers in both fields. She is the mother of four grown children, and currently lives in Dolores, Colorado, where she co-directs the effort to develop the Sophia Peace Center.  She is the author of Giving Birth To God: A Woman's Path To Enlightenment.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225594809000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225334968000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seminar: FEAR: Why We Are Afraid &amp; the Path to Fearlessness</name><id>9058894</id><headcount>14</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225409400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/9058894/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/f/global_1078639.jpeg</photo_url></item>