<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>31 Everett St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.379974</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Stebbins Hall RM 302 -  Lesley Unviersity</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1499680</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117119</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! &amp;nbsp;I mentioned this&amp;nbsp;to a lot of you already&amp;nbsp;but if you arent doing anything tomorrow, come check out the show I directed at Lesley!&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Admission is free!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seed of Spirit GenY  &lt;br /&gt;An Interactive Theater Piece  &lt;br /&gt;written and performed by Caitlin Green &lt;br /&gt;Direction by Jason Jedrusiak &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;Performance Thursday, Feb. 10th &lt;br /&gt;7:30PM &lt;br /&gt;Stebbins Hall RM 0302 &lt;br /&gt;Lesley University &lt;br /&gt;31 Everett Street, Cambridge, MA &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br /&gt;Seed of Spirit GenY is the first piece of the SeekExploreCreate Collection, based on my personal experiences working on a permaculture farm in Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Yucatan Peninsula.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Devised through improvisation, movement, and storytelling technique, the overall goal of the piece is to engage, provoke thought, and encourage high school and college students to reconnect with their inner selves as they deal with the difficult period of transition.  &lt;br /&gt;The piece broadly questions our connection to ourselves and each other in this time of technology and media buzz.&amp;nbsp; It also questions the &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; first attitude in contrast to &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; first, using the analogy of a supportive and inter-connected sustainable garden.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Breaking the fourth wall, it addresses the audience as travelers, &amp;ldquo;where are you going?&amp;rdquo; but most crucially, &amp;ldquo;where are WE going,?&amp;rdquo; challenging the audience to focus upon making decisions that affect one another from a holistic stand-point.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A period of time away from my cell phone and constant influx of media, I learned a lot about my own disconnection to myself and discovered my strong material, media, and technology attachments.  &lt;br /&gt;As I faced intense fears in anticipation of graduation, I found clarity when I decided to spend time on a permaculture farm re-connecting with myself and nature, completely immersed in a different culture.&amp;nbsp; I hope my life changing story will help others through the big and over-whelming journey of, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s next?&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Walk up the stairs, follow signs, etc!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297388477000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><why>Hi everyone!  I mentioned this to a lot of you already but if you arent doing anything tomorrow, come check out the show I directed at Lesley!    Admission is free!</why><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>laughingmatter</urlname><id>1386175</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Great Boston Chapter of Laughing Matter - Auditions Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297352274000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tonight see an interactive show I directed @ Lesley Uni! Admission free!</name><id>16516567</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297384200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/laughingmatter/events/16516567/</event_url></item>