<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Runtime: 2hrs: 6min | PG-13 some intense sequences of sci-fi action and violence, and brief suggestive content

Director: Jon Favreau

Starring Robert Downey Jr., Sam Jackson, Gwen Paltrow, etc.

Genre: SF Action, comic book, etc.

More info: &lt;a href="http://imdb.com/title/tt0371746/" class="linkified"&gt;http://imdb.com/title/tt0371746/&lt;/a&gt;

Reviews: &lt;a href="http://www.darkhorizons.com/reviews/ironman.php" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.darkhorizons.com/reviews/ironman.php&lt;/a&gt;

Trailer: &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/ironman/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/ironman/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/zbFuW_Jkbg8&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

Description: Based on the Marvel Comics Character; Billionaire playboy industrialist Tony Stark makes weapons for the U.S. government. While out on a field test of one of his inventions, he is wounded, captured and forced to make weapons for the enemy. Instead, he fashions himself a crude power armor to save his life and facilitate his escape. When he returns home, he revises his armor and finds purpose as the Armored Avenger Iron Man!

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what your going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix AHEAD of time! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

If it's downstairs, I'll be right behind the corded rope after ticket stubs have been ripped in front of the popcorn counter. If it's upstairs, I'll try to grab one of the tables in front of the coffee house near the large monumental windows.

I'll be there around 6PM. We want to reserve some good seats so please get there as EARLY as you can! I'll wait til 6:45PM and then I'm going in. The film begins@7PM. Please buy tix EARLY! You can buy it TODAY:
&lt;a href="http://www.fandango.com/ironman_98591/movietimes?date=5/2/2008" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.fandango.com/ironman_98591/movietimes?date=5/2/2008&lt;/a&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. After the film ends, we'll all gather outside the door of the movie you just watched, so look for us!</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212077706000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>6</count></rating><why>We won't bite. Love to have discussions about the films after movie ends. The group often goes out afterwards and socialize.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198726806000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Iron Man</name><id>6974329</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209767400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6974329/</event_url></item>