<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>107 N Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03301</zip><lat>43.207620</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>NH State House</name><city>Concord</city><id>671402</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.536620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WHAT: State House Training, Lunch, and ... support education freedom!&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Wed., Feb 11, 10:00 AM - 3:00 PM (come for the whole time, or, more importantly, just come just from 1:00-3:00 PM!)&lt;br /&gt;WHY:&lt;br /&gt;1) Learn how laws are really made in New Hampshire&lt;br /&gt;2) Become a more active Liberty Advocate&lt;br /&gt;3) Support education freedom! Even if you don't homeshcool, it is important to oppose extreme regulation, whoever it targets. First they came for the home-schoolers...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCHEDULE:&lt;br /&gt;10:00 AM - Meet in the State House cafeteria (in the basement -- ask anyone at the State House and they'll be happy to direct you). From here we will take a quick tour and sit in on some public hearings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30 AM - Lunch at one of the fine establishments in Concord (location TBD).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1:00 PM - Representatives Hall for public hearings on HB367 and HB368, two anti-homeschool bills that need to be fought. Come sign in on the blue sheets to register your opposition to these bills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you wish to present public testimony with something both specific and directly related to these two bills, sign up to testify with a pink card. Having a copy of your testimony for the members of the committee is recommended. Keep your remarks to no more than 3 minutes and do not repeat what others before you have said. It's OK to say something like, &amp;quot;My points have already been made, but I wish to register my opposition to this bill&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For updates, please visit this event on &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=65556706010" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234538115000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234151416000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>State House Training, Lunch, and Support Homeschooling!</name><id>9703206</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234364400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/9703206/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/f/a/global_3188554.jpeg</photo_url></item>