<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Overall moderate hike on Case Mountain, 744 ft. altitude. Hike will be for 3 hours and exact route depends on conditions. We'll go as far as we can. Generally we'll take the white trail to the peak, yellow trail on to the east side of the park and then north to the pond and back to white trail and out. The start of the hike from the parking lot is somewhat steep to the peak but after that it is much easier. We'll meet in the parking lot. Bring water.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A trail map can be found in the &amp;quot;50 Hikes in Connecticut&amp;quot; book (most recent edition for the East) by the Connecticute Forest and Parks Association. There is no meal planed for after this hike given I have to be to work by 11:30 AM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/direction via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=650+spring+st.&amp;amp;city=manchester&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topographical map of the area via Google Maps:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;q=299%2BCold%2BSprings%2BRd,+beacon+falls,+ct&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=41.445493,-73.069468&amp;amp;spn=0.018561,0.031929&amp;amp;t=p&amp;amp;z=15&amp;amp;iwloc=addr" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this hike is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt; ) so please direct questions on the hike to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1217655554000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><why>Try a weekday morning hike!</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1216703929000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to Case Mtn. in Manchester CT</name><id>8387006</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1217246400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/8387006/</event_url></item>