<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Main Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02818</zip><lat>41.663240</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>885-2200</phone><name>The Grille on Main</name><city>East Greenwich</city><id>907107</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449763</lon></venue><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;***UPDATE: Due to unprecidented demand for this restaurant, I am increasing the number of spaces for this event to 30.  The restaurant is willing to sit us in 2 tables of 15, with each table having it's own beverage bill and food bill.  This is a trial run, so let's hope it's a success!***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OK, everybody, thanks so much for being patient with me!  It has been &amp;quot;one of those months&amp;quot; so everything is kinda crazy right now.  Since that is the case, I went the sort of easy route and I picked one of my favorite restaurants this month.  It is the Grille on Main in East Greenwich.  It's a great restaurant with lots of ecclectic food choices, simple and easygoing environment.  This is the website to get more information &lt;a href="http://www.pinellimarrarestaurants.com/grill_on_main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, which includes a PDF of their menu.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because last month's payment went so smoothly, I am suggesting we do it that way again.  Basically we will have one bill for food, which will be divided equally among members then a second bill for beverages and alcohol.   This way we can order appetizers as a table and everyone can enjoy with minimal confusion.  Then the ones who choose not to indulge in &amp;quot;adult beverages&amp;quot; won't have to worry about paying extra when just enjoying non-alcoholic drinks.  Please let me know if this is a problem for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the meeting fills up, and you are interested in attending, please RSVP &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;, but add a note that you &amp;quot;would like to be wait listed&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, if you have paid the $1 towards Meetup fees at the last Dine Out event you attended, you do not need to pay this time.  I am trying to keep it where people only have to pay at every other event attended.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks again everyone for your patience!  I really enjoy this group and look forward to it every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's to good food and good conversation!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Please see my profile piccy to see what I look like(hint- I'm the one with red hair).  ;-)</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1209392154000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>8</count></rating><why>We're a great group of people and the restaurants so far have been excellent!</why><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>diningout-617</urlname><id>790320</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>25</yes_rsvp_count><created>1203781674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Rhode Island Dining Out April Meetup- The Grille on Main</name><id>7392174</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209164400000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/diningout-617/events/7392174/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/c/7/global_3518247.jpeg</photo_url></item>