<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>380 Winter Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.397719</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-890-7800</phone><name>Best Western</name><city>Waltham</city><id>746917</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.258767</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>December 17, 2009- Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;Networking Extravaganza and Charity Auction&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Networking Extravaganza and Auction Fundraiser for Rosie's Place &lt;br /&gt;Happy Holidays from BostonAREIA!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy Networking, Deals, Prizes and Fun!!!   Bring your deals, bring your business cards, bring your comfortable shoes! You'll want to speak to as many people as possible at this all-evening networking event. And we'll make sure we identify the people you want and need to speak to at the beginning of the evening, so you don't miss anyone who can help you build your business!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BostonAREIA Auction for Charity  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Bid on real estate investing products and bootcamps - all proceeds go to Rosie's Place, a sanctuary for poor and homeless women in Boston. BostonAREIA especially supports this non-profit because of it's dedication to prevention of homelessness and eviction.   Their homelessness prevention initiatives, such as rental assistance and support services, provide families the help they need to remain in their homes.   Give back to the community and gain valuable real estate investing knowledge!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Up for auction:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donna Bauer: The Notebuyer; Note Buying &amp;quot;The Ultimate Short Sale&amp;quot; (a $1,499 value!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Than Merrill: two tickets to his Marketing &amp;amp; Wholesaling&lt;br /&gt;Bootcamp ($2000 value!) Either February 4th to 7th in San Diego, CA or June 24th to 27th in Boston, MA &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wendy Patton:  2 tickets to her &amp;quot;Soft Market Investing&amp;quot; Bootcamp in spring 2010 ($1994 value!) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scott Meyers: The Complete Guide to Finding, Evaluating and Purchasing Self Storage Facilities ($1297 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray Giumentaro: 2 tickets to his &amp;quot;DNA of Success&amp;quot; Bootcamp, January 16-17, 2010  ($900 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nick Aalerud: 2 hours of real estate investing mentoring &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Linda Huuskonen: 2 tickets to her Powerhouse Wealth Strategies Workshop, January 9-10, 2010 ($595 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boston AREIA: 2 tickets to the Wholesale Workshop on February 6, 2010 (a $598 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sean Carpenter: 2 tickets to his bootcamp, Government Deal Funding for Real Estate Investors and Developers ($2,497 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kim Harrington: 1 ticket to her bootcamp, Maximizing Your Profits in Today's Hot Short Sale Market (a $995 value!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thomas Kish: course - &amp;quot;Real Estate Investors Guide: Creating Wealth Without Cash&amp;quot; and 4 hours of time to answer real estate investing questions and help with analyzing deals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to pre-bid on these items, please call Boston AREIA at 1-781-287-0270.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have original courses that you would be willing to donate to our auction? It's a great opportunity to clean out your closets, help Rosie's Place, help fellow investors, and have some fun at the same time!   Donated courses must be original and not copied.  We will obtain permission from the speakers to resell the donated courses for charity. If you would like to donate course, please e-mail dianne@bostonareia.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.memberize.com/clubportal/Fundraising.cfm?clubID=1762&amp;amp;campaignID=162" target="_blank"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to donate to Rosie's Place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monthly Meeting&lt;br /&gt;5:30 - 6:15 PM - Power Hour - Networking &lt;br /&gt;6:30 PM - Meeting &lt;br /&gt;Location: Best Western Hotel, 380 Winter St, Waltham, Ma &lt;br /&gt;Free to members, Visitors only $25 at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne Shvanda</member_name><member_id>7024028</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261266039000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>investing-376</urlname><id>551165</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>The Boston Area Real Estate Investors Association</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257297076000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Networking Extravaganza</name><id>11788175</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261092600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/investing-376/events/11788175/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/4/b/global_1787963.jpeg</photo_url></item>