<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be putting everyone on the waitlist and we will add people to the trip as soon as we review your answers to the questions and/or talk with you. There will be no more than 10 people total on the trip including organizers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; This is a cross post with the AMC, and you will have to register on that site too at this link: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/regi/343"&gt;regi/343&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. You don’t have to be an AMC member to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Read the entire description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;before you RSVP and &lt;strong&gt;answer all questions that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - if so, use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;What we're doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This trip is meant for experienced hikers who have overnight backpacking experience and are conditioned for hiking 13 miles/day with a lot of elevation gain and a full pack for part of the trip. Please do not sign up if you have never backpacked &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; if you haven't hiked more than 12 miles per day. The plan is to backpack two days, climbing six 4000 footers. We will begin our trip at the Ammonousuc campsite Friday night in Twin Mountain, NH. Alternatively you can meet us at the Zealand trailhead at 7:00 am.&lt;/span&gt; In the morning we will head over to Zealand (4260 ft.) through some steep ups and downs ~5.5 miles. We will drop our packs at the junction of the Zealand spur trail and hike to Zealand Mountain. Then we will continue our trip over Mt. Guyot to the tentsite. We will stop at the Guyot tentsite, unload and set up camp before going to the three Bonds. First we will summit Mt Bond (4698 ft), and then to Bondcliff (4265 ft.) and return to West Bond (4540ft.). If the group is too tired or it is too late, we may save West Bond for the second day. The first day will hike 13.2 miles with an elevation gain of 5203 ft. The book time for this hike 9 hours and 10 min, not including breaks and setting up our tents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The second day we will eat breakfast, pack up and hike 2.8 miles to South Twin (4902 ft.). We will then hike 1.3 miles to North Twin (4761 ft.) and then out the North Twin trail to the trailhead where we have spotted a car or two. Day two we will be hiking 8.5 miles with an elevation gain of&lt;/span&gt; 1,500 ft. with a book time of 5 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are a very slow hiker and expect us to constantly wait for you. We will not be rushing this hike, but you must be in appropriate physical condition and used to hiking with a full pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;- all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dogs are not permitted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;on this hike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~1.5 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike about 21.5 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 6,673 feet&lt;/strong&gt; over the two days which means hiking more than 14 hours, not including breaks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain. We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Weather&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.07655124823634&amp;amp;lon=-71.47404461425782"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;(noaa.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will finalize the details before the trip but be sure you have all the gear needed for a cold weather backpack. Guyot tentsite is very crowded and you will be expected to share a tent with someone else unless your tent is very small. We will discuss this prior to the trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation. Failure to bring the basics puts you and the rest of the group at risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions either refer to the list below or contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/492954/Moderate_Weather_Backpacking.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;Click for a list of required items needed for a cold weather backpacking trip&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for an idea of the required group gear needed for a warm weather backpacking trip&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;TENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;: This is not car camping – we won’t have unlimited space to set up our tents. Unless you will be using a one-person bivy sack or a one-person hammock you will need to share a tent with someone - use the comment section for this event to help coordinate this and the organizers will discuss with you too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;WATER PURIFICATION &amp;amp; STORAGE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;: Please make sure you&lt;/span&gt; have a water filter or some other method of purifying and storing you own water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;FOOD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;: Each person is responsible for his or her own food – you will need to carry it and cook it yourself. I have a supply of freeze dried entrees that you can purchase at cost with advance notice (or I wont bring it). Make sure you have plenty of snacks and lunch foods. You will need to store all your food and scented items in the bear locker on site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;STOVE &amp;amp; FUEL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;: We several stoves and fuel. I have a canister stove and a small pot suitable for boiling water but it's too small for more than 2 or 3 people. Let me know if you have a stove and pot and what type/size and we will coordinate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;MONEY:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;You will need to bring $8 cash to pay the caretaker if he or she is still there, plus ($5-10) cash for a pro-rata share of the campsite on Friday night if you are planning to join us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will finalize the details before the trip but be sure you have a little extra space in your backpack after you pack your gear. I will coordinate with everyone to make sure we have the necessary group gear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not assume others will have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;If you don't have what you need you will not be allowed to participate - even if you carpooled with someone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will be meeting at the Zealand Road trailhead (at the very end of Zealand Road) provided we have done a car spot the night before.  If not, we may need to meet at the North Twin trail instead. google maps: &lt;a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;q=zealand+road+nh&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=0x4cb477dc45da45d9:0x389b501a465ed572,Zealand+Rd,+Jefferson,+NH+03583&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=iYNrUI-PJ4f50gH4y4DgDg&amp;amp;ved=0CCEQ8gEwAA" class="linkified"&gt;https://maps.google.com/maps?oe=utf-8&amp;amp;client=firefox-a&amp;amp;q=zealand+road+nh&amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=0x4cb477dc45da45d9:0x389b501a465ed572,Zealand+Rd,+Jefferson,+NH+03583&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;ei=iYNr...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000FF"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Friday Night: Ammonousuc Campground Twin Mountain.  Sat 7 am Zealand Trailhead end of Zealand Road off 302 past Twin Mountain</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pam</member_name><member_id>6419698</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark Chiurri</member_name><member_id>46583982</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350814017000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349228919000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Backpack the Bonds and the Twins--Advanced</name><id>85226942</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>126000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350687600000</time><rsvp_limit>2</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/85226942/</event_url></item>