<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before signing up for this event, Please read the entire Write Up and understand and agree to the enclosed Liability Waiver.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Event Rating:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; font-size : small"&gt;MODERATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Distance:&lt;/span&gt; 4.5 &lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; font-size : medium"&gt;MILES&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Time Duration&lt;/span&gt;: 2&lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; font-size : medium"&gt;  HOURS&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Blaze Orange&lt;/span&gt;:NOT  &lt;span style="color : #ff6600 ; font-size : medium"&gt;REQUIRED&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone ,sorry for the late posting .We will be venturing back  into Snake Den   State Park this weekend . Our host will be  Arthur R. Iannelli. It  has  been said this is Rhode Island ' s best keep secret or even a hidden gem  . Snake Den has its towering 394'  summit . Don't laugh, It will at least  offer us a descent view of the valley . There are plenty of outcroppings small streams farmland  and yes a quarry .  This hike will be approximately 4.5 miles at a moderate pace and should take about 2  hours..&lt;strong&gt;Please bring water,and food .Hydrate before the hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arthur&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following was taken from a state website .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The State of Rhode Island acquired the land, now known as Snake Den State Park in 1969. It is a combination of farm land and woodland and comprises 744 acres. The prior owners were many generations of the Dame family and, before that the Steere family, an old family throughout Johnston and surrounding towns. DEM’s headquarters for the Parks and Recreation Division is housed in a 22 room former farm house of the Palazzi family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name, Snake Den, derives from a canyon-like stone fissure located in the park. Like other farms in the Johnston area, the stone in the Snake Den outcrop was quarried for building material for Providence. The actual location of the quarry is on that portion of the property once owned by the Waterman family. Its stone was used in the building of the First Congregational Church in Providence, better known as the First Unitarian Church, designed by John Holden Greene, one the Benefit Street landmarks on historic College Hill. The nearby quarry of Bear Ledge provided the incredible columns for the Providence Arcade of 1828.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Liability Waiver &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Safety First!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Arthur</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur R. Iannelli</member_name><member_id>27636382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366047874000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RhodeIslandhikingclub</urlname><id>1527097</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Hiking Club        " Walks and Rambles "</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365971710000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snake Den State Park</name><id>114328132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1365972300000</time><rsvp_limit>5</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RhodeIslandhikingclub/events/114328132/</event_url></item>