<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;DAY/TIME:&lt;/b&gt; Wednesday, July 29, 3 p.m. to ????? I'll be there until around dinnertime (I have a dinner date). NOTE: I have an appointment at 1:30, so can't be at the Studio until 3, but if another Studio member can be there earlier, we'll move the start time back to earlier in the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AGENDA:&lt;/b&gt; No scheduled activities. Arrive and leave when you want. Work on your own projects at your own pace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;AMENITIES:&lt;/b&gt; Free parking. Table space and a chair. Access to some tools (paper cutter, heat gun, etc.). Access to a fridge, microwave, toaster oven, kitchen sink and restroom; access to Wi-Fi if you need to use your computer while you're there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; $5, regardless of how long you stay. If people would like dinner, we can go out or get take-out (so bring a little extra cash for that, if you're interested).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHO MAY ATTEND:&lt;/b&gt;Any member of the NE ATC+ or Altered Art/Assemblage Meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/b&gt; Your own materials and projects to work on (just as you do for the regular Meetup; if you're a newbie, see &amp;quot;What to Bring to a Meetup&amp;quot; in the Files section.) A few basic supplies--scissors, glue, tape, etc. -- are available for loan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HOW TO SIGN UP:&lt;/b&gt; You must RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; using Meetup's RSVP function so we know who's coming and how many to expect. If your plans change, PLEASE switch your RSVP to “no” ASAP. &lt;u&gt;Please RSVP even if you're a Studio member who's planning to be there anyway.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANCELLATIONS:&lt;/b&gt; If you must cancel after the Open Studio has started -- PLEASE e-mail the Open Studio host. If we need to cancel for any reason (highly unlikely, but it could happen) we'll post a message here AND e-mail anyone who's signed up. For your own protection, we suggest checking your e-mail just before you leave the house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRANSPORTATION/DIRECTIONS:&lt;/b&gt; Sorry, we cannot provide or arrange transportation of any kind. If interested in sharing a ride, you may post a notice on the Message Board to see if anyone can help out. Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>They'll know me.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>emelengy</member_name><member_id>4250560</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Pat</member_name><member_id>4858394</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250105475000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247579399000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Studio at ArtStudio 360  in Holliston</name><id>10873148</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1248894000000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/10873148/</event_url></item>