<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>943 Namquid Drive</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02888</zip><lat>41.741898</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-572-3390</phone><name>Game On!</name><city>Warwick</city><id>1111698</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405803</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Get your game on every other Wednesday with D&amp;amp;D Encounters, an ongoing mini-campaign where you’ll play two encounters every other week at your local game store. Earn exclusive rewards as you gain Renown Points for accomplishments made during each season!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Season 3 takes place at the historic and timeless classic &amp;quot;Keep on the Borderlands.&amp;quot;  This season is all about the new D&amp;amp;D Essentials line of products, utilizing rules that allow new players to get in on the ground floor of 4th edition while granting veteran players a whole new set of character options.  There are pre-generated characters available or if you'd like, you can use the rules out of the D&amp;amp;D &amp;quot;Red Box&amp;quot; and the &amp;quot;Heroes of the Fallen Lands&amp;quot; to create your own.  This season spans twenty weeks with five chapters of four encounters.  It'll span from late September to early February.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have friends or family interested in D&amp;amp;D and looking for a great introduction to what 4th edition has to offer, have them come and join us for an evening of adventure at Veteran's Gaming in Warwick.  Sessions will start at 6PM and should run from 2-3 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who played in Seasons 1 and 2, Rewards Cards earned in those adventures are fully legal for use in all subsequent seasons.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanios</member_name><member_id>4187193</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297044249000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Gamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dnd-240</urlname><id>47127</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>The Rhode Island Gamers Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283450571000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>D&amp;D Encounters Season 3:  Keep on the Borderlands</name><id>vwbkpypdbdb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1296687600000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dnd-240/events/15926915/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/f/global_6578223.jpeg</photo_url></item>