<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Everything is coming together for our incoming call center in Marlborough, MA.  We have a room with tables, chairs, and phones.  We are in need of several computers, monitors, keyboards, and mice so we can enter the data directly into the database.  Can anybody loan us some?  We're still working on the list and the scripts.  We hope to finalize everything Saturday morning and start making calls in the afternoon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We plan to operate all day, every day, until further notice.  We have acquired a 5-line call center, and we have the option of expanding as our operation grows.  (Hopefully, some of the people we contact will become call center volunteers!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once we get up to speed, we want at least 6 volunteers onsite at all times, although we can operate with fewer when necessary.  We'll use the meetup calendar to schedule volunteers.  I'll create different meetup events for various time periods throughout the day.  RSVP for as many slots as you can.  The second American Revolution needs you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This specific meetup event is for the timeslot on Saturday from 10 am - 2 pm.  Don't expect everything to be running smoothly on our first day.  This is complex stuff, and we're doing the best we can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This should be more fun than the &amp;quot;cold calling&amp;quot; we were doing before.  Here's how it works.  A computer system somewhere makes many simultaneous calls with our recorded message.  If the call recipient is a Ron Paul supporter, they press &amp;quot;*&amp;quot; to talk to a live volunteer.  The system transfers the call to us, and one of our 5 phone lines rings.  The system automatically throttles its output calls to keep our incoming lines busy, but not overflowing.  (Cool, eh?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The computer system deals with hangups, answering machines, and rude responses.  You only get calls from Ron Paul supporters!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This technology has been used before, including in Nevada, our best finish yet!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Cunningham</member_name><member_id>1757740</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1201533106000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1690</urlname><id>950430</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Massachusetts Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201182772000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Setting up phone banking</name><id>7185379</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201359600000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1690/events/7185379/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/b/global_2993979.jpeg</photo_url></item>