<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Okay guys, we've got dinner plans for the Scavenger Hunt!!  Yippee!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be eating at the Thai Place, hopefully around 5 p.m., but with the chaos of the Saturday before Halloween in the Halloween mecca of New England, be prepared for some waiting:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at 4:30 at the National Park Service Salem Visitor Center (2 New Liberty St Salem, MA 01970) the same site of our hunt meeting (at 6:30), and then head to the restaurant together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For anyone taking the 4:30 Commuter Rail out of Boston, just meet us at the restaurant at 5 pm or as soon as you can get there.  We'll save a spot for you as long as I know you're coming.  So please RSVP with a definitive yes (and make a note about your plans), or you'll be stuck sitting at another table:-).  Thai Place is located in Museum place mall, next to the cinema on Church street.  Check out the website for directions: &lt;a href="http://www.thaiplace.net/direction_map.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thaiplace....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know that you are definitively coming with a yes RSVP so we can arrange a table to the best of our ability amidst the chaos of Halloween in Salem.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be meeting in front of the Visitor Center at 4:30, or look for our table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225139567000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224776126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pre-Scavenger Hunt Dinner at Thai Place</name><id>9017932</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224966600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/9017932/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>