<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Gulu-Gulu has a regular Monday night game night that they are looking to beef up the attendance for, and I am more than happy to oblige by posting an event on our calendar.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have quite a few members who have an interest in Trivial Pursuit, especially the board game Trivial Pursuit: In Pursuit (which is a teams version of the game for 4-8 players); however, we always have too many people to bust it out at game nights.  So, I thought it would be perfect to give the game its own Meetup limited to 8 players.  Now, should we wind up having less than 4 people who can attend, I will bring a different edition of Trivial Pursuit.  Either way, it should be a fun night of trivia.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gulu-Gulu is accessible to most of downtown Salem.  Parking can usually be found on Washington St., in the Church St. lot, and in the lot between Lynde and Essex Streets (by the YMCA).  Gulu-Gulu has a great food and beverage menu that can be found at www.gulu-gulu.com.  I do request that when we hold Meetups in food or drink establishments that everyone in attendance order at least one item or beverage.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note, the above listed phone number belongs to Liv not to Gulu-Gulu.  It is to be used should you need to contact me the evening of the event.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the one there with Trivial Pursuit.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Liv and David</member_name><member_id>2975279</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221861108000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Game Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>salemboardgames</urlname><id>636262</id><group_lat>42.5200004578</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9000015259</group_lon><name>The Salem Board Games Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219969640000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Trivial Pursuit at Gulu-Gulu</name><id>8643707</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221517800000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/salemboardgames/events/8643707/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/9/1/global_2907729.jpeg</photo_url></item>