<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>23 Pleasant Street</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04011</zip><lat>43.914007</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>725-5242</phone><name>Curtis Memorial Library</name><city>Brunswick</city><id>1194587</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.967528</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>suggested donation @door</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a 3-hour introductory evening workshop with Lisa Fernandes on how to &lt;strong&gt;plan, convene and get results from Open Space meetings&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Open Space Technology (not "open space" as in land preservation) democratizes and decentralizes the meeting process and harnesses the passion and creativity of participants to create astoundingly effective outcomes. &amp;nbsp;Many people from around Maine are expressing interest in experimenting with this technique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3063/2919311068_b8629e0994.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This session is suitable for anyone who would like to &lt;strong&gt;re-energize the work of their group&lt;/strong&gt; or organization, finds ways to &lt;strong&gt;engage more people&lt;/strong&gt; in meaningful efforts and action, and those who are eager to &lt;strong&gt;experiment with this technique&lt;/strong&gt; to see how it could work for them. &amp;nbsp;This is not just for people who find themselves in the facilitator role, but for &lt;strong&gt;all people who want to get good work done in groups&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Far from being unstructured, Open Space provides &lt;strong&gt;just the right amount of structure&lt;/strong&gt; so that the participants' energy and passion turn the meeting into an effective vehicle for engagement and effective outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5:30 Welcomes &amp;amp; Introductions (All)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6:00 to 7:30 Nuts-and-Bolts of Open Space (Planning, Convening, Follow-up)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7:30-8:30 "Mini Open Space"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8:30 Closing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-hosted by Merrymeeting Permaculture &amp;amp; Transition&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pls use the comments are to organize carpools if needed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/9/e/event_103071102.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;More about Open Space:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Open Space Technology is one way to enable all kinds of people, in any kind of organization, to create inspired meetings and events. Over the last 20+ years, it has also become clear that opening space, as an intentional leadership practice, can create inspired organizations, where ordinary people work together to create extraordinary results with regularity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In Open Space meetings, events and organizations, participants create and manage their own agenda of parallel working sessions around a central theme of strategic importance, such as: What is the strategy, group, organization or community that all stakeholders can support and work together to create?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With groups of 5 to 2000+ people -- working in one-day workshops, three-day conferences, or the regular weekly staff meeting -- the common result is a powerful, effective connecting and strengthening of what's already happening in the organization: planning and action, learning and doing, passion and responsibility, participation and performance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href="http://www.openspaceworld.org/"&gt;Open Space World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking is on the street or in the library parking lot on the street behind it http://www.curtislibrary.com/about-us/directions/</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Amory Weld</member_name><member_id>8312043</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason Rawn</member_name><member_id>39592512</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333980507000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332249878000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Occupy Your Agenda: An Introduction to Open Space Meetings</name><id>57096532</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333661400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/57096532/</event_url></item>