<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>US-202</address_2><address_1>231 Litchfield Turnpike</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06057</zip><lat>41.819870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nepaug State Forest</name><city>New Hartford</city><id>733897</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.958260</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/c/1/5/event_23183573.jpeg" width="310" height="206" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am continuing my slow recovery from achilles tendon surgery.&amp;nbsp; This&amp;nbsp;is a beautiful area near Satan's Kingdom and includes the Tunxis Trail.&amp;nbsp; I am doing a 5 mile loop that will include the&amp;nbsp;Tipping Rock loop and&amp;nbsp;the Rome Spare Outlook.&amp;nbsp; I cannot guestimate the time because I cannot predict the speed.&amp;nbsp; Those of you who want to sprint through the woods, this is not for you.&amp;nbsp; We are not meandering but the pace will be reasonable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will begin at the Nepaug Park entrance off Rt. 202. &lt;strong&gt;To get there, at the intersection of Rts. 44 and 202 in Canton, travel west on 202 for 3 miles.&amp;nbsp; The Nepaug State Park sign and entrance will be on the right.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; When you pull in continue down the road about 1/4 mile.&amp;nbsp; There is a parking area of sorts on the left hand side. NO BATHROOMS...be warned.&amp;nbsp; I included the link to the trail map for those who would like to know the plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/backpacking/NepaugCampSite2.pdf"&gt;http://www.ct.gov/dep/lib/dep/stateparks/maps/backpacking/NepaugCampSite2.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This a hike out in the woods so plan on bringing a small pack, water, &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lunch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, bug spray, sunscreen, waterproof boots, layered clothing, camera.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As at my events, NO DOGS, NO CHILDREN please.&amp;nbsp; This is an adult only outing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on "Count me in" or "Yes" or "Maybe" for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Jeep Liberty</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Janice</member_name><member_id>3804430</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>3</waitlist_count><updated>1306073838000</updated><rating><average>4.73000001907</average><count>11</count></rating><why>Getting outside with like minded people is great.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304600810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hiking at Nepaug State Forest (Tunxis Trail-Tipping Rock Loop) Canton, CT</name><id>17553963</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1305381600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/17553963/</event_url></item>