<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Skyline Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01605</zip><lat>42.282416</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Green Hill Park</name><city>Worcester </city><id>918893</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.775371</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, the Greater Worcester Humanists get together to get some sun and have a cookout! They have burgers, hot dogs, veggie burgers for the morally superior, and lots of side dishes and wonderful desserts from the membership's fine chefs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once all are plump and satisfied, there's more time to get some sun and play outside. There are lively sessions of volleyball, frisbee, cricket, and whatever else people want to play at. Or, folks just sit back, soak it all in, and chat with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year's outing is back at Green Hill Park in Worcester on Saturday, June 16th from 11AM to 3PM. The GHW organizes would love for any like-minded folks in the area to come on out. Bring the whole family as this is a most kid-friendly event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is free and open to all. This is also a great opportunity to introduce curious people to the local secular community; so feel free to invite that guy in the office who always asks about Humanism, or that friend who's been talking about wanting to hit a meeting. &lt;br /&gt;

 If you can't make the meeting and want to contribute, please feel free to contact worcesterhumanists@yahoo.com. For more information, visit the GWH event page at &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/63181022/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/63181022/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339870410000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1338294495000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer Day Out at the Park with the Worcester Humanists</name><id>66753132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339858800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/66753132/</event_url></item>