<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Deb recommended this walk and it does seem like there is lots to see there, so lets explore the beach before it gets too crowded in the summer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the Caddy Memorial Park parking lot at 11:00. From there we will explore the trails in the salt marsh, then walk along Wollaston Beach and take in the scenery. There are plenty of restaurants there and we will choose one for lunch after the walk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some of teh descriptions I found on the web:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located on Quincy Shore Drive, Quincy's largest beach offers 2.5 miles of clean sand, swimming, lifeguards, free parking, a bathhouse with public restrooms, restaurants, and local activities such as a volleyball challenge during the summer months.&lt;br /&gt;Caddy Memorial Park, named for Private First Class William R. Caddy, USMCR (1925-1945), is located along Black’s Creek and across from Wollaston Beach Reservation. Caddy Memorial Park and Black's Creek Salt Marsh were used by the Native Americans for fishing, shellfishing, and hunting. Colonists harvested salt hay from the marsh and established several tide grist mills around the estuary. The park is significant not only for its beauty, but also for its history. In 1999, when a new playground was being built at the park, Massachusetts state archeologist Brona Simon discovered rare Native American artifacts, including 256 stone tools, on the site.&lt;br /&gt;Quincy Shore Reservation offers a variety of recreational opportunities. Quincy Shore Drive links Wollaston Beach with Caddy memorial Park and Moswetuset Hummock. The 2.3 mile beach is popular for its jogging/bicycling trail and swimming. Caddy Park on the southern end of the beach has over 15 acres of fields and marsh as well as a play area, lookout tower and picnic tables. Moswetuset Hummock, on the beach's northern end, is a National Historic Site. Once a summer campsite of Native Americans during the 1600's, it is a mixture of woodland trails and open marshland. The site which has a short loop trail, offers views of Quincy Bay and 144-acre Squantum Marsh.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1243869049000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240347415000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quicy's Wollaston Beach </name><id>10236596</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243695600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/10236596/</event_url></item>