<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>204 S Main St</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.823138</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-272-3970</phone><name>Cable Car Cinema</name><city>Providence</city><id>763529</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.405437</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Cable Car Cinema in Providence is showing "WUNDERKINDER", a German movie on Monday, February 18th and although it's part of the Providence Children's Film Festival and although it revolves around three 8-year-olds, this Englisch subtitled film is geared more to an adult audience, since it involves the invasion of soviet Ukraine in 1941 by the Nazis and their imposition of strict racial rules whose aim was the extermination of Jews:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in 1941 during World War II in the Ukraine, Wunderkinder tells the story of three exceptionally talented children who have to learn to use their musical skill, their undying friendship and all their courage to survive in the face of a grown up world gone mad.The young and highly talented violinist Abrascha (Elin Kolev) and the no less gifted pianist Larissa (Imogen Burrell) are celebrated as child prodigies of classical music. They play in all of Russia’s great concert halls – before the party elite and even Stalin himself, Hanna (Mathilda Adamik), daughter of the German brewer Max Reich (Kai Wiessinger), is herself a talented violinist and wishes for nothing with more desire than to be taught with the Russian “Wunderkinder.” Larissa and Abrascha react with caution. Only when their teacher Irina Salmonova (Gudrun Landgrebe) consents to teach Hanna as well does a close friendship develop between the children. But it is soon put to a hard test...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Projo gave WUNDERKINDER a great 4-star review!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie starts at 6.15 p.m. but I plan on being there half an hour early to get tickets and popcorn :-).Tickets are $ 7.50 for adults, $ 5 for children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope some of you will join me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ich wuensche allen ein schoenes Wochenende!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Hanna&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the German flag!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Hanna</member_name><member_id>3913437</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361245455000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Language &amp; Culture Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>language-63</urlname><id>531356</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence German Language Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1360938477000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WUNDERKINDER - 4-star rated German movie playing a the Cable Car Cinema!</name><id>104731782</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361227500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/language-63/events/104731782/</event_url></item>