<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Starr King Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03584</zip><lat>44.418267</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Starr King Trailhead</name><city>Jefferson</city><id>1247432</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.468010</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: &amp;nbsp;Ashley&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;read the entire event listing&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;before you RSVP and&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;answer all of the questions&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;that are part of the RSVP process. If you RSVP from a mobile device you may not see them - visit the site using a computer so you can answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your safety and the safety of the group is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of the trip; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you may put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiking safely is about being prepared to respond to an emergency situation or being able to spend a night in the woods if you have to. Bring your own stuff and know how to use it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=================================================&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We're Doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come join me on a moderately paced, 7.2 mile round trip hike to Mt. Waumbek, standing proudly at 4006' and occupying rank# 46 on NH's 48 4000-footer list. &amp;nbsp;I know, I know...it's not a Prezzie and not Franconia Ridge, however if you are working on your Winter 48, it's gotta be done at some time. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are newish to winter hiking, this is a good starter mountain. &amp;nbsp;The first 2.6 miles on the Starr King Trail are a gradual climb until we reach Mt. Starr King (3907'), which does offer some views and a good place to rest/grab an extended snack (as long as temps are not too blistery). &amp;nbsp;From there we "press on" for another 1 mile until we reach our goal, Mt. Waumbek at 4006'.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We will start as a group, and finish as a group. &amp;nbsp;Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's meet at the parking spot near the Starr King Trail trailhead at 930A. &amp;nbsp;Please try to be on-time. &amp;nbsp;Jefferson, NH is approximately 170 miles from Boston, and a little over 3hrs driving time. &amp;nbsp;This doesn't factor in gas fill-ups, carpooling meet-up, and/or coffee and its related bathroom stops.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This hike is for the most part wooded with no ridge exposure, however expect winter conditions (it is winter, and we are hiking our Winter 48, ya know); so pack accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am allowing guests and dogs on this hike.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;===================================================&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This trip is considered&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;MODERATE&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/photos/2030971/"&gt;Click here for information about&amp;nbsp;our trip ratings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I have traveled these trails many times, but also&amp;nbsp;researched this trip using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;=========================================================&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. The higher we climb the colder, windier, and wetter it will be - we will need to be prepared. Remember, on average it gets 3-4 degrees (Fahrenheit) colder for every 1,000 feet of elevation gain. Wind chill becomes a serious danger at these elevations in winter conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day before this event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====================================================&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or out on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. While we may not need snow shoes on the hike you need to bring them to the trailhead - know how to attach them to your pack in case we do need to bring them along. Traction - microspikes or Hillsound trail crampons (which are not actually crampons) required. &amp;nbsp;Bring crampons with you to the trailhead (and know how to use them), and we will assess whether or not these are needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and conducts heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket (e.g. fleece or down). Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants (e.g. gore-tex). Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, neck warmer, and glove liners. &amp;nbsp;Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens&amp;nbsp;(e.g. gore-tex).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip -&amp;nbsp;do not rely on a&amp;nbsp;hydration pack (even an insulated one)&amp;nbsp;because the hose tends to freeze. Use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead (e.g. nalgene).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;You should always be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket (which packs small and weighs just ounces).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries (lithium work best in colder temperatures). Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera. &amp;nbsp;Sled (in case there is enough snow to sled back down the trail). &amp;nbsp;Your silly side. &amp;nbsp;Your sense of humor. &amp;nbsp;Your ability to play "Name That Tune" as I am the song-belting master. &amp;nbsp;Thermos with hot cocoa or soup to share with your new friends. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;====================================================&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate&amp;nbsp;in this activity; you know and will follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/index.php?page=hiker-responsibility-code"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>White Lincoln MKX with MA Plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ashley Carneal</member_name><member_id>7483830</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326137944000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325703832000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH Winter 48 - Mt. Waumbek  (Moderate)</name><id>46648032</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325946600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/46648032/</event_url></item>