<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a local paddle to replace the Saturday rained out event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 77. North wind between 5 and 9 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tides will be in our favor to go down stream all the way past Seldon via the CT river,&lt;br /&gt;then go up Seldon Creek, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch somewhere on the Island or near Walebaone Cove entrance,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later the tide will offer an access to this area on our way back..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More DETAILS TO FOLLOW LATER TODAY WHEN I HAVE TIME TO ADD INFO.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Might as well start out a bit earlier and call it quits earlier also. we can do our lunch right on Seldon Island or somewhere on the way while out on the water: Pack a good lunch might not have time for our traditional late barbie-q&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunset is at 7 pm now.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I dont think anyone wants to do a barbie-q ??? maybe at Gillette Castle ??&lt;br /&gt;or just go home..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hadlyme Ferry launch area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Follow the signs to Gillette Castle but keep heading a bit past it to the south&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting There, From Hartford,&lt;br /&gt;take I-91 south: take Exit 22s. (left hand exit) = Route 9 South , take Exit 7, (rte 82 to the Goodspeed Oprah House)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;at the end of the exit ramp take a left onto Middlesex tpk=rte 154 for a few hundred feet then back onto rte 82 east, cross the river and pass the oprah house (stay on 82), go up the hill till you reach the intersection of rte 151..take a right there, stay on 82, about the 4 th road on the right is River Road=rte 431, take River Road down for about a mile and a half..Then look for Gillette Castle Park Road Entrance on the right..&lt;br /&gt;BUT KEEP GOING PAST IT..&lt;br /&gt;The road name changes to Geer Hill Road and ends at ret 148= Ferry Road,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take a right on to Ferry Road, take the parking lot entrance just before the ferry.&lt;br /&gt;Unload there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For GPS / maps: this location dosent have a good address for them, but for the closest LANDMARK use 100 Geer Hill Road, Old Lyme,&lt;br /&gt;and or just follow the directions above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking Location:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atlantickayaktours.com/pages/subpages/other/Maps/Selden-Island.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.atlanticka...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tide Info:&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Hadlyme starting with September 13, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Su  13      Low   1:30 AM     0.4   6:28 AM    Rise 12:02 AM      41&lt;br /&gt;    13     High   7:01 AM     2.4   7:02 PM     Set  3:50 PM&lt;br /&gt;    13      Low   1:28 PM     0.5&lt;br /&gt;    13     High   7:39 PM     3.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this RIVER  trip with WERNER Fiberglass and  Carbon paddles with paddle leaches..Now All Kayaks come with &amp;quot;Yakpads&amp;quot; brand Gel High Back Seats also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ya wont get that from your local Rent-A-Yak places..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lady, Short Sea Kayak Necky Eliza Fiberglass Version 16 ' with Fibergalss Werner or Greenland Paddle or Heavy Plastic paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak, Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed, with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak Riot Tourlite 15', with Fiberglass Werner Camano or Greenland wood paddle= ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak, Cobra Expidition SOT 18', with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner Wind Dancer 18', Long sea Kayak with Werner Carbon Kaliste Paddle= ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red NDK Greenlander Pro 18', Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Werner Fiberglass Camano Paddle or Greenland wood Paddle or heavy plastic paddle= = ?????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;see ya soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1253466815000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252672446000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kayucking at WaleBoane Cove and Seldom Creak &amp; I Land @ the CT River in Hadalime</name><id>11346129</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252857600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11346129/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/0/3/global_4970051.jpeg</photo_url></item>