<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 6</address_2><address_1>163 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02053</zip><lat>42.147101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 533-0669</phone><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name><city>Medway</city><id>911296</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.427202</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Circle of Angels Gathering&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;March 17th&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7pm - 9pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cost $25 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Presented By Patricia Rainville...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.Patricia has been in the health and wellness business for 20 years. It began in 1990 with massage school where I found my true calling in the fields of alternative medicines and energies. While there I became interested in Reiki healing energy and became a reiki master. I also became interested in aromatherapy and herbs as a way to enhance healing and spent a season apprenticing with an herbalist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Angels uplift and inspire us. They help to lighten our burdens and thereby help us to remember a lightness of being that is joyful and happy where things go more smoothly. Connect with the angels often, you'll be pleasantly surprised and delighted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Circle of Angels is a spiritual meditation gathering. At each gathering we invoke the Archangels Michael and Raphael for clearing and healing and obtain individual message for those who attend. &lt;br /&gt;

The evening begins with a clearing meditation that will cleanse your energy and aura of fear cords, psychic debris, negative energies or entities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Circle of Angels is a small gathering of about 6 - 8 people and each person receives hands on energy healing and a message. After this each attendant pull a card from an angel card oracle deck for additional details to your message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

There is also time at the end of the evening for sharing of experiences. People usually leave feeling relaxed, refreshed and revitalized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Please be aware that the class is limited to 8 people. If you are interested in joining the class please call or email to reserve your spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email solsticehealing@yahoo.com or Call 508-533-0669&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Solstice Healing</member_name><member_id>9244342</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363572470000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center</urlname><id>1422661</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Solstice Healing Arts Center</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361824927000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Circle of Angels</name><id>106366002</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1363561200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Solstice-Healing-Arts-Center/events/106366002/</event_url></item>