<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Upper Mill Brook Conservation Area (60.6 acres) is a diverse property which contains both open and wooded swamps, deciduous woodland, a brook and several ponds, with beavers in residence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While a basic tour takes about 45 minutes, additional extensions onto Wayland conservation land can add up to another 2 hours. The main trail is easy; however the extension to Claypit Hill Road is moderately difficult.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;trail map at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.svtweb.org/upper-mill-brook-conservation-area" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.svtweb.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;Peace Lutheran Church at 107 Concord Road (Route 126) allows its parking lot to be used for public parking when it is not being used for church activities; please avoid Sunday morning. There are also footpath entrances from Concord Road, Glezen Lane and Claypit Hill Road. From the intersection of Routes 126 and 27 in Wayland (at the Wayland Public Library, just north of Route 20), go north on Route 126 approximately 1 mile to the Peace Lutheran Church on your right. Park at the back of their parking lot; an informational kiosk is located in the back of their lawn, behind a small fenced in playground, the trail starts from the kiosk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunch afterwards at:&lt;br /&gt;Sky Sudbury&lt;br /&gt;120 Boston Post Road (Rte 20)&lt;br /&gt;Sudbury, MA 01776 &lt;br /&gt;Tel: 1.978.440.8855&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sky-restaurant.com/design/v2/content/sudbury/sudbury_menu_lunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.sky-restau...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1228750527000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226889844000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Upper Mill Brook Conservation Area walk</name><id>9176151</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228577400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9176151/</event_url></item>