<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Meeting fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>James E Richardson is an Industrial Designer and new-product development consultant who was based in southeastern Connecticut for 25 years until recently relocating in southern Maine. He has been involved in developing industrial and consumer products for major corporations like Anhueser Busch, Miller Brewing, and News America-in-Store, and has consulted on numerous new product based entrepreneurial startups. Some of his past projects can be viewed at www.richardson-assoc.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Mr. Richardson has been awarded 19 US patents for product innovations,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;was the president of the Connecticut chapter of the Inventors Association, (IACT) and has been the subject of numerous articles in national publications like the N.Y. Times and Fortune magazine. He has been a regular guest speaker at the University of Maine law school entrepreneurial seminars and a speaker at inventor and entrepreneurial organizations in the Northeast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Last year Mr. Richardson, along with marketing clients, invented and developed two new products. One licensed product is called SunCalc, which lets gardeners place plantings in ideal light conditions. The other product is a unique cooler for draft beer that is being contract manufactured in the US and sold exclusively to Anhueser Busch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; His talk will outline the process of developing a new product using solid modelling and SLR prototyping methods as a development tool. He will show other prototyping methods using past projects as examples.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Jim, his artist wife Suzanne, and their “still-under-restoration lobster yatch” live in Eliot Maine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;www.richardson-assoc.com&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the SEC Education Room 1st Level</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Cormier</member_name><member_id>6323188</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244065314000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Innovators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>innovation-49</urlname><id>987180</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5400009155</group_lon><name>Innovators' Resource Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233795007000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Innovators' Resource Network April Meetup</name><id>9675664</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238625900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/innovation-49/events/9675664/</event_url></item>