<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>The movie tickets are available now.  I strongly advise those who wish to see the show to get them in advance.  The show time is at 7PM.   Lets meet at the escalators at 6:30 PM.  For those of you new to the group, we meet at the lobby level, in front of the escalators next to the front entrance.  I wear a little badge to help those who don't know me already to find me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We usually grab something to eat/drink after the show.   We often go to a nearby brewery after the show, but I am open to other ideas.  Anyone know a good chinese restaurant that is not too far a walk from the theater?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next movie in the crazy Pirates of the Caribbean releases this weekend.   Call me crazy, but I loved the first two and wouldn't dream of missing the third.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope some of you enjoy these films as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like some more details on the film, check out:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.darkhorizons.com/2007/piratesofthecaribbean3.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.darkhorizo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update with film times when they become available.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did check on line and tickets are not yet available for this show.    Buying ahead will probably be wise and I will keep my eye out for when they do become available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1180391827000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1178040852000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pirates of the Caribbean</name><id>5729185</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1180218600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/5729185/</event_url></item>