<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Blue Hills Reservation is certainly the best destination for hikers looking for a great experience without the hassle of driving for 3 hours to New Hampshire or Eastern Massachusetts. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On this 6-mile loop in Blue Hills Reservation, you’ll see dense hardwoods, meadows, ponds, glacial leftovers, rocky hills, and sweeping views of Boston. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Direction to traihead: I-93 S to exit 5B (MA 28 N/Milton). Take MA 28 N for .5 mi. and park in small dirt clearing on L.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail Description:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will hop on blue-blazed Skyline Trail to Blue Hills Reservation Location: 42.21457°, -71.06989° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Swing R @ 2054 marker onto gravel road, then cross Hillside St. Location: 42.21235°, -71.09251° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Look for blue-blazed North Skyline Trail to L of park HQ building Location: 42.21435°, -71.09410° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At five Corners; bear R, staying on Skyline toward Great Blue Hill Location: 42.21700°, -71.10267° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quick side trip: Bear R @ Y for beautiful picnic spots near two ponds; return to main trail and turn R for Woolcott Hill. Then it’s a steep, rocky ascent of Great Blue Hill Location: 42.21615°, -71.10551° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summit: Stone tower with views of skyline and harbor. Continue W on Skyline Trail .1 mi. to weather observatory (founded 1885) then retrace E on Skyline Trail for .05 mi. and turn R onto S. Skyline Trail Location: 42.21358°, -71.11266° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R onto blue-blazed S. Skyline Trail for rocky descent, then uphill through pines and past glacial remains Location: 42.21258°, -71.11265° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cross Hillside St.; L then quick R through parking lot, following Skyline Trail; in .1 mi., when Skyline Trail goes L, continue straight on gravel road then bear L on paved Bugbee Path, heading uphill Location: 42.21282°, -71.09682° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;L onto orange-blazed Massachuseuck Trail (where road widens); at next T-junction, go L onto Doe Hollow Path Location: 42.21102°, -71.08990° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bear R, leaving Doe Hollow Path; continue on orange-blazed trail; gradual climb on loose rock and packed-dirt trail Location: 42.21308°, -71.07898° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;R to rejoin Skyline Trail (blue and orange trails overlap) to trailhead Location: 42.21468°, -71.07159° &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All maybes will be changed to No's on December 9 so that anyone interested in going may attend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>DIANNE AND I WILL BE IN A BLACK TOYOTA ECHO WITH MAINE PLATES</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>2</waitlist_count><updated>1230223972000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225998701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SKYLINE TRAIL LOOP</name><id>9107717</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229263200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9107717/</event_url></item>