<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Route 117/Bus #70 or #170</address_2><address_1>1056 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.376331</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-891-7677</phone><name>Cafe Angelinos</name><city>Waltham</city><id>931399</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.254417</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>“ We had 13  A*W*E*S*O*M*E  cribbage and King Cribbage players that all had a great time from 6 until 10 last night! Come on down and join us May 18 :) ”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Denise, after you left Mark could do no wrong, he was on a  H*I*G*H roller gang buster winning streak and left ME in the dust! Mark, don't ever let this happen again, okay, please :(&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We welcomed Ian back with King Cribbage and was happy to have Amy for the first time and Dave we missed you and your braille puncher! When we get back together on the 18th, Art will be certifiable as he is going in for training for dance teaching - congrats Art!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Mark left me in the dust I did really great with Joe on reverse cribbage because I was on as real losing streak! which helps in reverse cribbage. But then we took on partners with the girls (Pam and ME) going up against Emad and Joe. We left even steven with both sets skunking out the other  :)  Ya know, Emad gets just as sad/mad as I do when losing, he just isn't as vocal as ME!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Teresa stepped right up to the plate with both cribbage and King Cribbage for the evening, as did Gabe (the other King Cribbage owner) and Larry!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“ We had 13 A*W*E*S*O*M*E cribbage and King Cribbage players that all had a great time from 6 until 10 last night! Come on down and join us May 18 :) ”  It was so much G*R*E*A*T FUN last night, thanks ALL ! ! &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the back room with our cribbage boards at the ready ! !</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Micki E</member_name><member_id>4468648</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274224466000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Cribbage Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WalthamCribbage</urlname><id>378600</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>Waltham Cribbage!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272163805000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltham Cribbage Meetup: Welcome to May Flowers !!</name><id>lczhnynhbxb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1274220000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WalthamCribbage/events/13281306/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/5/5/global_12747413.jpeg</photo_url></item>