<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>33 Harrison Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.351883</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Encuentro 5</name><city>Boston</city><id>669041</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.061220</lon></venue><fee><label>fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>(buy-in + donation)</description><amount>12.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;We've teamed up with the Liberation Poker League to bring you a night of meeting like-minded progressives, raising cash for liberation, and poker action! Ante up for the revolution and fund local causes fighting against oppression. New to poker? Come at 6:30pm for an intro-tutorial and then enter the Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Tournament!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SCHEDULE &lt;br /&gt;

 6:30 p.m.: Intro to poker/lessons &lt;br /&gt;

 7:00 p.m.: Tournament starts &lt;br /&gt;

 8:00 p.m.: Last buy-in/chance to enter &lt;br /&gt;

 10:30 p.m.: Winners take it all (and by that we mean the pot goes to the charity of their choice - this isn't gambling or a fundraiser for the host organizations).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HERE'S HOW IT WORKS &lt;br /&gt;

 All levels of experience are welcome for Tournament-style Texas Hold &amp;lsquo;Em Poker- You choose the Pro or the Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Table. You buy-in (pay to play) for $10 and declare your Radical Cause. You meet (and bet, bluff, and showdown) activists and their causes from across Boston. If you win either tournament, the money goes to your Radical Cause!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT TO BRING &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; $12 ($10 buy-in + $2 SoJust donation) &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; More $ to buy back in if you get knocked out early &lt;br /&gt;

 &amp;bull; A potluck dish or beverages&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So look no further if you want to cross-promote your events and campaigns, you're seeking like-minded progressives to hang out with in Boston, or are new to the area and looking for groups to get involved in. At Socializing for Justice (SoJust) events you can hang out with friends, make new ones, find a date, get the scoop on a job, and find out what's going on this weekend - political or social. And the best part is that SoJust members share your vision of building a more just world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.encuentro5.org/home/directions"&gt;DIRECTIONS&lt;/a&gt;: Encuentro 5 is a Boston movement-building space in Chinatown. It's home to several of Boston&amp;rsquo;s antiwar, pro-immigrant, and environmental- and economic-justice projects. It&amp;rsquo;s accessible from the Red, Orange and Green line. The space has an elevator, but it is housed in an old building that is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay connected with the Liberation Poker League - "like" their &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Liberation-Poker-League/96182554941"&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt; and read their &lt;a href="http://liberationpokerleague.wordpress.com"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust is all about building a cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoJust isn't a non-profit 501(c)(3).&lt;/strong&gt; We're a grassroots volunteer-run member-supported cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have 1800+ members, hosted 100+ events and manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at www.sojust.org. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network, please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/dues/" target="_blank"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.meetup.com/1/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1319327149000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315799834000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Liberation Poker for Justice</name><id>33175212</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319322600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/33175212/</event_url></item>