<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;FYI, questions about my hikes are best asked by posting a "comment" to the correct hike...I can't always keep up with my email.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very beginner hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/f/0/event_103715312.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Very easy, est. 2.5 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike extension&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Moderate 2.5 or 3 miles (see description RE: tower) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;TOTAL LONG HIKE&lt;/strong&gt; 5 or 5.5 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/a/4/event_103715492.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll hike at 10am from the Visitor's Center, accessible only by the West Entrance (the one with state police barracks). You may want to arrive early to gaze at the reservoir and take pictures! Quabbin Reservoir provides water for the entire Boston Metropolitan area and a few other communities. It's &lt;strong&gt;huge&lt;/strong&gt; (18 miles long), and home to bald eagles, deer, moose, bears, hawks, turkeys, turkey vultures, bears, foxes, etc!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very beginner hike:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of Winsor Dam, we'll immediately leave the road, away from the reservoir. This pretty path winds downhill through the woods, ending at a small rotary behind Winsor Dam. From there, we'll take another trail southwest towards a small power station, follow the stream east from it, and cross a pretty footbridge just before the Swift River.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike the portion of the Swift River you see from the spillway...stick-straight and boring...the leg from here south is pretty, especially with trees downed from winter storms that are magically blooming, anyway! The trail narrows further south, but it's very easy with one small hill. Watch out for tree roots, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no bridge over the Swift River except at Route 9, so we'll use that to cross, then pick our way down the rocky banking on the other side. We'll take the trail on this side back to the park. Shortly before the park road, we'll have lovely views of the back of Winsor Dam and the waterfall gushing from the spillway and underneath the stone bridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, those who only wanted a 2.5-mile hike, walk left to the rotary and over Winsor Dam. Enjoy the beautiful views and perhaps a picnic before driving home, or go inside the Visitor's Center to learn about local wildlife and flip though binders of Quabbin history, with photos of the disincorporated towns and the construction of Quabbin Reservoir. They even have videos and a VCR and TV right there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hike extension:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want more than 1 hour of mild exercise and don't mind steep hills? This is for you! Our destination is a dramatic viewing spot, Enfield Overlook. (Perhaps the viewing tower, too!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the group splits, we'll go straight past the dramatic spillway and the DCR boat cove. &lt;em&gt;(Please stay to the side; the main park road is busy with motor vehicles.)&lt;/em&gt; After the cove, it's steep uphill for 1 mile to the rotary. However, on paved road, it's easy to keep a steady pace uphill. We'll pass through the rotary and downhill 1/4 mile to Enfield Overlook, our picnic spot. Here, you can gaze up both the West and Middle Branches of Quabbin Reservoir and Prescott Peninsula, which divides them. Also, unless it's foggy or extremely hazy, you have a clear view of Mount Monadnock in New Hampshire!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If no one's pressed for time time on our way back, we can detour from the rotary to the tower on top of Quabbin Hill. This adds barely 1/2 mile (barely 1/4 each way) to the distance&lt;em&gt;. (I estimate the hike and picnic at Enfield Overlook would end at 1pm without this detour.)&lt;/em&gt; The views from the tower are even more spectacular, including all but the most northern reaches of the reservoir, Baffle and South Baffle Dams where we hiked a few weeks ago, Mount Monadnock, Mount Wachusett, Mount Greylock in western Massachusetts, and on extremely clear days, Hartford, Connecticut!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If time is an issue for some, we'll all head straight back, or we can split up if no one minds. You do &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; need a map to get back to the car...just turn left at the rotary, and after the long downhill turn right after the spillway. You'll see when we're hiking up, it's obvious...with metal posts and a gate to stop cars from driving over Winsor Dam, which is right there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could also drive to the tower after the hike. (You'd need to exit the park and re-enter at the Middle Entrance, because you can't drive over Winsor Dam.) FYI, I have no time constraint myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just like those who took the "very beginner" hike, Winsor Dam will be the final leg of our hike. I can point out some trees where bald eagles are known to be nesting or hanging around this year. (Had a nice conversation with DCR staff today while checking the trails.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No swimming, wading, or climbing the water side of the dam. (Public water supply.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No pets. (Same reason.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Carry-in, carry-out." There are trash cans inside the Visitor's Center, but for the hike, plan to carry any trash you make back with you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not remove items from the reservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid brushing against tall grass, twigs, and downed branches whenever possible. Deer ticks are bad this year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Bring:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"Deep woods"-type insect repellant with DEET or Pemethrin. &lt;em&gt;(If you spray only your ankles, that's pretty much useless! You pick up ticks by brushing past vegetation.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water/drink. (Short hike 1 hour or less, long hike 3 hours.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snack/lunch for picnic at Enfield Overlook (long hike).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cameras highly recommended!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No special clothing or equipment required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;FYI, there are full facilities (bathrooms, potable water) at the Visitor's Center.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On the longer hike, there are outhouses with sanitizer at Enfield Overlook. If we go to the tower, there are proper bathrooms, but the water is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; potable (drinkable).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/hr&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions to the West Entrance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions from Worcester and points East:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Route 9 west. (From the North, use I-290 to get to Route 9.) Pass through Leicester, Spencer, the Brookfields, and Ware. After downtown Ware and some steep hills, there's not much except scattered houses. Before the first (East) entrance, you'll see a dirt pulloff where fishermen park, with a small wood barrier to a trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Park has &lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; entrances, but you can only get to the Visitor's Center via the &lt;strong&gt;West Entrance&lt;/strong&gt;. It takes 5 minutes to pass all 3 entrances, all on the right. Please look for a white "QUABBIN RESERVOIR WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a small, blue "State Police" sign. The parking lot is immediately before the state police barracks and Visitor's Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google maps is messed up! (The marker is further west on Route 9 than it should be.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From North-Central Massachusetts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you live closer to Route 31 or 122 than to I-290, just take the appropriate route South to Route 9, then follow directions "from Worcester" as above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From points North and West (or Route 2):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If coming from the North (or from Route 2), take Route 202 South for at least 20 minutes, until you hit Route 9. Turn left for Route 9 East. The West Entrance is the first entrance on your left. (There are no landmarks I can think of, but it's about 2 miles.) Please look for a white "Quabbin Reservoir WEST ENTRANCE" sign and a blue "State Police" sign. The parking lot is immediately before the state police barracks and Visitor's Center.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I drive a small, white Dodge Stratus</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333908340000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332535137000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Very beginner" hike @ Quabbin: Swift River, etc (+ extension: Enfield Overlook)</name><id>57593602</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333807200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/57593602/</event_url></item>