<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>13 Branch St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01844</zip><lat>42.705210</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Valley Office Park</name><city>Methuen</city><id>669264</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.214195</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;It's that time of the year to go see the awesome trees!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;PLEASE NOTE:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;We are changing the date of this event to Saturday 11/26. Please update your RSVP if you are not able to make the new date!&amp;nbsp; Thank you!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have done this a few years in a row and we are never disappointed, so let's go again!&amp;nbsp; This is one of the best ways to help us get into the Christmas spirit and go to the BEST Tree Festival. There will be over 200+ decorated Christmas Trees and you can buy tickets to win on the beautiful trees.....what a concept: a tree that comes all decorated....and who knows maybe you could get lucky enough to win one of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visitors are invited to attend the Festival and view the 200+ trees donated by individuals, businesses, organizations, and school groups from Methuen and several Merrimack Valley communities. Their is a cafe where we can grab a snack and last year they had a mini auction from donated items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COST:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 General Admission: $8 for Adults, Children under 12 FREE!&amp;nbsp; (there is an extra charge if you buy the raffle tickets to try to win a tree) &lt;br /&gt;

 Children age 14 or younger must be accompanied by an adult. &lt;br /&gt;

 Tickets for the raffling of the trees is a separate cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 From the North: Take Route 93 S, Exit 46 - follow signs for Rt. 113 W toward Dracut. Bear right off the exit ramp. Follow the signs to the Festival of Trees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the South: Take Route 93 N, Exit 46 - go 3/4 of the way around the rotary. Bear right on to 113 W toward Dracut. Follow the signs to the Festival of Trees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that if you are running late, can&amp;rsquo;t find us or need to cancel at the last minute, the meetup phone number is: 978-304-2811.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Dues:&lt;/strong&gt; Please remember that if you have not paid your dues for this year, be prepared to pay them at this event. If you need to find out if you owe money, please look at your profile page where it states &amp;ldquo;Membership dues last recorded by your Organizer&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to change your RSVP to an event if your plans change. Also don&amp;rsquo;t forget after attending a meetup event to let your Organizers know if you had a good time by rating the meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank You, we look forward to seeing you at this event. &lt;br /&gt;

 Donna &amp;amp; Janet&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>As you face the building, go through the door on the RIGHT and meet in the lobby/where you hang up your coats.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322401868000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318624566000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Festival of Tree's.</name><id>37421982</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322334000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/37421982/</event_url></item>