<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Building 54</address_2><address_1>77 Massachusetts Avenue, Cambridge</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.359097</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>MIT, Room 54-100</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>609289</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093636</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;What the Evidence Shows&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sounds of explosions coming from each of the WTC Twin Towers were heard well before the collapses began. These were reported by over 118 first responders in the FDNY recorded &amp;quot;oral histories&amp;quot; (the release of which was resisted by the City of NY until forced by a New York Times FOIA filing). Numerous accounts of &amp;quot;flashes of light&amp;quot; which commonly accompany the detonation of demolition charges were also reported. Video footage reveals the striking symmetry, explosiveness and rapidity of the Towers' destruction. This destruction differed from the more classic controlled demolition of WTC 7 in its extreme explosiveness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each rubble site contained tons of molten metal &amp;quot;flowing like lava&amp;quot; in the basements - as observed by Leslie Robertson, WTC structural engineer, and numerous other first responders. The temperatures of these flows were far in excess of anything possible from a jet fuel fire or from the burning contents of the buildings. Scientists have determined conclusively that thermate - a high-tech incendiary - was used. Chemical traces of thermate were found in the steel and dust. Each &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; exhibited thick billowing pyroclastic dust clouds that rapidly expanded to over ten times the volume of the buildings. Each also showed squibs (explosive ejections of pulverized building materials) easily observed in many of the videos. The twin towers were explained to have &amp;quot;pancaked&amp;quot; down, however there was no stack of floors found at the bottom - nearly everything was blown outside the footprint of the towers in a symmetrical pattern extending 1,200 feet in diameter around each building - and 90,000 tons of concrete , metal decking and floor trusses were completely missing from the debris field.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most damaging to the official story, WTC building 7 was a 47-story high-rise not hit by an airplane and yet became the 3rd modern steel-framed skyscraper to collapse symmetrically at near free-fall speed on 9/11 - in the exact manner of a controlled demolition with explosives. It collapsed into a neat, compact pile, exhibiting ALL the classic features of controlled demolition:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Rapid onset of &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;    * Sounds of explosions at ground floor - a full second prior to collapse&lt;br /&gt;    * Symmetrical &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; - through the path of greatest resistance - at near free-fall speed (i.e. the [core] columns offered no resistance)&lt;br /&gt;    * &amp;quot;Collapses&amp;quot; into its own footprint - with the steel skeleton broken up for shipment&lt;br /&gt;    * Massive volume of expanding pyroclastic dust clouds&lt;br /&gt;    * Tons of molten metal found in basement by demolition workers&lt;br /&gt;    * Chemical signature of thermate (a high-tech incendiary) found in slag and dust samples&lt;br /&gt;    * Rapid oxidation and intergranular melting found (by FEMA) in the structural steel samples&lt;br /&gt;    * Expert corroboration from controlled demolition professionals&lt;br /&gt;    * Foreknowledge of &amp;quot;collapse&amp;quot; by First Responders, media, NYPD, FDNY, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can review all of this evidence and much more online at www.AE911Truth.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you - we look forward to meeting each of you at the forum!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Richard Gage, AIA, Architect&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Architects and Engineers for 9/11 Truth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday May 16, 7:00 pm No RSVP for this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Check www.ae911truth.org for any room change)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Notes from recent forum participants?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;AE911Truth exposes that a localized failure in a steel-framed building like WTC7 cannot cause a catastrophic collapse like a house of cards at free-fall speed without a simultaneous and patterned loss of several of its columns at key locations within the building?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kamal Obeid, PE, Structural Engineer&lt;br /&gt;Fremont, CA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;quot;I think we were all shocked when the buildings came down; it just didn't seem right. Richard Gage, AIA does an excellent job uncovering the problems with the official explanation in a scientific, non-partisan way. It's &amp;quot;An Inconvenient Truth&amp;quot; about 9/11 that everyone should be aware of. Brace yourselves.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Mungenast, AIA&lt;br /&gt;Somerville, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The presentation by AE911Truth.org brings serious doubt to the official story. It is very difficult to understand how all 3 Trade Center buildings could have come down the way they did, solely as the result of the 2 airplane impacts and resulting fires.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jeffrey G. Arnold, Architect&lt;br /&gt;Orinda, CA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;?AE911Truth.org defies the official version of a complete structural failure of WTC Towers 1 and 2. AE911 proves that a free fall of these steel structures into their own footprint is a story without merit and a challenge to common sense.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Osvaldo Valdes, Architect&lt;br /&gt;New York City&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>http://whereis.mit.edu/map-jpg?mapterms=54-100&amp;amp;mapsearch=go</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211151801000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210729371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11: Blueprint for Truth / The Architecture of Destruction</name><id>7933483</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1210978800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7933483/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>