<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to the &lt;b&gt;&amp;quot;The Shift&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Movie and Discussion. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doors open at 6:45 , then until 7:15, we'll meet, mingle, munch food, enjoy drinks and introduce ourselves.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 7:15 to 9:00 we'll watch the movie and then follow it up discussing what ways of using the information in our daily lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I was younger watching TV I remember hearing Archie Bunker say that Edith was going through &amp;quot;the change&amp;quot;. I heard of many people uprooting and changing their life by going through &amp;quot;a mid life crisis&amp;quot;.  In the last few months I have heard so much more about this topic. What creates these changes in our lives and how does it serve us in the bigger picture? After watching the movie we will talk about the shift. This shift effects everyone, our grandparents, our parents our neighbors and friends. It is sometimes tough to go through it and it is even harder to watch the ones we love go throught it. What do we need to know to make 'THE SHIFT&amp;quot; a little easier?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne talks about the 5 key characteristics for a man before the shift and after the shift. Changes from ego to connectiveness. After learning more about this topic I can clearly see the people I love going through it. In fact after learning the list of charticistics that women go from and the list they go to I can also see from my history when I began my &amp;quot;shift&amp;quot;. Now I have a greater understanding of why I had many of theses changes. I am greatful for the big picture! I am no longer fighting the flow, I am going with the flow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join the group movie and discussion. The discussion is so much better with more input!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you then, &lt;br /&gt;Barb&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask the hostess for "The Abundance Meetup"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb Tremlett</member_name><member_id>8282665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257724115000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Enlightened Abundant Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>LawofAttractionandAbundance</urlname><id>1244444</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5</group_lon><name>Abundance, Empowerment and the Law of Attraction</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255997370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie and Discussion "The Shift" Starring Wayne Dyer</name><id>gdptkympbhb</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1257465600000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/LawofAttractionandAbundance/events/11664685/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/0/0/global_11472512.jpeg</photo_url></item>