<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>295 3rd Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.365233</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 714-3974</phone><name>Voltage Coffee &amp; Art</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1459875</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.082700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;(Disclaimer: Because of SEC regulations, we can only allow expert investors to be in the meeting. E&lt;span&gt;ntrepreneurs are not allowed to solicit investments of any kind. Also, just to set the expectation right, we rarely see any VC. You can drop by anytime, and leave anytime without offending us. After entering the Voltage, you need to take 2 right turns, and you will see us on right - the most excited group around &lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/981263258369601089/img/smileys/smile.gif" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fellow web entrepreneurs and VCs gather once a week in Boston to grab some coffee, free WiFi, and chat about what's new. Around the world, tech entrepreneurs and investors are meeting regularly to drink coffee, network and hopefully do deals. No more of the old-school "please send us your executive summary before we'll even talk to you". A place to find opportunities. Where and when is it? Held every Thursday morning from 8:30a-10:30am at Voltage Coffee &amp;amp; Art, 295 3rd Street in Cambridge. &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/voltage-coffee-and-art-cambridge-2" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/voltage-coffee-and-art-cambridge-2&lt;/a&gt; Why? Well, one of the things I've heard repeatedly is: 1. investors are inaccessible 2. entrepreneurs need regular physical space to meet, not just each other but also also network with investors and corporates We all get an enormous amount from informal contact with both entrepreneurs and investors. On OpenCoffee: "What really stood out for me this week was the feeling of people clustering into short meetings and really getting work done. OpenCoffee is deliberately during the day to encourage real professional networking rather than social networking - so the vibe of people getting things done and making connections is really excellent."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(The above Text right after disclaimer was written by our famous founding organizers.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After entering the Voltage, you need to take 2 right turns, and you will see us on right - the most excited group around</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nabeel</member_name><member_id>300948</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mili Ray</member_name><member_id>14627097</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339127651000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>OpenCoffee-Cambridge-Meetup</urlname><id>1367493</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>OpenCoffee Cambridge Entrepreneurs-VCs Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337809964000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Entrepreneurs &amp; VCs Face-to-Face at OpenCoffee Cambridge Weekly Meetup</name><id>qqtdxcyqjbkb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339072200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/OpenCoffee-Cambridge-Meetup/events/66060652/</event_url></item>