<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Rockport, Massachusetts</address_1><state>Ma</state><lat>42.655651</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Halibut Point State Park</name><city>Rockport</city><id>5374222</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.620323</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;OK, this is COMPLETELY exploratory, as I have never been to either place, but have heard quite a bit about them lately....must be destiny that I go :) I don't know what to expect at all, so please come prepared for lots of wandering and map reading. Also, I believe these are primarily level trails, but be prepared for some climbing over rocks, pebbles, roots, loose ground, gravel...whatever may come. I do not believe any of this would be considered advanced hiking by any stretch...walking trails from what I've heard. However...be prepared to walk along rocks. We will explore both Halibut State Park, the adjoining Trustees property, Halibut Point Reservation, and I'm hearing about "Sea Rocks" being nearby but not sure what they are...so maybe that area too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan for a couple hours, and I do have a fairly quick walking pace. Please be on time....I usually wait for stragglers, but in the winter it's harder since we get cold if we stand around waiting too long. Bring $1 for Meetup Fee (please...we appreciate this small contribution towards the rather pricey membership costs Meetup charges to have this group), and $2 for parking. Dress accordingly, bring a snack and water if you'd like, and remember we'll be near the water...so plan to be a little chillier there. This event will be cancelled due to lack of interest (several people) or inclement weather (rain, heavy snow, or below 15 degrees). I look forward to seeing you and exploring this (new to me) park!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/northeast/halb.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/halibut-point-reservation.html#t1"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/halibut-point-reservation.html#t1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Marilee </member_name><member_id>6596076</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327944833000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327623692000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Explore Halibut Point State Park and Sea Rocks</name><id>49797702</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327860000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/49797702/</event_url></item>