<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Gulf Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01226</zip><lat>42.486083</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mass AT: Gulf Rd., Dalton Trailhead</name><city>Dalton</city><id>6536562</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.184133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winter hibernation is over! Part 7 of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail! Join us on Saturday April 14th to do the seventh part of a series of hikes that I will be scheduling to do the entire length of the Massachusetts Appalachian Trail. We will meet at the AT trail head on Gulf rd in Dalton, which will be the ending location of our hike. We'll then leave half the cars and drive over to the AT trail head &lt;span&gt;at the intersection of Pittsfield rd and Beach rd in Washington, MA&lt;/span&gt; (the ending location of the last hike). The total distance of this hike is about 10.5 miles.....total elevation change is a loss of 750ft. We don't see that very often...mostly flat or downhill...good way to ease me into hiking season. Based on our past hiking speeds this will be about a 7 hour hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Mass AT Hiked Before this section: &lt;span&gt;52.7 out of 89.7 59%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Total Mass AT Hiked After this section: 62.6 out of 89.7 70%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This Hike for Me?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a long hike with minor elevation change. Please bring plenty of water (I'm bringing 3 liters) appropriate hiking attire (no jeans or cotton, hiking boots not sneakers), rain gear in case the weather turns nasty, lunch, and snacks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Trailhead Directions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Providence 2 hours 45 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trailhead lat/lon:&amp;nbsp;42.483412,-73.17903&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trail head parking lot is on Gulf rd right near downtown Dalton. &amp;nbsp;Google Maps link to the location and directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?daddr=42.482495,-73.179567&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=42.483412,-73.177314&amp;amp;spn=0.013688,0.027874&amp;amp;sll=42.483412,-73.17903&amp;amp;sspn=0.013688,0.027874&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=mift&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=16&amp;amp;z=16" class="linkified"&gt;http://maps.google.com/maps?daddr=42.482495,-73.179567&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ll=42.483412,-73.177314&amp;amp;spn=0.013688,0.027874&amp;amp;sll=42.483412,-73.17903&amp;amp;sspn=0.013688,0.027874&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;mra=mift&amp;amp;mrsp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Route&amp;nbsp;Information (starting from Beach and Pittsfield rds in Washington)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.2 miles to Blotz rd (mainly through Pittsfield's watershed...lots of streams and bogs)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 miles to Grange Hall rd, some views of Pittsfield along the way&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;2.1 miles to a live railroad crossing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;1.6 miles to trailhead on Gulf rd (includes a walk through metropolitan downtown Dalton)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carpool Option&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please use the comments section to coordinate with other hikers if you want to carpool. There is limited parking so car pooling is&amp;nbsp;recommended....just remember that we do have to carspot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Massachusetts Appalachian Trail Series&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/9/4/event_107413972.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;MAP NOTE: What we have hiked is in black, current section in red, remaining trail red dots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Waiver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the leader(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you for yourself, your heirs, executors, and administrators release, hold harmless, and indemnify the leader(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>AT Trailhead on Gulf rd in Dalton, look for a grey Nissan Juke with RI plates. Cell: 508-414-8544. See google maps ink below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>8198993</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334529853000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>adventurers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sports-26</urlname><id>1285971</id><group_lat>41.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5500030518</group_lon><name>RI Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333579212000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Massachusetts Appalachian Trail: Part 7</name><id>59283452</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334410200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sports-26/events/59283452/</event_url></item>