<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a return to Vlora but this time we're going for brunch. And Vlora does a great... brunch!! And... the space is great for large groups of very social brunch lovers!!! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we can get a large group to come, they'll work with us by proving us with deals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting at the bar for a mimosas and/or sangrias. You'll really like Vlora! The staff is friendly and extremely accommodating. And the food Delish....!  I really like this place a lot. And it's family owned and run by a husband and wife. And this is their only place.  I also like that Cinque Terre Italy is featured on one of the walls there, a place I know well.  It's a good omen :) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Vlora Restaurant&lt;br /&gt;www.vloraboston.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;545 Boylston St (Right across the street from Copley Sq. (just below GNC)&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02116&lt;br /&gt;(617) 638-9699&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About Vlora:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Vlora is a wonderful space with a fantastic Mediterranean menu and an extensive wine list, right in the heart of the Back Bay.  Authentic Mediterranean fare finally has a  home in the Back Bay. Vlora is located in a subterranean Boylston Street space, right across the street from Copley Square (just below GNC). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located in the heart of Boston's Back Bay (Boylston Street and Clarendon Street), Vlora restaurant focuses on truly authentic Mediterranean cuisine that is characterized by an emphasis on flavors and taste and the use of the freshest ingredients. Owned and operated by husband and wife team Aldo Velaj and Cindy Tsai, the restaurant is named after Aldo's home town. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu stems largely from the Northern Mediterranean region of Southern Italy, Greece and Albania. The Restaurant's cozy subterranean location and trendy atmosphere mimic the lounges prevalent in NYC and Paris, Milan and Florance. Featuring an extensive yet reasonably priced wine and beer menu, the restaurant also offers food from 7am until 1 am seven days a week. GUYS... here's a late-night venue!!! :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anyway...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be there and Hope to see you at Vlora!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Need to RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241059237000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236312349000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Lazy Brunch at Vlora. You'll love this place!!!</name><id>9893587</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238868000000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/9893587/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/3/a/global_7657338.jpeg</photo_url></item>