<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Owl's Head&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you hoot like an owl and &lt;b&gt;hike at a moderate plus pace equal to book time or better?&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Do you need The Owl to complete your 48?  &lt;br /&gt;If so join this mid week hike.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a long day with an early start time of 7:00 am sharp - approximately 18 miles round-trip, 2,850 feet elevation gain with a book time of 10:25.  Travel will occur on both official and unofficial trails including a bushwhack through the Pemigewasset Wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our plan is take the Lincoln Woods Trail to Black Pond.  From here we will bushwhack north to the Lincoln Brook Trail to the foot of the Owlshead slide and follow an unofficially maintained trail to the viewless summit.  It is estimated bushwhacking from Black Pond will save about one mile each way in addition to avoiding a number of difficult brook crossings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Only experienced hikers able to go at a moderate plus pace equal to book time or better should sign up for this trip.&lt;/b&gt;  Group size is limited to 8 participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the NEHAAG disclaimer.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gear List, Mandatory:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Topo Map &amp;amp; Compas&lt;br /&gt;Food and Water: Plenty of high-energy snacks and at least four quarts of water. It will be a long day. &lt;br /&gt;Headlamp of Flashlight with spare batteries (if you don’t have one, purchase at Wal-Mart for $16.00) &lt;br /&gt;Clothing: Light-weight to mid-weight synthetic shirt/pants - no jeans or cotton sweat shirt/pants. &lt;br /&gt;Outerwear: Light-weight to mid-weight waterproof rain jacket (with hood) and pants made of either coated nylon or breathable fabric (e.g. Gore-Tex or similar). &lt;br /&gt;Other Gear: sunscreen, baseball hat, sunglasses and insect repellent. &lt;br /&gt;Waterproof Boots and an extra pair of socks&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>TBD</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott</member_name><member_id>7235827</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1221661652000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1220831155000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Owl's Head by way of Black Pond Bushwhack, strenuous</name><id>8710265</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221044400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8710265/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/9/b/global_5432459.jpeg</photo_url></item>