<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;As some of you may already know, I've had some involvement with a local trails association called the North Quabbin Trails Association, also known as the NQTA. NQTA is comprised of a collaboration of nature lovers and local businesses working together to blaze new trail systems and maintain existing trails as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There is an upcoming informative event on NQTA and the region's trail systems with several speakers being invited to inform us of the area's abundant offerings nature wise. I may possibly be among them. I do have to study for final exams that week which unfortunately, has to take presidence although I am flattered to be asked to take part in this and will try to make it.This is also an opportunity to meet like minded people whom are interested in trail blazing, hiking, etc.... &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Please take the time to check out this wonderful organization online at&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://nqta.org/" class="linkified"&gt;http://nqta.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you would like to take part and attend the dinner and informative meeting, please sign up on our site. If you'd also like to sign up on NQTA's site, here is where you can do that as well&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;&lt;a href="http://nqta.org/events/" class="linkified"&gt;http://nqta.org/events/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;.Please indicate on our site if you have signed up on NQTA's site. Otherwise I can just give them our headcount. I hope to make this event and hope to see many of our people there who have an interest in our local trails.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Thank you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Event:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;May 13, 2013, 6 PM at the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge at 92 New Athol Road in Athol, &lt;strong&gt;This has been changed to the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge from the original location.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;North Quabbin Trails Association will be hosting Evening with the Neighbors, a collaboration of outdoor organization retail operations and lodging establishments in the North Quabbin area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There will be spaghetti, soup, salad, and desserts served. An $8 donation will be collected per person. The representative from each organization will make a 5-minute presentation. Fun and exciting raffle items will be available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.nqcc.org/images/directions.gif" alt="Directions to Athol-Orange Elks Lodge" width="807" height="57" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/span&gt; From the East:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 2 West to Exit 16&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take a left off ramp onto Route 202, towards Athol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive approximately 2 miles. When you get to McDonalds Restaurant (set of lights), take a left onto Route 2A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive approximately 0.7 miles to the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge on your left (across from Newcomb Motors) at 92 New Athol Road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Worcester:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 190 North to Route 2 West toward Leominster/Fitchburg to Exit 16&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take a left off ramp onto Route 202, towards Athol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive approximately 2 miles. When you get to McDonalds Restaurant (set of lights), take a left onto Route 2A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive aporoximately 0.7 miles to the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge on your left (across from Newcomb Motors) at 92 New Athol Road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the West:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 2 East to exit 16&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take a right off ramp onto Route 202, towards Athol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive approximately 2 miles. When you get to McDonalds Restaurant (set of lights), take a left onto Route 2A&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive approximately 0.7 miles to the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge on your left (across from Newcomb Motors) at 92 New Athol Road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Amherst:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take Route 202 North into Orange and continue on toward Athol until you come to a set of lights at McDonalds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take a left onto Route 2A and drive approximately 0.7 miles to the Athol-Orange Elks Lodge on your left (across from Newcomb Motors) at 92 New Athol Road.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Here's Bob's email to me:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Hi Cheryl,  I'd  like to invite you to speak at this event and invite your online group also our web is now live &lt;a href="http://nqta.org" target="_blank"&gt;nqta.org&lt;/a&gt; and I'm going to have our online person ( Amy ) contact you about web and Facebook connections thanks Bobby&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Also part of Bob's message....&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Hello to  fellow leaders to outdoor organizations , retail and lodging owners.  NQTA is tasked with this years " Evening with the Neighbors "&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;NQTA in Collaboration fashion we would like to have a true across the board representation of our Region.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;On Monday,  May 13 th from 6 pm to 8 pm at the French Club or American Legion. ( depending upon response)  there will be a dinner of Spaghetti and Meatballs,  Pete Mallett "s famous Chicken Noodle Soup,  Salad and Desserts for the incredibly low price of only $8.00 .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Along with established neighbors we will be Welcoming our newest partners from Peak Expedition and Greenworks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;The event will be set up so that all groups,  community leaders,  and owners of businesses will have a 2 to 5 minutes forum to give details and updates of their worlds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;This is an excellent opportunity to Market your Message out to the like minded community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;There will be a silent raffle held throughout so that if you could see your way to contributing a prize to the cause We will be grateful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;All monies collected will be utilized for critically needed stewardship tools for NQTA and contribute to the ongoing renovation occurring at MREC to turn it into a true Outdoor Community Center for our Region.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;I will be stopping by to review this event with as many of you as I can.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you are on this e mail you are identified by NQTA as a Guest Speaker and we will be Honored by your presence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;If you could please send out the notice to your members so they may join us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Also could you please respond ASAP as getting a count is critical on our location of holding this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;What"s needed is desserts and raffle items.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Thanks to all my peeps it has been a pleasure to getting to know you and this will a truly beneficial event for all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;You've probably noticed this is now NQTA"s new e mail address and you can visit us on our new website&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;a href="http://nqta.org" target="_blank"&gt;nqta.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Happy Trails&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;Bobby Curley&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : medium"&gt;President NQTA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>NQTA ~North Quabbin Trails Assoc</member_name><member_id>88144122</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368498997000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364832494000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NQTA's Evening with the Neighbors event</name><id>112079152</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368482400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/112079152/</event_url></item>