<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>on the Beverly Wenham Line</address_2><address_1>Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01936</zip><lat>42.583458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Long Hill/Sedgewick Gardens</name><city>Beverly/Wenham</city><id>528816</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.842564</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Property Description  114 acres | Established 1979 &lt;br /&gt;From 1916 to 1979, Long Hill was the summer home of noted author and editor of The Atlantic Monthly, Ellery Sedgwick, and his first wife, Mabel Cabot Sedgwick, an accomplished horticulturist, gardener, and author of The Garden Month by Month. The Federal-style house was completed in 1925 and contains original woodwork from the ca.1812 Isaac Ball House in Charleston, South Carolina.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mrs. Sedgwick designed and planted the original gardens. After her death in 1937, Mr. Sedgwick's second wife, the former Marjorie Russell, herself a distinguished gardener and propagator of rare plants, added many plants to the gardens, including unusual species and varieties of trees and shrubs, some introduced by the Arnold Arboretum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today the gardens reflect the collective interests and tastes of both women. Five acres of cultivated grounds are laid out in a series of separate garden &amp;quot;rooms&amp;quot; surrounding the house. Each area is distinct in its own way and is accented by garden ornaments, structures, and statuary. The gardens are flanked on all sides by more than 100 acres of woodland as well as an apple orchard, meadow, and agricultural fields.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Trails &lt;br /&gt;2 miles of trails and footpaths. Moderate hiking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Library &lt;br /&gt;The Sedgwick Garden Library contains an extensive collection of horticultural periodicals, books, and videos. The library is free and open to the public year-round, Monday-Friday, 9AM-5PM. At this time books cannot be removed from the library. Visitors are welcome to use the library for reference only.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When to Visit:&lt;br /&gt;Garden and grounds open year-round, daily, sunrise to sunset. Allow a minimum of 1.5 hours.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission Fees &amp;amp; Permits:&lt;br /&gt;Free to all. On-site donation welcome from nonmembers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Regulations / Advisories:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs must be kept on a leash at all times.&lt;br /&gt;Seasonal hunting is permitted. See details below left.&lt;br /&gt;How to Get There:&lt;br /&gt;From Route 128, exit 18, take Route 22 (Essex Street) north 1.3 mi. Bear left at fork in road and continue for 0.2 mi to brick gate posts and entrance drive on left. Parking area (50 cars) located about 100 yards up the driveway on the left. Overflow parking in field&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1234717184000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1232215701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHESTNUT HILL WALKING MEETUP-LONG HILL</name><id>9544190</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234108800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/9544190/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/0/a/global_6852778.jpeg</photo_url></item>