<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join fellow members of the SSDOMG as we enjoy a Saturday Evening Potluck Social!  We asked you in a Poll if you would be willing to attend a Potluck and the majority of those who voted said Yes.  So, pull out your favorite recipe or grab something from the supermarket.  Either way, be sure to have a list of ingredients for those with food allergies.  Enjoy an evening with the SSDOMG without having to figure out the tax and tip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be gathering at a member's home so here are some ground rules and guidelines.&lt;br /&gt;*SSDOMG Members Only&lt;br /&gt;*You have to have attended:&lt;br /&gt;-1 event since November 1, 2008 OR &lt;br /&gt;-2 events since January 1, 2008 OR&lt;br /&gt;-3 combined events with the SSDOMG or SSFMG since joining either Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What will be provided by your Host and Organizer Team:&lt;br /&gt;-Paper Goods&lt;br /&gt;-Plasticware&lt;br /&gt;-Water&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to optimize the food we will be enjoying here is a recommended list of items to choose from.  &lt;br /&gt;-Appetizers: Limit of 3, max of one hot item.&lt;br /&gt;-Beverages: Limit of 1 per 3 attendees.  Please bring a variety of 2 beverages.  Options include regular soda, diet soda, lemonade, etc.&lt;br /&gt;-Desserts: Limit of 2, max of one hot item.&lt;br /&gt;-Fruits and Veggies: Preferably as part of a main dish.  Maximum of 2.&lt;br /&gt;-Main Dishes: Minimum of 3, including but not limited to: Meat Dish, Seafood Dish, Veggie Dish, Combination Platters such as Chicken Broccoli and Ziti.  &lt;br /&gt;-Salads:  Maximum of 2.  &lt;br /&gt;*Cold items should be brought cold and hot items should be brought hot.&lt;br /&gt;*Please contact the Host/Organizer if you need to heat an item.&lt;br /&gt;*&lt;i&gt;Please state the category of the item you are bringing in your RSVP Comments.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please state in your RSVP Comments the category of the item you are bringing and please be as precise as possible by stating the name of the item so as to avoid having too many of any dish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allergies: If you have an allergy please note it in the Talk About It Section.  Even though my home is non-smoking, neighbors are allowed to smoke in their individual units.  I can attest that I do smell cigarette smoke on occasion.  In addition, even though my home is animal-free, neighbors are allowed to have small pets.  I know of one cat in the building.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to join us on Saturday, March 7th @ 5:30pm to approximately 8pm (or later!) for a fun evening of socializing and eating in a relaxing environment!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday Evening Potluck Social&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 7th @ 5:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Angela’s Condo&lt;br /&gt;Braintree, MA 02184&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers/Hosts: Angela&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minimum and Maximum number of attendees: We desire a minimum of 8 attendees by 12noon on Thursday, March 5th.  The maximum number of attendees is approximately 15 people. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadline: Friday, March 6th @ 4pm / No new RSVPs will be accepted after 10am on Saturday, March 7th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guests: Sorry, Members Only at this event!  Please see guidelines above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Late Arrivals: So that we may all enjoy the food and each other’s company without having to “wait a few more minutes as another dish is on the way” we ask that you please arrive by 6pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price Range: Whatever you choose.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Event Fee: NONE!  The only cost is the items you bring.  &lt;i&gt;If you do not have any items indicated in your RSVP Comments by the RSVP Deadline, the Organizers/Hosts will buy appropriately when shopping and you will be expected to reimburse them $6.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cash Only Policy: Please bring cash! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Directions, including phone #s (to be used only if necessary) will be emailed to all Yes RSVPs around the time of the RSVP deadline.  Located near Exit 17 on Route 3, the Braintree T, and along a bus stop.  Please be sure to read the Directions email as it will include parking information.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>You will have directions right to my door!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238021813000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1234995826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Saturday Evening Potluck Social!</name><id>9770793</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1236465000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/9770793/</event_url></item>