<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Gosling Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.092457</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-432-6166</phone><name>Regal Fox Run Stadium 15</name><city>Newington</city><id>866554</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.798381</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please use the address below to watch The Hunger Games trailer. &lt;br /&gt;

www.youtube.com/watch?v=OgssLmsOa2s&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every year in the ruins of what was once North America, the Capitol of the nation of Panem forces each of its twelve districts to send a teenage boy and girl to compete in the Hunger Games. A twisted punishment for a past uprising and an ongoing government intimidation tactic, The Hunger Games are a nationally televised event in which "Tributes" must fight with one another until one survivor remains. Sixteen year old Katniss Everdeen volunteers in her younger sister's place to enter the games, and is forced to rely upon her sharp instincts as well as the mentorship of drunken former victor Haymitch Abernathy when she's pitted against highly-trained Tributes who have prepared for these Games their entire lives. If she's ever to return home to District 12, Katniss must make impossible choices in the arena that weigh survival against humanity and life against love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: We will meet inside the doors near the entrance at the right at 3:45p.m. This gives us time to all get together, purchase tickets, do introductions, find seats in the theater together, etc. Once everyone has arrived, we'll make sure we all purchase tickets for the same show. There are MULTIPLE shows that day, so please buy your ticket for the 4:20 showing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1333314176000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Singles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Trailblazers-seacoast-singles</urlname><id>519189</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Trailblazers- A Seacoast Singles Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333257899000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's watch a movie together: The Hunger Games</name><id>58732972</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1333309500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Trailblazers-seacoast-singles/events/58732972/</event_url></item>