<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I want to go see a movie this weekend.&lt;br /&gt;I've had several responses of interest for the Adrian Brody movie, so..THE BROTHERS BLOOM it is. :)&lt;br /&gt;The movie starts @ 6:45 so I'll plan to be there about 6:30. If anyone is interested we can plan  go for a bite afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;Lauren&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Synopsis of &amp;quot;The Brothers Bloom&amp;quot;:&lt;br /&gt;From their childhood in a long series of gloomy foster homes to their highflying lives as international con artists, Stephen (Mark Ruffalo) and Bloom (Adrien Brody) have shared everything. Bloom&lt;br /&gt;yearns for “an unwritten life”—a real adventure, one not dreamed up by his old brother. Eager to retire, Bloom agrees to take part in one last grand scam. He insinuates himself into the life of Penelope (Rachel Wiesz), a bored, single New Jersey heiress. When a genuine romance begins to blossom between them, he is reluctant to exploit her naiveté, but Penelope has already taken the bait: She impulsively joins Bloom, Stephen and their “associate,” a sexy Japanese explosives expert named Bang Bang (Rinko Kikuchi), on an ocean liner to Greece. Penelope is convinced she’s happened upon the adventure of a lifetime and offers to bankroll a million dollar deal. As Stephen’s elaborate web of deceit pulls tighter, Bloom begins to wonder if his brother has devised the most dangerous con of his life....&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lauren</member_name><member_id>1192026</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245105177000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>hartfordmovies</urlname><id>712992</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Hartford Area Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1244693943000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A movie: The Brothers Bloom (seems most everyone has seen Star Trek already)</name><id>10627268</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244932200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/hartfordmovies/events/10627268/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/b/8/global_5165560.jpeg</photo_url></item>