<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>326 COMMERCIAL STREET</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.365448</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>DAVIDE RESTAURANT</name><city>BOSTON</city><id>4281572</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051155</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;For our next meetup, Lets meet at Davide. We got a good deal at a great restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We get 26% off on any of the mouth-watering food and drinks offered on the menu. Come have fun, enjoy a great meal, and make new friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Davide Restaurant:&lt;/strong&gt; Davide pays homage to the rich traditions of Northern Italian cuisine with a modern interpretation of many regional Italian dishes. Fresh seasonal ingredients are the core of their menu selections. The passion for cooking is show-cased one plate at a time with rich, simple, vibrant ingredients. Davide put a strong emphasis on their wine list and has been Winner of the Wine Spectator Award 15 plus years and running. Davide has also earned numerous other accolades over the years, including the Best of the Best 5 Star Diamond Award of Excellence as being "One of the top 50 Italian Restaurants in the United States", A Phantom Gourmet rating of "Greatness", a Five-Diamond award from AAA, a rating of Excellent from Zagat Survey, along with numerous other awards. Davide Restaurant located off the main street is referred to as the "Hidden Gem" or "best kept secret" by it's patrons who also boast "Avoid the tourist traps and come dine where Italians have dined for almost 30 years".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ticket will not be sold the day of the event, either at the place or online. Remember to buy your ticket at&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://speedeals.com/deals/1051"&gt;http://speedeals.com/deals/1051&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322062794000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ladies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostoncitygirls</urlname><id>1166008</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston City Girls</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321801874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Northern Italian Fare @ Davide Restaurant w/ 26% Off Meetup Discount</name><id>41812582</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322006400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostoncitygirls/events/41812582/</event_url></item>