<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Old North Dana Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01355</zip><lat>42.506814</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Quabbin Reservoir Gate 35</name><city>New Salem</city><id>907353</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.270399</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hmmm, lots of people have Martin Luther King Day off...let's play;-)!!! Anyone up for a nice hike on a gorgeous day....unlike today...brrr! Microspikes may be needed. Waterproof boots are essential. Please also be sure to bring water and dress appropriately for 30 degree weather. Must be able to walk at a moderate pace for approximately 5-6 miles, which most healthy people can do but just don't realize it. This is a beginner to intermediate hike with mostly flat terrain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning on being out there for approximately 2 1/2 - 3 hours. We can choose how long to make our trip together. Sorry for anyone with a best furry friend...this is not a dog friendly place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quabbin Gates 34-35 Old North Dana Rd., New Salem, MA A gate leading to a terrific path along the shores of the Quabbin Reservoir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description: A short walk of about 1/2 mile down the dirt road from Gate 35 leads through an oak-pine woods to the Quabbin Reservoir and a terrific path south along the shore. Keep watch on your return for a trail to the left where the dirt road arrives at the shore; this is Dike Trail, which crosses an earthen dam and connects with a paved road that returns to Gate 35.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a longer hike, take a side trip up a dirt road that heads north from this paved road. At the intersection just past Bassett Pond on the right, the road to the left leads to the fishing area at Gate 31; straight ahead is Gate 33; and the road to the right leads to Gate 34, near Old North Dana Road, about 1/2 mile east of where you parked at Gate 35.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions: From Rte. 2, take Exit 16 and go south on Rte. 202. Turn left on Rte. 122 and go about 3 miles to Old North Dana Rd. Turn right and proceed 1 mile to Gate 35.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Roadside parking. I drive a 2003 maroon Monte Carlo.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326812334000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326654828000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Quabbin Gate 35 Hike on Martin Luther King Day</name><id>48203772</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326736800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/48203772/</event_url></item>