<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.357613</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>DCR Hatch Memorial Shell</name><city>Boston</city><id>735555</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.072815</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: deeppink"&gt;If you're on Twitter, FOLLOW US @nerdfunboston to get up-to-the-minute updates on the day of the concert.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;INCREASED ATTENDANCE CAP!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of Boston's biggest parties of the year is held to celebrate Independence Day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year marks the 37th year of Boston's Fourth of July celebration at the Hatch Shell on the Charles River Esplanade.  The nationally televised July 4th concert is led by Keith Lockhart and the Boston Pops Orchestra with &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;special guest, country star, Toby Keith&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dress rehearsal is always held the evening before and is open to the public.  Why don't we get together, bring some blankets/tarps/picnic goodies and take in this Boston tradition?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are sound towers along the Esplanade and even in Cambridge, so it is easy to hear the concert from most anywhere along the Charles, but the best view is to be had from the Oval - the grassy area in front of the Hatch Shell stage.  To gain access to the Oval, concert-goers must pass through security and obtain a wristband.  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Items not allowed beyond security points:  alcoholic beverages, glass containers, tarps larger than 8’ X 10’ and sharp objects (e.g., knitting needles, metal tent spikes, can openers, metal utensils).  Chairs must be foldable and beach style.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt; Once you have a wristband, you can come and go as you please. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Gates at the Oval open at 4PM.  When the Oval is completely filled, no more wristbands will be distributed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;  With each passing year, dress rehearsal gets more popular with crowds - especially when there is a favorable weather forecast (and I anticipate a rather large crowd this year since July 3rd falls on a Saturday).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Let's plan to meet at &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;3:15PM&lt;/span&gt; *sharp* at the Public Garden on the corner of Beacon and Arlington to start heading over to the Esplanade by &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;3:30&lt;/span&gt;.  I will have a large Meet up sign.  I'll attempt to erect the meetup sign when we claim our spot so that any late comers (who can get in the oval) can attempt to find us.  Concert starts at 8:30PM. Feel free to bring games or anything else you think would help pass the time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;PLEASE BE FLEXIBLE AND UNDERSTANDING.  If it looks like we'd have better luck getting a spot together OUTSIDE of the oval (and its craziness), we may have to make that decision on a whim.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional information to consider:  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;concessions are expensive&lt;/span&gt;, so you may want to bring water, snacks and picnic stuff (enough to sustain you for 5+ hours).  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Weather is unpredictable&lt;/span&gt;, so you may want to bring sunscreen and a light jacket/sweater.  &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Some people aren't nice&lt;/span&gt;, so we will want to have blankets at the ready to RUN and claim/hold space by covering your entire perimeter of blanket/tarp with bags &amp;amp; bodies (or run the risk of the non-nice people moving your blanket and stealing space).&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;This is a HUGE group to try to organize at a general admission venue, so I'd like to break up the herd into smaller groups (once we arrive at the Public Garden).  Anyone willing to be an honorary Nerd Herder for the smaller groups is welcome!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, a last bit of advice, pack smart and take the T!! Nearest station is Arlington on the &lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Green Line&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Melissa G</member_name><member_id>5191305</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278425900000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>41</yes_rsvp_count><created>1274726481000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pops Goes the 4th - Dress Rehearsal</name><id>13580006</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278184500000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/13580006/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/b/global_15270251.jpeg</photo_url></item>