<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Worcester: Nature in Our City&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Photography Center of Worcester is calling for entries to a juried exhibition along the theme of &amp;ldquo;Nature in Our City.&amp;rdquo; These images will hang in the City Hall Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interpret the beautiful nature of the great outdoors. All photography submitted should depict Worcester&amp;rsquo;s natural area or be inspired by nature. This show will be designed to nurture positive connections in our city&amp;rsquo;s community and with our natural world. We will select photographs for inclusion in this exhibition based on high standards of creativity, quality and thematic relevance. Please submit photographic work inspired by wildlife, nature and native themes. Some examples would be Worcester&amp;rsquo;s amazing parks, animals, plant life, lakes, streams, rocks, gardens, insects, and other creatures. Some of the loveliest photographs have roots in the natural world. (ha ha ha Get it "roots...") Let&amp;rsquo;s show off what Worcester has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details you need to know.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a juried show. We only have 25 frames to fill in the gallery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need to submit a digital image(s) via upload to a web site for jurying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deadline for submissions for the jury is &lt;strong&gt;Oct 30th, 2011 Midnight &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please make your images 10 inches on the longest side at 150 DPI Jpegs and upload them here: &lt;a href="http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#103751" class="linkified"&gt;http://gallery.me.com/scotterb#103751&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The File name should be &lt;strong&gt;your name_title_number of submission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Example: DonnaDufault_LakePark_1.jpeg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please be sure I can find you on the Meetup Site to inform you of the selections. Several folks did not use their full names on the site and it was difficult for me to know how to contact you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are allowed to submit up to 3 images per person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will be notified on Nov 1st if your image or images have been chosen for the show. This will be posted on the Meetup Web site message board, and if you accept emails from the site, I will do my best to send individual notices as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have been selected, you will be asked to &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;print your image, mat it with a &lt;em&gt;white&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;mat that will fit into a 16x24 frame, sign it&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;come to the framing session on Nov 5th, 2011&lt;/span&gt;, so we can get these framed and ready to hang by the week of Nov 7th. (More details will be placed on the Meetup Web Site, Please check the calendar for that day.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I asked that you mark your calendars now with these details and deadline so you can be up on all the happenings. I look forward to seeing this groups submissions for this show! &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cheers,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Donna and Scotty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320068794000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318016413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Submit Photos for the City Hall Gallery's Next Show! Theme: Nature in our City</name><id>36555372</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319947200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/36555372/</event_url></item>