<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>360 State Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.305013</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>360 Screening Room</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1409628</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.922761</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;I have reserved the Screening Room at 360 State Street for another movie night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry about the Late notice, unfortunately my reservation was not accepted until earlier today.&amp;nbsp; But now I've got it, so we might as well use it, right?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP's are limited to 18 due to theater size, so please only say "Yes" if you're pretty sure you can make it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are to attend,&amp;nbsp;I will also need your &lt;em&gt;FULL NAME&lt;/em&gt; for the Concierge to let you in to the building.&amp;nbsp; So please, when you RSVP, either place it in your comment or contact me (AJ) by meetup e-mail or text message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Question: What Movie are we watching?&amp;nbsp; Answer: Come and Find out!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, yeah, yeah, I know that may seem a little stupid.&amp;nbsp; But I didn't want to do anything to specific or special with this late notice on a weekend some consider a holiday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So Here's the deal:&amp;nbsp; I will bring a selection of my collection to guarentee we have enough choices.&amp;nbsp; Everyone else, at thier option can feel free bring &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;One or Two&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;DVDs or Blu-Rays of thier own, and those that show up on time will select.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully everyone will appreciate the bit of risk involved there for film choice, and the timing required&amp;nbsp;for the group to&amp;nbsp;pick a film during the social part of the evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start time for Socializing is 7pm, but we will not start showing the movie until shortly after 7:30. Don't plan to be any later than 7:30 though. (Note: this time there is another event going on adjacent to us, so showing up too much before 7 is not advisable.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to use the waiting list. As the date aproaches I can add people on the waiting list if someone else backs out, provided you sent me your name for the Concierge as a contingency. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Snacks:&lt;/span&gt; Bring your own Snacks and Beverages. (Just please be careful and responsible.) Sharing is encouraged! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Getting in:&lt;/span&gt; Enter the building through the State Street Entrance (Between the intersections of State with Court and Chapel) and talk to the Concierge, there are instructions near the call box and a bell button on it if the door is locked. If you really have trouble, pre-movie-start time you can call AJ at 315-345-9348. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Parking:&lt;/span&gt; There is metered street parking available near by on Orange Street and Court Street, pay until 7 pm. If you don't mind a longer walk, some of the Yale Lots are free in the evenings (I.E. Yale lot 51 on Temple Street Starting at 5). 360's Parking Garage is open to visitors for Credit Card Customers only at $5 Daily Max from 5pm on Friday through Sunday, the entrance is on State street just to the right of the buildings main entrance. Other local near by businesses may have open parking, however you're on your own there. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don't think I really need to say this, but: This is basically an extension of my home I'm inviting you into, there for I expect everyone will treat it with respect and not risk future events (or my lease). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Come to the building door, Ring the Bell Button, Concierge will Direct you. If you have more problems, you can try to call AJ at 315-345-9348.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AJ</member_name><member_id>9920708</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303772700000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>I have the Reservation anyways!</why><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1303265581000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>360 Movie: To Be Determined</name><id>17367707</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1303513200000</time><rsvp_limit>18</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/17367707/</event_url></item>