<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Oxford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375286</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard University Science Center - Hall A</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>776344</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.117034</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;A new free lecture series called &amp;quot;Science and Cooking&amp;quot; is being held this Fall at Harvard University on almost every Monday night at 7:00 pm usually in the Science Center D lecture hall. Go to &lt;a href="https://www.seas.harvard.edu/cooking" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.seas.harv...&lt;/a&gt; to view the scheduled lectures.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;: Heat, Temperature, &amp;amp; Chocolate&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When:&lt;/b&gt;Oct. 4th, 2010, 7 pm - 9 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Speaker:&lt;/b&gt; Enric Rovira&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Speaker:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seas.harvard.edu/news-events/calendars/science-cooking/heat-temperature-chocolate" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.seas.harva...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enric Rovira has known chocolate all his life. Rovira grew up surrounded by sweets in his father's pastry shop and from an early age he demonstrated a unique passion towards art and sculpting, using chocolate as his medium of expression. Rovira's passion for art and chocolate is revealed in his beautifully and uniquely presented bonbons, covered fruits and nuts, and chocolate bars&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I wonder how Enric Rovira is as a presenter? The last presenter we saw was an excellent chef but both he and the translator he spoke through were not good at all as presenters, and we ditched the lecture just before the Q &amp;amp; A session to grab beer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be hanging out in front of the doors to Lecture Hall D starting at 6:00 pm. Feel free to drop by! The lecture, although it starts at 7:00 pm, we probably should grab seats at 6:30 pm. We are competing for seats with the Harvard University underclassmen who are taking the actual science of cooking course who will also be attending this supplimental lecture. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is maybe an eight minute walk from the Harvard Square T: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=JF+Kennedy+St&amp;amp;daddr=Unknown+road&amp;amp;geocode=FcuOhgIducvC-w%3BFW-bhgIdidXC-w&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=dme&amp;amp;mrcr=0&amp;amp;mrsp=1&amp;amp;sz=17&amp;amp;dirflg=w&amp;amp;sll=42.374715,-71.117828&amp;amp;sspn=0.006008,0.009624&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;z=17" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Anybody want to go out for drinks after? John Harvard's Brewhouse usually has a lot of seats, especially on a Monday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Science &amp;amp; Cooking Lecture Series:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.seas.harvard.edu/cooking" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.seas.harv...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These lectures compliment a new General Education science course &amp;quot;Science and Cooking: From Haute Cuisine to the Science of Soft Matter&amp;quot;. Lectures are free, open to the public, and &amp;quot;consist of a brief introduction by Harvard professors followed by a broad-based talk by the chef that may or may not contain material relevant&amp;quot; to the class. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions and Parking:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://samsara.bebear.net/~alcrockett/sciencecenter/about/directions.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://samsara.bebear...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Our address is 1 Oxford Street, Cambridge MA. This is useful if you know where Oxford Street is, but since it is only about 1/3 of a mile long and inaccessible from Massachusetts Avenue, this is not much of a help for most people. We are very close to the intersection of Kirkland Street, which is also very short and again may be obscure to many who are unfamiliar with North Cambridge [...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This interactive official university map &lt;a href="http://map.harvard.edu/level2.cfm?mapname=camb_allston&amp;amp;tile=F7&amp;amp;series=N" target="_blank"&gt;http://map.harvard.ed...&lt;/a&gt; shows the Science Center in the middle of the image. This is a very good map, with links &lt;a href="http://www.hpai.harvard.edu/pr/maps/maps.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hpai.harva...&lt;/a&gt; to other various map resources at Harvard, MIT, and the MBTA. As you can tell from these maps, we are very close to the middle of Harvard Square. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Science Center has no parking garage. One can usually find a space on Massachusetts Avenue, but it may take a bit of searching. We recommend parking at the Alewife or Braintree MBTA stations and riding the Red Line to the Harvard stop&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Website of Alegio Chocolates:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alegio.com/er-rovira.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.alegio.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Enric Rovira is definitely the most deluxe of Barcelona's growing tribe of chocolate makers. Each of his unique creations is not only a work of art in form, but in taste as well. Having grown up surrounded by sweets in his father's pastry shop, today Enric uses chocolate as his artistic medium to portray the tradition and character of his city, Barcelona&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Can you speak Spanish?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The website of Enric Rovira is at &lt;a href="http://www.enricrovira.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.enricrovir...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286296750000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286134799000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Enric Rovira, Heat, Temperature &amp; Chocolate @ Science &amp; Cooking lecture, Harvard</name><id>14985344</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286233200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14985344/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/5/c/global_18441676.jpeg</photo_url></item>