<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Due to popular poll vote and timing wise, we're finally reading  We Were the Mulvaneys by Joyce Carol Oates&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;synopses copied from:  &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?isbn=9780452282827" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Moving away from the dark tone of her more recent masterpieces, Joyce Carol Oates turns the tale of a family struggling to cope with its fall from grace into a deeply moving and unforgettable account of the vigor of hope and the power of love to prevail over suffering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;he Mulvaneys of High Point Farm in Mt. Ephraim, New York, are a large and fortunate clan, blessed with good looks, abundant charisma, and boundless promise. But over the twenty-five year span of this ambitious novel, the Mulvaneys will slide, almost imperceptibly at first, from the pinnacle of happiness, transformed by the vagaries of fate into a scattered collection of lost and lonely souls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;It is the youngest son, Judd, now an adult, who attempts to piece together the fragments of the Mulvaneys? former glory, seeking to uncover and understand the secret violation that occasioned the family's tragic downfall. Each of the Mulvaneys endures some form of exile -physical or spiritual-but in the end they find a way to bridge the chasms that have opened up among them, reuniting in the spirit of love and healing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Profoundly cathartic, Oates' acclaimed novel unfolds as if, in the darkness of the human spirit, she has come upon a source of light at its core. Rarely has a writer made such a startling and inspiring statement about the value of hope and compassion.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For now, we're planning on heading back to the couches at Clear Conscience Cafe in Central Square. If our numbers overcome this, we'll rethink our winter plans:-)&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Will be trying to stake out the couches!  Look for the book on a table</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1231806356000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225217518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Readers:  We Were the Mulvaneys by Joyce Carol Oates</name><id>9048001</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1228780800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/9048001/</event_url></item>