<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>40 Talbot Ave</address_2><address_1>Aidekman Arts Center </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02155</zip><lat>42.404402</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 627-3518</phone><name>Tufts University Art Gallery</name><city>Somerville</city><id>1381807</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119043</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Tufts University Art Gallery has invited our group to visit their art galley and see their current exhibits.  It should be wonderful. Amy Ingrid Schlegel, Ph.D, the director will be present to show us around. This is one of the premier art galleries in New England. It is worth the trip. They have 3 current temporary exhibits and a permanent collection that is extremely rich in contemporary art.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a little more:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mission Statement&lt;br /&gt;The Tufts University Art Gallery animates the intellectual life of the greater university community through exhibitions and programs exploring new, global perspectives on art and on art discourse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gallery fosters critical dialogue through exhibitions and programs that explore fresh interpretations and scholarship on art, that provide a forum for art produced internationally by emerging and mid-career artists, and that feature new work of established artists.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Exhibition Programming&lt;br /&gt;The Tufts University Art Gallery's exhibition space consists of the Tisch and Koppelman Galleries, the Remis Sculpture Court, a new media wall for short video, film, and animation works, and the Slater Concourse Gallery (Tufts' community gallery). Exhibition space totals approximately 7,000 square feet. Four curated exhibitions and one juried summer exhibition take place in the Tisch and Koppelman Galleries each year, in addition to three MFA Thesis exhibitions and one Museum Studies Program exhibition; three exhibitions take place in the Remis Sculpture Court each year; and four to five continuous screenings of short video are featured on the New Media Wall each year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ase.tufts.edu/gal" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Q.</member_name><member_id>2269958</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1287760299000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fine Art Appreciators</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonVisualArtAppreciators</urlname><id>1280431</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Visual Fine Art Appreciators</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285090119000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tufts University Art Gallery</name><id>14846601</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1287698400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonVisualArtAppreciators/events/14846601/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/5/global_18143669.jpeg</photo_url></item>