<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ok, here's the deal...actually there are two deals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, whichever member of the Jumbo meet-up group records the highest hourly total of (legit) exercise in the Tufts Trek to Talloires exercise contest will be treated to lunch at the local restaurant of his or her choosing by ME! One winner (or more if there's a tie, I guess) will be treated each month from January through April as long as that individual emails me with their total hours logged within one week of month-end...so that's February 7 for the month of January, got it? Here's the catch: You have to at least beat me, otherwise lunch is on you....just kidding about the lunch, but if you don't beat my hours logged then I am the winner and I will just treat myself to a lunch of my choosing. Make sense?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oh, and by the way, this contest log is based solely on the honor system so please be honest about your "real" exercise. There's no taking credit for walking when all you were really doing was grocery shopping, ok? Also, if you're skiing for hours, that's great, record that exercise. If, on the other hand, you're sitting in the lodge, drinking cocoa or spending two-thirds of your time waiting in lines and riding chair lifts to the top of the mountain, please be honest about the time you were &lt;span style="color : #FF0000"&gt;actually skiing&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, second deal: I can't believe I am going to do this, but if more than five Jumbos from this meet-up group record more exercise time than I do between now and the end of the Trek to Talloires, I will grow a goofy-looking, &lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;70's style mustache&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for one month. Yes, I will stop shaving the 'stache from April through mid-May for an entire month. So bring it on!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, feel free to pass this invitation along to any faculty or staff who might be interested in trying to kick my arse at this contest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ok, one more thing, regarding the first challenge, you can only win one month so that we give others a chance to eat, er win. Sound fair?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rich K</member_name><member_id>9340572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359658967000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Jumbos</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group</urlname><id>1505274</id><group_lat>42.4000015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Tufts Faculty &amp; Staff Social Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357244371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jumbo Trek Challenge--January</name><id>97730282</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>24300000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359633600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Tufts-Faculty-Staff-Social-Group/events/97730282/</event_url></item>