<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>325 Ocean House Rd</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04107</zip><lat>43.594124</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cape Elizabeth Town Hall</name><city>cape elizabeth</city><id>1848191</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.227188</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://safelawns.org/chemical-reaction/images/cover.jpg" alt="A Chemical Reaction" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film and Discussion on Natural Garden Care with Paul Tukey on May 25th &lt;br /&gt;On Wednesday, May 25th, 2011 at 6:30 PM at Cape Elizabeth Town Hall, Paul Tukey&amp;rsquo;saward-winning 2009 documentary film, A Chemical Reaction, will be shown. It tells thecompelling story of Hudson, Quebec, the first town in North America to ban lawn andgarden chemicals. Mr. Tukey and other local natural lawn care experts will be present todiscuss natural lawn care and hands-on environmental stewardship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The event is free. It issponsored by Cool Cape, a local group working on environmental and climate change issues.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;There is increasing concern about the health and environmental effects of pesticide andherbicide use. In our efforts to rid our crops, homes, and gardens of weeds and pests, wehave surrounded ourselves with mixtures of chemicals with only minimal understandingof how they affect our health. Annually, Americans use more than 4.5 billion poundsof pesticides. Each year, thousands of people in the U.S. become ill as a result of acutepesticide poisoning. Yet we are just beginning to understand that even low levels ofpesticide exposure can be hazardous. Studies have linked low level pesticide exposure tocancer, damage to the nervous and reproductive systems, developmental and behavioralabnormalities including ADHD, disruption of normal hormonal function, and immunedysfunction. Three separate studies published last month linked pesticide exposure duringpregnancy to decreased IQ in children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Paul Tukey, a Maine resident, is an internationally-recognized critic of garden chemicaluse, and proponent of natural lawn and garden-care methods. Mr. Tukey&amp;rsquo;s concern aboutpesticides and herbicides began with his own experience with acute chemical sensitivityto products he used in his lawn care business. He went on to found the magazine and TVshow, People, Places &amp;amp; Plants, and subsequently the non-profit SafeLawns Foundation,which promotes natural lawn care methods, and is the author of The Organic Lawn CareManual. For more information on the May 25th event, contact Carol Hubbard at 650-9911 orhubbac@mmc.org&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1306681313000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306168245000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Film: A Chemical Reaction &amp; Discussion w/Paul Tukey</name><id>19397351</id><headcount>50</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306362600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/19397351/</event_url></item>