<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Harvard Square</address_2><address_1>42 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-547-6789</phone><name>Cambridge Center for Adult Education</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1170238</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121368</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>65.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Want to expand your repertoire in the kitchen and pick up a few new recipes along with some knife skills (or just get beyond using the can opener at every meal)?  Join us on Sunday, October 25th to cook with Chef JJ Gonson as she teaches us how to cook a delicious Fall meal using fresh, local ingredients.  After we prepare the meal we will enjoy the fruits of our labor!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In her words:&lt;br /&gt;The class is about thinking of cooking as an art form, using local, in-season ingredients. The goal is to help you to feel comfortable walking into the kitchen armed only with your instinct for flavor, color, and texture, and to encourage you to put down the recipes and rely on your senses. We will explore creating dishes of the season with local foods and flavors – focusing on why things taste the way they do, some kitchen tricks, and even a little bit of food science – to achieve our goal: a healthy, fresh, and delicious seasonal and locally grown meal. Together we will prepare a full dinner, including a fresh salad, entree, side dishes, and dessert, and then we will sit down and enjoy it together while we discuss what we have been doing. Come prepared to laugh and learn&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About JJ Gonson:&lt;br /&gt;JJ Gonson is a personal chef bringing over 20 years of restaurant and personal cooking experience to your table. She believes that you are what you eat, but that it doesn't mean you can't eat well! Using relationships with local vendors and farmers, she can prepare a wide variety of dishes including vegetarian, vegan, wheat free and organic meals. She specializes in working in the most sustainable way possible. Everything is made fresh and to order from healthy ingredients. Each meal is custom designed especially to suit your needs. She was named 2008’s Best Personal Chef by Boston magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more about JJ Gonson at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cuisineenlocale.com/2005/05/welcome.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cuisineenl...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What reviewers on Yelp! are saying:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“JJ is more than a cook. She loves to be around people and entertain them. She has a passion for food that can make you excited about cauliflower. (And I don't even LIKE cauliflower!!) If you have any chance to be around her, jump on it because her passion will get you excited about trying multiple cuisines and even trying your hand at cooking.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I had the pleasure of taking a class taught by JJ at CCAE, and I immediately knew I wanted to learn more about food from her. She's genuinely passionate about what she does, and it comes through in her cooking. “&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class limit- 15&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Suggested Attire: Comfortable clothes you can cook in!! Closed toe shoes, please.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: Cambridge Center for Adult Education Kitchen located at 42 Brattle St. in Harvard Square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cost: $65.00&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Leah</member_name><member_id>8965438</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256967421000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Social Networkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>socialnetwork-1382</urlname><id>1275022</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Things To Do: BOSTON</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250521671000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cooking Class</name><id>11129873</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256482800000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/socialnetwork-1382/events/11129873/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/f/9/global_5450809.jpeg</photo_url></item>