<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.348297</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>1602326</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084145</lon></venue><fee><label>Door fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$20 supports OB</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Unfortunately, the transformer fire in Back Bay last night left the area without power. So we have to cancel tonight's event. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Please join us at the &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/events/55667142/"&gt;99% Sprint Direct Action Training on Wednesday, April 11&lt;/a&gt; - where you'll be able to learn more about Occupy Boston and other groups planning actions against big banks and greedy corporations this spring.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice is throwing a party for Occupy Boston!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occupy Boston did not end when they were evicted from Dewey Square. Far from it. There are dozens of active working groups and endless events and actions taking place all around the city. General Assemblies are held several times a week and all they're missing is &lt;strong&gt;YOU!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SoJust is hosting this event so you can connect with this vibrant movement and find your place among the many volunteer opportunities. You'll meet members of several working groups and learn about upcoming actions. Learn more at &lt;a href="http://www.occupyboston.org"&gt;www.occupyboston.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What should you expect?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Our usual friendly and welcoming space where it's easy to meet people even if it's your first SoJust event. Plenty of socializing time to mix, mingle and network with fellow progressives. The opportunity to learn more about Occupy Boston and how you can support their efforts with a donation of money, supplies or time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost:&lt;/strong&gt; $5-$20 (sliding scale) collected at the door for Occupy Boston &lt;br /&gt;

 Raffle ticket for every $10 donated - win a $25 iTunes gift card! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;em&gt;Complimentary appetizers will be available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing for Justice is all about building a cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community and network in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance.&lt;/strong&gt; We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos. Join us if you are ready to go BEYOND ALLIES and build a CROSS-ISSUE PROGRESSIVE MOVEMENT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACCESSIBILITY: Must be 21+ to enter after 7PM. The venue is physically accessible - elevator is at the back of the venue and bathrooms are big enough for manual, but not motor-powered, wheelchairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PARKING: Lir is across from the Hynes Convention Center. Parking near Lir is really hard - you could get lucky or you could drive around for 30 or more minutes. There are parking garages by Back Bay station. Best bet is to take the T to Back Bay or Hynes Convention Center (which is the closest T stop).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HELP SPREAD THE WORD!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Invite your friends to this Facebook event: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/events/190887741014850/"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/events/190887741014850/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Join the SoJust Facebook group: &lt;a href="http://on.fb.me/SoJust"&gt;http://on.fb.me/SoJust&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 On Twitter? Follow &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/sojust" target="_blank"&gt;@SoJust&lt;/a&gt; and SoJust's Co-Founder &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/robbiesamuels" target="_blank"&gt;@RobbieSamuels&lt;/a&gt; and tweet about this event using #sojust&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_________________________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOCIALIZING FOR JUSTICE - &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 SoJust is all about building a cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance. We're doing it by putting the SOCIAL back in SOCIAL JUSTICE. We focus on creating welcoming spaces that foster relationship-building across issue silos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SoJust isn't a non-profit 501(c)(3).&lt;/strong&gt; We're a grassroots, volunteer-run, member-supported, cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community that's been growing steadily since August 2006. We have almost 2000 members, hosted 115+ events and manage an online hub of progressive events and resources at &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org"&gt;www.sojust.org&lt;/a&gt;. If you've benefited from this cross-issue progressive network, please contribute the suggested annual membership fee of $25. You may do this &lt;a href="http://www.sojust.org/dues/" target="_blank"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; or at any of our events. Thank you for helping us continue to provide a space for like-minded progressives of all stripes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know more about SoJust?&lt;/strong&gt; Check out our &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/messages/boards/view/viewthread?thread=3187615"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://sojust.org/photos/"&gt;past event photos&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alison Brill</member_name><member_id>4034719</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331767699000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329415737000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CANCELED: Socializing for Justice: Occupy Boston</name><id>52607442</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331762400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/52607442/</event_url></item>