<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Quincy St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.375618</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>433066</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114290</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Many songs and musical compositions were inspired by dreams. Paul McCartney famously dreamed the music for &lt;a href="http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=82"&gt;Yesterday&lt;/a&gt;. A dream inspired Jimi Hendrix to create &lt;a href="http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=2553"&gt;Purple Haze&lt;/a&gt;. The guitar riff for the Rolling Stones &lt;a href="http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=449"&gt;Satisfaction&lt;/a&gt; came from a dream. Some of the words for R.E.M.'s &lt;a href="http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=1741"&gt;It's the End of the World as We Know It&lt;/a&gt; came from a dream. A famous classical music piece known as the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Devil%27s_Trill_Sonata"&gt;Devil's Trill Sonata&lt;/a&gt; by Giuseppe Tartini was inspired by a dream. The list goes on and on. &lt;a href="http://www.songfacts.com/category-songs_inspired_by_dreams.php"&gt;Here is one partial list&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Whether you have dreamed music yourself or you appreciate music and the creative process or you want to encourage yourself to dream music, this will be an inspiring Meetup. If you have dreamed music, songs, or poetry, you are encouraged to bring them and share them. Whatever the source of dream songs, whether they come from our own subconscious or from the collective unconscious, or from our spirit guides, we will share our techniques for encouraging dream songs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This class will be led by Deerheart who has had many musical dreams and song dreams. He will share some of these and talk about them with the group. Deerheart is a &lt;a href="http://www.visionarydreamguide.com/"&gt;dream guide&lt;/a&gt; and a dream artist. He is the founder of &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/"&gt;Boston Dreamers&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/groups/36258693723/"&gt;Dream Blog Network&lt;/a&gt; on Facebook. His dream artwork and dream songs have appeared and will appear in the &lt;a href="http://www.soulstirring.org/"&gt;Mystical Art and Talent Show&lt;/a&gt;. Here is the &lt;a href="http://www.soulstirring.org/poster_october2011.html"&gt;poster&lt;/a&gt; for this year's show. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Payment is $10 and can be made online or in person. Anyone who cannot afford to pay is encouraged to attend anyway and should contact the group organizer &lt;a href="http://www.bostondreamers.com/message/?recipientId=7399016"&gt;Deerheart&lt;/a&gt; before attending. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Event will be from 7 pm until 9 pm. Space is limited to 15 people. RSVP requested. Please update your RSVP if you are unable to attend, to allow others to attend. Thank you. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 For directions and other information about location please visit the &lt;a href="http://www.swedenborgchapel.com/church/directions.html"&gt;Cambridge Swedenborg Chapel website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Side entrance by the parking lot, up stairs, through hallway, left through angel doorway, into parlor.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carl Schroeder</member_name><member_id>1741395</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deerheart</member_name><member_id>7399016</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318557198000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dreamers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonDreamers</urlname><id>1339734</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Boston Dreamers Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317002104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dream Songs &amp; Dream Music</name><id>34943502</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318374000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonDreamers/events/34943502/</event_url></item>