<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>201 Brookline Avenue, Boston, MA </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.344212</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Regal Cinemas Fenway 13 </name><city>Boston</city><id>513361</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.101936</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;SECOND SCREEN SOLD OUT! Both screens are now sold out. If anyone has an extra ticket, or cannot attend, let us know in the comments below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's meetup to see this intense, two hour big-screen presentation of this pivotal TNG storyline. In other words, it is going to rock!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Showtime is a little earlier than usual, 7PM, so we'll be meeting around 6:15PM in the lobby by the top of the stairs. I'll still be stopping by the Boston Beer Works beforehand for those who would like to join me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Best of Both Worlds – the two-part storyline comprising the third season finale and the fourth season premiere of the beloved series Star Trek: The Next Generation®- will, for the first time ever, be seamlessly tied together as one continuous and uninterrupted story digitally restored with new CGI effects… on the big screen! Audiences will also see special clips from “Regeneration: Engaging the Borg”, a behind-the-scenes look at the making of The Best of Both Worlds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't get sold out! Buy your tickets soon. You know this will be popular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="linkified" href="http://www.fathomevents.com/#!star-trek-best-of-both-worlds"&gt;http://www.fathomevents.com/#!star-trek-best-of-both-worlds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jerry</member_name><member_id>12227382</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366985635000</updated><rating><average>4.40000009537</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Sci-Fi/Fantasy Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-scifi</urlname><id>1434288</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Sci-Fi/Fantasy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>35</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361283534000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Star Trek: The Next Generation - The Best of Both Worlds</name><id>105320682</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>8100000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366930800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-scifi/events/105320682/</event_url></item>