<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We will be screening all or part of this new film by Brattleboro, VT, filmmaker, Chris Pratt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film is posted Online at &lt;a href="http://www.deceptionsusa.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DecptionsUSA.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However at our meet-up we will have the filmmaker live and in person for our discussions not just on the evidence of such horrific deceptions, but on how we can transform illusions toward a truth that sets us free. Science, fearlessness, appreciation of nature are dear friends for those facing reality with an integrity intact. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check our file for a flier for this event at our &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/files/"&gt;files section&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. Feel welcome to download and use file to show this film in your area. The film is also available from the filmmaker for TV broadcast. Help us spread the word on this film. Each chapter stands on its own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prologue&lt;br /&gt;Chap 1 - 9/11; &lt;br /&gt;Chap 2 - Bush/Cheney&lt;br /&gt;Chap 3 - Obama; &lt;br /&gt;Chap 4 - Power Elite;&lt;br /&gt;Chap 5 - Media Control; &lt;br /&gt;Chap 6 - New World Order&lt;br /&gt;Epilogue&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Life was so much better when I lived in the “bubble” unaware that my freedoms had some very distinct boundaries. If I stayed in my sandbox I was OK. But if I ventured out, if I became a critical thinker, read, questioned authority, thought beyond Democrat or Republican, realized that my opinion and perceptions were being managed by a corporate media, realized that there was no public policy only corporate policy, I became a subversive. But how could I reconcile continual war, wiretapping, unanswered 9/11 questions, torture, rendition, terrorism, the loss of freedom, police brutality, news suppression, the bailouts, evaporation of the public option, a toothless financial reform, no real audit of the Fed, BP's constant lies, political bribery, uncharged war criminals and corruption beyond belief. My country was disappearing. How could I do nothing?&amp;quot; --Chris Pratt&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.deceptionsusa.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DecptionsUSA.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1293810509000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291240008000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Deceptions USA - with filmmaker, Chris Pratt </name><id>15612482</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1293753600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/15612482/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/5/6/global_19977158.jpeg</photo_url></item>