<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4 Richmond Square</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02906</zip><lat>41.827108</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-521-9229</phone><name>Waterman Grille</name><city>Providence</city><id>699167</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.380879</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Monday&amp;nbsp;Night Meetup&amp;nbsp;series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in Providence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week's location is: The Waterman Grille (next to that pink building at the end of Waterman St. and in Richmond Square)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So its the first ever Providenece Cocktail Week! Funny how we're not allowed to use "pub crawl" in publications in PVD, but Cocktail Week is okay - hmmmm. Anyway, this is a fave locale by many, so walk, drive, and get yourself to this cozy little oasis on the far east side! in celebration of Cocktail week they are offering half off appetizers with the purchase of a signature Cocktail Week cocktail - so what's not to like? The Waterman Grille is at the end of Waterman Ave. in Richmond Square - all the way at the end of Waterman Ave. So at the end, you may have never seen it, but its a gem. If you've ever driven over the Henderson Bridge to East Providence, aka The Red Bridge, you've probably seen it on the right (at least you can' t miss the pink building). So let's check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours.  &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but we'e hard to miss!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302620641000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>Because its fun - and this week in celebration of Cocktail Week the Waterman Grille is offering half off appetizers with any signature Cocktail Week cocktail from 4-9pm!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1301527104000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Monday Night Meetup - Kick Off Cocktail Week at the Waterman Grille!</name><id>17122231</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302559200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/17122231/</event_url></item>