<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>61 Alps Drive</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.791257</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Langford School</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>1136103</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.600856</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Officer Brian A. Aselton Memorial Snow Dash 5K Road Race&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, January 10, 2010;  1:30 P.M.  Starts and finishes at Langford School, 61 Alps Drive.   Sponsored by the Parks &amp;amp; Rec. and the Police Dept. Proceeds will benefit the E.H. Police Department Child Safety and Crime Prevention Program and the Officer Brian  A. Aselton Memorial Scholarship Fund.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the 18th running of the Snow Dash race and 11th since the race was re-named after Officer Brian Aselton.  Divisions include 17 and  under, 18-29, 30-39,40-49, 50-59, 60-69, 70-79 &amp;amp; 80-up.  Trophies will be awarded for 1st, 2nd and 3rd in each division for men and women.  Advance registration through Dec. 24, 2009 is $20.00; $25.00 after Dec. 24 and on race day between 12  - 1 PM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Computerized results provided by Platt Systems. #14001-C. Results will be posted on www.plattsystems.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://easthartfordct.virtualtownhall.net/Public_Documents/EastHartfordCT_Parks/FallProgramFolder/SnowDash" target="_blank"&gt;http://easthartfordct...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is the update. Our meeting place will be located inside the elementary school at 1:00 PM. The registration area is located in a Large Gymnasium / Cafeteria type room. We will meet each other, stretch and relax before the big event. For new people, you might be able to recognize us by our pictures. I myself wear mostly all black for races. Anyways, if you do not pre-register - get there early before 1:00 PM to register.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards, if some of you want to hang out, there is an italian restaurant called Roma. We can get some lunch. It's located  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;358 Burnside Avenue&lt;br /&gt;East Hartford, CT&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 860.282.0298&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.capadiroma.com/italian-cuisine.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.capadiroma...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming out of the school, turn left onto Goodwin street, then turn right onto Long Hill Street and turn right onto Burnside Avenue. Roma should be on your right hand side about 1.5 miles down. This restaurant is merely a suggestion (I am unfamilar with East Hartford). If you guys think of any cool coffee places or whatever, let me know. See you all on race day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SAM Z&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at Registration inside school at 1:00 PM.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sam</member_name><member_id>4195296</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1263749383000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Runners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>5K-Runners-Meetup</urlname><id>1354697</id><group_lat>41.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5699996948</group_lon><name>5K Runners Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260137978000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snow Dash 3.05 Mile Road Race - East Hartford, CT</name><id>12031274</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1263146400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/5K-Runners-Meetup/events/12031274/</event_url></item>