<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>across from the State Police Station</address_2><address_1>220 Revere Beach Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02151</zip><lat>42.413663</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Revere Beach</name><city>Revere</city><id>1035055</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.989861</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>So there are more than 500 potential volley-ball players in this meetup group but we don't usually see many new faces on the meetups! It seems most of them are afraid of &amp;quot;not giving the level&amp;quot; or something like that. This is what some of us have been talking about lately and so we'll try to create more Recreational-level meetups.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So this is the first one I'm organizing! Initially suggested as an idea on the forum of the upcoming Sunday's meetup, this will be a more casual meetup for those who don't play so often, and an opportunity for the VB lovers who can make it for both days in the weekend!, so as this is not going to be so &amp;quot;serious&amp;quot;, we can combine it with some tan &amp;amp; swim sessions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to bring background music, drinks, food, building tools for the sand... whatever you want.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The location will be the Revere Beach! I'll send my phone number to the people that RSVP just in case we don't find each other. We will be guided by the good advice of Eddy to select a correct location to play and hang-out! (it seems the best place is by the &amp;quot;Bandstand&amp;quot; between Revere Beach Blvd and Shirley...)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Access by T: pick the Blue Line until Revere Beach St (1 stop before Wonderland).&lt;br /&gt;By car: it seems parking here is easier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO LET'S HAVE SOME FUN!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andres G. Aragoneses</member_name><member_id>8249754</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1251140960000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Volleyball players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>volleyball-122</urlname><id>585043</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Volleyball Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250872141000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>More beach volley on saturday for FULL TIME players (j/k, recreational level!)</name><id>11165977</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250967600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/volleyball-122/events/11165977/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/3/global_1997523.jpeg</photo_url></item>