<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>56-62 Orange Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.304443</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Foster's</name><city>New Haven</city><id>317131</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.925110</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Announcing a new Meetup for The New Haven Collective!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What: Foster's Happy Hour!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: October 20, 2008 6:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where: Click the link below to find out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meetup Description: Welcome to the Monday Happy Hours series!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event is open to all, especially those who hate Mondays and especially for those who want to check out the different bar scenes in New Haven.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week's location is: Foster's on Orange Street&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've ever watched WTNH Channel 8 news you will know that Foster's is the restaurant of chef-extraodinaire Dave Foster, where he is a regular guest chef on their cooking &amp;amp; dining spot, always surprising with delicious and unique cuisine! (Showcasing &amp;quot;eccentric American&amp;quot; cuisine as their website states.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have GREAT specials for the group this week:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Free samples of Chef Dave's amazing cuisine&lt;br /&gt;** HALF OFF ALL Martinis!&lt;br /&gt;** A discount on a seasonal beer - might be Sam's Oktoberfest or Harpoon seasonal.&lt;br /&gt;** Reimbursement for all your 2008 401(K) losses. (Ok, just kidding, wish we could, but the 1/2-priced martinis should help right?!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact is Ed (203) 583-9668&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;*** Important Message***&lt;br /&gt;Hi All! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those of you who have been around for awhile and those of you who are new to The New Haven Collective...we hope you are enjoying all the events the NHC has to offer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many of you are probably not aware, but due to the fact that we have a URL on Meet Up, the NHC (ROBEN specifically) gets charged $72 every 6 months. &lt;br /&gt;Last January we passed around a coffee can at an HH and collected a $1 or $2 per person to help towards the funding of the URL. We graciously accepted the $70+ we received. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ROBEN feels it's time to pass around the coffee can for your contributions. It will be at the HH on 10/20 at Fosters as well as the next few events in which ROBEN is attending. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thank you in advance for your generosity. We all appreciate it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Management &lt;br /&gt;ROBEN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come early, come late, leave early, stay late, everyone is always welcome...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nothing ever cancels Monday Happy Hours. &lt;br /&gt;Ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***Bring a friend***&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>16</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1225148739000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1223673882000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Foster's Happy Hour!</name><id>8939098</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1224540000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/8939098/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/9/global_3516057.jpeg</photo_url></item>