<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>197 New Britain Ave</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.743870</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-794-1817</phone><name>Growing Green Wellness Center</name><city>Hartford</city><id>765918</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.689377</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us on November 21st  for an evening of reflection and celebration on these two aspects of life, through restorative and relaxing yoga, pranayama, simple ritual and meditation. &lt;br /&gt;As the cold approaches, we remember the many traditions that honour both the dark and the light, especially as the winter solstice draws near. In many traditions, light and dark are essential components of a whole, such as the Taoist&lt;br /&gt;symbol for Yin &amp;amp; Yang.&lt;br /&gt;To many people, spirituality is synonymous with light and transcendence. Expressions such as to be enlightened, to receive insight or to see the light reflect the degree to which fire and light are part of our spiritual aspirations. Yet often it is our journey into the dark that leads us into this light.&lt;br /&gt;Candlelight yoga is by donation (suggested donation $10) no one turned away for lack of funds. All donations are to support the operations of the Growing Green Co-op's community center and healing arts space.  Purifying teas, juices and water will be provided for cleansing and hydration. The Co-Op's infrared sauna will be available in 10-30 minute sessions. Please arrive promptly at 6:00pm to sign up for the sauna! First come, first served.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just added!&lt;br /&gt;From 7:30-8:00pm, we will have an optional hula hooping session led by instructor Laurie Kammer.  Laurie will lead us through a relaxing  session that will move the body with grace and fluidity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your positive energy to share with the group!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$2 donation requested. Use of the sauna is optional for a $10 donation. All donations are to support the operations of the Growing Green Co-op's community center and healing arts space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://blogs.yogajournal.com/cityblog/Candlelight.JPG" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>zoraida</member_name><member_id>9306539</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259017648000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256309681000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Candlelight Yoga- Celebrate the Light and Dark</name><id>11693839</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1258844400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/11693839/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/2/global_11365362.jpeg</photo_url></item>