<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>in advance, 35 @ door</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We haven't been to a concert as a group in a while, and what better time to do it than to meetup for the Larry Harlow Concert!!!  We had a blast last year, so I'm looking forward to doing it again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AND!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, I'm scheduling a dinner at Bertucci's with the group prior to the concert.  RSVP SEPARATELY for the dinner by emailing me through the meetup group (&lt;a href="http://salsa.meetup.com/193/members/2622923/)"&gt;http://salsa.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;, as I only made reservations for 15 people.  Visit the calendar to RSVP for the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you guys there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ana :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************&lt;br /&gt;Going to the Larry Harlow Concert?!  Well, join us at Bertuccis for a dinner get together before the concert!  Dinners range $8 to $20 a plate.  Please bring cash to make the payment easy!  View the menu for this restaurant at the following link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bertuccis.com/Menu_Restaurant.php"&gt;http://www.bertuccis....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email me (&lt;a href="http://salsa.meetup.com/193/members/2622923/"&gt;http://salsa.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;) to RSVP for dinner.  You MUST RSVP for the dinner as I only made a reservation for 15.  Also, please be sure you can attend before RSVPing so you don't take another's spot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The dinner reservation will be for 6pm, and we will head over at 8pm to the concert for those that want to take the lesson at 8:30.  Can't make it to dinner?  Then join us at the concert instead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location for Dinner:&lt;br /&gt;Bertucci's&lt;br /&gt;799 Main St. Kendall Square Cambridge, MA 02138&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you then!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Larry Harlow and the Latin Legends Band&lt;br /&gt;Salsa Party July 21st 2007&lt;br /&gt;Hyatt Hotel, Presidential Ballroom Cambridge MA band&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Gala Event presented by Hernan Choque, Doors open at 8:00pm dance until 2am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the gallery to check out the LAST PARTY'S PICTURES ---&amp;gt; HERE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Hyatt Regency's Presidential Ballroom, overlooking Boston will the be location for a great and unforgettable concert.  After a very long time Larry Harlow and his orchestra will be performing their timeless salsa hits.  The house will packed with salsa enthusiasts and friends.  Do not miss the opportunity to be part of Boston's Salsa History!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What the experts are saying about him and his orchestra:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;THOROUGHLY ENTERTAINING...If you like salsa, and especially if you are an aficionado of what hard-core enthusiasts call 'la salsa brava'!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;That special sound that the Fania created is still alive and well in the Larry Harlow Orchestra. The band was tight, the singing was inspired and the dance floor was packed!&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SCHEDULE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00pm  Dinner at Bertucci's&lt;br /&gt;8:00pm  Doors Open&lt;br /&gt;8:30pm  Complimentary Salsa Lesson&lt;br /&gt;              Dance with DJ Hernan&lt;br /&gt;10:30     Band will start Promply first set&lt;br /&gt;              Dance Until 2:00 am &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get your tickets now... $25 in advance, $35 at the door&lt;br /&gt;Purchase you TICKETS now !!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to get the discount for the concert, you MUST PURCHASE your ticket in advance through Paypal or through Ana.  The discount will NOT be honored at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ana Masacote (manager)</member_name><member_id>2622923</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>15</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185290028000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>40</yes_rsvp_count><created>1183419350000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Larry Harlow &amp; Orchestra Back in Boston</name><id>5966193</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185055200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/5966193/</event_url></item>