<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Old Williams Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02715</zip><lat>41.803190</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Deb's choice</name><city>Dighton</city><id>8786992</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.171170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Bike Ride: 10:30-12:30, starting in Dighton and touring through Swansea and Rehoboth. Leave all your stress behind and chill in the country (cue the song by Three Dog Night) and join Kliby and me for a bike ride of approx 20 miles through sparsely traveled country roads (rendezvous point to be announced). You might glimpse wild turkeys, deer, horses, cows, goats, alpacas, foxes and sometimes even a brown bear! This is intended as a "No Biker Left Behind" ride, so as to end up in one group for the cookout at Deborah Klibanoff's (Kliby's) place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cookout: &lt;br /&gt;

Potluck Cookout after ride at around 1:00pm-till the food runs out, on Kliby’s deck and huge backyard. Bring your favorite brand of beverage/poison and a dish to share. Refrigeration and grill are available. For those of you who are culinary challenged (like me), there are always ice cream bars, bags of munchies and those wonderful fruit and veggie trays that markets put together. &lt;br /&gt;

 Deborah will supply all the paper goods, hotdogs on the grill, tuna finger sandwiches and a crock pot of meatballs and chocolate covered strawberries. We can avoid duplication if everyone posts what they intend to bring. Games are welcome; Deborah has croquet and a badminton set that should still be all there, and then of course we can sit around and get silly with trivia games (I'm the most trivial person you've ever seen, so there's stiff competition!)&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346898157000</updated><rating><average>4.92999982834</average><count>15</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1344283282000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Labor Day Weekend Bike Ride/Potluck Cookout (Dighton/Swansea/Rehoboth)</name><id>76597952</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346596200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/76597952/</event_url></item>