<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>283 Asylum St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.767433</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Burger Baby</name><city>Hartford</city><id>5238972</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.678383</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/d/9/8/event_86992632.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Country fried bacon. Duck fat French fries. Macaroni and cheese with lobster, Taleggio and black truffles. Decadence reigns at Hartford's&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/burgerbaby?sk=wall#!/burgerbaby?sk=info" target="_blank"&gt;Burger Baby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, which opened earlier this month in the former Mayor Mike's at 283 Asylum Street. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

The area's newest burger joint melds elements of fine dining and comfort food, under the direction of executive chef Matt Hauschild. Featured starters like Parmesan foam-topped hand-cut fries, roasted pork belly in a cider-grape reduction and seared rare tuna join timeless classics like fried pickles, matzo ball soup and Asian popcorn chicken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burgers (five- or seven-ounce patties) are ground from a blend of Porterhouse, Angus and chuck, served on grilled brioche buns with organic Boston bibb lettuce and marinated tomatoes. Specialty burgers include the Big Cheese (Taleggio-stuffed with pickled shallots,) Fire (hot smoked paprika, sauteed chilis, chipotle aioli) and the Meatloaf, with applewood smoked bacon, crispy onions and house-made ketchup glaze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The premium Wagyu burger, with 7 ounces of American Kobe beef and black truffle aioli ($14.95) has an optional foie gras add-on ($6.) Non-beef eaters can choose from veggie, ahi tuna, lamb and turkey options, as well as a lobster BLT with Meyer lemon aioli.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chefs' specialties include larger plates like short-rib macaroni and cheese, grilled hanger steak, roasted chicken and seared sea scallops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playful indulgences extend to the beverages, with boozy "spirited shakes" and alcoholic ice cream floats with beer, vodka and rum, along with creative cocktails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at this new venue...let's check it out. I'll be there for Happy Hour at 5pm- but you can come anytime. Happy Hour ends at 6pm...we will be having dinner at 6:30pm. C'mon out!!!&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look, or ask, for Terri...Cell is 203-808-5829</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327876898000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326923955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Burger Baby!!! New Burger Spot in Hartford!</name><id>48666712</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327701600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/48666712/</event_url></item>