<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plans are coming together for our first Beltaine celebration in member Cheryl Boyer's backyard, and there is still time and room for a few more people to join in. Cheryl and her family are hard at work preparing the grounds and a pole for our Maypole Dance. We will decorate it together as part of our ritual and celebration. We will circle the Beltaine fire &amp;amp; hope to have some drummers form Cheryl's  drumming group. Bring&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;drums&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;and music makers too.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;We will have a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;potluck&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;feast, with maybe the first grilling outside of the season , and we'll see what else we all choose to create together. We decided to include men we know this time, and to make this event family friendly - children adore Beltaine!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;As always, this circle is open to everyone's&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;inp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ut&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;for planning our ritual and celebration, so please add yours too. We are requesting the usual $10 donation, per person / family for basic supplies, but if contributing monetarily is an obstacle for you, you can find another way to contribute.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Bring extra&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;ribbons and flowers&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;for decorating, and  for making flower wreaths and crowns. (artificial ones are fine for decorating with too)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Outside candles&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;are nice too.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;We will send out an email with the address just prior to the event to those that RSVP. Parking on  street. if you don’t have a car you can take the train . Cheryl will send more details on that along with the location, soon. The train station in Natick is about a 20 min walk from the Boyer's house, and we can  arrange  pick  up from there. Carpooling would be great too - there are a few of us from around Brookline if we can co-ordinate.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;We hope to grill, and that means for the non-meat eaters too. If you want to barbecue something, bring what you like to grill. And don't forget&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;yummy barbecue&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;sauces and condiments. Please bring&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;drinks&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;to share for the cooler too.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Please bring a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;chair or two, or mat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;s to sit on the grass- whatever you want to make the day more comfortable for yourselves, your family, and more fun for all.  Anyone want to bring those tarot cards we were talking about, or other&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;crafts / magickal arts&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;to share? Early on in the party we will decorate the pole and erect it ceremonially…that way everyone’s included,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;especially the men&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;who join us!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;It will be lovely to see all the Goddesses &amp;amp; their families. Let’s make this a Beltaine to remember!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span&gt;Many bright blessings, Maiyim and Cheryl&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Location will be disclosed to participants.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>cheryl boyer</member_name><member_id>13670965</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Maiyim</member_name><member_id>63013452</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367247876000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Goddess</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>goddess-327</urlname><id>1289522</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Boston Goddess Circle</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1364047417000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate Beltaine</name><id>110658312</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367089200000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/goddess-327/events/110658312/</event_url></item>