<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>180 Lincoln Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.350489</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-426-0180</phone><name>District Restaurant &amp; Lounge</name><city>Boston</city><id>822612</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>New Year New You: Powerful Strategies for Success on Your 2009 Goals  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;The new year is coming!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is something magical about this time of year. We take moment to look back on the year that has passed and look at the goals we have accomplished and those that we did not. The ball drops and the slate cleans.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why not take the opportunity now to dramatically change your future and make 2009 your most amazing and joyful year? Learn key strategies and thought pattern shifts to make that will change your relationship with yourself, your work and your ultimate success.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seminar is free!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Ruth Hegarty, Self-Confidence expert and certified Law of Attraction coach for this fun, interactive and powerful workshop that will explode what you see as possible for yourself today, in 2009 and beyond.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ruth Hegarty is passionate about helping people create authentic personal power and confidence in all that they do. As a certified professional coach and educator, she is adept at creating and customizing tools and programs to help even the most unsure people transform themselves into joyful and powerful creators. Ruth is founder of Leap of Confidence, a leader in the empowerment field and an avid promoter of self-determination.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Download Ruth’s powerful free confidence building e-book and receive her latest articles at &lt;a href="http://www.confidencementor.com/id15.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.confidence...&lt;/a&gt; and receive a free subscription to her  popular online newsletter, “IALAC News” (it stands for I Am Lovable And Capable), which brings a weekly dose of practical and powerful confidence to its readers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Professionals of Color Business and Social Network aims to create a positive, relaxed atmosphere, were people can meet new friends and business contacts. We also invite speakers who will help us hone our networking skills, learn the art of small talk and develop our personal and professional skills.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Qiana Christian</member_name><member_id>5933597</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>12</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232062082000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Professionals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>businessnetwork-960</urlname><id>1253532</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Professionals of Color Networking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1227226367000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Professionals of Color Business &amp; Social Networking Group December Meetup</name><id>9203127</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1229643000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/businessnetwork-960/events/9203127/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/global_5310243.jpeg</photo_url></item>