<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>275 Research Pkwy</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.518325</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(203) 238-2380</phone><name>Four Points by Sheraton Meriden</name><city>Meriden</city><id>754650</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.763240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>CT REIA and Robyn Thompson presents:&lt;br /&gt;Rehabbing the Gold Rush of Foreclosures with Robyn Thompson &amp;quot;Rehab Queen&amp;quot; (All Day Real Estate Rehab Seminar)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$59 for CT REIA Members&lt;br /&gt;$29 for additional CT REIA Members&lt;br /&gt;$99 for not-yet-members&lt;br /&gt;Register at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=225" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=225" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;History Has Repeated Again! Are You Ready to Ca$h In? You'll be laughing all the way to the bank after learning Robyn Thompson's system for turning Junker Houses into Profits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Depreciating real estate&lt;br /&gt;* Hard-to-get mortgages&lt;br /&gt;* Small buyer’s pool&lt;br /&gt;* Extended Days-on-Market&lt;br /&gt;* Job layoffs all around...&lt;br /&gt;* Tightening Credit...&lt;br /&gt;* Vacant houses all over the place&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn Thompson real estate Sound Familiar? Well... That was the mid-90s.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The years that Robyn Thompson became the Queen of Rehab.&lt;br /&gt;She rehabbed 51 houses in one year...&lt;br /&gt;Robyn unlocked the key…&lt;br /&gt;and discovered the secret…&lt;br /&gt;To consistently making large profits PER HOUSE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So now it’s YOUR TURN. Robyn Thompson is coming back to share with you the INSIDER SECRETS YOU NEED TO PROFIT in 2010 and weed out the competition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a recent interview, Robyn said she likes to buy low and then ride the appreciation all the way to the top! If you need Cash now, buy right, rehab right, and sell higher FAST. If you want money later, buy right, rehab right, and hold for cash flow and appreciation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY DO YOU NEED ROBYN’S INFORMATION TODAY?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Over the past 5 years, you could make mistakes buying and rehabbing and still make money. But that’s not true right now.&lt;br /&gt;* You cannot count on appreciation&lt;br /&gt;* There are fewer buyers on the market - &amp;quot;A&amp;quot; buyers - and they are picky&lt;br /&gt;* You MUST have a system to capitalize on each dollar - means buying right, rehabbing quickly, adding &amp;quot;wow&amp;quot; features, finding &amp;quot;A&amp;quot; buyers, and selling fast&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An Exciting Educational All-Day Event On Saturday, February 6, 2010. Learn How to Put Cash In The Bank Each Month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robyn has shared her knowledge with thousands of students across our nation and is now coming to your city to explain her perfected system and how it will work for you. This is not a &amp;quot;blue sky&amp;quot; program but a reality and each and every one of you can place as she does Ca$h In The Bank. Robyn has rehabbed over 260 properties in her 11 years of investing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free CD for everyone who attends, courtesy of Robyn Thompson.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She will instruct you on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Her Buying Machine&lt;br /&gt;* Where to Find Properties to Retail&lt;br /&gt;* 10 Criteria to Ensure High Profit Deals&lt;br /&gt;* The Rehab Process&lt;br /&gt;- Locating the Best Contractors to Get the Job Done&lt;br /&gt;- Prescreening Contractors&lt;br /&gt;- Writing an Iron Clad Contract to Gain Control&lt;br /&gt;* 4 Strategies to Funding Deals when You Have No Money&lt;br /&gt;* Selling Houses in a Down Market&lt;br /&gt;- The Most Critical &amp;quot;WOW&amp;quot; Factors to Sell the House&lt;br /&gt;- Marketing to Attract &amp;quot;A&amp;quot; Credit Buyers&lt;br /&gt;- Prescreen Buyers in 4 Min to Ensure They Can Buy&lt;br /&gt;- Handling Marketing Response&lt;br /&gt;- Request for Credit Review&lt;br /&gt;- Qualifying Buyers&lt;br /&gt;* Income/Debt Calculations&lt;br /&gt;* Other Income Factors&lt;br /&gt;- Credit Score Guidelines&lt;br /&gt;- Finding Down payment Funds&lt;br /&gt;* Conventional Financing vs. Government Financing&lt;br /&gt;- &amp;quot;A&amp;quot; Credit Guidelines&lt;br /&gt;- Where to obtain Credit References&lt;br /&gt;- Options When a Buyer Just Can't Afford a House&lt;br /&gt;* Real Life Examples and Practice Problems&lt;br /&gt;* Streamline the Mortgage Process&lt;br /&gt;* Application to Closing Timeline&lt;br /&gt;* Missing Items List&lt;br /&gt;* Building Your Team&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you can see this will be a knowledge packed day full of excitement and education. Bring a notebook - you will be taking a lot of notes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't Wait! Register Now for this event: &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=225" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=225" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1265637991000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263221861000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rehabbing the Gold Rush of Foreclosures with Robyn Thompson "Rehab Queen"</name><id>12286041</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1265464800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/12286041/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/3/0/global_3120816.jpeg</photo_url></item>