<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Our theme for July is Fairytales:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the full story vist our files page &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/files/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once upon a time in a faraway land a princess was a bit tired of the local princes and found the fairies and witches in her kingdom a bit boring. In the princess’ kingdom the weather was always fine, the sky clear, the water sparkled, and the meadows were gold and green. The food was always fresh from the garden and good wine flowed in rivers. It was the best kingdom in all the land but still the princess was restless. One day she turned to her trusty friend, Rebellion and said, “Trusty friend, we must go on a quest! What we need is adventure and a change of pace.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Off the two friends went across the great land into unknown territories. After only a few days on the road, the princess and her trusty friend were caught in a storm so violent and dark that they could not see their own noses. They found shelter under a bridge to wait until the storm was over. Suddenly they heard the voice of the bridge troll rumbling out of the darkness. “Biddy, byddy, bootycall, who is under my bridge without a by-my-leave? You will pay the toll or pay the consequences!” &lt;br /&gt;“I will gladly pay the toll, troll, as long as it isn’t a bootycall.” said the princess, “We did not mean to trespass.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“You must cook me a dish based on the theme I choose, this is my toll!” rumbled the troll. “The theme is chin hair, HA, HA!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Without blinking an eye, the princess started her fire. She searched under the bridge and in the stream that the bridge crossed for herbs and greens, fish and berries. Then she and her trusty friend, Rebellion waited until they heard the clip clop of a billy goat crossing the bridge. (They knew it was only a matter of time given the compulsive bridge crossing behavior of billy goats.) Quick as a flash of lightening Rebellion grabbed the billy goat (they have little beards) from the bridge and threw it into the pot the princess had steaming on the fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later that evening as the skies began to clear the troll the princess and the trusty friend all sat around the fire well satisfied from their meal of fish goat stew in a fruit reduction.&lt;br /&gt;The troll nodded at the princess with approval and then he rumbled, “Princess you need a quest, so I will give you one. Travel east of the moon to the land of unexpected weather. Once there, you will have two more trials but in the end you will find your heart’s desire.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the moon high in the sky and the stars twinkling behind the wisps of cloud, the princess set off again, this time with direction and a quest. Her trusty friend was right behind her. They traveled through desserts and over mountains, they crossed great plains and skirted majestic lakes always following the moon and their hearts’ desire. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soon they arrived in a strange land where the leaves on the trees were orange and red and yellow. The wind blew first this way and then that and all the leaves began to fly off the trees and be carried away. As the princess and her trusty friend continued to travel in this land, the wind stopped and it became very sunny and hot but as soon as the princess took off her long skirt and jacket the clouds closed in, thunder and lightning flashed all around them. The princess was sure it would start raining so she looked for shelter. She found a small shack that was empty and went inside. When the princess looked out the window there was snow falling from the sky. “This must certainly be the land of unexpected weather,” cried the princess as she pulled out her fan to cool herself, because of the sudden heat wave that was melting all the snow. Her trusty friend nodded in agreement while gazing at the roof in response to the hail that was now pummeling the shack. “Wait ten minutes and it’ll change,” squeaked a voice from the cinder pot by the hearth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The princess and her trusty friend went over to the hearth and looked into the cinder pot to find a large elf, almost three inches tall who squeaked, “Biddy, byddy, bootycall, who is in my shack without a by-my-leave? You will pay the toll or pay the consequences!” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I will gladly pay the toll, elf as long as it isn’t a bootycall,” said the princess, “We did not mean to trespass.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“You must cook me a dish based on the theme I choose, this is my toll!” squeaked the elf, “The theme is sweet tooth, HA, HA!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Without blinking an eye, the princess started her fire. She searched the corners and the closets, she even looked under the carpet for sugar (all shacks have sugar somewhere if you know where to look) and spices, jars of jam and strings of cheese. Then she and her trusty friend, Rebellion, waited until they heard the pitter pat of the rain stop and the ran outside to gather flours. Quick as the tornado touching down in the front of the shack they threw the flours into the pot the princess had steaming on the fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later that evening as the skies began to clear of the deep fog, the elf, the princess and the trusty friend all sat around the fire well satisfied from their meal of sugar loaf with a jam infusion.&lt;br /&gt;The elf nodded at the princess with approval and then he squeaked, “Princess you need a place to live so I will give you one. This shack is yours to make into a home. Once it is a home, you will have one more trail but in the end you’ll find your hearts’ desire.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the moon high in the sky and the stars twinkling behind the wisps of cloud, the princess set off to make the house a home, this time with a project and her quests end in sight. Her trusty friend was right behind her. They traveled to Ikea and visited Home Depot; they crossed the river for antiques and even found work to pay for everything always following the moon and their hearts’ desire.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Soon the shack was a comfortable home for the princess and her trusty friend. There was a fire in the hearth and comfy chairs to sit in while watching the changing weather outside. The garden was planted with cucumbers and watermelons, beans and peas, three kinds of squash and two kinds of onions. Still as cozy as their house was the princess knew she had not yet found her heart’s desire. She had her trusty friend but sometimes she was a little lonely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One day she was making cookies when she realized she did not have vanilla. Her hands were covered with flour and she was wearing her apron so she did not want to go to the store. Her trusty friend, Rebellion, could not go to the store without her; he was trusty but not very good at shopping. So the princess decided to knock on the door of the shack just down the lane. She waited until the sun broke through the clouds after a rain shower and then trotted down to the neighboring shack. She knocked three times on the door. No one came to answer her knock. She peeked through the window but did not see anyone at home. What she did see was a bottle of vanilla sitting on the table. “I could just borrow the vanilla and return it before anyone gets home,” thought the princess. She tried the door and it was unlocked! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carefully, the princess crossed into the neighbors shack. She tiptoed to the table and picked up the vanilla. Just as she turned she heard a shout from the doorway, “Biddy, byddy, bootycall, who is in taking my vanilla without a by-my-leave? You will pay the toll or pay the consequences!” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“I will gladly pay the toll, neighbor as long as it isn’t a bootycall,” said the princess, “We did not mean to steal.” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“You must cook me a dish based on the theme I choose, this is my toll!” shouted the neighbor, “The theme is your heart’s desire, HA, HA!”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Without blinking an eye, the princess...wait did he say heart’s desire? The princess did not know what to do. She did not know where to search or even what to search for, she turned to her trusty friend, but Rebellion did not know. When you do not know what to do the best thing is to ask for help. So the princess and her trusty friend went into the village and to everyone they saw the princess asked “What can be cooked that shows me my heart’s desire? Can you please help me?” None of the villagers had an answer for her, though everyone promised to think about it some more. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The princess and her trusty friend went back to her shack. The princess cried and cried. “What will I do? I will have to pay the consequences if I cannot think of something before the moonrises. I might as well finish the cookies that got me into this mess.” So the princess finished mixing her cookies and soon had them steaming on the fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just as the princess pulled the last batch of her cookies from the fire there was a knock on her door. She and her trusty friend answered the knock to find one of the villagers standing there with a bowl of soup. “I made this soup to share with you and your neighbor, maybe this is your heart’s desire?” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Thank you,” said the princess, “Won’t you come in and join us for dinner?”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just as the princess pulled the soup bowls from the shelf there was a knock on her door. For the full story  and the happy ending vist our files page &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/files/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to RSVP early as we always fill up quickly. Do RSVP though, especially if it gets you on the waiting list. Usually the waiting list people get to join us for dinner. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plan to cook on site, unless your recipe takes 45 minutes or more to prepare start to finish. Because the oven opens and closes often baked goods (excepting cookies) are best done ahead of time. Remember this isn’t just a potluck; this is about sharing the pleasure of cooking and food, and learning from one another while drinking wine 'n stuff and having great conversations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you'd like to drink plus a little to share.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send the address a few days before the event</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278951894000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276139847000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes Monthly dinner Meetup</name><id>vmbmnynkbmb</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278716400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/13756687/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/2/a/global_15731674.jpeg</photo_url></item>