<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>450 Whitney Avenue</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.322885</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethesda Lutheran Church</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1133240</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.917299</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Alexis will be performing in a holiday season opera this Sunday. Her description is pasted below. Meet at the church at 6:45, and take seats at 6:50. Death, Taxes, Time and Neil all wait for no one, and my phone will be off once the show starts. Afterwards, we'll go out for food/drinks depending on people's interest. Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Alexis:&lt;br /&gt;I know most people don't think of opera as a good time... but... I know of one that is a good time, and a very Christmas-season kind of good time as well. On Sunday, December 6 at 7:00 at Bethesda Lutheran Church at 450 Whitney Ave., New Haven, there will be a production of Amahl and the Night Visitors by the WCSU Opera department - and I'll be the orchestra for it. This is a Christmas story, it's all in English, it's very, very charming, and it's under an hour long. The singers are terrific, the costumes and sets are great, and it's very, very worth your time to see this - this is quality. To boot, the only admission is a freewill donation to charity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was actually produced on television every year for a number of years back when major networks broadcast opera, and it became a family tradition for many to see it. Since then, it's been a family tradition to see live productions of it all over the country - it became an immediate part of the opera repertoire as soon as it was produced, and a big part of Christmas for many, many families instantly.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1262291470000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259782353000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Christmas Opera, featuring Alexis</name><id>12001485</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260143100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/12001485/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>