<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>235 South Pier Road</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02882</zip><lat>41.428730</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Narragansett Pier School</name><city>Narragansett</city><id>12969042</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.469849</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;While I have never run a Marathon, I have Biked in 20 Charity Bike Rides.  Aside from the Beautiful Sites, along the Ride, I always remember the Volunteers at the Rest Stops &amp;amp; those cheering at the Finish Line.  It appears, many of the Wounded, were the Spectators &amp;amp; Volunteers, whose cheering made all the Training worth while.  That is why I am dedicating this Ride to them &amp;amp; any Runners who were also Wounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way I see it, we have 2 choices.  We can run &amp;amp; hide or we can stand-up and not let those responsible, take control of our lives.  Patriots,  do not run and hide.  Now about The Ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an all Speed Ride.  You can Ride  12-17  miles ( 1/2 Marathon) or you can ride 25-30 miles, a full Marathon.  The Route is Marked &amp;amp; I may have a Map.  It is very scenic &amp;amp; flat. Plenty of Water Views.  OK there is a Hill on the second half of the ride, just like Boston.    We have rode some sections, but at least 1/2 - 3/4 will be new.  There are a couple of sidetrack options,  that is why the mileage varies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first half is basically a loop, that ends at Narragansett Pier.  The second half, returns by the same Route.  Should you get tired on the second half,  you can cross the Road &amp;amp; head back.  I plan to Ride in the 12-13 mile per hour range. Maybe a little slower, depending on who is Riding.   Since the Route is marked, the faster Riders, can go at their own pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not sure what to wear as a tribute to the Wounded.  American Flag ??  Feel free to offer suggestions. Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Directions:  95 South, Exit # 9- Route 4 South. ( this is a Left Lane Exit ),  Stay on Route 4, and it will become Route One South.  Stay on Route One &amp;amp; take the Route 108, Point Judith, Scarborough  Exit.  All three are on the Exit Sign.  Right at the end. Go thru 2 lights &amp;amp; the School is down about 1/2 Mile, on the Left, from the second light.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We are in the parking Lot, in Front of the School. I believe the Second Entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave N.</member_name><member_id>10478672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366596748000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Grinders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group</urlname><id>1500421</id><group_lat>42.0600013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2399978638</group_lon><name>The Foxboro Grind &amp; Grub Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1366075414000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bike a Marathon, in Narragansett,  in Honor of the Wounded in Boston</name><id>114548262</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366558200000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Foxboro-Cycling-Group/events/114548262/</event_url></item>