<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Suggested offering</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;'Desires of the heart' and interaction of spiritual forces. Jewish mysticism derives from Torah that 'for the sake of man all world was created'. Yet, if physical world was created for the sake of man, why do we face difficulties fulfilling our heart desires? Is there a difference between the desire of the heart and the thought? Do they come from the same source? Does G-d notice either, or both, and&amp;nbsp; what takes precedence? How does He respond, and why? What is Providence anyways?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on the teachings of classical Kabbalah and Chassidism. We will look at the 'interactions of forces' and the structure of spiritual system as outlined in the crucial work of Rabbi Moshe Chaim Luzatto, and at the 'role of man' -- our function and purpose based on the teachings of Chassidic founders and masters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In every group we learn some basics of Kabbalah fundamentals, and about methods of Jewish meditation, and try some applications of it. Our approach will be to combine theory with meditative practice, as much as we can, and integrate new information with spiritual and sensory experiences. Judaism is a religion which is very much involving our bodies, and meditative practices of Jewish mysticism are also intended to be applied and experiential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What your right hand may have to do with your excessive giving-in, or in contrary, with your tendency to judge. What happened in your lifetimes that may be affecting the state of your body. What is the balance of forces, and why is it vital. What is 'mindful heart' and how we achieve the state of heart-mind connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goal of our Kabbalistic studies and meditations is always to bring ourselves closer to Creator. We pose no other intentions or agenda in our studies other then 'binding with the Divine'. We understand this as 'ascending the Jacob's ladder' -- step by step, or by quantum leaps if we're lucky -- evolving to our higher selves, actualizing our potential and connecting 'heaven and earth' through our own personal transformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love -- Miriam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suggested reading: browse &lt;a href="http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/109853/jewish/Spirituality.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/109853/jewish/Spirituality.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Parking right on the street in front of the house is OK.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1309126865000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Kabbalah-and-Meditation</urlname><id>1557684</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>Kabbalah and Meditation</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308260175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kabbalah: 'What and Why' of Jewish mysticism.</name><id>22476161</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1309122000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Kabbalah-and-Meditation/events/22476161/</event_url></item>