<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>190 Plain Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01852</zip><lat>42.624763</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Veterans of Foreign Wars</name><city>Lowell</city><id>10183672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.318115</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/2/c/event_177715852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Join me for a fun night and help support a local teen who excels at skiing, and who, with his 8 teammates are coached by Eric Bergoust, 4 time Olympian Gold medalist, and Word Cup Titles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eric needs to come up with approx. $15,000. for travel, lodging, and entry fees, to continue on his quest for the GOLD!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $12.50 at the door, or you can pay $10 through paypal ahead of time, or certainly donate even if you can't make it Saturday.  Donate through paypal or send your contributions to Eric Loughran NorAm Expenses, PO Box 642, Pelham, NH 03076.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little more about Eric...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eric has been skiing since he was 2.5 yrs. old. At age 6 Eric joined the Loon Mtn. Freestyle Team.  At age 11 Eric became Regional Big Air Champion. At age 13 he got recruited by Wess Preston to go to Lake Placid NY to live and train at the Olympic Training Ctr. for the summer.  That winter Eric took 2nd place in Easter B Championships (this field consisted of the top 80 B freestyle skiers east of the Mississippi) At age 14 back to Lake Placid for the summer.  That winter Eric came in 3rd place at the National Junior Olympics for Aerials. The next summer, back to Lake Placid, and Eric was invited to stay on and train with the USA Developmental Team, training 8-12 hrs. a day, 5 days a week.  On Oct. 8, 2010 Eric was invited onto the USA Developmental team and competed on the Nor Am circuit, representing the USA in a series of competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NorAm tour is conducted for the top US and Canadian development skiers with addl. positions for other foreign competitors.  The mission of the NorAm tour is to aid in the preparation of athletes for World Cup Freestyle competition through the provision of high quality training and competiive opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the winter of 2011/2012 at age 16 Eric had his first Nor Am podium AND a 3rd place finish at junior nationals.  He is currently ranked 8th in the USA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join me for a night of food and fun, music and dancing, raffles, prizes and cheap drinks ;)  Let's support a local teen to help him fulfill his Olympic Goals!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>look for meetup signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1352692345000</updated><rating><average>3.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352205724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Local Olympian hopeful needs your support</name><id>90192462</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1352595600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/90192462/</event_url></item>