<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>If you don't have any plans for New Years Eve &amp;amp; don't want to spend an other night in front of the TV, you should join us at the The Sheraton Hotel in Framingham.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EVERYTHING IS PAY AS YOU GO, so nobody has to worry about committing to anything.  Anybody who is currently undecided can join us at anytime for the party @ Molly Malone's.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$20 is for the entrance into Molly Malone's all night. Molly is an  &lt;br /&gt;Irish Pub in the hotel &amp;amp; they will have a DJ.  It also includes the  &lt;br /&gt;midnight champaign toast.  Doors open @ 6 pm &amp;amp; it's on first come basis  &lt;br /&gt;for a table. We will try to get there early enough to get a table, but no guarantees  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They are also having a Prime rib dinner buffet at J. Weatherspoon  &lt;br /&gt;(sp?).  The buffet is all you can eat for $29.95 per person.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hotel is also offering packages that include room/buffet &amp;amp;  &lt;br /&gt;entrance into Molly's.  I'm not going to stay @ the hotel, but if  &lt;br /&gt;people don't want to worry about driving it's seems to be a good deal.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://specialoffers.starwoodhotels.com/SheratonFramingham/SO.htm?iATANumber" target="_blank"&gt;http://specialoffers....&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;=  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(I don't think I copied the address correctly, but if you google  &lt;br /&gt;Sheraton FRAMINGHAM you should be able to get to their site.  The  &lt;br /&gt;packages are under Hotel Offers.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;HAPPY NEW YEAR!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be @ Molly Malon's.  "Try and find us, Think of if as your last adventure of 2009 or your 1st in the new year.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281130664000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Ma-NH-Singles-Club</urlname><id>1356935</id><group_lat>43.1300010681</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9800033569</group_lon><name>Trailblazers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1262116711000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Year's Eve @ The Sheraton Framingham</name><id>12169832</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262311200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Ma-NH-Singles-Club/events/12169832/</event_url></item>