<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1018 Lowell St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01741</zip><lat>42.554726</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-369-7486</phone><name>Great Brook Ski Touring Center</name><city>Carlisle</city><id>518726</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.353287</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Night Skiing: Great Brook offers night skiing by lantern light on Tuesday and Thursday evenings, conditions permitting. Lanterns are lit on the 1-mile Lantern Loop from sunset until 9:00 PM allowing skiers the chance to admire the combination of brilliant night sky and glimmering snow. This is an especially worthwhile experience during a full moon. Headlamps and other forms of lighting are not permitted as they negatively affect other skiers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adult weekday/evening trail pass is $10 and a full package equipment rental is $13. Cash or check only. I am a novice skier, so this event is suitable for beginners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet in the ski rental hut at 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greatbrookski.com/default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.greatbrook...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Catch the spirit of winter at Great Brook Farm State Park! Located only 25 miles from downtown Boston, Great Brook Ski Touring Center provides over 10 miles of machine-groomed trails for cross country skiing from December 1 to March 20, snow conditions permitting. The trails include all levels of difficulty and explore the beautiful landscape of farmland, forests, streams and ponds at 1,000-acre Great Brook Farm State Park. Skiers can stride past fields and a working dairy farm on the easy Lantern Loop, venture through the quiet woods around Meadow Pond on the Pine Point Loop, or test their strengths on the hills of the more difficult Woodchuck Trail. The machine grooming at Great Brook leads the way with a wide, packed surface consisting of two sets of tracks and a smooth skating lane. Return to the ski touring center's rustic lodge, a renovated cow barn, to &lt;u&gt;enjoy a cup of hot chocolate and a seat beside the wood stove.&lt;/u&gt; If you have never cross country skied before, rest assured that Great Brook's many &lt;u&gt;easy trails are perfect for beginners&lt;/u&gt;. If you don't have cross country ski equipment, the ski touring center's huge rental inventory has every size.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297436542000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1295755031000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cross Country Night Skiing, lantern lit trail</name><id>16149727</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297382400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/16149727/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/5/global_20910693.jpeg</photo_url></item>