<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>If you have rock 'n roll dreams, this is the film for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About It Might Get Loud:&lt;br /&gt;The electric guitar has dominated popular music for the last half century. Anyone who has ever plugged into an amp understands its power. So does the average stadium crowd. But if you have too much exposure to amateurs, you might forget the incredible range of expression that the creation pioneered by Les Paul can achieve in the hands of masters. Director Davis Guggenheim, well-known for his Academy Award-winning documentary An Inconvenient Truth, deepens our appreciation for going electric by bringing together three virtuosos from different generations: Jimmy Page of Led Zeppelin, The Edge of U2 and Jack White of The White Stripes. It Might Get Loud weaves together their stories to reveal how each of them developed a unique sound. Unlike rock 'n' roll documentaries that focus on backstage drama, this one concentrates on the music, giving us intimate access to the creative process. What's more, we see each musician play new work that has yet to be released. You don't need to be an aficionado to enjoy the pleasure of this company. The film might not affect how you play, but it will change how you listen. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It Might Get Loud is a marvelous rock doc that manages to be wistful, tasty, and jam-kicking at the same time. In a high summit of electric-guitar fetishism, director Davis Guggenheim unites — and tells the separate stories of — three six-string wizards: Jimmy Page, the virtuoso fuzz-box classicist of Led Zeppelin, who is now an elegant moon-faced gentleman; The Edge, U2's mad scientist of sonic jangle, who shows you some of his tricks; and Jack White, the low-tech hell-raiser of the White Stripes, here to pay homage and also to represent, you know, the kids. The result is pure candy for the guitar hero in all of us.&amp;quot; Grade: A -- Entertainment Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;It’s a group portrait of three musicians and also, more intriguingly, a free-form historical and philosophical essay on the instrument that unites them.  The mystique of the electric guitar is as durable as anything in rock ’n’ roll. Whenever the power chord or the screaming solo seems destined for oblivion, it’s rescued and revived, either by a new generation of players or, as has been the case more recently, by a video game...&amp;quot; -- The New York Times&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note that the time is an estimate; I'll update it when the Kendall posts times for the 5th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Updated: The start time of the film is 4:20, but Meetup sets times in 15 minute increments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.  (Maybe we'll even have an air guitar contest!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251394960000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It Might Get Loud</name><id>11216543</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252181700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11216543/</event_url></item>