<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>77 Tanager St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02476</zip><lat>42.421910</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-648-3737</phone><name>Herb Pearce's</name><city>Arlington</city><id>899371</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.188564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Herb is going to be leading a fun workshop about Creativity. Here is a description of the workshop from Herb:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“People are often most happy when they are creative! It's important to have creative outlets in your life whether it's singing, dancing, mental creations, poetry, music, drama, sculpture, drawing, art, sports - the list is endless. Enliven your life and make new creations from your individual expression, feelings and intuitive spark. We will focus on the value of creativity, help clarify what you need to do to be more creative and we'll have lots of creative materials in the room to write songs, make a poster, sing, make up stories and allow your creative juices to flow.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The suggested minimum cost of attending the workshop is $15.00. A sliding scale of any amount is allowed if the cost would otherwise prevent you from coming. The traditional cost of this workshop has been $40.00 so if you can afford more than $15.00, it helps the presenter and those who pay less.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served. We are also welcomed to bring and share our own food as long as there is not any meat in it.  Herb always has great snacks.  Great food, company and creativity - an awesome way to spend a Friday night!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Herb Pearce</member_name><member_id>9052522</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1269817612000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Explorers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Intriguing-Lives</urlname><id>979502</id><group_lat>42.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1699981689</group_lon><name>Intriguing Lives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268031932000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Creativity</name><id>12814862</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269644400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Intriguing-Lives/events/12814862/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/0/0/global_7009024.jpeg</photo_url></item>