<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Brookview Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03087</zip><lat>42.787914</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Barb/Peanut's Condo</name><city>Windham</city><id>5327232</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.359375</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SING AND DANCE FOR A GOOD CAUSE !!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;I am looking for volunteers to join my music group in entertaining the residents of Independent Living, Assisted Living, Nursing Homes, Rehab facilities and senior centers in the Nashua, Manchester, and Salem areas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like to perform and to give back to your community … then this is the place for you! We are amateurs so all that we require is an open heart and an eagerness to brighten the lives of the elderly and infirm. So far, we have two guitars, a drum, a few singers, and a few dancers. We would love to add a keyboard, flute or violin. In addition to singers, dancers, and actors, we need someone to help with the bookings, costumes, and props.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of a typical concert format, this 45 minute variety show was designed to keep the audience focused and to encourage their participation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Sample:&lt;/span&gt; our 50’s set&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I told Every Little Star” (waving stars)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Donna” (stroll)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Diana” (skit)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yellow Submarine” (bobbing subs)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The Witch Doctor” (grass skirt, headdress, cursing stick and hand jive)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal is to perform every other week at 2:00 pm with periodic breaks. If that fits your schedule, please come to an informational session to find out what we are all about. Feel free to bring your instruments, your favorite songs, and your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event has been cross posted to other meetup so please RSVP on one site to avoid duplications. No need to RSVP "NO" ... "YES" RSVP's only. I will send the address to all yes RSVP’s on April 29th.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign in the window.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barb / Peanut</member_name><member_id>7901156</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1367352371000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley</urlname><id>1116818</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3199996948</group_lon><name>Meeting &amp; Greeting in So. NH &amp; the Merrimack Valley :)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1362764504000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SING AND DANCE</name><id>108288362</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1367344800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Dating-Meeting-in-So-NH-the-Merrimack-Valley/events/108288362/</event_url></item>