<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.360510</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Building E51, Room 335</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>376848</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084770</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;Please RSVP!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Featured Speaker: Ray Rondeau - Topic: Covered Calls: Calculations and Probabilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Covered Calls are a very popular strategy with the retail trader and one that is often viewed in the option world as a relatively conservative position.  In truth when this strategy is utilized by traditional methods, it offers very little downside protection and can limit profit potential to a substantial degree. Which often raises the question for the astute investor after looking at the mathematics, if they are even worth considering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; This presentation will focus on how, with a few modifications to traditional approaches, the Covered Call strategy can easily produce annualized returns in the 100% – 400 % range. In fact it will be shown that there are Covered Call Simulated Positions where annualized returns can reach far in excess of those figures near 1000% or better. Better yet we will look at a technique that is now available to the investor, where the selling of a Covered Call will always produce a better return than simply buying the issue alone.  Yes, no matter how high the issue rises in price the investor would be better off writing the call, which challenges the classic theory and limitations of the CC writers of the past.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To illustrate these concepts, the presentation will start with a focus on the basic classic approach of how the key statistics on covered calls are normally generated and interpreted: showing the specific advantages of these calculations and why interpreting these statistics is so critical for the ultimate long term success of this strategy. We will look at how the evaluation of these numbers gives the investor invaluable clarity and certainty in regard to the actual execution based decisions that must be made if one wants to trade this strategy successfully. The program gives a thorough explanation of each individual step and how each attendee can easily create there own Excel spread sheet to derive these outputs, which are achieved by simply entering in a few pieces of basic information for each potential position they wish to analyze. We then take these figures, and specifically show how to interpret outputs to answer many of the most important and common decisions in relation to setting up and monitoring covered call positions such as:.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Such as: &lt;br /&gt;Which specific strike should I target?&lt;br /&gt;Which months or how far out should I sell?&lt;br /&gt;When should I close the position or should I just attempt to let the option expire? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the basic methodology and approach has been described in full we will then explore some of the potential limitations of this classic approach and why some additional modifications to the models may be necessary and appropriate for your personal style of investing. These newer concepts are then reviewed looking back at a Covered Call trade that was executed with the RI AAII group in 2010. This example illustrates how the application of these statistics were used to open and modify what turned out to be very complex positions. Giving us another opportunity to explore a few advanced position modifications concepts on how to further improve trading performance with Covered Call positions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although the targeted returns and the 100% better than stock ownership alone approach can be controversial and does challenge some long term established beliefs, the material is logical and executable. Even if one never chooses to execute the transactions, the presentation should to expand each attendee’s way of thinking and evaluating all potential future option based positions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray's Bio:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ray is currently President of the Boston American Association of Individual Investors Chapter overseeing five New England States, and is also group leader of the Rhode Island AAII SIG.  Additionally Ray writes a biweekly technical analysis column for the national based website Indexuniverse.com which is the publisher of the “Journal of Indexes”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; A full time professional trader since 2001, Ray has been presenting throughout the New England region for the last 11 years, under the trade name: &amp;quot;Investorstein&amp;quot;. Recently Ray has expanded to a National level with appearances in New Jersey, Philadelphia, Florida and with a panel presentation scheduled for the prestigious 4th Annual Inside ETF’s Conference in Hollywood Florida on February 6 - 8th, 2011. Please reference:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.indexuniverse.com/insideetfsconference/past-agenda.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.indexunive...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; With an education in Mechanical Engineering, Ray has developed and applies a combination of techniques based on his personal strengths of probabilities and technical analysis. Trading for 18 years now, Ray has developed and incorporated his own style by utilizing various programs including Omnitrader, TCNet, Metastock, and ThinkorSwim. He currently focuses on his main platform, TradeStation, where he is a professional programmer, and executes approximately 1600 trades per year, trading, Forex, Options, ETF's and Stocks. Ray’s approach is one that focuses on gaining a predictable and measurable edge on each individual trade by synergizing various investment vehicles and taking advantage of the variances and skews that regularly occur throughout the related,, but still individual security markets. These hedging techniques and the focus on risk reduction are paramount to his style which strongly emphasizes probabilities, to determine investment related decisions and de-emphasizes thoughts and emotions with their obvious limitations. Further, in an effort to reduce market directional risk and all of its associated causes, equity market neutral techniques are then applied to protect the entire value of the portfolio, which greatly reducing the volatility of the entire portfolio and promotes consistent profits in bullish, bearish, and neutral market environments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;If we have time, we will do stock picks and Tips, Tricks and Techniques&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Stock Picks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your tickers - the group will analyze them on the fly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Tips, Tricks and Techniques&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your chance to tell your fellow traders some nugget that helps your trading.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;The agenda:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:30 Boston Tiger Financial Group Meeting (see below)&lt;br /&gt;7:00 Introduction, Announcements, Polls by Jeff&lt;br /&gt;7:10 Featured Speaker Ray Rondeau&lt;br /&gt;9:00 Stock Picks &lt;br /&gt;9:30 Tips, Tricks and Techniques&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;BOSTON TIGER PRE-MEETING Announcement:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Tiger Meeting of the Tiger Financial Network meets during the hour from 5:30 PM to 6:50 PM. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.tfnn.com/bostonmeeting.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.tfnn.com/b...&lt;/a&gt; to see the full announcement. For questions, see Bob Podd at bpodd@softwareresults.com. The meeting is the same room as the 7:00 meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To join our online discussion go to&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/bostonibd" target="_blank"&gt;http://groups.google....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;or send email to Jeff Orrik at orrik@comcast.net &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have a friend you talk stocks with, bring them with you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We strongly urge each person to make his or her own decisions about investing their money. Investment ideas and recommendations made during our meetings and in our online dialogs bear no liability by anyone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free and open meeting. No membership is required, but please RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jeff Orrik</member_name><member_id>1135788</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>17</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289349726000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Investor$ who think 4 themselve$</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BostonIBD</urlname><id>81154</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Investor's Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>67</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286555996000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Investor's Group October Meetup</name><id>15046589</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288220400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonIBD/events/15046589/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/5/global_18566197.jpeg</photo_url></item>