<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Salem Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.260864</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Worcester Public Library</name><city>Worcester</city><id>3879852</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.800133</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Images for the show have been selected! And Boy it was NOT easy to do!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can go to this web site and see the final choices:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.me.com/gallery/#103751" class="linkified"&gt;https://www.me.com/gallery/#103751&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your image appears there you need to make a print and have it matted to a 16x24 outside dimensions. Please use a white mat... read on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Yes! This meeting will be for the members who are participating in the upcoming show&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;"Nature in Our City&lt;/span&gt;" &lt;span&gt;to get details, learn about framing the prints, and discuss the opening of the show.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Participants; We will have your frame ready for you at this meeting. We will show you how to take your matted print and put it in the frame with the glass and how to seal it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;What you need to bring to the meeting: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please bring with you a Flat Head Screw Driver!! Everyone will need one to put the frames together.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Your Print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Your Mat - cut to fit your print.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;A back board to mount your print to and attach your mat to. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Bring your matted print. This means you need to have a mat cut! The frame size is 16x24 so the over all mat must fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We suggest making your prints 11x14 or 9x12 so they can have a nice white boarder around the image. We will not be accepting images that are not matted. SO no flush mounted images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want everyone to sign the mats - we will discuss where to sign the mat at this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will need a back board to mount the print to and then place the mat over it. This back board should be the exact same size as the mat you had cut for your print. I recommend it be the same material as the mat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ideally you will be able to reuse this mat for every gallery show you submit a print to. I recommend you have a professional framer cut the mat and give you a backing board at the same time. Simply tell them it needs to fit into a 16x24 frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please check in with me about the title of your print and the price you want to sell it for before you leave this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any questions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to our next show...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donna&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in the Banx Room to the left as you come in from the  parking lot...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320722481000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318016969000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framing Party for City Hall Gallery Selected Images</name><id>36556372</id><headcount>28</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1320499800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/36556372/</event_url></item>