<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Want to ride on the sweetest piece of tar cake anywhere?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We found it this summer - Greylock Road in North Adams, MA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It’s been totally rebuilt from the ground up,” quips Alec Gillman, program committee coordinator for the Department of Conservation and Recreation Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC).&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;He’s the friendly guy behind the desk in the Visitor Center on a sunny afternoon in April, fielding a flood of phone calls about the unveiling of the state-designated scenic byway to the top of the tallest peak (3,941 feet) in Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“The funny thing,” Gillman adds, “is a lot of the construction you can’t even see because it’s underneath or beside the actual road.”&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Aside from the silky smooth blacktop snaking toward the iconic Veterans War Memorial Tower at the summit, most noticeable are the redesigned pull-offs—about half a dozen of them—and new “rustic” guardrails made of steel-reinforced wood, which replace the old, industrial concrete bollards. The 200,000 or so sightseers expected each summer will surely appreciate the natural aesthetic.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;“Especially Fitch Vista on Notch Road,” Gillman says of the once-collapsed observation spot, restructured with a view toward the Hopper—the geological basin to the northwest of Mount Greylock proper, named by local farmers due to its uncanny resemblance to the funnel-shaped grain dispensers. “It mimics the restoration work done in the 1930s by the CCC.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;318 mi – about 6 hours 33 mins&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;source=s_d&amp;amp;saddr=42.245552,-71.591586&amp;amp;daddr=S+Main+St%2FUS-7+to:N+Main+St%2FUS-7+to:Notch+Rd+to:Rand+St+to:Main+St%2FNY-2+to:NY-22%2FNY-7%2FState+Route+7+to:South+St%2FUS-7+to:Hoxsey+St+to:42.245552,-71.591586&amp;amp;geocode=FbCdhAIdXpm7-w%3BFbq-iAIdeqGi-w%3BFZYQiQId0Jui-w%3BFYCZigIdvYyj-w%3BFZSNiwIdc46k-w%3BFSxTjAIdLuGg-w%3BFZLljQIdS9mg-w%3BFSxDjgIdrBmj-w%3BFae4iwIdk_Ki-w%3B&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;via=3,5,6&amp;amp;sll=42.98054,-72.647095&amp;amp;sspn=3.291163,5.701904&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=42.75029,-73.226624&amp;amp;spn=1.651759,2.850952&amp;amp;z=9" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be meeting at the service plaza on Rt 90 just past Rt 495 or at the Concord Rotary (route 2) depending on engine size make up - If you can sustain 60 for an hour, come on down!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ride might be canceled if overcast conditions are present, it makes the ride lots better if the sun is out - rain date: Sunday Sep 27th or TBA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paid Twisted Touring Members only on this ride, members wishing to join, fill out this form and hand in with $20 to Paul Shoemaker when you see him. &lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/379328/GBSC%20Liability%20Form%20309.pdf"&gt;http://files.meetup.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doug Alden</member_name><member_id>5206555</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jim Ricca </member_name><member_id>6927550</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254428593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252890522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2009  Ride Favorite: Greylock Mtn Road</name><id>11364368</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253962800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/11364368/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/7/7/global_9557751.jpeg</photo_url></item>