<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;   The season is turning inward and it is a great time for us to be turning inward also. We are having our monthly guided meditation class. It is a great class for those who have experience with meditation to take some time, come together in a group, and get in touch with our inner selves. THis is also a great class for beginning meditators or for those who would  like to learn how to meditate, as guided meditation leads you through every step to having a deep and meaningful meditation experience. Welcome, everyone, and friends are invited also.&lt;br /&gt;Blessings,&lt;br /&gt;Rev. Johanna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note our new location at 844 Grand Ave. in New Haven. It's a new building (that we own!) and we are working to make it as beautiful as our previous location. There is no official sign, yet, but there will be one on the door. We are in our temporary place on the third floor for a few weeks, until we can renovate and move into our spacious first floor commercial space. See you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ex: I'll be the guy in the back with a Meetup t-shirt</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rev. Johanna Knight</member_name><member_id>3799220</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224895007000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NewHavenMeditation</urlname><id>435918</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Meditation &amp; Inner Spirituality Group - New Haven</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221266325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Guided Meditation Class</name><id>8747252</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221780600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NewHavenMeditation/events/8747252/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/f/global_1078639.jpeg</photo_url></item>