<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Lets try something a little different!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have been thinking about checking out indoor rock climbing for a while now, and I suspect I am not the only one.  So let's try an indoor climbing beginner's course at &lt;a href="http://www.bostonrockgym.com/default.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Boston Rock&lt;/a&gt;, followed by lunch and some brews at Fitzwilliams Irish Pub, right around the corner at the Burlington Mariott.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For $60 you will get 3 hours of instruction and climbing, equipment rental, a daypass for the day of the class, and a 2 week gym membership.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to Boston Rock:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Qualified, patient instructors will guide you through the basics of using the equipment (climbing shoes, a harness, locking carabiner and belay device, and chalk bag are all provided) and developing safe climbing habits. You will learn the following skills: properly tying into the rope, safely belaying in a toprope system, catching a falling climber, as well as other basics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We have now passed the deadline to make group reservations for the beginner's class, but if you already know how to climb and want to join us, or, if you want to wing it, feel free to meet us at Boston Rock this Sat.  However, if you are interested in the class, please note there is no guarantee that space will be available. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you don't want to climb, but want to join us for lunch and brews, meet us at &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/fitzwilliams-irish-pub-burlington" target="_blank"&gt;Fitzwilliams Pub&lt;/a&gt; (Yelp review) around 1 PM or so.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember that rock climbing is a strenuous activity. Participation in climbing and related activities contain inherent risks and dangers including personal injury and damage to property. Participants must accept these risks and take full responsibility for their health and actions during the event or activity. In other words you don't get to sue anyone, and most definitely not the Organizers/Assistant Organizers!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George</member_name><member_id>6616482</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273080938000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1239056441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rocks, Boulders and Brews</name><id>10130087</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1242478800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/10130087/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/3/global_8028371.jpeg</photo_url></item>