<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>36 JFK St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Le's Vietamese Restaurant</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.120180</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;George Washington&lt;/b&gt; U.S. 2000  87 min. Film screens at the Harvard Film Archive at 7pm. We'll meet at the restaurant at 5.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; During the Fall-07 through Winter-08 season, The Harvard Film Archive has featured Q&amp;amp;A sessions with  highly acclaimed directors appearing- from the more widely known (Michael Haneke, Arthur Penn) to the lesser known (Lodge Kerrigan, Apichatpong Weerasethakul- still working on how to pronounce that last name and Jose Luis Guerin). In March, The HFA continues with a retrospective of young Independent  American director David Gordon Green (no relation-really!) appearing with his film &lt;b&gt;George Washington&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;I submitted the list for reserve tickets at 8 pm on Monday 3/3. and so reserved tickets are no longer available.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For these events, we are able to reserve up to 12 tickets at the group rate of $8. If you would like a reserved ticket, please RSVP Yes and send me an email with your full name so I can forward a complete list to the HFA. The deadline for the reserved tickets is next Monday, March 3rd. Since this is a Sunday night event I think it would be best to meet at the restaurant before the film. Le's Vietemese Restaurant is located directly above John Harvard's Ale House in the Harvard Square mini-mall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;GEORGE WASHINGTON&lt;/b&gt; was selected for the prestigious New York Film Festival and won the New York Film Critics Prize and then went on to win major festival awards internationally. Elvis Mitchell of The New York Times said ?There is nothing like this film this year or any other year; it?s a dream of a picture... This landmark achievement is not to be missed?. And Time Magazine wrote ?this film stands and soars on its own. Its moves to a seductive rhythm and vision. And it has, like each of the children in it, a restless beauty that haunts their lives and the viewer?s heart?. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;b]George Washington&lt;/b&gt; made when Green was 23,  is an almost awe-inspiringly accomplished movie with an absolute faith in its own aesthetic sense, and an unapologetic preoccupation with finding beauty in the look of ordinary places, people and things.  Guardian UK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The plot has nothing to do with our bewigged first president. George (Donald Holden) is a thirteen-year-old black boy living in a multiethnic town in North Carolina. He hangs with a handful of friends around a rusted-out railroad station. The film is narrated by Nasia (Candace Evanofski) in a style that evokes the Linda Manz voice-over in Terrence Malick's Days of Heaven. Nasia, who has just broken up with Buddy (Curtis Cotton III), sees quiet George as a romantic hero. It's a sharp contrast to the relationship between beefy Vernon (Damian Jewan Lee) and Sonya (Rachael Handy), a blond twig of a girl who helps Vernon steal a car. During a game, one of the kids is accidentally killed. A decision is made to hide the body, and Green focuses on how that decision affects the lives of the kids. Using nonprofessional actors and mostly improvised dialogue, Green creates a dreamlike evocation of youth -- the delicacy of Ted Orr's widescreen camerawork is extraordinary -- that is shattered by a pressing need for maturity. At times, the film recalls River's Edge and Kids as well as Days of Heaven, but, in essence, Green has created a work of startling originality that will haunt you for a good, long time.  Rolling Stone&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green's pace is measured. Shots are long and compositions are painterlike. &amp;quot;George Washington&amp;quot; is set in an impoverished world. Houses are little more than shacks. Businesses are abandoned, and the town square is nondescript and bleak. Nothing is pretty, and yet nothing is ugly, because Green's pace allows a sense of wonder to creep in. Any environment, seen through the eyes of childhood, has a shimmer of possibility. San Francisco Chronicle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green dismisses the quirky, hip tendencies found in many recent American Independent films, citing Robert Altman and Terence Malick as his influences. A child of the South, Green was born in Arkansas, raised in Texas, and studied film at the North Carolina School of the Arts, where he honed his trademark Southern Gothic style.   HFA description&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A complete review: &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/movie/review?_r=1&amp;amp;res=9E01E0D71E3AF93AA1575AC0A9669C8B63&amp;amp;oref=slogin" target="_blank"&gt;http://movies.nytimes...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you have any questions, please send me an email. I for one would not be surprised if David Gordon Green's  &lt;b&gt;George Washington&lt;/b&gt; is a great American film that those in control (the film distributers) stymied for lack of expected return on investment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there,&lt;br /&gt;Tom&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>When you get to the restaurant ask for the table reserved by Tom Green.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1205269849000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204246058000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>George Washington</name><id>7429329</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1205096400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7429329/</event_url></item>