<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>49 Washington Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01945</zip><lat>42.506479</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Abbott Hall</name><city>Marblehead</city><id>1026106</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.848212</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Welcome to Marblehead's 5th Annual Fall Festival presented by the Marblehead Chamber of Commerce!&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;9/25/09 UPDATE:&lt;/b&gt; I have asked a few people and the best place to Meetup is Abbott Hall itself, Janet and I will be by the entrance, I have never been here so I am not sure what it looks like.  Here is our Meetup cell phone # 978-304-2811.  Please call when you get there if you are not able to find us, or if you are running late and I will give you a land mark as to where we are at.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PARKING:&lt;/b&gt; I am told that the best places to park are on the side streets.  Or if you know a good place to park?  Post a comment on the bottom here and let us all know!  Thanks!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s go explore a new town, and check out their fall festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to see you all on a beautiful fall day!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fall Festival Artisan's Fair 2009 Saturday, September 26th from 9:30am – 5:00pm Abbot Hall Upper Grounds (Washington Street) Rain or Shine! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Saturday, September 26, 2009, the Chamber will host an Artisan Fair in conjunction with the 5th annual town-wide Fall Festival.  This event will be held on the grounds of Historic Abbot Hall, home of the original painting of the “Spirit of 76”! The Craft Fair will compliment other family activities including street entertainment, pumpkin decorating, and many other activities on Washington Street and Atlantic Avenue.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A little history on Marblehead: While Marblehead has been know through the years as the &amp;quot;Birthplace of the American Navy,&amp;quot; in recent times the town has also been known as one of the yachting capitals of the world. Pleasure boating is certainly a popular pastime of its residents. Visitors come from all over the world to view the original of the famous painting, &amp;quot;The Spirit of '76&amp;quot;, which is housed in Abbot Hall in the office of the Board of Selectmen, as well as to see the beautiful harbor crowded with sailing, fishing, lobster and pleasure boats.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's go check out this town, and enjoy their Fall Festival.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there! &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/smile.gif' border='0' alt='smile' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will see you at the entrance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254523313000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249134240000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's go check out Marblehead for their Fall Festival</name><id>11007458</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253977200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/11007458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/0/global_7284256.jpeg</photo_url></item>