<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>57 South Main Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03755</zip><lat>43.700668</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Nugget Theaters</name><city>Hanover</city><id>3433202</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.289513</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Sarah's Key at the Nugget. The movie is at 6:30. Let's plan on discussing afterwards at Molly's over late dinner, apps, dirnks, dessert or coffee. Folks wanting to meet before the movie can make plans/state their interest, etc. in the comments section. A synopsis follows. I think this movie has some subtitles. Synopsis Julia Jarmond (KRISTIN SCOTT THOMAS), an American journalist married to a Frenchman, is commissioned to write an article about the notorious Vel d&amp;#146;Hiv round up, which took place in Paris, in 1942. She stumbles upon a family secret which will link her forever to the destiny of a young Jewish girl, Sarah. Julia learns that the apartment she and her husband Bertrand plan to move into was acquired by Bertrand&amp;#146;s family when its Jewish occupants were dispossessed and deported 60 years before. She resolves to find out what happened to the former occupants: Wladyslaw and Rywka Starzynski, parents of 10-year-old Sarah and four-year-old Michel. The more Julia discovers - especially about Sarah, the only member of the Starzynski family to survive - the more she uncovers about Bertrand&amp;#146;s family, about France and, finally, herself.&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318085608000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1327432</id><group_lat>43.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-72.3000030518</group_lon><name>Lebanon/White River Junction  Hiking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1317577661000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie: "Sarah's Key" at Nugget Th., Hanover, NH Thur. 6:30</name><id>35832422</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317940200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Lebanon-Hiking-Meetup-Group/events/35832422/</event_url></item>