<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is the first of 2 events I will be scheduling to offer the opportunity to assist with staging a Waterfire.  The first one, we'll be helping with whatever needs doing during the pre-Waterfire setup.  Next month we'll volunteer for the early shift during the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a great opportunity to do something different and have plenty of chance to chat with other newcomers, other Waterfire volunteers and make great contacts within the community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will update this with the exact times of the effort, however, here's how it works;  I'll be coordinating with the Waterfire volunteer coordinator and let her know how many newcomers will be assisting.  She'll schedule us in and we'll show up and work a 4 hours shift, which will start somewhere around 1pm and end around 5pm.  Please do not signup if you cannot commit to the full 4 hour shift.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activities to be expected - wear working clothes and practical footwear (no flipflops or open-toed sandals!)&lt;br /&gt;  - Fuse Assembly for lighting braziers&lt;br /&gt;  - Building Braziers (in boats)&lt;br /&gt;  - Carnation Duty &lt;br /&gt;  - Gardening&lt;br /&gt;  - Assisting with Boat Maintenance&lt;br /&gt;  - Moving stuff, lifting stuff, etc.  - miscelaneous.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the volunteer shift is over, lets get together for drinks and dinner and enjoy watching the fires be lit knowing our contribution to this uniquely Providence event is well received and appreciated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free parking for volunteers is available at the Park Rite lot at 198 Dyer Street.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Volunteer Checkin tables are here, I'll be here and be easily found.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279419575000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1276347596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Day of Volunteering for  Waterfire, Dinner, Drinks and Hangout for the show</name><id>13778203</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279386000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/13778203/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/d/3/global_3163235.jpeg</photo_url></item>