<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>A day after Thanksgiving Feast! – Friday Nov. 26 at 3:00pm. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Day after Thanksgiving Dinner Party at a private home in Cumberland, RI.  Children are welcome.  The exact address and phone number will be sent to yes rsvps on Nov. 22.&lt;br /&gt;Each Adult is to bring an item to share (see list below).  If you are bringing children please bring their beverage of choice also.  There is no event fee for children.&lt;br /&gt;$5.00 cash event fee per adult will be collected at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please RSVP yes only if you are DEFINITELY 100% sure you are attending.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is what we have----&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YES&lt;br /&gt;Germaine – coffee, tea, plates, utensils, cups, glasses, ect….&lt;br /&gt;Deborah – vegetarian chili&lt;br /&gt;Mary Lou Silva - sparkling juice&lt;br /&gt;Phil B – case of coors and white wine&lt;br /&gt;Preeti Varma - a fruit platter&lt;br /&gt;Bob – stuffed mushrooms&lt;br /&gt;Linda – mixed salad &amp;amp; wine&lt;br /&gt;CherylBene - Pasta or Potato Dish&lt;br /&gt;Sandra – stuffed shells&lt;br /&gt;Nance&lt;br /&gt;Maria – cheese &amp;amp; crackers, wine&lt;br /&gt;Maureen- soup&lt;br /&gt;Charlie- yummy dessert&lt;br /&gt;Richard – 5 bottles of wine&lt;br /&gt;Robin – vegetable dish&lt;br /&gt;Flower Child - +1 - Side dish of potato ah, la Roberto.......and BYOB stuff&lt;br /&gt;Laurie - dessert - apple strudel&lt;br /&gt;Linda – lasagna&lt;br /&gt;Roger- Chili with ground turkey and beans, ~3 quarts&lt;br /&gt;Jaye – Chicken wings and wine&lt;br /&gt;Mark – adult beverage&lt;br /&gt;Helane – corn souffle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; If you are a yes, please write what you will bring in the RSVP comment box so every one can see- and we don’t have repeats.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list of what we need.  Let me know what you will be bringing – post it in your reply- Thanks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appetizer&lt;br /&gt;Veggie platter with dip&lt;br /&gt;Salad and Dressing&lt;br /&gt;Side dish – pasta or potato&lt;br /&gt;Other side dish&lt;br /&gt;Vegetable dish&lt;br /&gt;Soda &lt;br /&gt;Beer &lt;br /&gt;Other adult Beverage&lt;br /&gt;Juice &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Germaine</member_name><member_id>10481143</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>9</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1290894323000</updated><rating><average>4.92000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1287023596000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A day after Thanksgiving Feast! </name><id>15104248</id><headcount>21</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290801600000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/15104248/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/5/global_10674181.jpeg</photo_url></item>