<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>176 Mammoth Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03053</zip><lat>42.846500</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Homestead Restaurant</name><city>Londonderry</city><id>379105</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.361656</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The membership has voted! The August Restaurant of the Month is Homestead Restaurant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Restaurant of the Month:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Homestead of Londonderry represents the original Homestead of Dr. Watson. The large square Colonial with twelve rooms and nine fireplaces was constructed in 1810 and is one of the oldest buildings in the town of Londonderry. Through the years the Homestead had been a beacon of hospitality serving as a stagecoach stop in the late 1800s, known then as Plummers Tavern. The tavern welcomed guests traveling between Boston and Concord on Mammoth road and between Nashua and Exeter on old Dunstable road, now Rt. 102. Guests were welcomed to the common room with its circular bar in the Northwest corner of the main house. The marks from the old bar can still be seen in the wide pine flooring. On the fireplace wall high to the right is a little square cupboard, The Parsons Cupboard where the most select beverages are said to have been stored A later Tavern Keeper, C.B. Knowles, was reputed to have charged $1.50 per day for meals and lodging. Today the McDonough family opens their doors to offer you a glimpse of the past and a taste of the finest food and beverage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.homesteadnh.com/londerry.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.homesteadn...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Menu:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.homesteadnh.com/menu.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.homesteadn...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the South: &lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 north to exit 4. Turn left onto Route 102 west. The Homestead is 1.75 miles on the right. This is a four way stop light at the junction of Route 102 and Mammoth road. To access the parking lot you must turn right onto Mammoth road and then right again into parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the North: &lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 south to exit 4. Turn right onto Route 102 west. The Homestead is 1.75 miles on the right. This is a four way stop light at the junction of Route 102 and Mammoth road. To access the parking lot you must turn right onto Mammoth road and then right again into parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the East: &lt;br /&gt;From the seacoast, take Route 101 west to I-93. Take I-93 south to exit 4. Turn right onto Route 102 west. The Homestead is 1.75 miles on the right. This is a four way stop light at the junction of Route 102 and Mammoth road. To access the parking lot you must turn right onto Mammoth road and then right again into parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West:&lt;br /&gt;Take 101 East to Manchester. Take 293 south/ 101 east to I-93 south. Take I-93 south to exit 4. Turn right onto Route 102 west. The Homestead is 1.75 miles on the right. This is a four way stop light at the junction of Route 102 and Mammoth road. To access the parking lot you must turn right onto Mammoth road and then right again into parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Next Month:&lt;/b&gt; Cotton&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will have a meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>FAN Alliance</member_name><member_id>3072150</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219100882000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1217773139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dining Event: Restaurant of the Month Club August Meetup</name><id>8466867</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218927600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/8466867/</event_url></item>