<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>15 E Plain St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01778</zip><lat>42.321089</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508 652-9830</phone><name>Wayland Wellness</name><city>Wayland</city><id>714843</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.363756</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;Please Join Us for Another&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Free Evening of Guided Meditations&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Wednesday Evening, July 15th, 7:15 -8:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Wayland Wellness, 15 East Plain St., Wayland, MA 01778&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I haven’t been running these on consecutive months lately; but last month’s guided meditations evening was so powerfully wonderful that I just can’t wait to do it again!  We were soaring in peace and love!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I haven’t decided which meditations I’ll do this time.  Maybe I’ll be inspired to bring you into your inner sanctuary.  And maybe we’ll do a sacred journey.  Or maybe we’ll even do a moving meditation bringing your connection to Spirit into various contexts of your life.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As many of you now know, my guided meditations aren’t of your typical sort.  Using what I know about Neurolinguistic Programming to create desired changes and positive states, hypnotic language, law of attraction, meditation, and more, I guide you in various ways to inner states of calm, peace, love and connection to your sense of spirit.  I often also create opportunities to connect to your inner wisdom for learning and growth. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One way or another, you will leave feeling deeply relaxed, nurtured and enveloped in loving energy, and feeling good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So please join us!  The more people we have, the better the collective energy and experience. It will be so much better with you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;All are welcome. This is not strictly a meetup event. The class is appropriate whether you are a beginner to meditating, or experienced.  Please invite others to join you as your guest, or email Ann with their rsvp.  She can be reached at annide@newpossibilitiescoaching.com.  Please also forward this to your friends, family and groups.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&amp;quot;Ann has been a huge source of support for me. Her powerful meditations allowed me to access guidance and confidence beyond what I was able to tap into on my own.  She guided me to a place where I was able to meet a very wise part of myself that I can continue to count on and dialogue with when I need added support. Meeting this part of me helped me shift a long held belief that was not serving me or my business.  It was so freeing personally and created instant bottom line results in my business.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;Paula Gregorowicz&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;***Space is limited, so an RSVP is required.  Please only RSVP if you know you can attend, so no one will be left out unnecessarily, and let us know if your plans change, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;*** If you prefer to meditate lying down, please bring whatever you might need to be comfortable: mat, pillow, blanket, etc.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go to back of front lobby, near water cooler and go upstairs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248217362000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246214059000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Evening of Guided Meditations</name><id>10753702</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247699700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/10753702/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/3/4/global_5412564.jpeg</photo_url></item>