<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/b/a/2/event_68659362.jpeg" width="147" height="221" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the time of year to give thanks not only of what you have, but of the people you have in your life. And what better way than over great food and excellent conversation. Do you have a great recipe that will feed 10-20? Please make a batch and bring it on over. And in return, you can experience the food of others. The RSVP limit will be upped to 24 for this event over the usual 12, as we're not planning on playing any games that night (although who knows if Catch Phrase will get pulled out). It would be appreciated if we do have a higher than 12 RSVP count that some people bring chairs (I think I max out at seating for 14). Also, if it does get to 24 people, I might still up the RSVP limit, it will just be a slightly spread out night. When you RSVP, please try to indicate what you might bring or make, or email me as soon as you think of it so that we don't have multiples of the same things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if you made some new friends by being part of this group, please come join us in celebrating those new friendships and connections.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will email my house number the day of or before the event. Park on the same side as my apartment (north/downhill side)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nidal</member_name><member_id>8949503</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353263113000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Fun Folks</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RI-Games-Events</urlname><id>1435824</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Games &amp; Events Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350485724000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fourth Annual RI Games &amp; Events Big Meal Potluck</name><id>87366102</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353024000000</time><rsvp_limit>24</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RI-Games-Events/events/87366102/</event_url></item>