<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1815 Massachusetts Ave.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02140</zip><lat>42.387146</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-354-7766</phone><name>Tavern in the Square - Porter</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>859456</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.118996</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/e/0/event_93596032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;That's right - the folks at Science in the News are going to be talking about the neuroscience of - you guessed it - makin' whoopee! Join us at Tavern in the Square for another installment of Science by the Pint, as Catherine Dulac and colleagues present Sex Battles in the Brain: The Neuroscience of Sex. Their research involves the behavior of laboratory mice as their pheromone transmitters/receptors are altered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;For those who've never been, Science by the Pint is an event sponsored by Science in the News, an organization of Harvard graduate students who are dedicated to bringing cutting edge scientific research to the public in a fun and informal format.  The event features a main speaker who talks for about 5-10 minutes about their research, then the team comes around to individual tables and spends one-on-one time answering questions over food and refreshments.  There are drawings for prizes, and lots of nerdy fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The event officially starts at 7:00, but the earlier you get there, the better chance you have of finding fellow nerds and a place to sit.  Plus you can get your food and drinks, and be ready once things get going.  Doreen and I will have our nerdy Meetup pins, so look for us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Tavern in the Square is located on Mass Ave, just a short walk from the Porter Square Red Line stop.  But for those who prefer the ol' jalopy, there is parking along the left side and in back of the building.  Also you can park on Mass Ave, if you can find a spot. The meters stop collecting quarters at 6:00.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;And as I always warn, if you park in the Porter Square Shopping Center lot by Shaw's, Tags, etc., your sweet virgin car may have a dark alley encounter with some surly tow truck drivers, and it'll never be the same...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/"&gt;http://www.taverninthesquare.com/tavporter/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for us at the back across from the bar...we'll be wearing our Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334809257000</updated><rating><average>2.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>116</yes_rsvp_count><created>1333506020000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Science by the Pint: Sex Battles in the Brain - The Neuroscience of Sex</name><id>59165502</id><headcount>100</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334701800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/59165502/</event_url></item>