<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us for an informational gathering to learn about the upcoming July 2012 trip to OREGON!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;I'll be providing more details and be able to answer any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our location will depend on the number who RSVP to this info night. I'd like to do a private potluck unless the number is large enough to warrant a pub or restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll also begin to ask for deposits from those who have committed to the trip so I can make firm reservations. Places are already filling up for the summer so we need to act soon. A check for $400 will reserve your place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But RSVP for this night even if you're not sure about the trip yet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet from about 6pm to 8 or 9pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/43569912/"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Trip Description&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/43569912/"&gt;Join a select group of adventurers as we discover the wonders of Portland, Oregon and the Cascade Range in July 2012&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/c/d/4/event_77636532.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll explore active volcanoes and ancient lava flows,&amp;nbsp;10,000-foot peaks, Alpine meadows, living glaciers, hot springs, virgin forests with massive, moss-draped trees, and many of the spectacular waterfalls these Cascade Mountains were named for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll also visit beautiful Portland, lush with flowers and gardens, hand-crafted ales, smoked salmon, world-class wines, outdoor cafes and markets, beautiful architecture, colorful history, and the largest bookstore on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For ten years before coming to New Hampshire, I lived in Portland and explored Oregon's wild landscapes at every every opportunity. We'll be visiting places I came to know and love during those years and have always wanted to share with friends from New England.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be an active trip, planned around easy to moderate hikes each day. The following itinerary is still preliminary and is subject to change in its details - but not in its spirit. My goal is to create a trip with with a maximum of outdoor time and a minimum of driving while visiting some of the most amazing places that this spectacular region has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll arrive &lt;strong&gt;Saturday&lt;/strong&gt;, meeting at our (really cool) hotel in Portland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We'll have a great breakfast (with the best Northwest coffee) and explore the city, maybe visiting the &lt;a href="http://japanesegarden.com/"&gt;Japanese Gardens&lt;/a&gt;, Powell's City of Books, and a large&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.portlandsaturdaymarket.com/"&gt;outdoor art market&lt;/a&gt;. There's even a 5,000-acre city forest park with over 70 miles of hiking trails. We don't really even need to leave Portland!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/8/0/event_82168032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Monday:&amp;nbsp;We'll drive our spacious van to &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mt_st_helens"&gt;Mount Saint Helens National Monument&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;This very active volcano erupted in 1980, devastating the landscape for miles around it. There will be much to see and we'll be sure to get in a hike among the miles of trees snapped like twigs and enormous mud flows the explosion caused. If there's time, we might also visit &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ape_Cave"&gt;Ape Cave&lt;/a&gt;, one of the longest lava tube caves known to exist, before we return to Portland for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/5/2/event_82169522.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Tuesday:&amp;nbsp;We'll drive to the Columbia River Gorge National Scenic Area and begin a loop around the Cascade Mountains. The Gorge has sheer basalt cliffs and breathtaking waterfalls. We'll stop at several places along the way and then do one of the most beautiful hikes imaginable along a particularly spectacular side canyon. You'll lose count of the waterfalls and turquoise pools within the first two miles, and the trail is flat so it's also a very easy hike. Afterward, we'll visit the interesting town of Hood River for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wednesday:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We leave the river valley and head into the Alpine zone. &amp;nbsp;Mount Hood stands at over 11,000 feet and if conditions permit, we'll hike to one of the many glaciers flanking its summit. Fortunately, there's a fire road that will take us most of the way and the hike will be only moderately strenuous. As we stand at almost 7,000 feet, we'll be higher than any mountain in the eastern US but only 2/3 up Mount Hood. We should see colorful meadows of wildflowers, a roaring glacial river, and sublime views for a hundred miles, centered on a string of snow-capped peaks.&amp;nbsp;There is also an impressive depression-era lodge built with massive timbers where we can relax in front of a roaring fire.&amp;nbsp;And we'll sleep in a rustic lodge run by a local hiking and climbing group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/3/d/e/event_82169662.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Thursday: Ancient Forests. Virgin Forests. Old-growth. All names for the still-untouched tracts of land in the lower-elevation woods. The trees are 6 feet in diameter, standing over 200 feet tall, and hundreds of years old. Moss covered and mysterious, where spotted owls fly and plaintive, flutelike thrush songs echo through the deep forest. We'll take a short hike to a deep-woods hot spring. There are soaking tubs hewn out of giant cedar logs to relax in and as much of the forest to explore as we want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday&lt;/strong&gt;: In the Central Cascades, more virgin forest, rivers and waterfalls, and an ancient lava flow to explore. We'll choose a hike from among the many possibilities and stay in a former Catholic schoolhouse converted into a brewpub and inn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday&lt;/strong&gt;: We'll choose a morning hike or a mountain bike ride along the renowned &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://mckenzierivertrail.com/"&gt;McKenzie River Trail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; before returning to Portland later in the day with a group dinner to celebrate our journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunday&lt;/strong&gt;: Breakfast and flights home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/d/e/e/event_82168142.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This trip is for a small group of adventurers who want to get outside and enjoy some incredible wilderness &amp;nbsp;and an amazing city in the Pacific Northwest. Each day has physical activity but there will be options for just how much or little the individual or the group want to do. I've striven to find interesting but affordable lodging options, and accommodations will be in hotels and small bunk rooms. This is a group trip and we will be sharing rooms, meals, a comfortable van, and some incredible experiences together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dates&lt;/strong&gt;: Sat, July 14 - Sun, July 22&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost&lt;/strong&gt;: Approximately $1150 per person for a &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;minimum of 6 participants/maximum of 9&lt;/span&gt;. Airfare is not included and will range from about $350-$450.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's included&lt;/strong&gt;: 9 days/8 nights' lodging (Sat-Sat), National Forest permits and entry fees, 9 meals (3 days' worth), van rental, fuel, and insurance. And other expenses including guidebooks, maps, parking, hotel tips, etc. You only need to provide airfare and the remainder of your meals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVP to this post right away if you're interested and would like more information. There is a limited number of spaces and I need to gauge interest in order to make reservations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not hesitate to contact me with any questions or concerns. It will be a small group so we can adjust details to accommodate!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1328031774000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326999518000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Oregon Adventure Info Night</name><id>48781522</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327705200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/48781522/</event_url></item>