<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>West side of Route 16 (North of Jackson and South of Gorham)</address_1><state>NH</state><lat>44.146263</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rocky Branch Trailhead</name><city>Jackson</city><id>4951672</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.185097</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizer: Ken Hodges &amp;amp; Tomoko Nakajima&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shamelessly plagiarized, but with permission of Karine (and permission of Michael Blair), I copied her event description.&amp;nbsp; As Ken and I moved our Cannon, Cannonball, N/S Kinsman hike from Jan 15th to 22nd, we're now open on 15th.&amp;nbsp; We're on the waiting list to get in Karine's Isolation hike in Feb, but, there is perhaps very less chance to join as there are many people are on the waiting list.&amp;nbsp; So we decided to set up the same event and hike Isolation!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire&amp;nbsp;description&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;before you RSVP and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;answer all questions&amp;nbsp;that are part of the RSVP&lt;/strong&gt;. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event. If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk &amp;ndash; consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will hike the remote and beautiful Mt. Isolation (4,003 ft - #46 on the NH4K) in the Dry River Wilderness.&amp;nbsp;The open summit has&amp;nbsp;magnificent views in all directions especially of nearby Mt. Washington and the&amp;nbsp;Southern Presidentials.&amp;nbsp;We will use the&amp;nbsp;Rocky Branch Trail, the Engine Hill Bushwhack (bypassing 4 of the 5 Rocky Branch brook crossings), the Isolation Trail and the Davis Path. &lt;em&gt;To sign up for this hike, you should be an experienced winter hiker, who has recently completed hikes of at least 8-10 miles, and who consistently hikes at or better than book time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if&amp;nbsp;you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted&lt;/strong&gt; - all participants must be members of the Random Group of Hikers. This allows us to keep track of and communicate with each person who signs up to participate in our events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are discouraged&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike due to the uncertainty of conditions. If your dog has experience with long hikes of this nature in winter&amp;nbsp;conditions&amp;nbsp;and you are confident that he/she can handle this advanced hike, please email us to discuss.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (~ 2 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;out-and-back trip we&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;follow the Rocky Branch trail, to the Engine Hill bushwhack (to bypass 4 of the 5 Rocky Branch brook crossings and save some mileage), to the Isolation Trail to the Davis Path to the spur trail to Mt. Isolation.&amp;nbsp; We will&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hike about&amp;nbsp;13 miles&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;climb about 3,400 feet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;While it should take an average hiker&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;about 8 hours 15 minutes to complete&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;this trip, we may actually move slower because of winter conditions (trail breaking, route finding, changing gear/footwear, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;because of the pace, distance, and elevation gain.&amp;nbsp;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire&amp;nbsp;event&amp;nbsp;as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While we have traveled this route before,&amp;nbsp;we also&amp;nbsp;did research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's&amp;nbsp;"White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You should become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards&amp;nbsp;since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click below&amp;nbsp;for more information:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://peakbagger.com/peak.aspx?pid=6971"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;for&amp;nbsp;Isolation from Peakbagger.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;for trail conditions from TrailsNH.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions.&amp;nbsp;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time.&amp;nbsp;We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mountwashington.org/weather/forecast.php"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for current weather conditions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing, Gear, Equipment, and Supplies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Below is a list describing the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;required items to participate in this event. Hiking safely is about being prepared so that you can respond to an emergency situation or spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Waterproof/Insulated winter hiking boots with synthetic or wool socks. Gaiters to keep the snow out of your boots. Mountaineering snowshoes with aggressive teeth for traction while climbing. Kahtoola Microspikes or Hillsound Crampons are acceptable for this hike. &amp;nbsp;Mountaineering crampons with 10-12 teeth are optional. Since we won't be using these items all of the time either have space in your pack or a way to secure them to the outside of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clothing&lt;/strong&gt;: Dress in synthetics, fleece, and/or wool layers to easily regulate body temperature. Make sure your layers fit comfortably over each other. DO NOT WEAR COTTON - while cotton is a great insulator when it is dry, once wet it doesn't dry easily and it rapidly draws heat away from the body.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outerwear&lt;/strong&gt;: Insulated jacket. Windproof/waterproof shell (with hood) and pants. Make sure your outerwear fits comfortably over all of your other clothing. Fleece/wool hat, balaclava or face shield, neck warmer, and glove liners. Windproof/waterproof&amp;nbsp;over-mittens.&amp;nbsp;Goggles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food and Water&lt;/strong&gt;: Bring high-energy snacks, food for lunch - pack extra "just in case". Bring enough water to stay properly hydrated during the trip - use insulated wide-mouth bottles instead of a hydration bladder since the mouthpiece/tube can freeze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shelter&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Be prepared to&amp;nbsp;spend a night in the woods if you have to.&amp;nbsp;Options include an ultralight tarp, a bivy sack, or an emergency space blanket which packs small and weighs just ounces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Essential Gear&lt;/strong&gt;: Map and compass - don't just bring them know how to use them. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with two sets of spare batteries - lithium work best in colder temperatures. Personal first aid kit with an emergency space blanket. Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Matches or wind-proof lighter and fire starter. Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Sunglasses. Waterproof cover for your pack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional Items&lt;/strong&gt;: Trekking poles. Camera.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We will meet at the &lt;strong&gt;Rocky Branch Trailhead on Route 16&lt;/strong&gt; - several miles north of Jackson and south of Pinkham Notch and Gorham.&amp;nbsp; According to Google Maps this spot is about 150 miles from Boston and it should take about&amp;nbsp;3 hours&amp;nbsp;15 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?saddr=Boston,+MA&amp;amp;daddr=NH-16+N%2FPinkham+Notch+Rd&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sll=44.20447,-71.240818&amp;amp;sspn=0.002515,0.00523&amp;amp;geocode=FZ9WhgIdw7bD-ykbMT0NLWXjiTGg6GIBJL98eA%3BFTB_ogIdaPnA-w&amp;amp;vpsrc=0&amp;amp;mra=ls&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for the driving directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Once you open Google Maps simply change the generic starting point ("Boston, MA") to your own starting point to get customized directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our car will be either Honda CR-V(red) or  Subaru Outback(blue)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tomoko</member_name><member_id>8122788</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>ken hodges</member_name><member_id>8561025</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327369071000</updated><rating><average>4.57000017166</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326116717000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Isolation (INTERMEDIATE/ADVANCED)</name><id>47316502</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1326632400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/47316502/</event_url></item>