<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>One Kendall Square </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.367496</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 499-1996</phone><name>Kendall Square Cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>495181</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.090100</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

I will be at the theater by 6:50. We will head in to the theater at 7:10. The movie is at 7:20. This movie will be at the Kendall, and I'll be waiting at the balcony above the lobby with my red hat with the meetup logo. Just look up!

Always a good idea to buy your ticket online... this url works, but be sure to change the date! &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" class="linkified"&gt;https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231&lt;/a&gt;


[b]Description[/b]

From director Michael Radford comes FLAWLESS, a clever diamond-heist thriller set in swinging 1960s London. Demi Moore stars as female executive at the London Diamond Corporation that finds herself frustrated by a glass ceiling after years of faithful employment. She befriends a janitor (Michael Caine) who is reaching the end of his tenure at the company and is looking to help himself to a considerably more generous retirement package. Together they hatch a plot to steal a handful of priceless diamonds, setting off a swirling chain of events that send ripples all over Europe in this fast paced, stylish film. 


[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/2GfpT1GCXy8&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;


[b]Website[/b]

&lt;a href="http://www.flawlessfilm.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.flawlessfilm.com/&lt;/a&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be standing at the balcony above the lobby wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. Just look up!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1207482691000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>For the master Michael Caine, and one time highest-paid-actress-in-movies ($10 mil per pic!) Demi Moore. Come see if they've still got their chops in an old school heist picture. Also co-starring Lambert Wilson, the Merovingian in the Matrix sequels.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1202779489000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flawless</name><id>7313317</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1206744300000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7313317/</event_url></item>