<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Add some Eco to your Ego&lt;br /&gt;Energy Recycling and Conservation in Healing and Therapeutic Practices &lt;br /&gt;with Yuliya Cohen&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ability to let go and release energy has been treated as an icon of American virtues on the path of  self-growth. But do you know where the released energy goes?&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;As Eckhart Tolle explained in “New Earth”, released “pain bodies” can transfer and contaminate others.  Besides, most of us are already leaking energy from our energetic biofield.  What we need is to replenish it, not to lose more. As we get older, it becomes imperative to curb the loss.  We can learn to &amp;quot;recycle&amp;quot; our energy, rather than &amp;quot;lose&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;waste it.&amp;quot;   We have a great opportunity to revision healing ourselves in a way that recycles and conserves energy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;During our February meetup we will learn specific actions you can take to conserve your energy and limit impact of the ‘energetic pollution’ on the environment.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the beginning of each meeting, we have a chance to get to know one another and our professional specialties. We share a potluck lunch, and then have a featured presenter share about his/her work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please let me know what you'll bring for the potluck lunch when you RSVP.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$5 meeting fee.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will welcome you at the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Marks</member_name><member_id>5692888</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1236955743000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Alternative Health Practioners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>alternative-703</urlname><id>1152400</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.2099990845</group_lon><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1221589265000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Area Mind-Body Therapies February Meetup</name><id>8769343</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1234542600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/alternative-703/events/8769343/</event_url></item>