<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Join the Members and Guests of both the SSDOMG and the SSFMG as we attend the last of the Braintree Park's Department Summer Concert Series at Sunset Lake in Braintree. True West, a local country band, has been entertaining for years and they're a great band. For more info on the band check out their websites listed below. We'll be able to dance to lots of their songs and they're great entertainers. Feel free to bring drinks and snacks to share with others as well as a chair or blanket.  Angela will bring a large green blanket which can easily accommodate 6-8 people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://truewestmusic..." target="_blank"&gt;http://truewestmusic....&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the concert runs from 6-8pm, I plan to arrive by 5:45 to save some seating for us. Please note in your RSVP Comments what time we should expect you. Since I will be coming from a dr's appt, please look for Ann.  We will try to make arrangements for her to have the blanket and/or a Meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Who? ANYONE!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What? Free Summer Concert at Sunset Lake in Braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When? Wednesday, August 13th @ 5:45-8pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Where? Sunset Lake off Safford Street in Braintree&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why? Why not? It's free. It's summer. It's country music. There's opportunity to dance, socialize, and swim in the Lake as well. You can expand your social and musical horizons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How much? Nothing - It's FREE!!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How many? I'll be there w/ some of my friends. Come on out and join the fun. No minimum, no maximum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note the following in your RSVP Comments your&lt;br /&gt;Anticipated Arrival Time &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather Alternative: None.  If the concert is rained out Tuesday and Wednesday it will be cancelled.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organizers: Angela and Ann (SSFMG AO)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP Deadlines: 3pm on Wednesday, August 13th &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP so we will know whether or not to expect you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Sunset Lake, Braintree:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunset Lake is located off Safford Street off Route 37 in Braintree, just 3/4 mi south and east of Braintree's &amp;quot;5 Corners&amp;quot; intersection and ¼ mile south of Braintree High School. (Exit 6 off Route 128/95/93)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travelling South on Route 37 From “5 Corners:” Follow about ¾ mile passing BHS on your right. At your first light (sometimes flashing) take a right onto Safford Street. Follow straight into Sunset Lake Parking Lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travelling North on Route 37: Safford Street is at the first light after the intersection with the two banks in S. Braintree Square. Take a left onto Safford Street. Follow straight into Sunset Lake Parking Lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those w/o wheels, Sunset Lake can be accessed via the T bus. There is a stop near Safford Street on Franklin Street/Route 37. Unfortunately I do not know the bus numbers/routes so you'll have to check it out on the MBTA maps (mbta.com).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking: If the lot is full please find area parking (S. Braintree Square is ¼ mile away). Please do NOT park on Safford Street. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for the sandwich board sign at the intersection of Route 37/Franklin Street and Safford Streets.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for me and my green blanket.  If in doubt, look for my Blue Toyota RAV4.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1218836816000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218465331000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Concert at the Lake - Rain Date!</name><id>8520543</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1218663900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/8520543/</event_url></item>