<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Tamarac Lane</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06066</zip><lat>41.839682</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Belding Wildlife Management Area</name><city>Vernon</city><id>303287</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.446717</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Part two of our Father's Day double-header hike will be at the Belding Wildlife Management Area in Vernon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the 7-11 on Route 30 in Vernon at 3:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford, take I-84 to exit 66.  Turn left and left again at the flashing light.  At the next light, turn right on Route 30 and follow to the 7-11 on the left.  We'll meet there for convenience sake and then together, move the cars to the trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is about a 3 mile trail, with moderate ups and downs, beautiful views of the Tankerhoosen River and an old mill pond.  Well-behaved dogs are welcome and can play in the pond!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Tankerhoosen River and the surrounding area remained in pristine condition, Belding donated 282 acres of land his family acquired to the State. Today, the Belding Wildlife Management Area is home to thousands of tall evergreens that Belding planted, 82 bird species, open fields and a stretch of the Tankerhoosen River.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Good pizza place in the same plaza with the 7-11 if anyone wants a stop there afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182281479000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181954721000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Father's Day Double-Header, part 2</name><id>5896661</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182108600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5896661/</event_url></item>