<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Did you know clutter is ALIVE? And it feeds on energy and your feelings of self-worth? Although clutter is &amp;quot;equal opportunity&amp;quot; and can affect anyone. If you would like to learn more about the spiritual side of clutter, this meeting is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Reverend Todd Miller, Episcopal priest and rector of Trinity Parish will lead the discussion. A young, energetic and soulful man, I (Marilyn) have personally found his sermons to be life-changing. No matter what your beliefs, you will come away energized with new revelations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quick test for spiritual clutter: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;When I look at my physical clutter, do I understand how my mindset, emotions, and lack of self-nurturing have contributed to the mess around me?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do I understand the interconnection between the physical clutter in my life and the mental, emotional, and spiritual issues that are present?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do I have a hard time breaking habits that no longer serve me? &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;__________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:00-7:30 pm&lt;/b&gt; - Socializing (please bring your own goodies if you want any!).  I might bring a digital camera to post a photo of the meeting on our Meetup web site IF participants grant permission (please notify me of any privacy concerns).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;7:30~8:30 pm&lt;/b&gt; - &amp;quot;Exploring the Spiritual Side of Clutter&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Reverend Todd Miller&lt;/i&gt;, Episcopal priest and rector of Trinity Parish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;~8:30-9:00 pm&lt;/b&gt; - Sharing of decluttering successes and inspirations, group problem-solving, buddying up, + input to future Meetups: group SUCCESSION, future meeting topics and schedule, venue, speakers, organizers, activities, resources: how best to help YOU?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking available close by&lt;/b&gt;: On street parking is available on Homer Street, on the next block of Center Street just before Bow Street, and on Furber Lane behind the church.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public transportation&lt;/b&gt;: Take the Riverside (Green) line to Newton Centre. &lt;b&gt;Pickup at 6:50 pm from Newton Centre MBTA station and drop-off there again after the meeting, if needed, for those who make prior arrangements with our Assistant Organizer, Marilyn.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Follow the Meetup signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216344406000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215012853000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Exploring the Spiritual Side of Clutter</name><id>8263286</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216162800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/8263286/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/2/8/global_3017160.jpeg</photo_url></item>