<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Medford St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02474</zip><lat>42.414890</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781-646-4849</phone><name>Regent Theatre</name><city>Arlington</city><id>668943</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.150620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Myth is a film about pit bulls and those who love and defend the breed. It explores the contributing factors behind the public's generalized fear of pit bulls and examines the conflict existing between advocates and opponents of Breed Specific Legislation (BSL). It also investigates the myths associated with the breed and asks the question, "What exactly is a pit bull"? Supporters of BSL claim their goal is to put an end to dog attacks by targeting certain breeds of dogs that are "inherently vicious/dangerous" as well as dogs that tend to appeal to people who are involved in criminal activity, like drug dealers and dog fighters. Dog bite statistics published by the Centers For Disease Control (CDC) stating that pit bull "type" dogs are responsible for more fatal dog attacks than any other breed are routinely used to substantiate this argument. Opponents of BSL believe that such laws are a demeaning overreaction perpetuated by media bias and claim that dog bite statistics are unreliable sources of information regarding the "viciousness" of a breed. They argue that BSL is unenforceable and ineffective, and that it fails to reduce the occurrence of dog attacks because it fails to address the root cause&amp;mdash;people. Instead of focusing on and punishing owners who are irresponsible and criminals who use their dogs for illegal purposes, legislatures choose to place their focus on the dogs, making them into scapegoats. Many opponents believe BSL is the equivalent of racial profiling and banning a breed is, quite possibly, unconstitutional. Beyond the Myth challenges the idea that pit bulls are inherently vicious and goes one-on-one with people on both sides of this controversial issue. Visit &lt;a href="http://www.beyondthemythmovie.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.beyondthemythmovie.com&lt;/a&gt; for more info.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>White NEBBC T-shirts</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317515353000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1313169311000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Beyond the Myth" Movie Screening!</name><id>29257651</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316129400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/29257651/</event_url></item>