<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/234139723331517/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook....&lt;/a&gt; Saturday, January 28, 2012.Time10:00am until 9:00pm..Description Now or Never time, folks! Our Maine liberty loving friends are requesting HELP and this is the last weekend before the caucus' start! A full day of call banking, door knocking and sign waving (in that order of importance). Special guest at the Maine HQ is none other than... the Good Doctor himself! So bring something for him to sign, get your pic taken, but ABOVE ALL BE PREPARED TO WORK! Pizza will be provided by the Maine RP HQ. We've secured the Porcupine Party bus (decked out in Ron Paul banners) which will run from Manchester (leaving at 9am SHARP!) to Maine HQ and back to Manchester. Cost is $1/mile which will work out to around $10/person if we fill the bus (22 seats). We still need a driver (with insurance), however. Either way plan to spend a full day in Maine starting at 10am! Maine is WINNABLE! Lets stun the establishment, TOGETHER! PS Other candidates may be in Maine by then, so if we get enough people to turn out we may be able to peal off a contingent to go POSITIVELY support RP at their media filled events.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327933539000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1327425651000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Now or Never Super Trip to Maine!</name><id>49420392</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327759200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/49420392/</event_url></item>