<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan Gosling, one of our most talented and treasured indpendent film actors from Lars and The Real Girl and Blue Valentine, stars in Drive,&amp;nbsp;what looks like a not-to-be-mi&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; ssed thriller heist.&amp;nbsp; He doesn't carry the film alone.&amp;nbsp; See the promotional blurb below for an amazing ensemble cast.&amp;nbsp;The film has received a 95% Fresh rating from all critics of Rotten Tomatoes and a 91% Fresh rating from top critics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at 5:45 pm at Zaftig's for a deli&amp;nbsp;supper and&amp;nbsp;aim to be at The Coolidge by 7:15.&amp;nbsp; Betsey will have a red card stock Meetup sign visible at both places.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purchase your tickets in advance if possible.&amp;nbsp; This will be a popular film, though Sunday evenings don't usually sell out, there is always a first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please be sure to be responsible for your commitment to join us.&amp;nbsp; If your plans change, change your RSVP accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the Coolidge Corner website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakout Danish direcor Nicolas Winding Refn (&lt;em&gt;The Pusher&lt;/em&gt; Trilogy, &lt;em&gt;Bronson&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Valhalla Rising&lt;/em&gt;) throttles into the Hollywood fast lane with the precision-crafted action caper &lt;em&gt;Drive&lt;/em&gt;: Cannes Film Festival sensation and this fall's hottest film. Starring Ryan Gosling, Carey Mulligan, Bryan Cranston, Christina Hendricks, Ron Perlman, with Oscar Isaac, and Albert Brooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ryan Gosling stars as a Los Angeles wheelman for hire, known only as "Driver", stunt driving for movie productions by day and steering getaway vehicles for armed heists by night. Though a loner by nature, Driver can&amp;rsquo;t help falling in love with his beautiful neighbor Irene (Carey Mulligan), a vulnerable young mother dragged into a dangerous underworld by the return of her ex-convict husband Standard (Oscar Isaac).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a heist intended to pay off Standard's protection money spins unpredictably out of control, Driver finds himself driving defense for the girl he loves, tailgated by a syndicate of deadly serious criminals (Albert Brooks and Ron Perlman). But when he realizes that the gangsters are after more than the bag of cash in his trunk&amp;mdash;that they're coming straight for Irene and her son&amp;mdash;Driver is forced to shift gears and go on offense.&lt;/p&gt;
290 Harvard Street, Brookline MA 02446&lt;span&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;Recording &lt;span&gt;617&amp;ndash;734&amp;ndash;2500&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>5:45 pm Zaftig's, 335 Harvard Ave, Brookline 02446 - 7:15 Coolidge Corner Theater  Betsey has a black pocketbook and red stock Meetup sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Betsey Glaser</member_name><member_id>9513701</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316462780000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1316038472000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Drive  7:15 pm The Coolidge  5:45 Zaftig's</name><id>33590392</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1316387700000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/33590392/</event_url></item>