<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>4763 Killington Rd</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05751 </zip><lat>43.620342</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>802-422-6200</phone><name>Killington Mountain Resort</name><city>Killington</city><id>740268</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.803588</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>60.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone, I'm Jason and as a new assistant organizer, I have a sweet trip planned that's open to all of you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip is next Saturday, March 28th up to Killington for the Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trip cost is $60 per person which gets you the following:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     Full Day Lift Ticket to Killington and Round Trip Transportation from Boston &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(We will leave and return to 412 Massachusetts Ave, across the street from Mass Ave Orange Line T Station.)  We will leave &lt;b&gt;6am&lt;/b&gt; and we will arrive back around &lt;b&gt;7:30pm&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus&lt;/b&gt; on top of that, you have the option of FREE rentals and FREE lessons. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE Ski/Snowboard and Helmet Rental - there is a rental shop at 412 Massachusetts Ave, where you'd have to stop in prior to the trip to get fitted sometime before Saturday morning.  Time for fittings will be pretty much anytime between 5pm-8pm this upcoming Tuesday through Thursday.  If none of these times are possible, please email me and we will arrange something.  There will be limited time Saturday morning for Rental fittings).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FREE Lessons will happen on the mountain that morning for anyone who is interested. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its a great deal for experienced individuals and for individuals or families who may want to learn to ski or snowboard. Advanced Lessons may also be available, let me know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For payment you can pay by check to myself, Jason Jedrusiak or Youth Enrichment Services or we can accept credit card payments in person or by phone at (617) 267-5877 ex. 12 (M-F 9am-5pm) for Will Morales who is helping me organize the trip.  Please RSVP ASAP as spots are limited.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To rsvp or for any questions or for further details feel free to call me at 617-869-1551, email me, or message me through meetup.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for the great deal, this trip is being sponsored by a local non-profit that I have volunteered for the last 3 years who I am donating my time and effort to this year to run the Boston Marathon for the first time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Youth Enrichment Services, Y.E.S., has been around for over 40 years now and normally in winters each weekend we bring up local youth to various mountains in the area, many of whom have never seen a mountain.  And as volunteers we are trained each year to teach them skiing and snowboarding.  Check out www.yeskids.org if you'd like any more info.  &lt;b&gt;All the money from this trip will go right back into Y.E.S.'s youth programming!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be organizing everyone onto the bus!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jason</member_name><member_id>3307420</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1238927347000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Snowboarders</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>snowboard-46</urlname><id>389975</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Somerville Snowboarding Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237663486000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>$60 Killington Mountain Resort Trip next Saturday, March 28th!!!!</name><id>10004151</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238234400000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/snowboard-46/events/10004151/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/b/1/global_7764945.jpeg</photo_url></item>