<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>*** Snow depth of about 4 inches likely with new and old snow. Some ice may be under the new snow. Be prepared! ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moderate winter hike on Case Mountain, 744 ft. altitude. Hike will be for 3 hours and exact route depends on conditions. We'll go as far as we can. Generally we'll take the white trail to the peak, yellow trail down to the blue trail (Shenipsit Trail) and take that south as far as we can go. The start of the hike from the parking lot is somewhat steep to the peak but after that it is much easier. We'll meet in the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map can be found as hike #6 in the &amp;quot;50 Hikes in Connecticut&amp;quot; book by the Connecticute Forest and Parks Association. There is no meal planed for after this one given the late hour but we could head out for ice cream after.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will be about 40 F for the hike but you'll be hot after the start so wear layers for warmth (avoid cotton material). Wear boots as it may be snowy and muddy! Bring a quart of water and some trail food/lunch for energy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford:&lt;br /&gt;* Take I-84 East to I-384&lt;br /&gt;* Take Exit 4 off of I-384 (Highland St.)&lt;br /&gt;* From the end of the Exit ramp, right onto Spring St.&lt;br /&gt;* Go about 0.2 mile and make a sharp left and you'll see a small parking lot at the bottom of the hill on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/direction via MapQuest:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/map.adp?formtype=address&amp;amp;country=US&amp;amp;popflag=0&amp;amp;address=650+spring+st.&amp;amp;city=manchester&amp;amp;state=ct" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this hike is Kevin S so please direct questions on the hike to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Dark blue Dodge Grandcaravan, CT plates. Meet at hike location.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204864723000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>A winter experience which may be cold and there may be some snow and ice.</why><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204119750000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Winter Hike to Case Mtn. in Manchester CT</name><id>7418308</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204484400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/7418308/</event_url></item>