<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/4/3/c/event_80833372.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Showtime is 7:45.&amp;nbsp; I will be at the theater by 6:45 and we will head in for seats by 7:15.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This looks like a fun way to learn about some history. Been a while since I have seen Cuba Gooding Jr. in a movie.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; He seems to be an expert and touching my buttons and making me cry a little.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As I like to see these movies during opening weekend, it is usually a good idea to buy your tickets ahead of time....especially if it is a big movie with lots of buzz.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after and bring cash.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; January 20, 2012 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; 20th Century Fox, Lucasfilm &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Anthony Hemingway &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; John Ridley &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Cuba Gooding Jr., Terrence Howard, Bryan Cranston, Nate Parker, David Oyelowo, Tristan Wilds, Cliff Smith, Kevin Phillips, Rick Otto, Lee Tergesen, Andre Royo, Ne-Yo, Elijah Kelley, Marcus T. Paulk, Leslie Odom Jr., Michael B. Jordan, Jazmine Sullivan, Edwina Finley, Daniela Ruah, Stacie Davis, Gerald McRaney &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Drama, War &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; PG-13 (for some sequences of war violence) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; Not Available &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; 1944. World War II rages and the fate of the free world hangs in the balance. Meanwhile the black pilots of the experimental Tuskegee training program are courageously waging two wars at once &amp;ndash; one against enemies overseas, and the other against discrimination within the military and back home. Racial prejudices have long held ace airman Martin "Easy" Julian (Nate Parker) and his black pilots back at base - leaving them with little to do but further hone their flying skills - while their white counterparts are shipped out to combat after a mere three months of training. Mistakenly deemed inferior and assigned only second-rate planes and missions, the pilots of Tuskegee have mastered the skies with ease but have not been granted the opportunity to truly spread their wings. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Until now. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 As the war in Europe continues to take its dire toll on Allied forces, Pentagon brass has no recourse but to reconsider these under-utilized pilots for combat duty. Just as the young Tuskegee men are on the brink of being shut down and shipped back home, Col. A.J. Bullard (Terrence Howard) awards them the ultimate chance to prove their mettle high above. Undaunted by the prospect of providing safe escort to bombers in broad daylight - a mission so dangerous that the RAF has refused it and the white fighter groups have sustained substantial losses - Easy's pilots at last join the fiery aerial fray. Against all the odds, with something to prove and everything to lose, these intrepid young airmen take to the skies in a heroic endeavor to combat the enemy &amp;ndash; and the discrimination that has kept them down for so long. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Trailer 1 (7.29.11):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://www.comingsoon.net/news/movienews.php?id=80471"&gt;Flash/HTML5 Player&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327322553000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1324321034000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Red Tails (7:45PM Show)</name><id>44924222</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327189500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/44924222/</event_url></item>