<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>on the Beverly Wenham Line</address_2><address_1>Essex St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01936</zip><lat>42.583458</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Long Hill/Sedgewick Gardens</name><city>Beverly/Wenham</city><id>528816</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.842564</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Walk in the gardens at Long Hill and around the woodland trails through the pine trees - about 90 minutes. This is a TTOR property on Route 22 in Beverly. I would recommend waterproof foot wear AND yaktrax or similar as there will probably still be a lot of snow or ice on the trails - and terrain is a bit rocky / hilly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 1916 to 1979, Long Hill was the summer home of noted author and editor of The Atlantic Monthly, Ellery Sedgwick, and his first wife, Mabel Cabot Sedgwick, an accomplished horticulturist, gardener, and author of The Garden Month by Month. The Federal-style house was completed in 1925 and contains original woodwork from the ca.1812 Isaac Ball House in Charleston, South Carolina. Mrs. Sedgwick designed and planted the original gardens. After her death in 1937, Mr. Sedgwick's second wife, the former Marjorie Russell, herself a distinguished gardener and propagator of rare plants, added many plants to the gardens, including unusual species and varieties of trees and shrubs, some introduced by the Arnold Arboretum.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today the gardens reflect the collective interests and tastes of both women. Five acres of cultivated grounds are laid out in a series of separate garden &amp;quot;rooms&amp;quot; surrounding the house. Each area is distinct in its own way and is accented by garden ornaments, structures, and statuary. The gardens are flanked on all sides by more than 100 acres of woodland as well as an apple orchard, meadow, and agricultural fields.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Red Subaru wagon with kayak holders in the Parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1232899578000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231077136000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Long Hill, Beverly - a walk in the woods and gardens</name><id>9439709</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1231601400000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/9439709/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/f/d/global_6592605.jpeg</photo_url></item>