<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>400 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.347622</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-357-7387</phone><name>DoggieDay Playcenter</name><city>Boston</city><id>668961</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.068500</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>We did this last year and had a blast-it gets super crowded at the starting point so prepare yourself in terms of parking.  Bring you cameras and your creativity in regards to outfits-people go all out for the occasion--not to be missed!  Let's show some Frenchie presence!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4th Annual Divas Unleashed™ Halloween Pet Parade&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Benefiting the American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty &lt;br /&gt;to Animals (ASPCA)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Sunday, October 26, 2008&lt;br /&gt;Check-in: 10am-11:30am&lt;br /&gt;Where: DoggieDay Play Center @ 400 Tremont Street, Boston 02116&lt;br /&gt;More Info: www.doggieday.com/halloween&lt;br /&gt;Photos from last year: www.lamusephoto.com click on ‘view your &lt;br /&gt;shoot’, click on Divas album&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Save the Date All!&lt;br /&gt;This year, our annual Halloween Pet Parade, Divas Unleashed™ &lt;br /&gt;promises to be bigger and better than last year, including the &lt;br /&gt;prizes! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the third year in a row, Randy Price of WHDH Channel 7 News &lt;br /&gt;will be your Emcee for the Finalist Fashion Show and will be &lt;br /&gt;awarding the prizes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, your Grande Divas are Universal Motown recording &lt;br /&gt;group JADA; you can view their website at www.jadamusic.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Judges:&lt;br /&gt;Freelance Fashion Writer and Stylist, Erica Corsano&lt;br /&gt;Dir of Marketing for the ASPCA, NY&lt;br /&gt;AKC Judge&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Again for the third year in a row, the parade is led by the &lt;br /&gt;Salem High School Marching Band and Color Guard. You will be &lt;br /&gt;led down the parade route to the sounds of some of your &lt;br /&gt;favorite Halloween songs including the theme to Star Wars, the &lt;br /&gt;Munster Mash and many others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ruff Ruffman from FETCH on PBS for kids! will be marching with &lt;br /&gt;our VIP’s&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Photographers and Press:&lt;br /&gt;You can be a star! Each year in the past, the parade has made &lt;br /&gt;it onto many news stations and internet sites. This year will &lt;br /&gt;be no exception!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to the news coverage with video and print, we have &lt;br /&gt;put together of group of our own ‘paparazzi’ or ‘paw-parazzi’ &lt;br /&gt;for the day. Assembled will be a group of professional &lt;br /&gt;photographers snapping candid shots at what we hope to be each &lt;br /&gt;participant with your hopes of making it big! These photos &lt;br /&gt;will be posted on their respective websites within days after &lt;br /&gt;the parade. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parade Route:&lt;br /&gt;At 12noon, the parade commences at 400 Tremont Street, Boston &lt;br /&gt;MA 02116; The DoggieDay Play Center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The parade will be led down Tremont Street heading toward the &lt;br /&gt;Boston Common, making a slight left onto South Charles St, &lt;br /&gt;continuing across Stuart Street, across Boylston Street at &lt;br /&gt;which point the parade marches up into the Boston Common on the &lt;br /&gt;sidewalk, heading to the band stand where festivities and &lt;br /&gt;awarding of prizes will take place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;For those who will be driving in for the parade, parking can &lt;br /&gt;best be found at the end of the parade route at the Boson &lt;br /&gt;Common Parking garage located underneath the Boston Common. &lt;br /&gt;($11 all day)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Donations are as follows;&lt;br /&gt;$25 donation enters you and/or your pet in the parade to &lt;br /&gt;march. You and/or your pet will be entered into the costume &lt;br /&gt;contests and a chance to win amazing prizes. You will also &lt;br /&gt;receive an event nylon tote/backpack to trick or treat to &lt;br /&gt;sponsors and vendors for fun give-aways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$50 donation gets you all of the above, BUT, as a VIP, you will &lt;br /&gt;march at the front of the parade, behind Universal Motown &lt;br /&gt;recording group JADA, Randy Price, our celebrity judges and the &lt;br /&gt;Salem High School Marching Band with Boston Celebs, which may &lt;br /&gt;include radio personalities, news anchors, athletes, writers, &lt;br /&gt;politicians, etc. You will receive an event VIP badge for &lt;br /&gt;access to this section of the parade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some prizes are as follows;&lt;br /&gt;Two-night stay at the 70 Park Ave hotel in NYC&lt;br /&gt;One-night stay in Deluxe accommodations at the MUSE hotel in NYC&lt;br /&gt;One-night stay in Deluxe accom. at the Intercontinental Boston w/ dinner for &lt;br /&gt;2 at their restaurant Miel&lt;br /&gt;Two night stay in a Jr. Suite at the historic Omni Parker House with dinner for &lt;br /&gt;2 one night&lt;br /&gt;One-night stay at the Hyatt Regency, Downtown&lt;br /&gt;One night stay in Deluxe accommodations at the Nine Zero Hotel, Boston&lt;br /&gt;One night stay in Deluxe accommodations at the Onyx Hotel, Boston&lt;br /&gt;One night stay in Deluxe accommodations at the Hotel Marlowe, Cambridge&lt;br /&gt;Blue Man Group tickets&lt;br /&gt;$100 gift certificate to the Melting Pot &lt;br /&gt;$100 gift certificate to Fugakyu in Brookline&lt;br /&gt;(3) Dinners for two at California Pizza Kitchen&lt;br /&gt;Dinner for 4 at Jacob Wirth Restaurant and Pub&lt;br /&gt;Dinners for two all over Boston&lt;br /&gt;Planet Dog Gift baskets&lt;br /&gt;And much more……….&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Costume Categories;&lt;br /&gt;Most Outrageous Dog&lt;br /&gt;Most Original Dog&lt;br /&gt;Best Group or ensemble&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the parade route, JP Licks will be serving &lt;br /&gt;coffee, hot chocolate, doggie sorbet (and ice cream, depending &lt;br /&gt;on the weather…)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your dog brushes up on their commands, because after &lt;br /&gt;the prizes have been awarded in the costume contest, stick &lt;br /&gt;around, Randy Price will be ‘Simon’ in a game of “Simon Says….”&lt;br /&gt;(for the dogs)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be in front of the entrance to Doggie Daycare-by the coffee stand</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1274716123000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>French Bulldog Owners &amp; Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>BostonFrenchBulldogs</urlname><id>213526</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston French Bulldog Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1222832623000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>4th Annual Divas Unleashed™ Halloween Pet Parade</name><id>8869833</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1225031400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BostonFrenchBulldogs/events/8869833/</event_url></item>