<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Northern Blvd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01950</zip><lat>42.813284</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Plum Island Point</name><city>Newburyport</city><id>706565</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.814106</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Bring Mom along to meet your new and old friends of Meetup while we take an afternoon hike thru the Parker River National Wildlife Refuge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you come with a Mom or alone, this will be a great afternoon hike amongst the Wildlife. We will meet at the Visitor's center and get a map of the refuge. Below is a little bit of information about the wildlife refuge:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Parker River National Wildlife Refuge is located approximately 32 miles northeast of Boston on Plum Island. Plum Island is a natural barrier island stretching along the Massachusetts Atlantic coast between the mouth of the Merrimack River to the north and the mouth of the Ipswich River to the south.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blue heronThe Refuge occupies the southern three-fourths of the island and is 4,662 acres in size. Included within this space are 6.5 miles of sandy beach, approximately 3,000 acres of salt marsh, three managed fresh water impoundments, and one of the few unspoiled dune-beach complexes still existing in the Northeast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Located along the Atlantic Flyway, the Refuge is of special significance to waterfowl and shorebirds, including the federally threatened piping plover. A Refuge bird checklist, including a seasonal occurrence listing, is available at the Visitor Center in Parking Lot 1, the entrance Gatehouse, or by contacting Refuge Headquarters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mothers and Children are welcome to this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you and Mom at the Refuge.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>At the Visitors Center</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna </member_name><member_id>2153112</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273601623000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Singles, friends, newly single</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Connections-and-Friends</urlname><id>1381795</id><group_lat>42.6800003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8499984741</group_lon><name>Connections and Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1272236078000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mother's Day Hike on Plum Island Point</name><id>13287668</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1273428000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Connections-and-Friends/events/13287668/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/5/global_14625973.jpeg</photo_url></item>