<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/a/0/e/event_208855822.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This Trailer looked intense and I loved &lt;span&gt;Noomi Rapace in the original Girl with the Dragon Tattoo.   Hope she is as cool in this role. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;Showtime is at 5:40.  It is going to be a little tight for me and others to make it, so I am going to change things up a little.  I will leave work around 5...I am at Kendall and it is only two stops, so I should be there about 5:10 or so.   I will go directly to the theater and try to wait in the hallway outside for a bit.   Hopefully, being this early we won't have trouble finding seats.   But we should really try to grab seats by 5:20.   Then we can take turns doing the snack runs while others hold our seats. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993366"&gt;Fandango.com is selling tickets right now.   Be warned though, there are sometimes hiccups to the system, especially the mobile app.  Not being able to complete a transaction does not mean they are sold out.  Wait a bit and try again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group ahead of time, come find us after. We gather in the hallway outside of the theater we just saw the movie in, to discuss the film a bit, allow for restroom breaks and to get a head count of all those who would like to go out after for drinks and munchies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;$$$$Managing the after event is much easier if everyone brings cash, so please plan ahead if you want to go out with the group after.$$$&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;Movie Details&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Release Date:&lt;/span&gt; March 8, 2013 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Studio:&lt;/span&gt; FilmDistrict &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Director:&lt;/span&gt; Niels Arden Oplev &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Screenwriter:&lt;/span&gt; J.H. Wyman &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Starring:&lt;/span&gt; Colin Farrell, Noomi Rapace, Dominic Cooper, Terrence Howard, Isabelle Huppert &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Genre:&lt;/span&gt; Action, Thriller &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;MPAA Rating:&lt;/span&gt; R (for violence, language throughout and a scene of sexuality) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Official Website:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.blooddemandsblood.com" target="_blank"&gt;BloodDemandsBlood.com&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/DeadManDown" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/deadmandownfilm" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;Plot Summary:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;"Dead Man Down" is an action thriller that stars Colin Farrell and Noomi Rapace as two strangers whose mutual desire for revenge draws them together and triggers an escalating trail of mayhem. The film, which also stars Academy Award-nominee Terrence Howard and Dominic Cooper, marks the American theatrical debut of director Niels Arden Oplev (the original "The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo").&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be wearing a meetup pin.  If the movie is showing upstairs, I will grab a table by the windows at the top of the escalator.  If the movie is showing downstairs, I will be near the ropes by the concession stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Doreen Charbonneau</member_name><member_id>2902873</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1362921885000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361839054000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dead Man Down (5:40PM Show)</name><id>106409382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1362780900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/106409382/</event_url></item>