<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We're hosting an additional Circle this month - and hoping to expand to a circle every other week by the end of the summer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So what is this about?&lt;/b&gt; It's about the totally responsible and mature choice to connect to a group of men to offer mentoring and be mentored. The most powerful, successful and brilliant men in the world have circles of advisers - people they trust to share their highs and lows with - people they work with to refine their ideas, make better choices, take risks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kings have courts. Presidents have cabinets. CEO's have boards of advisers. Religious icons have disciples. What we provide is a space to learn deeply about yourself in the company of other men. To challenge yourself, to be recognized for the brilliance that you bring to your world, to get honest about what's REALLY going on with you, to share in the passages of your life. We are confidants, friends, challengers, sounding boards - we are a band of brothers united by a desire to make ourselves &lt;b&gt;- and the world -&lt;/b&gt; a better place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many men are these days are isolated from one another and from themselves. Many of our relationships are shallow and don't begin to honestly address the difficulties and triumphs in our lives. Open Men is about getting honest, bravely taking responsibility for your life and helping other men while you help yourself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are invited. Bring a friend.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We park right by the big AtoZ Moving Trucks - look for the parking along the building.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Boysen </member_name><member_id>7527796</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248306991000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Men</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>openmen</urlname><id>1200732</id><group_lat>42.1199989319</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5500030518</group_lon><name>Open Men's Group - Personal Mastery Workgroup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1247260720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Men's Group - Mentoring, Self-Awareness and Support</name><id>10848819</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1247698800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/openmen/events/10848819/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/b/d/global_4591725.jpeg</photo_url></item>