<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rt. 18</address_2><address_1>798 North Bedford Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02333</zip><lat>42.055115</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508.350.1000</phone><name>F1 Boston Outdoor Track</name><city>East Bridgewater</city><id>146593</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.952438</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;F1 Outdoors Launches Championship Kart Racing School&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Two Day High Performance Kart Racing Instruction for &lt;b&gt;All Skill Levels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;** Edit 8-11-2010 ******************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;If you are currently racing in a Rotax Senior / Masters Class you will be able to use your own kart. The cost will be &lt;b&gt;$399&lt;/b&gt;. Drivers are responsible for your equipment and fuel after the 5 gallons. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For all other driver you will be using CRG KT11 Rotaxs. The cost will be &lt;b&gt;$799&lt;/b&gt;. No other cost for fuel or equipment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a program designed to teach the fundamental skills needed to own and operate a high performance kart. This two-day school will consist of on track instruction as well as trackside and classroom sessions, which will recap and refine what is being learned. Over the course of the school, techniques involving passing, racing line, race craft, tuning, and general upkeep will be covered. This school is meant to serve as a means of building what is needed to be successful in karting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;********************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;F1 Outdoors has launched a new program, the Championship Kart Racing School, that puts drivers in competition-designed high performance karts - teaching them skills and tactics the very best drivers use at the highest levels of competition. The 2-day, limited enrollment program provides hours of track time with top-notch instructors, plus classroom sessions that help racers hone their mental ability as well as their physical skills.  A class is scheduled for Aug 18 -19.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Competitors pilot state-of-the-art high performance CRG KTII chassis equipped with 28-horsepower Rotax FR 125 engines. Capable of speeds up to 75 mph, these are the same karts used by the VW Jetta TDI Cup kart qualifiers, one of the most competitive kart racing events held each year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Class sizes are limited to 10 students, ensuring a low student/instructor ratio. All participants must be licensed drivers 18 years or older. All aspects of the program take place at F1 Outdoors, considered the 'gold standard' of outdoor tracks by the prestigious World Karting News magazine. The classes run 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. each day and includes lunch, the itinerary features:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DAY ONE: Learning the ropes - with 6 track sessions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The day 1 starts in the classroom, with an overview of the basics involved in driving and operating a high performance kart.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Next comes a track walk, where drivers learn about the racing line &amp;amp; braking points. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The six track sessions start with lead/follows with the instructor at a medium pace, gaining speed progressively, learning kart performance and reactions at different speeds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunch and a discussion of the morning's driving are held between the two sets of driving sessions. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;After lunch, high speed driving sessions focus on braking and passing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;DAY TWO: Advanced &amp;amp; and Accelerated Skills&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;The day starts in the classroom with a recap of Day 1 training, followed by a high speed lead/follow session. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Session 2 on the track focuses on high speed passing drills, timed to gauge improvement through the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Session 3 is all racing - a high speed open lapping session with passing allowed, with timed laps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;All the track time is followed by lunch and a discussion of the morning sessions and Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;After lunch, three more track sessions include timed high speed open lapping session, focusing on passing techniques&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee for the 2 day program: $799&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1209048/Championship_Kart_Racing_School_Brochure.pdf"&gt;Brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1209048/Championship_Kart_Racing_School_insert.pdf"&gt;Class Outline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://files.meetup.com/1209048/2010_Championship_Kart_Racing_School.pdf"&gt;Registration Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information and enrollment details, call 781.228.2009 or email LeaguesAndSchools@F1Boston.com.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This is hosted by F1 Boston.  Please go to the registration office, and the F1 Staff will guide you (I will NOT be attending)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deepak</member_name><member_id>2592822</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282142615000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Racing Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>racing</urlname><id>1209048</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>Racing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1280953374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2 Day Championship Kart Racing School</name><id>14320544</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282138200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/racing/events/14320544/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/8/global_4661928.jpeg</photo_url></item>