<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Westbound-behind Chuck E. Cheese)</address_2><address_1>3 Vision Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.300643</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitney Place Assisted Living</name><city>Natick</city><id>766030</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.354550</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;In our daily lives, we all deal with long to-do lists in an attempt to juggle work and family, friends and play as well as our health and well-being. And at times, all the juggling might take a toll, causing us to question our sense of balance.That is why, we have chosen the topic of The Balancing Act for our next Net-Working Women Meeting and asked group member and Certified Professional Life Coach Sibel Babacan, Ph.D., CPCC to lead a workshop on the subject:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this 2 hr hands-on workshop, Sibel will guide us in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;determining what life balance means, feels and looks like for each one of us,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;getting clear about where we currently are and where we would like to be,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;discovering specific steps to create the path for this individual sense of balance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;and identifying key points for staying on this path even when things get hectic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sibel is no stranger to the joys and challenges of The Balancing Act as a Mother, Business Owner, Wife, House Manager and Volunteer. Her quest for a balanced and joyful life made her experience living in different states and continents as well as successfully completing a major career transition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Sibel and her Coaching Practice, please visit her web-site at www.drbeeorganizingsolutions.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340290585000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337721111000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Balancing Act Workshop</name><id>65894742</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340146800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/65894742/</event_url></item>