<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 Edgell Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.302986</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Center of Light</name><city>Framingham</city><id>6258312</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.434021</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/9/2/event_7927570.jpeg" width="145" height="133" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Why have the churches for centuries created so many rules and regulations that have stripped the spirit out of worship and praise of God? Why is it if you do all the “right things” you still feel incomplete or wrong? Isn’t it time you understood the truth? Meet Mother Clare, Christian Master Teacher, she will teach you the difference between spirituality and religion and guide you to the return of a deep spiritual consciousness. Mother Clare has quite an interesting history. Raised in Switzerland by Baptist missionaries, she initially rebelled against Christianity and tried her hand at many different spiritual paths. She lived in a yoga ashram and trained with the Sufis for a number of years before finding the Christian mystical path. In addition, she was a professional certified midwife for 18 years, and practiced psychotherapy in Boston, Massachusetts after obtaining a graduate degree in Counseling Psychology and post-graduate training in Jungian Analysis. Mother Clare is known for her clarity and deep compassion. She is the author of Giving Birth to God: A Woman’s Path to Enlightenment and Mystical Roses of Peace. She lives at the Center of Light in Dolores, Colorado and oversees the Sophia Peace Center. Visit MotherClareWatts.com to learn more about her, watch her videos and purchase her books. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Suggested Donation: $25 • Bring a Friend for Free &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350701074000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Meditators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>meditation-226</urlname><id>262460</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Metro West Meditation Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349278657000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Spirituality, Not Religion with Mother Clare Watts</name><id>85302522</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350689400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/meditation-226/events/85302522/</event_url></item>