<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please join Reed &amp;amp; Reed (construction contractor), MaineDOT and the cities of Portland and South Portland in celebrating the &lt;strong&gt;Grand Opening of the new Veterans Memorial Bridge&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ceremony starts at &lt;strong&gt;10 AM&lt;/strong&gt; with a dedication to our veterans, speeches, ribbon cutting, followed by the procession of vehicles, pedestrians and bicyclists. All 5 lanes of the bridge will be open to pedestrians and bicyclists from 9:30 to 11:30 am. The only motor vehicles allowed on the bridge that morning will be those in the parade. This small parade will start with approx 10 vehicles, followed by bicyclists and pedestrians. The bridge will be open to all traffic later that afternoon. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

They are suggesting people arrive on the Portland end of the new bridge by 9:45 am as the ceremony starts promptly at 10 am. Fore River Parkway will be closed to all vehicle traffic (except Mercy Hospital patients) from 9:30 to 11:30 am so IF people come by car, please park on Commercial Street and ride to the new bridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please arrive early as parking is limited to neighboring streets. The Mercy Hospital parking lot is NOT available for public parking. A shuttle service along Commercial Street will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FMI: www.veteransmemorialbridge.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/a/c/event_133135212.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John Brooking</member_name><member_id>2040136</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340993537000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Bike Commuters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Bike-Commuting</urlname><id>225788</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Bicycle Commuting</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340672429000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Grand Opening of the New Veteran's Memorial Bridge</name><id>70735272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340892000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Bike-Commuting/events/70735272/</event_url></item>