<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>10 Eliot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372595</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Charlie's Beer Garden</name><city>Cambridge </city><id>966779</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121617</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;OK: The Sex and the Drugs I really can't help you with....I'm sort of lame in that regard...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But how about some booze at Charlie's Beer Garden and then some ice cream at JP Licks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's go to Charlie's: It's outdoors, nice beer, nice ambiance, they have a great menu (It beats getting heat stroke on the Esplanade and waiting 12 hours for the Pops).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can get ice cream when we're ready at JP Licks (or any other establishment) and maybe head down to the river to watch the fireworks or just chill out on the Cambridge Common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spirit of democracy, we'll let the group decide what they want when they get to the Garden. We can chill there, throw a frisbee around at the common (supply your own) or if you're ambitious, head down to the river and watch the fireworks (I hear it's better on the Cambridge side).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why barbeque when you can order food off the menu?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRING&lt;/strong&gt;: A frisbree if you want to play on the Common afterward&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE&lt;/strong&gt;: Charlie's Beer Garden in Harvard Square&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TENTATIVE PLANS&lt;/strong&gt;: Ice cream, chill on Common, watch fireworks (up to group)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TIME&lt;/strong&gt;: 1PM. There might be a crowd and we may leave the garden, so you may want to get there closer to 1pm than 2pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY&lt;/strong&gt;: Boston is a mad house on the Fourth and a full day on the Esplanade can be pretty hot and uncomfortable...Beer garden nice!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you come out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will try to be near the back to the left when you walk in</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave </member_name><member_id>10064486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341466410000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>fun-with-alcohol</urlname><id>985138</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Fun with Alcohol!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341155785000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sex, Drugs, and Ice Cream - All-American Fourth</name><id>71506632</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341421200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/fun-with-alcohol/events/71506632/</event_url></item>