<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Mt. Zealand&lt;/b&gt;, one of the official 4000 footer's itself is viewless, but the trail goes by the Zeacliff outlook which has great views.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Zealand Trail starts out very amiably with a low grade, good footing and plenty of width. This is typical of trails that follow old railroad grades as this one does. There's not much to see in the first 1½ miles except for forest and a few streams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The grade stayed flat all the way to the &lt;b&gt;Zealand Ponds&lt;/b&gt;, where there are some very nice views. One of the several foot bridges Mt. Tom and Mt. Field are both visible from the ponds, and give you a taste of what's in store later. A couple footbridges were constructed, making the trip here very comfortable.&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/1/6/c/event_2004940.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hike-nh.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hike-nh.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At about 2.5 miles, the Zealand Trail turns into the Twinway Trail (part of the AT) and starts its ascent. The trail is still fairly wide and easy to travel. After about 5 minutes, on the left hand side of the trail, you will see a sign for the &lt;b&gt;Zealand Falls&lt;/b&gt;. A 25-foot detour, falls are beautiful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hike-nh.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hike-nh.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Return to the trail and you will next reach Zealand Falls Hut (2.7 miles).&lt;br /&gt;The hut is fairly large, accommodating 36 people year round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The views from the front of the hut are spectacular, as well as from the stream next to the hut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a dog friendly hike, but animals are not allowed in the hut should you stop for a break&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting here is fairly easy, the ascent to the hut is about 700 elevation gain from the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail continues from the Zealand hut at about the same grade (about 30°) and stays fairly wide. Follow the trail up. There are views near Zeacliff Pond&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At about 3.7 miles, the trail levels off and you think you may have reached a summit. This is not the summit. That is 2 more miles. There is a very small sign that says simply, &amp;quot;View&amp;quot; on the left of the trail. TAKE THIS DETOUR. It offers one of the finest views in all of the White Mountains from a cliff called the &lt;b&gt;Zeacliff.&lt;/b&gt; From the Zeacliff, Mt. Carrigain, Mt. Hancock, and some smaller peaks. are viewable&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/2/6/event_1775622.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the highlight of this hike, and &lt;u&gt;Beginner  hikers can decide to return to the parking lot. for a RT hike of 7.4 miles.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The plateau ended and begin the ascent again at about 4.1 miles. The grade here is a little steeper and more difficult, but still easily passable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hike-nh.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hike-nh.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hike-nh.co.." target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hike-nh.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;there is a ladder built into the trail to assist because the terrain is too difficult to traverse.&lt;br /&gt;Continue on the twinway until you reach the &lt;b&gt;Zealand summit 5.5 miles from the trailhead.&lt;/b&gt; There is a small cairn marking a side path 0.1 mile to the true summit. It is wooded and a summit sign is here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/b/2/9/thumb_1775625.jpeg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For this hike you will return the same way. Twinway to Zealand Trail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(rt: 11.0 miles, 2,300 elevation gain, average book time 7 hrs).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The weather is changing. Pack a fleece top and windbreaker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can finish the hike at a local pub if the group wishes.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the parking lot</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1220967807000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219526575000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fall Colors of Mt Zealand and Zeacliff</name><id>8606171</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1220794200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/8606171/</event_url></item>