<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi everyone!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JREX is hosting a great event to help connect local Japanese communities, companies, etc. together.  It's a great opportunity to find out more about what our local Boston Japanese community has to offer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our group has also been offered a table for introducing our very own meetup group to the local community.  Please let me know if you would be willing to volunteer for an hour to host our table.  I will also need volunteers to help create new paper materials that describe our group.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location:&lt;br /&gt;Boston Public Library&lt;br /&gt;Hunneman Hall&lt;br /&gt;361 Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Brookline, MA 02445&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Presented by JREX&lt;br /&gt;Planned &amp;amp; Operated by J Magazine, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored by Japanese Business Association of New England&lt;br /&gt;Japanese Association of Greater Boston&lt;br /&gt;Under the Auspices of Consulate-General of Japan in Boston&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About the Event:&lt;br /&gt;For Japanese communities (groups, organizations, companies, etc) and those who are interested in Japanese communities to gather in one place and share the information they have. For the newcomers from Japan and anyone who are interested in Japanese communities to know the existing Japanese communities of New England area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Art of J: Stage performances &amp;amp; demonstrations, craft exhibitions and sales, etc&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;People of J: Promotion of groups, organizations, companies (flyer distribution, etc)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taste of J: Sales and promotions of lunch box, snack, drinks by restaurants&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Admission Fee: Free&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will have our own table for introducing ourselves to the local meetup community.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robert Schuman</member_name><member_id>2969623</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1289229581000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Japanese/English Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>boston-japanese</urlname><id>86694</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0800018311</group_lon><name>Boston Japanese &amp; English Language Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288071648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>J Expo 2010</name><id>15231047</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1289062800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-japanese/events/15231047/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/9/5/global_19087941.jpeg</photo_url></item>