<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Smith Neck Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06371</zip><lat>41.293165</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Great Island Old Lyme Boat Ramp</name><city>Old Lyme</city><id>699545</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.323266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather...Saturday: Mostly sunny, with a high near 81. Calm wind becoming south between 7 and 10 mph. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Afternoon:  SW wind 5 to 7 kt. Sunny. Seas around 1 ft.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain or not so good weather cancels this event.&lt;br /&gt;I will make a best guess decision as necessary by 10 am the day of the event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Road Traffick Report    ????&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tides for Saybrook Jetty starting with August 15, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Day        High      Tide  Height   Sunrise    Moon  Time      % Moon&lt;br /&gt;           /Low      Time    Feet    Sunset                    Visible&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sa  15      Low  12:13 AM     0.5   5:59 AM    Rise 12:07 AM      37&lt;br /&gt;    15     High   6:08 AM     3.0   7:48 PM     Set  4:09 PM&lt;br /&gt;    15      Low  12:00 PM     0.8&lt;br /&gt;    15     High   6:45 PM     4.4&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COOLERS AND LUNCH ON THE BEACH,&lt;br /&gt;THE LATER BARBIE-q PARTY IS AT 7 FALLS AGAIN OR ANOTHER LOCATION (DEPENDS ON AVAILABILITY) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an area that is good for both recreational and sea kayakers..&lt;br /&gt;But recreational kayaks should have a blow whistle, float bags, a paddle leash, a paddle float , pump and...shouldnt go out in the deep too far. BUT RIDE THE INTERESTING WAVES HERE.&lt;br /&gt;BUT REMEMBER you seen a recreational kayak sink before your eyes at Bolton lake..the body has never been recovered either, no PFD was worn either.&lt;br /&gt;for sea kayakers..well you know what its like out here..so i dont have to tell you anything,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DONT FALL IN, JELLY FISH, Ells, and Big Fish ARE HUNGRY....&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;BRING UMBRELLAS AND OTHER BEACH STUFF&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This time we can play in the surf and other sea areas...since we already did the river part..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Great Island area provides paddling in the secluded back channels, side rivers, and coves that parallel the lower Connecticut River near the mouth on the east side. You wind through 10-foot-tall marsh reeds and generally avoid the voluminous summer boating traffic. Whereas deeper-draft boats have to pay attention to the charts, kayaks can wander all over the place in the shallow waters here. Another advantage of the lower Connecticut is that three-quarters of the 1-mile?wide mouth averages a few feet in depth, which serves to keep motorboats to a minimum or forces them into the west channel, which exits through two stone breakwaters beyond Saybrook Point Lighthouse. The water just off the breakwaters is also very shallow? even small boats sometimes get grounded. Great Island offers good summer sea kayaking amid marsh grass, seaside goldenrod, glasswort, sea lavender, and water hemp.&lt;br /&gt;This popular launch site, located less than 500 feet from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area, provides visitors with opportunities to explore tidal marshes and a barrier beach. It is important to note, however, that motorized vessels must remain a reasonable distance away from the Great Island Wildlife Management Area upon launching. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; LOCATION ...APX  #95 (use whatever the gps indicates) Smith Neck Road&lt;br /&gt;Old Lyme, Connecticut for GPS users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TO AVOID TRAFFIC I WILL LOOK AT OTHER ROUTS AND POST THE MOST LIKELY ROUTE THAT HAS THE LEAST TRAFFICK if it seems Saturday is better than sunday for other beach goers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THE PREVIOUS ROUTE from hartford:  Apx 45 minutes.....BUT  A LOT LONGER IN TRAFFICK&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Take rte 9 south past Essex to 95 North , rte 9 ends here, stay to the left fork&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Take I-95 North to Exit 70. (Its right over the CT river bridge)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the end of the exit ramp, turn right onto Route 156/Shore Road &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;1.7&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; miles. to Smith neck rd  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;as you go along, Count 3 streets on right,   ( look for Jonny cake Hill rd is on left) DIRECTLY across is the next right 3rd one = Smith Neck Road, (you cant see the name its occluded by the Yellow Left turn arrow Diamond Sign)  &lt;br /&gt;turn right onto Smith Neck Road, and proceed 0.7 miles (to its end at the boat ramp).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will have the Avalon with the kayak trailer and most likely i put the orange cones somewhere visible.&lt;br /&gt;I dont expect this area to be filled..but dont know..our group Should doubble park with each other to save room for other boaters if you want to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Active Rain or high wind (10+) , High seas (3+) canceles the event......The back up plan is to do the LUTENEANT  River since we already did the Blackhall if the weather isnt nice enough for the ocean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kayaks Available:&lt;br /&gt;Make sure you are familiar with their characteristics on maybe 1 to 2 or so foot waves..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;$ 20 dollar doughnation per AL's Kayaks Used on this ocean all day trip and new carbon paddles &amp;amp; paddle leaches..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Brown Bathtub, Recreational Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Pungo 12' with flotation bags installed=   &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;CARLYN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Blue Flipper Dipper, Short Sea Kayak = Riot Tourlite 15'=     FRAN&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Yellow Bananna, Long SOT Sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Cobra Expidition SOT 18', =  ALEX&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Eddyliner, Long sea Kayak with Carbon Kalista Paddle= Eddyline Wind Dancer 18'=    DURELLE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Red Greenlander, Fast &amp;amp; Long Sea Kayak with Fiberglass or Greenland Paddle= NDK Greenlander Pro 18'= ME I GUESS..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring extra food, or adult Bugg Juice for later at the 7 Falls ( OR OTHER SITE)  on the return trip also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See ya all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALTERNATE ROUTE:&lt;br /&gt;I have not tried this route but will try it this time:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SO I HAVE NO IDEA IF ITS BETTER OR NOT, BUT I DONT EVEN WANT TO WASTE TIME WITH MIDDLETOWN TRAFFIC SO IT MIGHT BE BETTER, DONT KNOW..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM HARTFORD: RT 2 TOWARDS NORWITCH DIRECTION,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THEN TAKE RTE 11 TO END THEN TAKE RIGHT ONTO RTE 82,&lt;br /&gt;FOLLOW THIS FOR 3.8 MILES TO RTE 156,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TAKE 156 SOUTH FOR 10.3 MILES,&lt;br /&gt;LOOK FOR THE SMITH NECK RAOD ON THE RIGHT.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear my Bright Orange Hunting Hat</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1250785002000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249874749000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> *Saturday Kayak Event at GREAT ISLAND *  Sea &amp; Rec Kayaks OK</name><id>11074581</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1250355600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/11074581/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/a/global_5044522.jpeg</photo_url></item>