<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>PARTY TIME--in a new location! ***NOTE: I e-mailed the address and phone number to everyone who RSVP'd yes on Monday 12/3 -- if you didn't get the message with the details, contact me to let me know, as the address *will not* be posted on the public Web site. Thanks!*****&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The function rooms at the restaurant where we'd tentatively planned to gather are now booked for a big company holiday party that day. After looking at some other options, I asked Pam whether we could take her up on her offer to host us at her place. She graciously agreed. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So we will be meeting at Pam's *cat-free* home in Natick rather than in Braintree.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For those who've been to Meetups at the Michaels store in Natick: Pam's place is about 1.5 miles from there. For those who haven't: It's a short distance from the Mass Pike (exit 13), Route 30 or Route 9. I'll send the address in a separate e-mail rather than posting it on the public Web site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We'll show what we've been working on, swap some cards and talk about some fun stuff for 2008.  We'll also do a small goodie-bag exchange--see the message boards for updates about participating in this. Should be lots of fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pam will provide coffee and snacks. I'll provide beverages and more snacks. If we want to order out for lunch, we have many, many options right nearby; we can decide early on what we want to do. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay tuned for more details; just wanted to let you know about the location change! &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1197309969000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192991389000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>December Meetup: Holiday Party--new location in Natick!</name><id>6590820</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197136800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/6590820/</event_url></item>