<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Recreational Paddle at a familliar place for a few of you.&lt;br /&gt;And a good place to learn for the new paddlers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jean is someone i have met a few years ago and paddled many different kinds of water with..and always have had a good time..&lt;br /&gt;Oh yeh LL BEANER is open now too..SPEND SOME MONEY THERE...lots of it...get a kayak for this event..or buy one of mine...&lt;br /&gt;Anyway......&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FROM THE AMC WEBSITE:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct-amc.org/paddle/Instructionals.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct-amc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lower Bolton Lake, Pretty as a Picture!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Activity: Paddling  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;additional directions: its the pretty much the same.&lt;br /&gt;Directions: &lt;br /&gt;take Rte 384 East to Bolton Notch (off of rte 84 in East Hartford / Manchester line area) &lt;br /&gt;Follow 384 to the end.. &lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (left part of fork) rte 6 is to the right, stay on 44 &lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light. &lt;br /&gt;The next light has the boat launch to the left and a church to the right. (across from South Road) &lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mapquest, GPS and others use 1,000 Boston Turnpike (rte 44) Bolton to get you close enough..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Subcategory: Paddling - Flatwater  &lt;br /&gt;Status: OPEN  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Lower Bolton Lake is pretty as a picture! A perfect place for beginners. Motorboats are limited to 6 horsepower and you'll likely see more small sailboats than powerboats. This is a natural lake within the Thames River drainage basin with a moderate amount of development. Meet at the state boat launch at 1 pm, hope to launch about 1:30 pm. Hard rain, thunderstorms cancel. Paddlers under 18 years old must be with parent/guardian. Friendly dogs are ok. Registration is not required for this trip. However, you may wish to contact me if you have any questions at phone below or call my cell on the weekend: 203-606-9459. Detailed driving directions are at END of this posting. From 9 to noon I'll be at the grand opening of the first LL Bean store in Connecticut at the Promenade Shops at Evergreen Walk in South Windsor.Please stop by to say hello! Directions are on the LL Bean website (see below). Directions to Lower Bolton Lake state boat launch ramp for paddle at 1 pm: From North, West, or South: Take I84 or I91 to Hartford, then proceed as follows: Go east on I84 to I384 (just over 4 miles). Go east on I384 to end (a little over 7 miles). Stay in left lane at end of highway (important) to stay on US44 east. Go straight through first stop light. Just before second stop light, turn left into state boat launch area. (Across street from white church.) From Northeast: Go southwest on I84 to Exit 67 (State Route 31). Go south on SR31 until it ends at US44. Go right on US44 about 2 miles to stop light with white church on left. Just past stop light, turn right into state boat launch area. (Across street from white church.) From East: Go west on US44 through Mansfield Depot to intersection with State Route 31. Continue west on US44 about 2 miles to stop light with white church on left. Just past stop light, turn right into state boat launch area. (Across street from white church.) From Southeast: From Willimantic, go northwest on US6 to US44 west. When US6 joins US44 west, road splits into divided highway. On divided highway, take first exit to stay on US44 west. On exit ramp, take first legal left toward US44 east, then take left again to get on US44 east (watch for route signs). As soon as entrance ramp joins divided highway, move to left lane (important) to stay on US44 east. Go straight through first stop light. Just before second stop light, turn left into state boat launch area. (Across street from white church.)  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Related Website(s):  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ct-amc.org/flatwater/index.shtm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ct-amc.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.llbean.com/shop/retailStores/southWindsor/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.llbean.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Date(s): August 12, 2007 (Sun)  &lt;br /&gt;Location: Bolton,  Connecticut, East of River,  CT  &lt;br /&gt;Trip Difficulty: Beginner  &lt;br /&gt;Sponsoring Chapter: Connecticut &lt;br /&gt;Leader: Jean Trapani &lt;br /&gt;203-221-7439 &lt;br /&gt;flatwater@ct-amc.org  &lt;br /&gt;Registration is not required for this trip. However, you may wish to contact us if you have any questions. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok i wish you all a good day..&lt;br /&gt;I have to be a DEVIL this day and cant be there..the water puts out my fire...&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1187111081000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1186776923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Paddling The Bolton Lake with the AMC and Jean Trapani</name><id>6159068</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1186938000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/6159068/</event_url></item>