<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;As a special holiday treat the Coolidge Corner Theatre is proud to welcome the &lt;span style="color: green"&gt;Brookline Chorus&lt;/span&gt; as they perform a few short holiday songs before Friday and Saturday's 7:10 screening of Black Swan.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=615521cb-c61a-41c9-abd2-f75643670013&amp;amp;evtinfo=9920~3c2614bd-0781-48b8-a8a2-e21eaa37e962&amp;amp;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets for Black Swan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: brown"&gt;John will be at the Panera Bread at 6:00 pm for those who would like to meetup before the film, sip some black tea, and get in line at the theater at 6:30.  Afterwards, I plan to make reservations at Pho Lemongrass for after-film discussion. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;BLACK SWAN&lt;/u&gt; follows the story of Nina (Natalie Portman), a ballerina in a New York City ballet company whose life, like all those in her profession, is completely consumed with dance. She lives with her retired ballerina mother Erica (Barbara Hershey) who zealously supports her daughter’s professional ambition. When artistic director Thomas Leroy (Vincent Cassel) decides to replace prima ballerina Beth MacIntyre (Winona Ryder) for the opening production of their new season, Swan Lake, Nina is his first choice. But Nina has competition: a new dancer, Lily (Mila Kunis), who impresses Leroy as well. Swan Lake requires a dancer who can play both the White Swan with innocence and grace, and the Black Swan, who represents guile and sensuality. Nina fits the White Swan role perfectly but Lily is the personification of the Black Swan. As the two young dancers expand their rivalry into a twisted friendship, Nina begins to get more in touch with her dark side with a recklessness that threatens to destroy her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;from the New York Times:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A witchy brew of madness and cunning, “Black Swan”  tells the story of a ballerina who aches, with battered feet and an increasingly crowded head, to break out of the corps. Played by Natalie Portman  in a smashing, bruising, wholly committed performance, the young dancer, Nina, looks more like a child than a woman, her flesh as undernourished as her mind. When she goes to bed at night, a nearby jewelry box tinkling “Swan Lake,”  a crowd of stuffed animals watches over her, longtime companions that — as Nina and this dementedly entertaining film grow more unhinged — begin to look more like jailers than friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following the film, we'll look for a place to enjoy food/drink/discussion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;John&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be gathering members at the exit to the lobby by holding a red and Black Meetup Sign and singing his Swan Song.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292291929000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291561709000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Black Swan</name><id>15646750</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292112000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/15646750/</event_url></item>