<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Salutation St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.366180</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>6177232226</phone><name>Boston Harbor Community Church</name><city>Boston</city><id>1204466</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052368</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is going to be hideously difficult for anyone to get to the new MIT Media Lab Extension Building since it is so early, but I am going to get out of work early, head down there to crash this event, and try to save a few seats at 5:00 pm so we can sit as a group. Anybody care to join me? It's a great way to see the new building which is not usually open to the public. The sixth floor has a spectacular view of the Boston skyline. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... Technically, we aren't &amp;quot;crashing&amp;quot;... I received explicit permission from the head of MIT's Center for Transportation &amp;amp; Logistics that fifteen people from our group could attend this lecture that starts at 5:30 pm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;From MIT's Engineering Systems Division site:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://esd.mit.edu/digest/2010/030310.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://esd.mit.edu/di...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tuesday, March 16, 2010&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;b&gt;CTL Distinguished Speaker Series&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Speaker&lt;/u&gt;: Chris Anderson, Editor-in-Chief, Wired Magazine&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Title&lt;/u&gt;: The New Industrial Revolution: Why Atoms are the New Bits &lt;br /&gt;Refreshments will be served and the talk will be videotaped.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 5:30-6:30pm &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&amp;gt; E14-633 (Media Lab Extension Building, 6th floor)&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to Meet:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher will be attempting to save a few seats upstairs in the lecture hall on the sixth floor of the Media Lab Extension Building &lt;a href="http://tech.mit.edu/V130/N12/medialabext.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://tech.mit.edu/V...&lt;/a&gt; starting at 5:00 pm. He's not sure how many seats he can save. If we can't sit with each other, let's regroup after the lecture so we can look around the new building (if we are allowed), then grab dinner. T.J. is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About CTL:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ctl.mit.edu/index.pl?id=2167&amp;amp;isa=Category&amp;amp;op=show" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctl.mit.edu/in...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Center for Transportation &amp;amp; Logistics is part of the Engineering Systems Division in the School of Engineering.  The center is widely recognized as an international leader in the field of transportation and logistics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Along with basic contributions to the understanding of transportation system planning, operations and management, its efforts include significant contributions to logistics modeling and supply chain management for shippers; to technology and policy analysis for government; and to management, planning and operations for trucking, railroad, air and ocean carriers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In addition to administering the Master of Engineering in Logistics program, the Center helps coordinate the extensive transportation and logistics research conducted throughout MIT. At any given time, research efforts typically number over 100, ranging from modest projects involving a single faculty member and a few students to large-scale international programs involving scores of people and a full-time research staff&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is the Media Lab:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.media.mit.edu/about/faq" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.media.mit....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The MIT Media Laboratory was founded by MIT Professor Nicholas Negroponte and the late Jerome Wiesner (former science advisor to President John F. Kennedy and former President of MIT), who foresaw the coming convergence of computing, publishing, and broadcast, fueled by changes in the communications industry. As this convergence accelerated, it spurred interconnected developments in the unusual range of disciplines that the Laboratory brought together, including cognition, electronic music, graphic design, video, and holography, as well as work in computation and human-machine interfaces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;True to the vision of its founders, today's Media Lab continues to focus on the study, invention, and creative use of digital technologies to enhance the ways that people think, express, and communicate ideas, and explore new scientific frontiers. For information on current research activities at the Lab, please see the Research section&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;From the original Wired article:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;In the Next Industrial Revolution, Atoms Are the New Bits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chris Anderson, 1/25/2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wired.com/magazine/2010/01/ff_newrevolution/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wired.com/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... I already wrote to Local Motors two weeks ago -- discussed in the article -- to see if we could have a group tour... I haven't heard back yet. And it was a no go on scheduling a tour of FabLabs since the Media Lab is usually not open to the public. Ah, well. I'll keep an eye out for more events like this... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Here’s the history of two decades in one sentence: If the past 10 years have been about discovering post-institutional social models on the Web, then the next 10 years will be about applying them to the real world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This story is about the next 10 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Transformative change happens when industries democratize, when they’re ripped from the sole domain of companies, governments, and other institutions and handed over to regular folks. The Internet democratized publishing, broadcasting, and communications, and the consequence was a massive increase in the range of both participation and participants in everything digital — the long tail of bits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Now the same is happening to manufacturing — the long tail of things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The tools of factory production, from electronics assembly to 3-D printing, are now available to individuals, in batches as small as a single unit. Anybody with an idea and a little expertise can set assembly lines in China into motion with nothing more than some keystrokes on their laptop. A few days later, a prototype will be at their door, and once it all checks out, they can push a few more buttons and be in full production, making hundreds, thousands, or more. They can become a virtual micro-factory, able to design and sell goods without any infrastructure or even inventory; products can be assembled and drop-shipped by contractors who serve hundreds of such customers simultaneously.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Today, micro-factories make everything from cars to bike components to bespoke furniture in any design you can imagine. The collective potential of a million garage tinkerers is about to be unleashed on the global markets, as ideas go straight into production, no financing or tooling required. 'Three guys with laptops' used to describe a Web startup. Now it describes a hardware company, too&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;[ &lt;b&gt;MORE&lt;/b&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.wired.com/magazine/2010/01/ff_newrevolution/all/1" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.wired.com/...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Chris Anderson, according to Wikipedia:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Anderson_(writer" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.o...&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Chris Anderson (born 1961) is editor-in-chief of Wired, which has won a National Magazine Award under his tenure. He wrote an article in the magazine entitled The Long Tail , which he expanded upon in the book The Long Tail: Why the Future of Business Is Selling Less of More (2006). He currently lives in Berkeley, California, with his wife and five young children. He is the chairman of a new startup, BookTour.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] Before joining Wired in 2001, he worked at The Economist, where he launched their coverage of the Internet. He also has a degree in physics from George Washington University and did research at Los Alamos National Laboratory. He has also worked at the journals Nature and The Scientist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;His newest book, entitled &lt;i&gt;Free&lt;/i&gt;, which examines the rise of pricing models which give products and services to customers for free, was released on July 7, 2009, by Hyperion&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>7</waitlist_count><updated>1268948640000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268071670000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Chris Anderson, Editor of Wired, "Why Atoms are the New Bits" @ MIT Media Lab</name><id>12818111</id><headcount>13</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1268775000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/12818111/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/1/d/global_13600637.jpeg</photo_url></item>