<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Kendall Sq</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.366326</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-499-1996</phone><name>kendall square cinema</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>681789</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.091795</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>They come around the final turn heading for home, the crowd rises to their feet as 23 horses stampede to the finish line, the track announcer growls out the familiar phrase, &amp;quot;..and DOWN THE STRETCH THEY COME&amp;quot;.  You have goosebumps....this is your movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the Kendall website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This riveting documentary chronicles the journey of six diverse, hard-working trainers as they jockey for a position along the 2006 Kentucky Derby trail. Known as &amp;quot;the greatest two minutes in sports,&amp;quot; the Kentucky Derby is racing's Holy Grail and every horseman's ultimate goal. From Hot Springs, Arkansas, to Dubai in the United Arab Emirates, directors Brad and John Hennegan traveled more than 150,000 miles during a 16-month period to document every major horse race on the road to the 2006 Kentucky Derby. In addition to providing an intimate inside look at the amazing people who dedicate their lives to the sport of horse racing, the film features never-before-seen footage of a young Barbaro?the thoroughbred who captured the fascination of the world, first as he made history on the racetrack with a 6½-length romp in Kentucky Derby 132, and then as he bravely battled complications from a catastrophic leg injury and laminitis.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note:  I have just verified that the start time is 7:30pm! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AFter the movie we'll go to Cambridge Brewing Company to discuss.  I'll be in front of the theater (near the screen) after the movie with a meetup sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Frank&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>AFter the movie, I'll be up front near the screen holding a professionally laminated Meetup sign!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frank</member_name><member_id>4007722</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1208869552000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><why>This is should be an exciting documentary.   The group sees a diverse selection of movies: Foreign, arthouse, independents, and documentaries (small and large).  A great way to share the viewing experience with others and discuss it afterwards</why><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207491858000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Movie: "The First Saturday in May!"</name><id>7684401</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1208647800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/7684401/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/9/1/global_3818193.jpeg</photo_url></item>