<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;OPEN BAR CRUISE!!! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Departs Saturday, November 26, 2011 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Returns December 3, 2011 &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Ports include St. Maarten, St. Thomas and Nassau &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;7 Night Cruise roundtrip from Miami aboard&amp;nbsp; Norweigian Cruise Line's NEWEST Ship EPIC (&lt;a href="http://www.epic.ncl.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.epic.ncl.com&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Here are the pics from our last cruise. We had so much fun. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258016/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258016/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258033/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258033/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258071/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258071/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258826/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/Singles-In-The-Suburbs/photos/258826/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cruise rate includes: &lt;br /&gt;1. OPEN BAR PACKAGE* &lt;br /&gt;2. Accommodations &lt;br /&gt;3. Meals (This is FREESTYLE cruising, no set dinner times, no stuffy formal dinners - eat at your choice of The Manhattan Room, Taste, La Cucina, Teppanyaki, Wasabi, The Epic Club, Cagney's Steakhouse, Spiegel Tenant, Shanghai's, Le Bistro, O'Sheehan's, and many many other options!) &lt;br /&gt;4. Snacks - available 24 hours a day &lt;br /&gt;5. 24 hour room service and 24 hour pizza delivery anywhere on the ship &lt;br /&gt;6. TONS OF ENTERTAINMENT OPTIONS** &lt;br /&gt;- SHOWS including THE BLUE MAN GROUP, CIRQUE DREAMS, LEGENDS IN CONCERT, FAT CATS, SECOND CITY AND HOWL AT THE MOON &lt;br /&gt;- NIGHTLIFE including Spice H20 (an Ibiza inspired beach club), Bliss (a lounge/dance club), Svedka Ice Bar (that's right, one of only 14 ice bars in the world, kept at a chilly 17 degrees with tons of vodka to go around), O'Sheehans Irish Pub - a 24 hour pub...that's right A TWENTY FOUR HOUR PUB ON A CRUISE WHERE WE WILL HAVE OPEN BAR, Shaker's Martini Bar, Maltings Whiskey Bar, Cascades Bar, Cagney's Bar, Cigar Bar, Poolside Bar and the Sake Bara and MUCH MORE &lt;br /&gt;- CASINO (including free gaming lessons) &lt;br /&gt;- Aqua Park, Bowling, Rock Climbing, Basketball, Swimming &lt;br /&gt;- Spa &lt;br /&gt;- EXCURSIONS AT PORT - Of course, for extra fees, you'll have tons of options for excursions at each port...scuba diving, hiking, boating, TONS of options! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;**Most of the shows are included in the cost of the trip, but will require advanced ticketing.&amp;nbsp; Other entertainment, and admittance to a handful of restaurants and the pizza delivery, may incur a fee outside of your cruise price and will be paid by you directly to the ship once you sign up or play or attend.&amp;nbsp; Here is a link to the dining and what is complimentary and what may incur other charges:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://epic.ncl.com/the-experience/dining/" class="linkified"&gt;http://epic.ncl.com/the-experience/dining/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;PACKAGE RATES ARE BASED ON DOUBLE OCCUPANCY CABINS: &lt;br /&gt;- Inside Cabin - $1,151.62/per person &lt;br /&gt;- Balcony Cabin $1,391.62/per person (Private Balcony) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;CRUISE RATE ABOVE includes all items above including the OPEN BAR PACKAGE*, PORT CHARGES, AND TAXES! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;RESERVE YOUR SPOT: &lt;br /&gt;You can now reserve your spot by simply making a $250.00 deposit. Email Paul directly by sending an email to paul@mygetawayguru.com to arrange payment and a space on this cruise. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The final payment is due by 9/3/11. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;*Ask for details on the Open Bar Package as restrictions apply. Includes all house call and premium beverage charges and bars, lounges and restaurants; Private Island (when applicable; House Wine in restaurants; NCL House Wine by Glass; Unlimited fountain soda; Domestic (US) &amp;amp; Import Beer; one drink per guest per order; and includes your gratuity on the drinks!&amp;nbsp; (Excludes room service beverages; super premium and ultra premium brands; wine or liqour by the bottle; mini bar purchases; canned sodas; red bull; cocktail parties; hors d'oeuvres or food items like milk shakes; speciality cofees; speciality beer more than $4.95 in price; bottled water; cigarettes; cigars and souvenir glassware). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Discounted Group Rates are per person based on double occupancy in US Dollars. Rates and cabin availability are subject to change until deposit is placed on the booking. Rates do not include airfare, onboard purchases, gratuities (NCL suggests about $12/day to cover your tip for your room steward, etc. - which can be prepaid) (other than on the drinks included in open bar), or travel insurance. Must be 21 to sail with this group as well as one person in the cabin must be 25. Travel insurance is highly recommended. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;ALSO IF YOU NEED A ROOMMATE - please put "looking for a roommate" in your RSVP so that Paul can try to group you accordingly!&amp;nbsp; Roommates aren't guaranteed but I'll try my best.&amp;nbsp; (The room will have two twin beds, unless you state that you have a roommate and would prefer one bed). &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;IN ADDITION - AFTER YOU HAVE PAID YOUR DEPOSIT, PLEASE UPDATE YOUR RSVP WITH "DEPOSIT PAID" so that Lindsay, Paul and I can keep track of how many people are going on the trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be at the ship in port!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul</member_name><member_id>2104380</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1322324540000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>BOOZERS</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BOOZE-CLUB-Boston</urlname><id>1553338</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>! BOOZE CLUB - Boston !</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>31</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306962841000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Open Bar Cruise to St. Maarten, St. Thomas and Nassau from Miami</name><id>20574391</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1322319600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BOOZE-CLUB-Boston/events/20574391/</event_url></item>