<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Mallinckrodt Building, Harvard University, 12 Oxford St, Cambridge 02138</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380329</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Pfizer Auditorium</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1630603</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.138908</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/7/4/0/event_55466432.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hey kids - spring has sprung (well, sorta), and it's time again for the Science in the News spring lecture series :) Join us as our good friend and former director of SITN himself, Marshall Thomas, presents Sudden Death: A Tale of Cell Suicide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For newcomers to the SITN scene, Science in the News is an organization of Harvard graduate students dedicated to bringing cutting edge research to the public in a fun and informative format.  Their lectures are clear and well presented, and allow for lots of questions and interaction from the audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lecture is from 7:00 to 9:00 (or thereabouts).  We'll begin gathering in the hallway at the entrance to the lecture hall about a half hour beforehand, then go in and get seats about 10-15 minutes before it starts.  There are snacks and refreshments, and afterwards we'll head to one of many Harvard Square watering holes for food, drinks, and discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you miss the group beforehand, just look for us outside the auditorium afterwards - we won't be too hard to find.  Just look for a gaggle of nerds looking like they've just been edjumacated and ready for fun and merriment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/"&gt;https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/sitn-seminars/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the entrance to the auditorium...we'll be wearing our Meetup pins</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>5195575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1366292258000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1365124850000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>SITN Spring Lectures - Sudden Death: A Tale of Cell Suicide</name><id>112766382</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1366237800000</time><rsvp_limit>60</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/112766382/</event_url></item>