<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Rt. 9 Eastbound)</address_2><address_1>686 Worcester Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01701</zip><lat>42.297932</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-626-8989</phone><name>Whimsy arts and crafts studio</name><city>Framingham </city><id>766011</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.425194</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: violet"&gt;Come learn more about our chapter, have some refreshments, and possibly even win some door prizes. We'll have information about our meetings, moms nights out, and playgroups, including a special Under One Club for moms of infants under one year old. This is a moms only evening event, but non-mobile infants are welcome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Each month we hold bi-weekly meetings on hot topics for moms. We also organize kids activities from organized meetups at playspaces to events like fire station tours. Every month we  also organize moms activities- which include scrapbooking nights, dinners out, book groups and other events.  We periodically hold family events also. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We feature a number of sub-groups including a special needs group, a seasoned moms group, a book group,  and a cooking group. We communicate every day through a VERY active local email list where we discuss everything from the best local pediatric dentist to answering questions on toilet training, sleep issues, looking for local preschool  and daycare recommendations and hundreds of other topics. We have members in Framingham, Natick, Sudbury, Wayland, and Ashland and other surrounding towns. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: limegreen"&gt;*JUST IN***  A Sample of our Fabulous Door Prizes!!!  More are coming in everyday!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Complimentary Photo Session with Sara Sun of Sublime Photo Art + one 8x10 Print ($250 value)&lt;br /&gt;2. Hola La- Free (Spanish language classes) sesssion, puppet and CD (over $200 value)&lt;br /&gt;3. GymFit- $50 GC&lt;br /&gt;4. Arbonne- Spa Night- Foot soak, mini facial, skin care and make-up lesson plus $25 in free products for yourself and 3 guests (value of $150)&lt;br /&gt;5. Ultimate Bootcamp- Free 4 week session (value up to $279)&lt;br /&gt;6. Dream Dinners- Gift basket&lt;br /&gt;7. Build a Bear- Cuddles and Stuff basket&lt;br /&gt;8. Lia Sophia- $25 GC&lt;br /&gt;9. The Littlest Spa- Free facial along with a small bag of homemade soaps and bath salts&lt;br /&gt;10. Life coach- 45 minute free session via the phone&lt;br /&gt;11. Priceless Conversation- Have a taped converation between two people that others in family can go on to enjoy for years to come (value $199)&lt;br /&gt;12. Fashion consult- Have fashion consultant accompany you shopping to help you pick out the perfect outfit- 2 hour session (value $150)&lt;br /&gt;13. Manicure GC (2 of them)&lt;br /&gt;14. Yoga DVD- compliments of Jenn Mitchell- Fitness coach&lt;br /&gt;15. Bugaboo Creek- GC&lt;br /&gt;16. Big Fresh- GC&lt;br /&gt;17. Binary Mom T-shirt&lt;br /&gt;18. Massage- Free 30 minute massage&lt;br /&gt;19. Styles and Smiles- 1 free childs haircut&lt;br /&gt;20. Stampin It Up- Stamping supplies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;**More coming in each day...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will also be a door prize of a free one-year membership drawn from the names of those who officially join that evening!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn even more about the chapter, go to our local site at &lt;br /&gt;www.metrowestmothersandmore.org&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whimsy is located in the Ski Market Plaza on Rt. 9 Eastbound in Framingham. It is located opposite Trader Joes and Whole Foods.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tanya</member_name><member_id>7153030</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266953728000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Moms</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>mothers-and-more-metrowest</urlname><id>1284421</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>Mothers &amp; More MetroWest Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>32</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251067045000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>OPEN HOUSE!!!</name><id>11180923</id><headcount>55</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255647600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mothers-and-more-metrowest/events/11180923/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/5/a/global_8459978.jpeg</photo_url></item>