<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Austin Ave.</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02828 </zip><lat>41.884872</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-949-1456</phone><name>Henry Steere Orchards </name><city>Greenville</city><id>1390195</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.570752</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Let’s go apple and pumpkin picking on Sunday Oct. 10, at Henry Steere Orchards, in Greenville, RI.   I will have my 12 year old son, so bring the kids! You can meet me near the band at 1:00pm, or e-mail me through the group to meet earlier or car pool.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henry Steere Orchards &lt;br /&gt;150 Austin Ave., , Greenville, RI, 02828   401-949-1456&lt;br /&gt;Looking to enjoy a traditional New England experience and support your local farmer this fall? Join Henry Steere Orchards, of Greenville, RI, as they hold the annual APPLE FEST: A Fall Harvest Celebration on Sunday, October 10th, from 9 am to 5 pm. The festival will take place on the orchard grounds at 150 Austin Avenue (off of Rt. 44), and will feature live music by the AppleHead String Band, free samples of apples and baked goods, pies and other apple and pumpkin products for purchase, a jam sale, and hayrides, along with the pick-your-own apples and pick-your-own pumpkins that the orchard offers regularly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The AppleHead String Band, a lively local band with an old-timey sound, plays traditional American music from 1-3 pm. There is no admission fee. Scenic hayrides through the apple orchards will take place between 12 pm and 5 pm, and tickets will be half-price for the event. Pick-your-own-apples and pick-your-own pumpkins will be available throughout the day. The orchard will be offering free samples of apples, baked goods, and recipes, in addition to apple pies, apple crisps, apple cakes, hot mulled cider, gourmet chocolate and caramel apples, pumpkin breads, and other apple and pumpkin treats for sale. All baked goods and apple products are homemade. In case of heavy sustained rainfall, a rain date has been scheduled for Sunday, October 26th. &lt;br /&gt;A fourth generation orchard, Steere Orchard was established in 1930 by Arthur W. Steere and his son Henry J. Steere. Today, Jim Steere, grandson of the original owner, and his son John continue the tradition. It is one of the oldest and largest orchards in the state. All apples sold at the farm stand are grown at the orchard. The orchard also specializes in peaches, which are available until mid September every year. Steere Orchard is open for pick-your-own apples every day from 9 am-5 pm during September and October, and the farm stand remains open through the end of December. &lt;br /&gt;In addition to the baked goods offered for the festival, the orchard will have available all of the regular products that can be found there all season long, including pumpkins, candy and caramel apples, jams, jellies, fruit butters, salsas, local Rhode Island honey and maple syrup, hardy mums, squash, gourds, hay bales, Indian corn, sweet cider, apple crisp mixes, and of course, apples of all kinds.&lt;br /&gt;For more information, contact Steere Orchard at (401) 949-1456.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet me where the band is playing at 1:00pm</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Germaine</member_name><member_id>10481143</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286885010000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285855924000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fall Harvest Celebration </name><id>14950102</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286730000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/14950102/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/e/3/global_13367603.jpeg</photo_url></item>