<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>209 Joralemon Street</address_1><state>NY</state><zip>11201</zip><lat>40.692680</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Brooklyn Borough Hall and Plaza</name><city>Brooklyn</city><id>7376812</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.990211</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/9/9/c/event_122710652.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; The Brooklyn Book Festival is the largest free literary event in New York City, presenting an array of national and international literary stars and emerging authors. One of America’s premier book festivals, this hip, smart diverse gathering attracts thousands of book lovers of all ages to enjoy authors and the festival’s lively literary marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to this festival a couple of years ago and had a great time. I've been wanting to go back. It has something for everyone, literary fiction, genre fiction, young adult, kids books, non-fiction, current events, indie publishers, you name it, they've got it. There are author panel discussions, publisher panel discussions, book readings, book signings, and lots vendor tables, sometimes with free material. It's a great opportunity to support indie publishers and step out of your reading comfort zone if you so choose. As we get closer to the event I'll tweak the details, pick a place for us to meet for lunch and add links for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the information center in Grand Central Station and take the 4 or 5 subway to Brooklyn Borough Plaza. It's the first stop In Brooklyn and the plaza is a short walk from the station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check out their website here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.brooklynbookfestival.org/BBF/Home" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.brooklynbookfestival.org/BBF/Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/c/d/0/event_122711472.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll meet at the information center in Grand Central Station and take the 4 or 5 subway to Brooklyn Borough Plaza</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Merrill</member_name><member_id>7492092</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1348489697000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Arts  lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Arts-Cultural-Events</urlname><id>1343414</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>Arts &amp; Creative Cultural Events</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337918751000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brooklyn Book Festival</name><id>66276132</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1348408800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Arts-Cultural-Events/events/66276132/</event_url></item>