<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Harvard Square, Cambridge</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373581</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Harvard Square, The Pit</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1081024</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119622</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>All Out for Rosie Jiménez Day, Saturday, October 3rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Demand the Repeal of the Hyde Amendment!  Defend Abortion Access!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On October 3, 1977, Rosie Jiménez, from McAllen, Texas-- a low-income 27&lt;br /&gt;year old mother of a 5 year old daughter-- died from complications arising&lt;br /&gt;from an unsafe abortion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rosie Jiménez was the first known victim of the Hyde Amendment. This piece&lt;br /&gt;of legislation, passed in 1976, allows for federally funded abortions&lt;br /&gt;under Medicaid only in cases of rape, incest, or if the woman’s life is in&lt;br /&gt;danger.  Ms. Jiménez’s death came only weeks after this statute, the first&lt;br /&gt;direct assault on the Roe v. Wade Supreme Court decision of 1973, took&lt;br /&gt;effect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 1992 to 2002, national protests took place on October 3rd in memory&lt;br /&gt;of Rosie Jiménez and to call for the repeal of the Hyde Amendment. It’s&lt;br /&gt;time we revived this National Day of Action. Let’s make sure that a&lt;br /&gt;radical voice for reproductive rights continues to be heard: a voice that&lt;br /&gt;places abortion in the context of human rights, socialized health care,&lt;br /&gt;social and economic justice, and independent political action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So this October 3rd, Rosie Jiménez Day, speak out in her memory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Demand an end to restrictive state laws, to the wholly inadequate number&lt;br /&gt;of abortion facilities and providers, and to discrimination against young,&lt;br /&gt;low-income, and immigrant women, and women of color. Honor our allies--&lt;br /&gt;like doctors David Gunn, George Patterson, John Britton, Barnett Slepian,&lt;br /&gt;and George Tiller; clinic employees Shannon Lowney and Lee Ann Nichols;&lt;br /&gt;and security personnel James Barrett and Robert Sanderson-- who risk, even&lt;br /&gt;sacrifice, their lives for abortion rights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Organize and hit the streets to demand abortion access for all women, and&lt;br /&gt;protection for abortion clinics and providers. Only our grassroots efforts&lt;br /&gt;will bring about the repeal of the Hyde Amendment, guarantee our right to&lt;br /&gt;reproductive freedom and to healthcare justice and equity, and stop all&lt;br /&gt;forms of violence against women.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Women’s Commission, Socialist Party USA&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be holding signs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Matthew Andrews</member_name><member_id>5009779</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254953929000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Socialists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsocialists</urlname><id>519668</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Socialist Party USA -- Boston Branch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1254362180000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rosie Jimenez Day - Repeal the Hyde Amendment!</name><id>11514741</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1254585600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsocialists/events/11514741/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/f/2/global_10995826.jpeg</photo_url></item>