<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Union Square, opp. Jackson Mann School &amp; Twin Donuts</address_2><address_1>One North Beacon Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02134</zip><lat>42.353745</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-254-8883</phone><name>Grasshopper All-Vegan Restaurant</name><city>Allston</city><id>748467</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.137379</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>This is a post of a Boston Vegetarian Society event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We wouldn't normally pick Labor Day for a nutrition speaker event, but this is the day that Brian Clement will be in Boston and we could not miss the opportunity to bring him to you -- and for FREE no less!  Note the 2 PM start time, earlier than our usual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LABOR DAY MONDAY, SEPTEMBER 7, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 PM - Speaker/Seminar (FREE)&lt;br /&gt;3:30 PM - SOCIAL DINNER/VEGAN BUFFET - let us get to know you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2 PM - &amp;quot;Healing Yourself, Healing the World --&lt;br /&gt;Live Long and Healthy and Create a Disease-Free Future&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are very pleased to present Brian Clement, Ph.D., N.M.D., Director of the renowned Hippocrates Health Institute in West Palm Beach, Florida, whose philosophy is that a pure enzyme-rich plant diet, complemented by positive thinking and non-invasive therapies, are essential elements on the path to optimum health.  Hippocrates Health Institute has been a leader in the field of natural and complementary health care and education since 1956.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr. Clement is an author, international lecturer, and Director of the Hippocrates Health Institute which for a half century has been helping people heal themselves.  Dr. Clement will explore 50 years of clinical research and human experience dealing with serious illnesses, disease prevention, life extension, and natural anti-aging. He will explain how each of us can increase the quality of our health and well-being.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Q &amp;amp; A and book sales and signing will follow presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:30 PM - SOCIAL DINNER/VEGAN BUFFET&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For today's event we are aiming to add some raw food items to Grasshopper's generous buffet. Includes appetizers, soups, salad, and numerous entrees for only $9.50+ tax + tip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL WELCOME  -  No RSVP needed.  Just turnip!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LOCATION for seminar and dinner:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grasshopper (an all-vegan restaurant)&lt;br /&gt;1 North Beacon St.&lt;br /&gt;Union Square, Allston (Boston)&lt;br /&gt;617-254-8883&lt;br /&gt;See directions below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evelyn Kimber&lt;br /&gt;Boston Vegetarian Society&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.BostonVeg.org" target="_blank"&gt;www.BostonVeg.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Info:  617-424-8846  BVS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---------------------&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS:&lt;br /&gt;---------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grasshopper is located in Union Square Allston (the intersection of Cambridge St., Brighton Ave, and North Beacon St.) The Jackson Mann School is on one side of Union Square, Grasshopper is on the opposite side, and Twin Donuts is on another side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BY PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION (Green Line or buses) --&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The closest subway stop is Allston St. on the Green Line B car (Commonwealth Ave. line).&lt;br /&gt;Get off there; facing outbound, take a right on Allston St.&lt;br /&gt;Follow Allston St. 4/10 mile to where it ends at Brighton Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Turn left (at Burger King) and walk 50 yards to Union Sq.&lt;br /&gt;Grasshopper is on the opposite side of the square.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The #66 bus (Dudley Station - Harvard St. - Union Square - Harvard Square)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The #57 bus (Kenmore Station - Union Square - Watertown Square)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The #64 Bus (Oak Square - Union Square - University Park or Kendall Sq.- Central Square)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BY CAR --&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking:&lt;br /&gt;Free street parking.  Allow time to find a space.&lt;br /&gt;There is a big Super Stop &amp;amp; Shop parking lot two blocks away.  It is posted as customer parking only, so if you need groceries or to shop, you can look into parking there.&lt;br /&gt;Pass Grasshopper and continue west on N. Beacon St.  Go straight through the light at Everett St.&lt;br /&gt;Turn right on Arthur St. (between Volvo and Wolfers Lighting.)  Turn right into the Super Stop &amp;amp; Shop lot.&lt;br /&gt;Park at the far end, in front of A.J. Wright.  On foot, turn right out of the driveway, one block up Everett St., then left on N. Beacon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Kenmore Square in Boston, stay right at the fork and get onto Commonwealth Avenue.&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Comm. Ave. and when it bends to the left (trolley tracks will bend to the left) you go *straight* onto Brighton Ave.  Continue several blocks into Union Square.  You will see Twin Donuts ahead.  Grasshopper is&lt;br /&gt;on the right side of the intersection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Storrow Drive, turn onto Cambridge Street (opposite the River Street Bridge) and follow it straight into Union Square.  Grasshopper is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;gt;From Mass Pike, take Exit 18 toward Allston/Brighton.  Get on Cambridge St. and follow it straight into Union Square.  Grasshopper is on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted by Martha Muehe &lt;a href="http://www.essenic.com" target="_blank"&gt;(www.essenic.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252519806000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252094086000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brian Clement - Grasshopper - BVS </name><id>11291687</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252346400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/11291687/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/d/4/global_10258052.jpeg</photo_url></item>