<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Nathan Batalion,ND  World-Renowned Philosopher&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nathan Batalion,ND international lecturer, co-founder Raw-Wisdom Community,  featured Tuesday December 1, Optimum Health Solution~Raw New England Dinner Speaker Series on:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REVERSING GRAVE HARMS OF POLLUTION AND GENETICALLY MODIFIED FOODS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nowadays we're inundated by chemical and genetic pollution. Imagine not just greed is at fault and to reverse things, we shift to a life-centered vision of nature .&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nathan Batalion has a BA in religion and philosophy, an MA in Asian Studies; an MBA in Accounting and is a PhD candidate in environmental philosophy at Binghamton University. He also studied towards an Oriental MD degree at The Pacific Institute and is a licensed Naturopath as well as health and life coach. Nathan is the popular author of 50 Harmful Effects of Genetically Modified Foods, plus a co-founder of both the Raw-Wisdom Community (a branch of Dr. Gabriel Cousins' Tree of Life) and the Gerson Wellness Center at Sedona. Nathan yet further studied raw and vegan diets at Hippocrates in Puerto Rico and with the late Dr. Bernard Jenson. Lastly, as a youth he was a math prodigy who won math competitions until one day his left-brain functions shut down after a high fever. Nathan then got a glimpse into a unique way of understanding our grand universe, one that differs from contemporary physics, chemistry, and most ancient traditions. From this glimpse he developed a profoundly life-centered view of nature. He's here to share this extraordinary experience plus offer a hopeful, positive message on how we can turnaround or heal our culture's growing eco-health crises.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When:  Tuesday, December 1, 5:30 - 9:30 pm&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      5:30 pm registration&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      6:00  Aimee Perrin, Raw Chef &amp;amp; owner of Aimee's Livin' Magic, will demonstrate how to make it through the winter happily staying raw. She will demonstrate how to make a warming, spicy raw Winter Red Soup at the December potluck.&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      6:15  Gourmet living food potluck&lt;br /&gt;    *&lt;br /&gt;      7:15  Nathan Batalion's exciting presentation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Where:  UMass Waltham Center, 240 Beaver St. Waltham, MA 02452&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nathan is donating his speaker fee to &amp;quot;Optimum Health for Kids&amp;quot; in the Boston Public Schools.  Save $5.00; RSVP at www.optimumhealthsolution.org/blog  OR CLICK HERE&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;$20 at door.  Bring organic, unprocessed, raw/vegan dish for 8 or pay $10 to eat.  CLICK HERE&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Questions? Call Betsy 781-899-6664 or 617-835-2913 or email betsy@optimumhealthsolution.org.  Donations to OHS non-profit &amp;quot;feeding children a healthy future&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Nathan will have the following for sale -&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DETOXING AIDS&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;· Relax 100% Far Infrared Portable Home Sauna $850 Christmas Season Price.&lt;br /&gt;· Far Infrared Lamp $150 and Heater $100&lt;br /&gt;· Best Home Non-Toxic Cleaning System - Prices Vary&lt;br /&gt;· Organic Skin Care Products - Prices Vary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;OTHER PRODUCTS&lt;br /&gt;· Nada Chair - $70&lt;br /&gt;· Synopsis of The China Study &amp;amp; CD - Nathan Batalion &amp;amp; T. Colin Campbell $10&lt;br /&gt;· 50 Harmful Effects of Genetically Modified Foods &amp;amp; CD - By Nathan Batalion $10&lt;br /&gt;· Healing Breast Cancer Through the Arts - By Melinda Elliott; donation&lt;br /&gt;· Set of 14 CDs From Raw Spirit Festival 2009 in DC, includes my presentation $75.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4177857</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Deborah</member_name><member_id>6769449</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259879921000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259696826000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nathan Batalion @ OHS Potluck</name><id>11992237</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259706600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/11992237/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/8/b/global_12055931.jpeg</photo_url></item>