<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Emergency meeting of anyone who is threatened by foreclosure, in a "short sale" situation (owe more than what you can get for your property), thinking of filing bankruptcy, or wants information on loan modification and fraud involved with some companies (ie...Home Protection Firm and Home Care Alliance Group out of California) and/or what you can do to help your current situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you in a difficult situation right now?&amp;nbsp; I hate to admit this but...join the club...I'm a Realtor who has overbought, gotten underpaid and gotten screwed this past year, by a bank and 2, yes 2 (I didn't learn my lesson the first time) loan modification companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will start at 5pm, by everyone bringing something good to share, and at&amp;nbsp;6:30-7 pm start discussion until about 9pm...hopefully, we'll be around a campfire later in the evening, if the town allows a permit for one.&amp;nbsp;Please don't be late and interrupt the discussion, and the latest we'll be here is 11pm, as I cannot make this a late night...I'm working in the morning early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please put in your reply what you could bring...no chips please, I've got plenty.&amp;nbsp; Fruit, Veggies, Grill your own stuff...salads always welcome, and of course a few sweet treats ;) BYOB, bug spray&amp;nbsp;and a chair in case we go outside.&amp;nbsp; I have marshmallows and VERY long sticks...lol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If tomorrow doesn't work for you, please email me at 
&lt;a href="mailto:stisbert@yahoo.com"&gt;stisbert@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;, and I'll set up a night this coming week.&amp;nbsp; Put in the subject "meeting of the minds" so I won't delete you.&amp;nbsp; This is my business email, answered right away, whereas my meetup email, I forget to answer sometimes...oops, sorry, I've been&amp;nbsp;very busy in Real Estate lately, thank&amp;nbsp;goodness!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you soon,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;susan&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will send directions to those who say they are coming...</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>susan tisbert</member_name><member_id>3950284</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315174383000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1315083234000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>urgent foreclosure, short sale, bankruptcy meeting...</name><id>32156102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315170000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/32156102/</event_url></item>