<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;La fille du RER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; (The girl on the train)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's meet for this movie about a real event that occurred in Paris.  There's a very similar event that occurred late last year in Australia that caused riots and death threats against Australians in India - and is still causing major cross-cultural incidents to this day in Australian-Indian relations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Where:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Cable Car Cinema&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;204 south main street&lt;br /&gt;providence, rhode island&lt;br /&gt;Ph: 401.272.3970&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;When:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Wed 3 March 6:15pm (movie starts at 6:30pm)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tickets:&lt;/i&gt; $8.50 general admission; $6.50 student admission&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll meet outside the cinema at 6pm to make sure we get tickets.  If you can't make it until about 6.15, let me know and I'll buy a ticket for you.  It's important to go in by 6:15 because seating is limited and we'd like to sit together if possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the movie, we can go for a coffee or stay for the next movie &amp;quot;Francaise&amp;quot; that screens at 9pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More details about the film are below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stevie&lt;br /&gt;____________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;La fille du RER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; (The girl on the train)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;DIRECTED BY&lt;/i&gt; André Téchiné&lt;br /&gt;France | 2009 | 105 m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;CAST&lt;/i&gt; Catherine Deneuve, Emilie Dequenne, Michel Blanc&lt;br /&gt;View trailer (in French with subtitles)&lt;a href="http://www.lafilledurer-lefilm.com/international/" target="_blank"&gt;Lafilledurer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andre Téchiné's many admirers will not be disappointed by his latest offering. In the words of one of the main characters, the film is ostensibly &amp;quot;the story of a lie,&amp;quot; but as always with this director, the pleasures reside in the fine detail rather than the broad sweep. Téchiné's starting point is a true story that provoked a controversy in France five years ago: a young woman claimed to have been the victim of an anti-Semitic attack on a Paris commuter train, creating a media uproar that drew in even the head of state. But in the end, the affair was revealed to be a hoax. Téchiné is less interested by the case itself than its impact on the lives of the family and friends surrounding the girl: her mother, her lover, and her best friends who have to choose sides.&lt;br /&gt;_________________________&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a blue and pink flamingo beanie</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1268623972000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>French Speakers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>providencefrenchlanguage</urlname><id>1145546</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4599990845</group_lon><name>The Providence French Language Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267479485000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>French Film Fest - La fille du RER</name><id>12747977</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1267657200000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providencefrenchlanguage/events/12747977/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/1/6/global_13407350.jpeg</photo_url></item>