<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston, MA</address_2><address_1>1 Norway St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.345245</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Christian Science Center</name><city>Boston</city><id>174055</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.087660</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Nate Aune will just be returning from the Snow Sprint in Austria, and will give a summary of the work that was done on the mountaintop including Multimedia / Plone / Zope3 / Web 2.0 topics. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the 4th year of the legendary &lt;a href="http://plone.org/events/sprints/snow-sprint-2007" target="_blank"&gt;Snow Sprint&lt;/a&gt; which gathers more than 50 programmers from around the world to partake in extreme coding, extreme skiing, and extreme drinking. ;)  See photos from past Snow Sprints &lt;a href="http://flickr.com/search/?q=snowsprint&amp;amp;m=tags&amp;amp;z=t&amp;amp;s=int" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your interested in knowing what what's the latestest and greatest in the Plone world, this meetup is for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.bostonplone.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonplone.org/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonplon...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The entrance is in the center of the long building next to the reflecting pool. Tell the security guard you are here for the Plone Users Group meeting. Call me on my cell if you have trouble. If coming by T, closest stop is green line Symphony T stop. Hynes Convention Center is also very close, as is Mass Ave (Orange line). Parking at the Christian Science Center underground parking garage available, but will cost $5. Please let the parking attendant know that you are here for the Plone Meetup hosted by Danny Robert.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that while the official location of the church is 1 Norway Street, the meetup location is in the Christian Science Church Park and is closer to Huntington Ave. See this &lt;a href="http://tinyurl.com/yegprt" target="_blank"&gt;Google map&lt;/a&gt; for clarification.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nate Aune</member_name><member_id>58579</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273540918000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Plonista</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonplone</urlname><id>207992</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The Boston Plone Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169168674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Boston Plone February Meetup - Snow Sprint wrapup</name><id>5406184</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1172188800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonplone/events/5406184/</event_url></item>