<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>60 Masonic Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01060</zip><lat>42.318802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Media Education Foundation</name><city>Northampton</city><id>159327</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.633499</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Films and discussion on &lt;br /&gt;World Trade Center building-7&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, September 11, 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The public-invited program begins at 2:00 PM, but we are meeting by noon to join and invite those participating with the weekly noon peace vigil. We will be passing out our press release-&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;September 11 Event in Northampton, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valley 9/11 Truth - www.Valley911truth.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Northampton -- For more than three years members of Valley 9/11 Truth have been holding meetings, films and discussions on 9/11. The evidence uncovered by independent researchers show that it was impossible to cause three steel-framed buildings to collapse at nearly free fall speeds with the official explanation of office fires and jet fuel. Not only had this never happened before or since, but evidence published in the peer-review, highly respected, The &lt;a href="http://www.bentham-open.org/pages/content.php?TOCPJ/2009/00000002/00000001/7TOCPJ.SGM" target="_blank"&gt;Open Chemical Physics Journal show military grade nano-thermite explosives were found throughout the dust&lt;/a&gt; at 'ground zero' soon after their collapse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evidence regarding a cover-up of what happened on September 11 is important because two wars have been justified by the alleged attacks. The issue of building a Muslim community center in NYC is another example of the importance of valuing a scientific investigation, and sticking with principles in the US Constitution. Instead, 9/11 has appeared to many as a coup d'etat to mislead people, as National Academy of Science member Lynn Margulis wrote in her article. &amp;quot;Two Hit, Three Down - The Biggest Lie.&amp;quot; (1)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The focus of programs Saturday, September 11, 2010 at the Frances P. Crowe community meeting space (60 Masonic Street) will be covering the sudden descent of World Trade Center (WTC) building 7. &amp;quot;Building what?&amp;quot; was asked by Judge Edward Lehner upon hearing mention of WTC Building 7. But no wonder why he would miss something as significant as that, the so-called official 9/11 Commission omitted this fact from their Report!?! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Ray Griffin said: &amp;quot;Recognizing the high correlation between those who know about the collapse of WTC 7 and those who believe that a new - or rather real - 9/11 investigation is needed, I propose that the international 9/11 Truth Movement initiate, starting this September, a world-wide, year-long 'BuildingWhat?' campaign. Through this campaign, we would seek to make the fact of its collapse so widely known that the mention of Building 7 would never again evoke the question: 'Building What?'&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The program begins at 2:00 PM at the Frances Crowe community meeting space with &amp;quot;9/11 Blueprint for Truth: The Architecture of Destruction.&amp;quot; Following films will be discussions. The film beginning at 7:00 PM is called The Reflecting Pool. At 9:00 PM the film will be a new DVD interview with Richard Gage, AIA. Any changes will be posted at www.valley911truth.org.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The public is invited free of charge. However donations will be appreciated to support costs of the event and to donate to BuildingWhat.org for television advertisements in NYC on WTC-7.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) Two Hit, Three Down - The Biggest Lie&lt;br /&gt;National Academy of Science member and Distinguished Professor endorses&lt;br /&gt;David Ray Griffin's work exposing the truth of 9/11&lt;br /&gt;By Lynn Margulis&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.tumblr.com/post/353434420/two-hit-three-down-the-biggest-lie" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://rockcreekfreepress.tumblr.com/post/353434420/two-hit-three-down-the-biggest-lie" target="_blank"&gt;http://rockcreekfreep...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Without truth there can be no justice. &lt;br /&gt;Without justice can there be peace?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule of Films&lt;/b&gt;  (discussions follow)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:15 PM – 9/11 Blueprint for Truth&lt;br /&gt;4:15 PM – WTC Exposed In 3-Minutes&lt;br /&gt;[dinner break?]&lt;br /&gt;7:00 PM – The Reflecting Pool &lt;br /&gt;9:00 PM – New interview with Richard Gage, AIA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event if free, however donations are appreciated to cover costs and to donate to: &lt;a href="http://buildingwhat.org/" target="_blank"&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Building What?&lt;/b&gt; Campaign - BuildingWhat.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Go to &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/files/"&gt;FILES&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to download a flyer and press release to help promote this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What did we really lose from the 9/11/01 Alleged Terrorist Crimes? Has society been brought to new lows in an investigation cover-up while denying hard evidence and basic laws of science, justifying wars, and depleting our economy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For additional details on films and more:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Valley911truth.org &amp;amp; &lt;a href="http://www.flybynews.com/"&gt;FlybyNews.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284225432000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282336061000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Valley 9/11 Truth - September 11, 2010</name><id>14487797</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284219900000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/14487797/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/1/global_576113.jpeg</photo_url></item>