<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>581 Massachusetts Ave </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02139</zip><lat>42.364742</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-524-1667</phone><name>Harvest Co-Op Market/Clear Conscience Cafe</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>428348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.102600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Alright, I admit it.  I picked out a chick book from amongst all the ties.  It's summer....time for brain candy! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The History of Love by Nicole Krauss&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Copied from &lt;a href="http://www.powells.com/biblio?show=HARDCOVER:NEW:9780393060348:23.95#synopses_and_reviews" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.powells.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;A long-lost book reappears, mysteriously connecting an old man searching for his son and a girl seeking a cure for her widowed mother's loneliness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leo Gursky is just about surviving, tapping his radiator each evening to let his upstairs neighbor know he's still alive. But life wasn't always like this: sixty years ago, in the Polish village where he was born, Leo fell in love and wrote a book. And though Leo doesn't know it, that book survived, inspiring fabulous circumstances, even love. Fourteen-year-old Alma was named after a character in that very book. And although she has her hands full ? keeping track of her brother, Bird (who thinks he might be the Messiah), and taking copious notes on How to Survive in the Wild ? she undertakes an adventure to find her namesake and save her family. With consummate, spellbinding skill, Nicole Krauss gradually draws together their stories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;This extraordinary book was inspired by the author's four grandparents and by a pantheon of authors whose work is haunted by loss ? Bruno Schulz, Franz Kafka, Isaac Babel, and more. It is truly a history of love: a tale brimming with laughter, irony, passion, and soaring imaginative power.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214435015000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Book Readers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bookclub-797</urlname><id>507213</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>20ish &amp; 30ish Boston Book Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207930270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cambridge Meetup: The History of Love by Nicole Krauss</name><id>7720421</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214262000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bookclub-797/events/7720421/</event_url></item>