<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>take I91 exit 8, head west</address_2><address_1>Cascade Falls Rd off hwy 131</address_1><state>VT</state><zip>05030</zip><lat>43.450001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>NHgreyjay cellphone 603-477-5116</phone><name>Mount Ascutney, Weathersfield Trailhead</name><city>Ascutney</city><id>256316</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.419998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;img src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/d/d5/Ascutney_Mountain_Vermont_USA.jpg/300px-Ascutney_Mountain_Vermont_USA.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is my local mountain with well marked trails that will get you into condition for any White Mountain hike. Lots of good scenery, waterfalls and with this group: conversation and someone to cheer you to the top. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mount Ascutney is Vermont's only monadnock, or lone mountain. Particularly noteworthy about the mountain is its granite outcrops, one of which, at its peak, serves as a launching point for hang-gliders. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of four hiking trails that go to the summit of Mt. Ascutney, the Weathersfield Trail is probably the most scenic. Highlights of this trail include Little Cascade Falls (.04 miles), Crystal Cascade Falls (an 84 foot high waterfall at 1.1 miles), Gus's Lookout and the West Peak Vista where in the summer months, hang gliders launch from. There is also a great observation platform on the summit for hikers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(elevation, 3144ft).Elevation gain: 2250 ft.Total: 6.2 miles Rating: moderate due to the elevation gain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;trail concerns:&lt;/b&gt; possible ice and wet trails. Proper hiking clothing, Leg gaiters and foot traction advisable. Stair like climbing, a few stair cases. Trail is well marked, but attention needed to not divert to the many herd paths.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to the trailhead&lt;br /&gt;The trail head parking area is located off Route 131 in Weathersfield, Vt. From the Ascutney Exit on Interstate #91,turn west on Vt Route 131 and travel 3.5 miles to an intersection where the Cascade Falls Road meets with 131. Turn right onto Cascade Falls Road and follow the signs to the trail head. No facilities at the trail head. Gas food and restrooms at the I91 exit. Many places to get a bite to eat after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we &lt;br /&gt;have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the &lt;br /&gt;hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your response/signing up for a hike certifies that you have read, understand, and agree with the &lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/283/pages/disclaimer/"&gt;NEHAAG disclaimer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://images.intellicast.com/images/icons/66_wtext.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227971756000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1226277084000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Ascutney Weathersfield Trail: Photographer's Delight!</name><id>9128338</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227451500000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/9128338/</event_url></item>