<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>111 Providence Pl</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.828996</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Napa Valley Grille</name><city>Providence</city><id>691528</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.424635</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>It's Restaurant Week in Providence, Let's eat!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To prove your voice can make a difference, we're headed to Napa Valley Grille, a place one of our members just mentioned never visiting and thus, we're off, to try it in the prix fixe restaurant week style that makes checking places out affordable. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Restaurant Week runs from July 7th - July 19th and details on other participating restaurants can be found at &lt;a href="http://www.restreview.com/rest_week_pv/pv_rest_week.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.restreview...&lt;/a&gt; should you find time to frequent the city and grab some chow (and lemme know, maybe I'll join ya!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Napa Valley Grille is located in Providence Place Mall, and parking is available in the Mall lot.  It's an easy shot off 95.  Directions are available off the Napa Valley Grill website at &lt;a href="http://www.napavalleygrille.com/providence/contact.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.napavalley...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll be meeting between 6:30-6:45 pm in front of the restaurant on Providence Place.  If it's raining, head inside.  Will send out my cell phone number to my yes's for anyone stuck in traffic and running late.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget guys, this is a reservation, and if you RSVP yes, and take a reserved spot, we do expect you to show up.  Hence, no maybe's.  If your plans change, please change your RSVP accordingly. RSVPs will close 24 hours prior to the event and any change in plans thereafter must be directed straight to my email or cell phone.  Three missed yes RSVPs and you lose your chance to join us in the future.  These restaurants are going to be packed, and it's only fair to them to provide accurate numbers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More carefree, wishy-washy, maybe options to come:-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions, contact Lisa&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa/vetchick</member_name><member_id>4120480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215988626000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214239578000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Providence Restaurant Week- Napa Valley Grille</name><id>8197419</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215815400000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/8197419/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>