<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>to be announced...</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358431</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>TBA</name><city>Boston</city><id>1328273</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059773</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$15 per person at event</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Cattail Harvest- Saturday, April 9, 1-3pm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The   cattail is a plentiful food source that was a staple for the native   people of this area. Whether you are interested in supplementing regular   dishes with a taste of the wild, becoming more intimate with nature,  or  surviving the collapse of the commercial food network, you should  make  acquaintance with the cattail.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Now   is an appropriate time to harvest the rhizomes and sprouts. In this   hands-on workshop we will dig up and collect cattail sprouts while   discussing preparation methods. The facilitator will also explain how   different parts of the cattail can be used at different times of the   year for food and practical objects. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Jules   Kobek is the co-founder of DIO (Do-It-Ourselves) Skillshare,   facilitating workshops on skills of urban sustainability, such as   sprouting, growing vegetables, and constructing raised garden beds. She   also leads nature walks to identify edible weeds. After gathering urban   wild food for several years, Jules has expanded her foraging to   woodlands and marshes. &lt;/span&gt;She is studying ethnobotany- the  study of  the relationship between plants and people in different  cultures- and  is also learning wilderness survival skills.  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;In Arlington on the Minuteman Bicycle Trail near a bus stop.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;$10-15 payable in cash at event.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt; Bring waterproof boots and a trowel or digging stick &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Call &lt;a target="_blank"&gt;617-492-2340&lt;/a&gt; by April 6 for registration, directions, and questions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #888888"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Call 617-492-2340 by April 6 for registration, directions, and questions.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1302432992000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Cattail Harvest - Wild edibles and foraging for nature's super foods - a regular staple for health and sustainability and fun!</why><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300805370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wild Forage with Jules Kobeck</name><id>17011901</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302368400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/17011901/</event_url></item>