<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>900 East Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.527122</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Comfort Inn</name><city>Meriden</city><id>1046895</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.772480</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Mastermind Group Meeting January 25, 2012 5:15 to 7:00 pm Comfort Inn. 900 East Main Street. Meriden, CT Register and Learn More at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=405" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt; The CT REIA mastermind group's purpose is to share thoughts, ideas, opinions and information. To be successful, it is also important to be supportive, and industry-based. When we create a group that is industry-focused as in real estate, we gain the ability to see things not only from our own perspective, but also with the collective group experience, we have the ability to see things from a new and different perspective. It is from that collective process... we can tap into new ideas. As individuals, we cannot achieve this on our own because our own views are limited, but with a real estate mastermind group, the possibilities for expansive thinking are endless. ============================== ============================== Apartment Owners Meeting January 25, 2012 7:00 to 9:00 pm Comfort Inn. 900 East Main Street. Meriden, CT Register and Learn More at &lt;a href="http://www.ctreia.com/events.php?a=v&amp;amp;i=393" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ctreia.com...&lt;/a&gt; Learn from and network with other apartment owners in Connecticut. The Apartment Owners Association of Connecticut is the largest state wide association representing the interest of apartment owners. Right now is a great time to buy and hold properties long term. If you are currently a landlord or planning to be one soon, let the CT REIA team of experts teach you how to do it right or have it done for you without costing you an arm and a leg. You will Discover: -------------- * How to manage your own properties, tenants and maintenance. * How investors can be more hands off. * How to hire and use a good property management person or company. * Multifamily benefits. * How to choose the best tenants. * How to deal with tenants and handle tenant issues. * How to modify your lease and rental application. * The New Security Deposit rule * Why you should never have an eviction again. * Building code before you buy. * Landlord laws and regulations. * How to eliminate pests from your properties. * How to work with a professional property management firm. * And much more. Everyone attending will receive: -------------------------- * Connecticut's &amp;quot;very best&amp;quot; apartment lease with all its polices and procedures. * Refreshments.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Linda Baumgarten</member_name><member_id>6320255</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1327535172000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Real Estate Investors</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ctreia</urlname><id>989128</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>CT REIA - The Connecticut Real Estate Investors Assn. Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1326810441000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Connecticut Apartment Owners Meeting and Mastermind Group January 2012 Meeting</name><id>48440992</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327529700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ctreia/events/48440992/</event_url></item>