<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello All,  &lt;br /&gt; Happy Woofoween!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's that time of year again. The annual Diva's Unleashed Halloween pet parade!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a great event for all those ghoulish pups and pet parents. You can choose to wear a costume or just dress up your pet for the Costume contest and walk the parade with all your pet pals.  &lt;br /&gt;This year proceeds will go to sponsor Canine Companions for independence.   &lt;br /&gt;Find out more:  &lt;a href="http://www.doggieday.com/halloween/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.doggieday....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FYI qickie: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, October 28, 2007 &lt;br /&gt;Check-in 10a-12n &lt;br /&gt;parade begins at 12noon &lt;br /&gt;This year the parade will feature Randy Price whom will Emcee the Finalist Fashion Show! &lt;br /&gt;There will  be Grande Diva in a one-of-a-kind Grande Diva costume designed by David Josef of David Josef Fashions &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The event is sponsored by WFNX, Stuff@Night, Boston.TV and the Boston Phoenix to name a few?.  &lt;br /&gt;There is a $25 donation, this automatically reg. you for the pet contest. Proceeds are for charity. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please also see our message boards for more information as some of our  members have done a great job posting other local events happening on or about  Halloween in and around the Boston area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather permitting, I would like to try to continue to keep both meetups in two locations (just as we have for the summer). Members can choose to attend the Commons at 11AM and 1PM and we will also continue to hold meetups at 1PM at Doggie Day, Boston (Tremont Street). Let's try to continue to hold both for the November meetup! &lt;br /&gt; THIS MAY BE THE LAST OUTDOOR MEETUP DUE TO THE COLD WEATHER. Then we will only hold one location at Doggies Day for the months of Dec, Jan and Feb...but more information will be posted on that subject at a later date. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those of you who would like to attend the park in the morning then move onto to Doggie day at 1pm are welcome to do so, but PLEASE as always make a note in the rsvp so that we can keep track of the numbers :)  &lt;br /&gt;If anyone has any further questions regarding this please also post them on the message board thread for the Sunday meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Boston Common (near the Boylston T stop/Lowes theater side) 11:00AM and 1:00 PM (leave an rsvp on the message board if you plan to go to the park at 1pm)  &lt;br /&gt;2. DOGGIE DAY PLAYCENTER (Tremont Street, South end, Boston ...our usual location 1:00PM ONLY!!!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay well...ST&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan</member_name><member_id>2067938</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194969993000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Chihuahua Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>chihuahua-99</urlname><id>32412</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Boston Chihuahua Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>37</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192377732000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Chihuahua November Meetup</name><id>6548057</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1194796800000</time><rsvp_limit>95</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/chihuahua-99/events/6548057/</event_url></item>