<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just hoping that you will be able to forgive my transgressions and consider joining Breezy and I on a hike.   Wow ... Not sure how I got so off track with organizing.  Sadly between Breezy's health hiccups and my being on the road most of May through this week I completely dropped the ball.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thankfully Luis and Kate are always Amazing and I am happy to report Breezy is now a healthy pup.  This in mind ... How does a quick hike up and down the red loop this Tuesday at 6:30 sound to you? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The loop is fun up the hill and then down we can easily do the loop in about 45 minutes, 30 if we hurry, or an hour if we are walking at a slow pace.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll Be the brunette at the ski lodge parking lot in the white vintage, old, audi with my cute puff of a bichon Breezy ...  After the hike lets consider going to the halfway cafe where we can dine on the patio and our pups can be leashed to the outside of the patio on the walkway, if other guests are on the patio ... or if we are the only patio visitors ... pups and people can relax together.  Best of all they are open to holding tables for us if I can get an idea of who would like to enjoy a drink and/or a bite after the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking for directions - Here are the ones I grabbed of bluehillsski.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take I-93 South / US-1 South.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From the Cape: Take MA-3 North towards Boston.&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 20 on the left onto I-93 South / US-1 (toward I-95 / Dedham).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;From Providence: Take I-95 North (Crossing into Massachusetts).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 12 towards Boston (I-93 North / US-1 North).&lt;br /&gt;Take Exit 2B / Milton onto MA-138 North / Washington St.&lt;br /&gt;Blue Hills Ski Area is approximately 1 mile on the right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chat soon,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kristan&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll Be the brunette at the ski lodge parking lot in the white vintage, old, audi with my cute puff of a bichon Breezy </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristan</member_name><member_id>8717151</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1281572400000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>dog-hiking</urlname><id>1123750</id><group_lat>42.2299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8899993896</group_lon><name>Dog hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281126370000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Evening Hike @ the Blue Hills</name><id>14343083</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1281479400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/dog-hiking/events/14343083/</event_url></item>