<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Broad st</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04217</zip><lat>44.400806</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bethel Inn</name><city>Bethel</city><id>830512</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.788117</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;EVENT:&lt;/b&gt; Join us for a Mosaic of Mass tradition – our annual winter weekend trip to the Bethel Inn &lt;br /&gt;in Bethel, ME. (When we are there, it turns into Beth El!). Enjoy the comforts of a first class inn for &lt;br /&gt;two nights, two sumptuous buffet breakfasts, a Saturday night 3-course gourmet dinner, a swim in &lt;br /&gt;an outdoor heated pool, and a workout room all at an unbelievably reasonable price. Nearby is &lt;br /&gt;Sunday River (info at www.sundayriver.com), a world class downhill ski resort renowned for its &lt;br /&gt;snow conditions even this early in the ski season. After skiing and dinner on Saturday evening, &lt;br /&gt;relax by the fireplace and enjoy games and good conversation. You can read more about the &lt;br /&gt;Bethel Inn at &lt;a href="http://www.bethelinn.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bethelinn....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Trip Coordinators:&lt;/b&gt; are Henri Menco and Barry Polsky and for any questions send them an email at: bethel@mosaicmass.org &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;MEET:&lt;/b&gt; A list of members will be made available for the purpose of facilitating ride sharing to the inn &lt;br /&gt;on Friday evening (about a 3 ½ hour drive from Boston).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP:&lt;/b&gt; Required by Monday, November 17. Mail your check, made out to MOMC of MA, to Barry Polsky: &lt;br /&gt;77 Hancock st, Somerville MA  02144.  Please include your town, email address, phone number(s), whether you would like a lift ticket for Sunday River, who you would like as a roommate, whether you agree to be on a list for carpooling, and whether you have any objection to being included on a list of participants. Absolutely no reservations will be taken after December 11. First come, first serve with respect to rooms - most of our rooms will be in the main inn but later registrants will be given rooms in the Oaks or Pines, a short walk from the main building. The latest registrants will be offered rooms in outlying buildings about a 10-minute walk from the main inn - you will be informed beforehand if this is your only choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;COST:&lt;/b&gt; Includes two nights lodging, two breakfasts, and one gourmet dinner. Regular rate is an amazing $185. Early bird rate is even more amazing $180 if we get your check by November 10th. The Late rate is $200 if we get your check after November 17. Late checks will be accepted only as availability allows. &lt;br /&gt;There are a very limited number of single rooms available –add $50 to the rate if you want a single room. &lt;br /&gt;There are larger deluxe rooms available for an extra $90 per person for doubles or $100 per person for &lt;br /&gt;singles. Reserving one of these rooms guarantees that you will be in the main inn. There is an option to &lt;br /&gt;arrive earlier than Friday or stay later than Sunday for an additional $110 per night double occupancy, you &lt;br /&gt;can call the inn directly to make these arrangements. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;LIFT TICKETS:&lt;/b&gt; We will be ordering our lift tickets directly through the Bethel Inn. When you RSVP, please indicate whether you would like a lift-ticket. If so, how many days do will you be skiing? Also, are you or anyone in your party a Senior (over 65), Young Adult (13-18), or Junior (6-12)? We must have your request &lt;br /&gt;for lift tickets by December 14. You will pick up your lift-ticket when you check in and the cost will be charged &lt;br /&gt;to your room Account. More info will be forthcoming as to lift ticket prices but they will be substantially less&lt;br /&gt;than mountain prices.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will all be meeting at the Inn</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David</member_name><member_id>4431256</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1261354265000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>friends and members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>mosaicofmass</urlname><id>416725</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>Mosaic Jewish Outdoor Club of Massachusetts</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1257114855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The 16th Annual Bethel Inn Winter Weekend</name><id>11763818</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1261180800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/mosaicofmass/events/11763818/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/9/0/global_1883520.jpeg</photo_url></item>