<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;b&gt;131 West Shore Road, Ellington, CT!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: purple"&gt;So many people asked me if I was going to repeat my July 4th party this year, but I just wasn't able to do it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But the lake is beautiful and I got my dock (somewhat) repaired, AND, &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;I'm turning 50 on August 27th!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.followupsuccess.com/wp-content/uploads/2008/09/50th-birthday-cake.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, for gawd's sake, someone remember to bring CAKE.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's a running joke among my friends that because, like Carrie on Sex in the City, I've never had a wedding shower or a baby shower, I should &amp;quot;register&amp;quot; for my 50th.  I'm considering it...watch my website, www.toniandrews.com, for updates on that front. But one thing I know I DO want on my list is a big, honkin' birthday party.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your bathing suit as there will be swimming.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will provide the grill, ice, paper plates, cups, napkins and utensils. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;YOU bring all of the food and drink (and booze).  &lt;img src='http://img1.meetupstatic.com/img/smileys/biggrin.gif' border='0' alt='biggrin' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also appreciated are lawn chairs, canopies, umbrellas, coolers, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone wants to come over early and set up (because it's my birthday and therefore I should do little more than sit on a throne and supervise) please do so. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And, if someone wants to pick up some fireworks for those of us still hanging out after dark, I wouldn't object...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Street parking on West Shore Road is, as you will remember, tight, but you can also park on Route 30 -- a set of stairs runs down to the lower road -- or at Crystal Lake Self Storage, which is about 1/4 mile away. You can unload first and then take your car up there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Toni</member_name><member_id>4890008</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1252969704000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun Seekers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mixing-it-Up</urlname><id>768057</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>MIXING IT UP IN WEST HARTFORD AND BEYOND</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249129269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Toni Celebrates the Second Half of Her Life!</name><id>11007184</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252256400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mixing-it-Up/events/11007184/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/a/2/global_10166722.jpeg</photo_url></item>