<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Longmarsh Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.114132</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sweet Trail</name><city>Durham</city><id>1429864</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.903655</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;New date for this - &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;Sunday, Nov. 18&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300 ; font-size : x-large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The recently completed Sweet Trail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/1/8/event_172631032.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;runs from Longmarsh Road in Durham to the shore of Great Bay in Newmarket. The area is crawling with beavers and the trail crosses about the longest active beaver dam you'll ever see! Ponds full of wildlife are everywhere and the area feels surprisingly remote.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt;: From Durham follow Rt 108 a couple of miles to a left on Longmarsh Rd. Follow Longmarsh to its end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time/Distance&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;This is an easy and mostly flat but very scenic trail. If we followed the entire length, it would be 8.6 miles roundtrip. We don't have to hike that far and the group can decide if we should turn around before reaching Great Bay. Figure on 2-4 hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #993300"&gt;There will be food and drinks afterward in Durham!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/5/4/event_172631092.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://durham.nh.us/generalpdfs/Sweet_Trail.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Sweet Trail Map &amp;amp; Brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://durham.nh.us/generalpdfs/Sweet_Trail.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;The Nature Conservancy, the Town of Durham, and the Great Bay Resource Protection Partnership helped plan and develop the trail which highlights diverse wildlife habitats through the 2500 acre Crommet Creek watershed. The trail crosses land owned by NH Fish and Game, Society for the Protection of NH Forests, Town of Durham and The Nature Conservancy. The goal of the trail was to create a longer and more remote hiking and wildlife viewing experience. It was constructed with the help of local volunteers, New York City youth, and AMC trail crews.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos3.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/b/c/c/event_172631212.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;There are several picturesque overlooks and bridges along the trail offering views of beaver ponds and a great blue heron rookery. It is not unusual to see American black ducks, osprey, beaver, turtles and many&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;songbirds along the trail. From freshwater marshes to tidal creeks, you will see the interconnections between fresh and saltwater habitats and the abundance of life that depends on these ecosystems. The trail was named in honor of Cy and Bobby Sweet of New Castle, NH who have generously supported conservation work at Great Bay for many years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 AS A CONDITION OF ATTENDING THIS MEETUP, YOU AGREE TO hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer and his heirs, and all members and participants of the Seacoast Outdoors Meetup group from any and all claims for injury, illness, death, and/or property damage including those caused by negligence, ignorance, inexperience and other reasons. You also agree to assume all mental, physical, financial, and/or other risk associated with this meetup. Kayaking, camping, hiking, bicycling, and other activities pose inherent risks and dangers. Participation in these activities is voluntary and dependent upon your own personal judgment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008080"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time/location subject to change due to weather and other factors.  ALWAYS check for updates prior to leaving your house.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Pilla</member_name><member_id>7841451</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1353336962000</updated><rating><average>4.69999980927</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>Seacoasters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SeacoastOutdoors</urlname><id>1441594</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>Seacoast Outdoors</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1352295315000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A Sweet Walk in the Woods</name><id>90345752</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1353258000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SeacoastOutdoors/events/90345752/</event_url></item>