<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi - &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is Rob P., the &amp;quot;founder&amp;quot; of the brand new &amp;quot;FREE Live Outdoor Music&amp;quot; MeetUp Group.  Welcome!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I mentioned in the group intro, I'm posting a bunch of freebie concerts, fireworks, etc. on this site for anyone/everyone to use - whether someone wishes to gather a group for a particular event, go solo, or not - whether I attend, or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As this is brand new, the word hasn't gotten out as yet, so not much interest in this evening's &amp;quot;Glamor Girls&amp;quot; in Southington.  I've seen them a couple of time before and think they are great fun!  I wish I had more time to get the word out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bottom Line:  I also run a group via the &amp;quot;Single Event&amp;quot; called &amp;quot;Rob's Wacky Wednesday&amp;quot; (that I'll start posting on this site), wherby we meet a couple/few times per month to attend the new Funny Bone Comedy Club inside Manchester's Buckland Hills Mall.  Had the Glamor Girls event gathered more &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; rsvp's I would have attended that, but since not, I'm more inclined to go to the Funny Bone show @ 7:30 this evening (gather @ 6:30).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We've had from 6-24 people gather per show.  I did not advertise it this week, waiting to see how the response went for &amp;quot;Glamor Girls&amp;quot;, so likely just a handfull will attend this evening.  Would you like to join us this evening?  If so, rather than pay the $10 for this evening's show, purchase a promo tee-shirt for $15 to get in for free thie evening and almost ALL WEDNESDAY shows - whether you attend with our group or on your own.  Such a deal!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, because I bring in a lot of business to the club, they periodically toss me some freebie tickets to the weekend shows.  I have a bunch of tickets for this weekend, but depending upon the weather and free concerts status, going kayaking, etc., have yet to ascertain to which show.  The weekend headliner is a VERY funny guy - Alonso Bodden, from Comedy Central's &amp;quot;Last Comic Standing&amp;quot;.  (Sometimes the weekend headliner performs on Wednesdays, sometimes not.  It'll be a different comic this evening).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let me know if you'd like to join us this evening and/or for the weekend show (limited # of free tickets available).  The sooner, the better!  If so, please share your phone number, especially cell#, so we can coordinate info, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Rob&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Pudney&lt;br /&gt;live in Meriden / work in Bloomfield&lt;br /&gt;rep06450@cox.net&lt;br /&gt;C: (860) 690-9595&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182552072000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entertainment CT VIP Clubbers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Entertainment-CT</urlname><id>530639</id><group_lat>41.6899986267</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7300033569</group_lon><name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club Music Theatre Golf Friends</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182363608000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rob's Wacky Wednesday - Funny Bone Comedy Club</name><id>5913834</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182378600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Entertainment-CT/events/5913834/</event_url></item>