<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>(Route 10)</address_2><address_1>450 East Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06062</zip><lat>41.652217</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(860) 410-1829</phone><name>Sushi Red</name><city>Plainville</city><id>1211068</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.869848</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Okay...I think I finally picked a date for this!  Sorry about the delay and indecision.  This event is now going to be on a Friday and at a later time.  There is a great coffeehouse called Jitters right down the road from Sushi Red.  Jitters has live music on Friday and Saturday nights.  I thought that it night be a fun option for people to head over there after dinner, if they choose...to hear some music and have some great dessert (yes, Jitters has ice cream...but you have to eat some amazing pie with it, sorry...). Check out Jitters here...there is a $5.00 cover...music usually starts around 8:30 and goes until 11. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jittersclub.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.jittersclu...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;-----------------------------------------------------------  &lt;br /&gt;Last week, on the way home, I had the great pleasure of stopping by Sushi Red on Rt. 10 (East Street which becomes Queen Street) in Plainville.  I had called earlier, and the man on the phone asked me to come in and talk to him about our group and what kind of accommodations we would need.  I found this to be notable and respectable, since most restaurants jump at the chance to serve a big group, no matter what.  This first impression of the man, who turned out to be Hong, the owner and head sushi chef at Sushi Red, proved to be very accurate.  He sat me down, offered me green tea, and talked to me about our group and his food.  After I explained a bit about us, he said that he would like us to come and &amp;quot;enjoy his sushi offerings.&amp;quot;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sushi Red is an immaculate, new, cozy, simple restaurant.  I think we will have an amazing semi-private experience there.  Hong and his assistant will be on hand to prepare lots of yummy rolls for us.  He asks only that we be patient, that they may be a little slow in preparing such a big order.  He seemed pleased when I explained how we tend to place our orders in &amp;quot;rounds.&amp;quot;  The rolls on the menu look simple but delicious...one example is the &amp;quot;Sweet Roll&amp;quot; - Tamago, Avocado, and Crab Meat Roll topped with shrimp.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One note:  I am not sure that alcohol is served at Sushi Red, but I will find out and let you know.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you can make it!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kelly   &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kelly S</member_name><member_id>2538500</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272236367000</updated><rating><average>4.32999992371</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Sushi Lovers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sushi-ct</urlname><id>900540</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>New Haven County Sushi Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1268014499000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Color Sushi Red!</name><id>12812686</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1270855800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sushi-ct/events/12812686/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/6/c/global_7885132.jpeg</photo_url></item>