<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 212 Second Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03102</zip><lat>42.980226</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rail Trail and Piscatauog River Park</name><city>Manchester</city><id>971255</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.471628</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A new section of the rail trail that goes along the Piscataquog River Park on the west side of the Piscataquog River has been newly constructed and is now walkable.  Now one can walk along the Merrimack River on the east side from Sundeen Ave near the Queen City Bridge to the Fisher Cat Stadium and if one crosses the Hands Across the Merrimack River pedestrian bridge one can now walk from 2nd St all the way to the Nazaire Biron Bridge on Kelly Street by the West Side Ice Arena.  Then if one crosses over to the east side of the Piscataquog River by anotherf foot bridge one can follow the rail trail into the center of Goffstown Village.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Starting at 2nd St we can hike along the trail in which ever direction (east or west) strikes our fancy. There are parts of the trail you might want to leash your dog and other parts where the dog can go off leash if you want.  I particularly like the parts of the rail trail that go along the water.  There are places where the water dogs can get near the banks of the Piscataquog River not that far from the rail trail and some places might be safe for the dogs to get wet and others not depending on the strength of the current.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new trail section makes parts of the Piscataquog River Park way more accesible than it was before. Which ever parts of the trail we decided to walk we would be retracing our steps along the same trail to get back to the cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a good sized parking lot at 212 Second St. on the east side of the street which is opposite the Second St. Laudromat.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a maroon Chevy van with the NH license plate 237  1623 and 2 dogs.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244070801000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243550476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rail Trail and Piscataquog River Park  </name><id>10517743</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1243778400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/10517743/</event_url></item>