<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>46 Great Hollow Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06796</zip><lat>41.829121</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(800) 895 5222</phone><name>Mohawk Mount Ski Resort</name><city>West Cornwall</city><id>817635</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.322932</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hey Gang!&lt;br /&gt;    Tired of not getting to do a face-plant into a snowbank at happy hours? Then lets try something a little different: snowboarding! (Or skiing.) Mohawk Mountain in West Cornwall has some good day packages. If you've never tried it, no problem, neither have I! Other members joining us are veterans, so you can come with me to the beginner trails or take on the expert slopes with them. Gigi was kind enough to provide the following details and advice:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The all morning package runs from 8:30-6.  &lt;br /&gt;The &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;beginner package is $65&lt;/span&gt;, which includes equipment, a 1.5hr lesson, and access to beginner slopes.  &lt;br /&gt;The &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;non-beginner package is $86&lt;/span&gt; , and includes equipment, a 1.5 hour non-beginner lesson, and access to all slopes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Update: the good point was raised that &lt;span style="color: red"&gt;skiing is also available&lt;/span&gt; for those who'd rather do that. The above rates apply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;We'll arrive at 9:00 and take the 11:00 lesson&lt;/span&gt; (both beginner and non-beginner lessons occur at the same time). Why two hours before the lesson? It takes a while to get your gear rented and on, and you'll get much more out of your lesson if you've at least started to feel out what it's like to stand, slide, and get back up when you fall (which will be OFTEN and amazingly discombobulating at first).  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For people who own their own equipment, you can just opt for a lift ticket: $50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Its about a 1.5 hour drive from New Haven, so try to leave around 7:00 a.m. to account for any stops needed - coffee, gas, more coffee, etc. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Full details about the resort are available at &lt;a href="http://www.mohawkmtn.com/CMX/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mohawkmtn....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm really excited about this! See you there!&lt;br /&gt;-Neil&lt;br /&gt;1-203-645-2008&lt;br /&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1264428226000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263403026000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Snowboarding (or skiing) novice or expert: $65/$86 = equipment, lesson, lift tix</name><id>12308903</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1264255200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/12308903/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/4/a/global_351658.jpeg</photo_url></item>