<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Hosts:&lt;/b&gt; Natasha Kapij, School of Passion,&lt;br /&gt;Aaron Cantor, yoga artist and&lt;br /&gt;The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group &lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A special THANKS to Natasha Kapij&lt;/b&gt;, creative &amp;amp; passionate BostonLOA member, for organizing this celebration!.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://lawofattraction.meetup.com/139/members/4901904/"&gt;http://lawofattractio...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 7 PM - 1 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP only if you are definitely coming!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're &amp;quot;attracting&amp;quot; over 150+ like-hearted, passionate people together from different communities!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;In the spirit of the ancient Greek symposium, we welcome you to join us for a true feast for body, mind and soul. Come meet great people, sample delicious food, be uplifted by enlightening ideas, get a massage, watch dazzling performances, listen to amazing live music, and dance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sound great? Because it is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The celebration is kicked off with a presentation by &lt;b&gt;Yasuhiko Genku Kimura&lt;/b&gt; on &lt;b&gt;cultivating passion, vision, and the mastery of life through the creative act of &amp;quot;authentic thinking&amp;quot;&lt;/b&gt;.  Yasuhiko creates &amp;amp; leads transformational programs around the world using his Zen-like Socratic method of philosophical inquiry.  He is widely recognized for his unique ability to integrate advanced Western scientific thought with intuitive Eastern spiritual insight to bring about radical and lasting transformation in individuals and organizations. His numerous writings and seminars are acclaimed for their originality and spiritual depth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yasuhiko is a transhumanist philosopher, an ordained Zen Buddhist priest &amp;amp; scholar.  He is considered one of the most original, visionary thinkers in the field of integral and evolutionary philosophy.  He is a creator and leader of transformational programs; consultant-advisor to leaders in business, science, and cultural organizations.  ( www.via-visioninaction.org )&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is an amazing opportunity for us all to meet an enlightening and inspiring visionary and thinker who has dedicated his life to creating heaven on earth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll enjoy &amp;amp; participate in various &lt;b&gt;Performances&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;*A demonstration by master yogic artist, Aaron Cantor&lt;br /&gt;*The hypnotic rhythms of the &amp;quot;hang drum' an amazing instrument that is part sound sculpture, part Tibetan singing bowl, part steal drum, part tabla and totally amazing by Ehssan.&lt;br /&gt;*Flamenco Guitar with Juanito Pascal and Anish Shaw.&lt;br /&gt;*Zen sword demonstration by martial artist, Ben Booth.&lt;br /&gt;*Zumba performance and &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;yes...bring your dancing feet...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; led by Selio Silva.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***************************************************************************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Parking:&lt;/b&gt; Please find parking anywhere along streets, except along the railroad.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Chew-Hoong</member_name><member_id>3101506</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1233886396000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>47</yes_rsvp_count><created>1233027241000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Join us for a Celebration of Passion, Vision and Mastery of Life</name><id>9609383</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1233360000000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/9609383/</event_url></item>