<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>300 Summit Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.746391</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Cinestudio at Trinity College</name><city>Hartford</city><id>4861412</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.692970</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If you have to see two films this year (the first being the The Hobbit) this is the movie to see. Made for less than $100,000 this film won both at Sundance and at Cannes Film festivals. With 2 non-professional actors, this is one of the best films of the year. And it may not win an Award at the Oscars because the two main actors aren't part of the Screen Actors Guild!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;(US, 2012) Directed by Benh Zeitlin. Screenplay by Lucy Alibar and Benh Zeitlin, based on the play by Lucy Alibar. Cast: Quvenzhané Wallis, Dwight Henry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Armed with a 16mm camera and a limited budget, a New Orleans collective of filmmakers took off for a Louisiana bayou to make a movie (with non-professional actors Quvenzhané Wallis and Dwight Henry) about a 6-year-old girl named Hushpuppy and her father Wink, living on the economic edge. What they came back with is homegrown magic realism and two astonishing performances - along with the Grand Jury Prize at Sundance and the Cannes Film Festival prize for Best First Film. Much of the enchantment springs from Hushpuppy, a fiercely imaginative child whose spirit is alive with the beauty - and dangers - of the natural world. “For all of its mystical elements, it is a coming-of-age story, anchored by one of the most affecting young performers in recent memory - consider Quvenzhané an early lock for a Best Actress nomination at the next Academy Awards.” Peter Howell, Globe and Mail 93 min. &lt;a href="http://www.welcometothebathtub.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.welcometothebathtub.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be in the lobby.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bill</member_name><member_id>4262367</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350570571000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Indie Film Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>indiefilm-235</urlname><id>1188113</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Beyond the Multiplex: Hartford's Indie and Foreign Film fans</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350266338000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Beasts of the Southern Wild</name><id>86995282</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350515700000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/indiefilm-235/events/86995282/</event_url></item>