<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I know that most of you are very interested in getting out on the water and getting up-close to boats. So rather than an official meetup for June, I want to let you know about a free sailing event and a chance to see world-class racers first hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over Memorial Day weekend, Boston Sailing Center will offer free sailing trips around Boston Harbor. No experience is necessary and all ages are welcome. The Center is located on a converted Louisiana riverboat docked at Lewis Wharf, a short walk from Faneuil Hall Marketplace and the Aquarium T station (Blue Line). For details, visit: &lt;a href="http://www.bostonsailingcenter.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonsail...&lt;/a&gt;. Of course (caution, shameless plug ahead), if you want to take sailing lessons or get a sailing membership, I suggest SailTime Boston and sister-school Black Rock Sailing School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Transat, a single-handed race across the Atlantic from Plymouth England to Boston, is scheduled to finish in Boston on Friday night. The boats will be docked at Rowes Wharf over the weekend. I imagine that you will be able to get very close to the boats, and some may even be open for boarding and skippers may eb on-hand. This is a rare chance to see an Open 60 up-close; I wouldn't pass it up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No RSVPs necessary. Enjoy!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 16327</member_name><member_id>16327</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1211810867000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Boston Sailing Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-sailing</urlname><id>135687</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Sailing Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1210158842000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Boston Sailing June Meeting</name><id>7890264</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211637600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-sailing/events/7890264/</event_url></item>