<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;So, are you ready to meet your dance partner ?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Laurent is inviting you to a summer (potluck) at Chaffinch Island Park, Guilford &lt;br /&gt;Please bring a dish of your choice or beverage. Indicate what you are bringing when you RSVP. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;Party starts at 1:30 pm until ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Join us for a relaxed afternoon of socializing and meeting new people! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Feel free to bring family, friends and any items that you might think could add to the fun, such as:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;• Frisbee &lt;br /&gt;• Badminton/Volleyball equipment &lt;br /&gt;• Cribbage/Cards &lt;br /&gt;• Wiffleball &lt;br /&gt;• Fishing Gear/Crab Nets&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music will be available too!~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions &lt;br /&gt;From the East: Take I-95 South to exit 58. Turn left off the exit onto Route 77 South (Church Street). Travel south on Route 77 for approximately 0.8 miles to the center of Guilford. Turn right onto Broad Street and then take a quick left onto Whitfield Street driving around the Guilford Town Green. Continue south on Whitfield Street for approximately 0.2 miles. Turn right onto Route 146 (Water Street) and travel approximately 1 mile. Turn a slight left onto Mulberry Point Road. Travel on Mulberry Point Road for approximately 0.5 miles. Turn left onto Chaffinch Island Road. Travel approximately 0.7 miles to the end of Chaffinch Island Road where Chaffinch Island Park is located. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the West: Take I-95 North to exit 58. Travel for approximately 0.3 miles and turn right off the exit onto Route 77 South (Church Street). Travel south on Route 77 for approximately 0.8 mile to the center of Guilford. Turn right onto Broad Street and then take a quick left onto Whitfield Street driving around the Guilford Town Green. Continue south on Whitfield Street for approximately 0.2 miles. Turn right onto Route 146 (Water Street) and travel approximately 1 mile. Turn a slight left onto Mulberry Point Road. Travel on Mulberry Point Road for approximately 0.5 miles. Turn left onto Chaffinch Island Road. Travel approximately 0.7 miles to the end of Chaffinch Island Road where Chaffinch Island Park is located.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Laurent Mullen</member_name><member_id>3427645</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283090939000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Ballroom Dancers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BallroomDanceClassCT</urlname><id>696005</id><group_lat>41.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8000030518</group_lon><name>Branford Ballroom Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281458570000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Summer (potluck) Picnic</name><id>14379280</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283014800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BallroomDanceClassCT/events/14379280/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/0/4/global_14013844.jpeg</photo_url></item>