<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Greetings newcomers group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If anyone is in town during the Thanksgiving week and wants an opportunity to socialize, read on. If you are traveling home and need an excuse to return to Providence a day early, read on. Otherwise, we'll see you on the other side of T-day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Several of us will be getting together informallly a few times this week. If you are around and want to join in, please rsvp and/or email me for my cell phone so you can find out where we are at the moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a tentative itinerary:&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday: Wing Night at the Abbey every week&lt;br /&gt;it gets crowded and wings sometimes sell out. I might stop in for a drink around 8 or 9.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday: &lt;br /&gt;8-10 Scurvy Dog, 1718 Westminster Street, &lt;a href="http://scurvydogbar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://scurvydogbar.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;possible dj at some point while we are there, but not sure when it starts&lt;br /&gt;10:30 - ? @201 Westminster where every Wednesday is &amp;quot;brit pop, indie, and 80's classics&amp;quot; so get your dance on with me and Edd!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday:&lt;br /&gt;Avery and E&amp;amp;O over on the west side tucked into the neighborhood behind Julian's on Broadway.&lt;br /&gt;Probably hit Avery first then walk to E&amp;amp;O, great neighborhood gems. Both close at midnight so maybe move on to Lily Marlene's on Atwells (a short drive) or Julian's (a quick walk might be better).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday:&lt;br /&gt;no plans yet, but who wants to get together? Maybe hit Wild Colonial or Snookers to play some pool or darts? Or Local 121 with a dj and dance floor after 11. Post a comment on this event meetup page for ideas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've been working lots of weekends lately so ready for some downtime and time out on the town without having to get up early the next day!! &lt;br /&gt;Happy Thanksgiving everyone!&lt;br /&gt;- val&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>7</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1259370777000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1258904759000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Thanksgiving week - evening socializing opportunities</name><id>11931266</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1259197200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/11931266/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/3/1/global_9136913.jpeg</photo_url></item>