<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Under the joint auspices of Boston Atheists and Skepchick.org, several of our Boston Atheists have decided to host a &amp;quot;ladies' night&amp;quot; as a chance for women atheists, skeptics and freethinkers to gather together for comaraderie and conversation. Having noticed that, in general, more men tend to attend Atheist meetings, they have decided to join forces with Skepchick.org to get more women atheists and skeptics out in numbers. That will provide them with the opportunity to discuss issues related specifically to women and atheism. It is not, however, intended to be a splinter group or to encourage gender separation; on the contrary, they hope this meeting will encourage more women to attend the regular Boston Atheist meetings in greater numbers! The first such event will be held at BA member Danielle's house. There'll be wine, snacks and desserts. Feel free to bring any interesting skeptic / atheist reading matter along. Since this is the first meeting of its kind, we can discuss what people would like to get out of future ladies' nights. If you have any questions, get in touch with one of the organizers, Nora, 857-221-2140, and Danielle, 973-464-8055. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nora asks that those interested in attending please sign up on the Meetup site or send an email to delaney_nora@yahoo.com so we can gauge numbers.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Your hosts are Danielle and Nora.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1235658853000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1201300639000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BA Ladies Night w/ the Skepchicks</name><id>7196133</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1201824000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/7196133/</event_url></item>