<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1846 Daniel Webster Highway</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03106</zip><lat>43.106395</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Heads Pond Hooksett</name><city>Hooksett</city><id>2686101</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449236</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Head Pond Rail Trail in Hooksett is a flat, wide trail most of the way. . There are a few places off trail along the way the dogs can access the water. There is a pond at the turn around point where the dogs can swim if it isn't iced over. &amp;nbsp;As this is a line hike (you come back the exact same way) on a easy to follow mostly straight trail any one getting to cold or tired before we reach the turn around point can easily find their way back to the parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Be aware that the third house down the trail has 2 vicious dogs with an electric fence but they can reach within 2 feet of the trail. &amp;nbsp;Fortunately that house is very near the start of the hike and won't take long to get past&amp;nbsp;if the dogs are outside. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This should be an easy hike for most people unless walking 4 miles is an issue for you. &amp;nbsp;Snow on the ground would make walking take more effort unless it is packed down. &amp;nbsp;If it is packed down it could be slippery at times. &amp;nbsp;In that case traction devices for your footwear and/or hiking poles could help prevent you from falling. &amp;nbsp;This trail is hiked year round.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/c/2/d/event_41959501.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>The parking lot for the trail head is at the intersection of Rte. 3 (Hooksett Rd.) and Post Rd near (almost opposite) Green's Marine</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1326642350000</updated><rating><average>4.78000020981</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>21</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325456959000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Head Pond - Rail Trail Line Hike  (2 miles 1 way - 4 miles round trip)</name><id>46183902</id><headcount>23</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1325948400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/46183902/</event_url></item>