<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>395 Concord Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02478</zip><lat>42.395687</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>National Association for Armenian Studies &amp; Research</name><city>Belmont</city><id>9705102</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.173843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jerry Lembcke is Associate Professor of Sociology at College of the Holy Cross in Worcester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building on focused sets of critical studies on political and cultural properties of PTSD as a socially constructed category, this presentation identifies how art, photography, silent film and later Hollywood film played roles in their respective time periods to write and rewrite the tangled story of military experience, masculinity, medical practice, and political and popular culture. This presentation makes clear that the reality of PTSD is far greater than that given by medical science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As this is the usual weekly Sunday service for Ethical Society of Boston, the lecture will be preceded by organizational announcements and a live musical performance, and followed by additional announcements, another musical performance, and a question-and-answer period. Anyone is welcome to attend, to hear the talk, enjoy refreshments, and meet people in the Ethical Society. There is no charge to attend, though visitors are invited to make a cash donation which helps to underwrite the costs involved with facility rental and the payment of speakers and musicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NAASR building is easily accessible by commuter rail -- it faces the Belmon commuter rail stop! -- as well as by car and bus. Parking can be found in the lot behind the building, in the adjacent lots, and on the street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information about ESB can be found at www.meetup.com/Ethical-Society-of-Boston/ and &lt;a href="http://bostonethical.org" class="linkified"&gt;http://bostonethical.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1359308040000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359205787000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ethical Society: A Talk on Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder by Jerry Lembcke</name><id>101467992</id><duration>7200000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1359300600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/101467992/</event_url></item>