<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>362 Chandler St, 5</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01602</zip><lat>42.262569</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-757-0411 </phone><name>The Q</name><city>Worcester</city><id>934545</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.829240</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>On Saturday April 25 The Q is hosting a vegan cupcake-on-a-string eating contest and cookie decorating. They're launching their new line of all-vegan, all-organic, all-fair-trade cupcakes and cookies. From now on, all of the The Q's baked goods are vegan and awesome. The yummy treats come fresh-baked from Worcester's own vegan bakery, Barely Legal Treats. Every month The Q features a new special cupcake and special cookie, in addition to their normal offerings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the Saturday kick-off event we will have the biggest selection of cupcakes and cookies yet. You can sample 10 different kinds of vegan cupcakes and 6 different kinds of cookies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Barely Legal is not your average bakery, so don't expect an average eating contest. Unlike other eating contests, you don't win by cramming your face full of cupcakes. The cupcakes are suspended from a string and hung from the ceiling. Contestants must hold their hands behind their backs and attempt to eat their cupcake fastest. The first person to finish a cupcake wins the round.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The cookie decorating is family friendly and will take place from 3pm-5pm. This is not a contest, everyone is a winner. Barely Legal will also have cupcake cookbooks and hip Barely Legal aprons and t-shirts for sale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Schedule for April 25:&lt;br /&gt;3pm Cookie Decorating&lt;br /&gt;4pm sharp cupcake eating contest begins&lt;br /&gt;6pm-Late live music and lots of yummy vegan cupcakes, cookies, etc&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1241278622000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1240001905000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Q is kicking off their All-Vegan baked goods with fun and more!</name><id>10208695</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1240686000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/10208695/</event_url></item>