<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Cambridgeside Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02141</zip><lat>42.367101</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617)621-8666</phone><name>Cambridgeside Galleria</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1184473</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.076376</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/1/8/6/event_236569542.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Hi Everyone, &lt;br /&gt;

 With the warm weather finally here, we are pleased to host a joint event with Beantown Cornhole Meetup group. This event is going to be so much fun!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cornhole, also known as (Bags, Baggo, or Bean Bag Toss) is becoming one of the best games to play outdoors. It is becoming a staple at Gillette stadium while tailgating. &lt;br /&gt;

 This Saturday, on the Roof deck of the Galleria Mall, we are going to host a one of a kind Cornhole tournament. Teams of 2, (pick out a cool team name) will compete to become Boston's Cornhole Champ. Winner's will win cash, prizes, and a Heavyweight Champion Belt!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During play, there will be a live band, and a DJ to keep us entertained during the matches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't have a partner, don't worry. We can find you a partner of a fellow meet-up member. All we ask is that you do not RSVP as yes....if you cannot attend ,since there will be a limit to the amount of teams that can play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is all for a non-profit organization that desperately needs to raise funds. The cost was originally $80 per team, however I was able to get members of Social Fun and Beantown Cornhole 50% off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, for $20 per person/ $40 per team you can play in the tournament, enjoy the music, meet new people, eat BBQ, and also enjoy FREE Samual Adams beer. (limit 3 beers per person). If you are not sold yet, let me not forget to tell you that you will get free parking to come to the event. Everyone who registers will get a free parking voucher so that your cost to park is $0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food-Beer-Social Fun-Live Band-DJ-Cash &amp;amp; other prizes- ALL while helping a great cause....for only $20 per person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the people are playing cornhole are new to the game, so don't think that you don't have a chance at winning. The rules will be explained, and it is as easy as throwing a beanbag, hoping to get it in a hole. That's it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't want to play, just come for the fun. You can sign up as a spectator only, but there won't be free beer to those people, since the cost is less to just watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For More details of the event, and to sign up....go to &lt;a href="http://www.beantowncornhole.com/tournaments" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.beantowncornhole.com/tournaments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tournament starts at 1:00 PM, but if you are going to play, you need to get there early to sign in. You can get there as early as 12:00 to sign in and practice your game. On the 2nd floor of the Galleria Mall, there will be a welcome table outside of the TJ Maxx store. They will sign you in, and send you up to the rooftop! This is going to be a unique experience to play a tournament on a rooftop in the middle of Boston!!! Don't miss out.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donnie</member_name><member_id>6998244</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368907978000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Members</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>SocialFun</urlname><id>950281</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>Social Fun</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368751357000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Rooftop Charity Cornhole Tournament and BBQ, and More!!!</name><id>119796382</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368896400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SocialFun/events/119796382/</event_url></item>