<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Roland Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.381300</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Crosby Whistle Stop</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>1300937</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.078300</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcT_WFs_gPKWz0xrbkoWW3S3hBb2Iwxd_nqnlRT_p5Ut561orW9_kQ" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Salsa Social is the perfect opportunity to meet and dance salsa with people from all over. Dancers and non-dancers come to share the dance floor with you. Whether you are a beginner or a performer level dancer it is the perfect occasion to do what you are so passionate about, dance. Tambó Salsa Social was created for that purpose. We provide the ingredients, you provide the passion and together see the funky results. This Salsa Social is also the best place to practice your moves, meet new dancers, find new friends, and learn more about the Boston Salsa Community events. Also, from time to time enjoy great performances by dance companies from all over the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SCHEDULE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn2.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTVLUhsVdky5pTbdFR6dUmD1_QgJqjnu-m0V683MjBM-pE3a94e1A" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lesson at 6pm with Metamovements For Beginners: Intro to Salsa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Experienced Dancers: You CHOOSE from... Cuban Salsa Rueda OR Spinning &amp;amp; Styling for Men &amp;amp; Women (on1 &amp;amp; on2) - Dance 'til 10pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Prices &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cover is $14 with salsa lesson $10 social only&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;How to find us&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will try to have a reserved table and so if you want to arrive later I will be there. And or I will have a sign indicating Tambo Salsa Social Meetup!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Questions/Concerns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://img.webring.com/globe1.png" alt="Dancers" width="150" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 0px 4px 0px 0px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not hesitate to send me your questions/comments/concerns. I am happy to answer all matter of meetup or salsa related questions as best I can and if I can't I will find someone who can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look forward to meeting all of you! Salsa party over here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Fundraising Information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSO77vewgLiEzLYD2W67tw2MsnH2nM_dCnn7XzZVdKkxcz2pfuN" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; Please note, below is the fundraising information that was sent to Salsa Community Leaders and is included for your help and support, please pass the word along: Hello Salsa Community Leaders! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

I am writing to let you know about an emergency fundraiser we are doing on Feb 16 at the Tambo Social with DJ Hernan &amp;amp; Jose Masso to support Jorge Arce &amp;amp; his daughter Charmaine Santiago Galdon.  I would like to personally invite you to attend as it will be a unique event, focused on celebrating the Afro-Caribbean roots of our dance, as well as a time to support two amazing artists who need our help. I would also like to request any type of donation you would be willing to make to our Silent Auction or Raffle.  We are hoping to have an assortment of private lessons, group classes, club passes, restaurant gift certificates, and other items that could appeal to dancers. Your support will be greatly appreciated. In addition to the awesome social dancing you've come to expect at Tambo, there will be much more!  Guest DJ Saoko will be in the house and, the event will include a percussion corner, so please bring your instruments and join Jorge there!  It will also feature an Afro-Caribbean dance lesson, and a Bomba Show with Jorge, Ozzy, Bomba Sankofa and other artists! &lt;strong&gt;WHY A FUNDRAISER?&lt;/strong&gt; In case you haven't already heard, Charmaine (Latin Dance Instructor &amp;amp; Youth Arts Coordinator at IBA) suffered an accident on January 20, 2013 which left her with severe head trauma.  She has been unconscious, under 24 hour supervision in the ICU since that time.  A recent college grad, she has dedicated her life to continuing her father's mission:  to celebrate Afro-Caribbean Culture, and share it with youth and the community.  She has touched hundreds of young people, and we want to support her recovery so she can continue her amazing work. Charmaine is the daughter of one of Boston's first salsa community leaders:  Jorge Arce. If you don't remember him, it's probably because he was active before your time as a salsero here.  He is a renowned Puerto Rican musician, dancer, actor and cultural historian who was influential in building our wonderful community between the years of 1985 and 2001.  He cared deeply about teaching students the history, and the essential connections between the music and the dance.  He also believed strongly in collaboration over competition, and the idea that we could only build a truly amazing Salsa Community in Boston by working together.  He willingly shared his knowledge, time, passion and even his following with other instructors, dancers and musicians in pursuit of that goal.  Living in Puerto Rico from 2001-2011, most of the newer faces in our community may not know that he was one of the founders who set us in this unique direction for which we are known as a city. When Jorge returned in 2011, he was looking forward to reconnecting to our community, and sharing his wealth of knowledge of Afro-Caribbean dance, music and culture with us. But since that time he has had a series of health crises that have kept him away:  he has gone thru quadruple by-pass heart surgery, major hernia surgery, and now the emergency hospitalization of his daughter. I would be grateful for any support that you can give, through spreading the word to your networks, to helping me locate donations, to your presence at the event.  Here are the links to FB and website. &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/150326851788860/?fref=ts" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/150326851788860/?fref=ts&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://metamovements.com/details/?id=tambosocial-afrocaribbean-16feb13a" target="_blank"&gt;http://metamovements.com/details/?id=tambosocial-afrocaribbean-16feb13a&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading and for your support!&lt;/p&gt;
Hugs, Anara 
&lt;p&gt;Lonzell&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will try to have a reserved table and so if you want to arrive later I will be there.  And or I will have a sign indicating Tambo Salsa Social Meetup!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lonzell Hall</member_name><member_id>55984162</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1361152720000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Salsa Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonsalsa</urlname><id>278345</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston &amp; Cambridge Salsa Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359475435000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tambo Salsa Social! **** Please read the fundraising info at the end! ****</name><id>101963692</id><duration>14400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1361055600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonsalsa/events/101963692/</event_url></item>