<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>5 Park Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02122</zip><lat>42.302662</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Paulist Center &amp; Chapel</name><city>Boston</city><id>11047352</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.052902</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Faitheist: How an Atheist Found Common Ground with the Religious - January Luncheon w/ Chris Stedman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TO REGISTER, please visit &lt;a href="http://faitheistluncheon.eventbrite.com" class="linkified"&gt;http://faitheistluncheon.eventbrite.com&lt;/a&gt;, call 617-969-9404, or email admin@massbible.org by Tuesday, January 22. A $15 donation is suggested to help cover the cost of food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the event description at www.massbible.org/chris-stedman-luncheon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stunning popularity of the "New Atheist" movement— whose most famous spokesmen include Richard Dawkins,  Sam Harris, and the late Christopher Hitchens—speaks to  both the growing ranks of atheists as well as the  widespread, vehement disdain for religion among many of  them. In Faitheist, Chris Stedman tells his own story to  challenge the orthodoxies of this movement and make a  passionate argument that atheists should engage religious  diversity respectfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Becoming aware of injustice, and craving community,  Stedman became a "born-again" Christian in late  childhood. The idea of a community bound by God's love—a love that was undeserved, unending, and guaranteed—captivated him. It was, he writes, a place to belong, and a  framework for making sense of suffering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Stedman's religious community did not embody this idea of God's love: they were  staunchly homophobic at a time when he was slowly coming to realize that he was gay.  The great suffering this caused him might have turned Stedman into a life-long New  Atheist. But over time he came to know more open- minded Christians, and his interest in service work  brought him into contact with people from a wide  variety of religious backgrounds. His own religious  beliefs might have fallen away, but his desire to  change the world for the better remained. Disdain and  hostility towards religion was holding him back from  engaging in meaningful work with people of faith.  And it was keeping him from full relationships with  them—the kinds of relationships that break down  intolerance and improve the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stedman draws on his work organizing interfaith and  secular communities, his academic study of religion,  and his own experiences to argue for the necessity of  bridging the growing chasm between atheists and the religious. As someone who has stood on both sides of  the divide, Stedman is uniquely positioned to present a way for atheists and the religious  to find common ground and work together to make this world—the one world we can all  agree on—a better place.Chris Stedman is the Assistant Humanist Chaplain at Harvard University and the Values  in Action Coordinator for the Humanist Community at Harvard (where he was previously  the inaugural Interfaith and Community Service Fellow). He is also the Emeritus  Managing Director of State of Formation at theJournal  of Inter-Religious Dialogue and founder of the first blog  dedicated to exploring atheist-interfaith engagement,  NonProphet Status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE BIO &lt;br /&gt;

Chris Stedman is the Assistant Humanist Chaplain at Harvard University and the Values  in Action Coordinator for the Humanist Community at Harvard (where he was previously  the inaugural Interfaith and Community Service Fellow). He is also the Emeritus  Managing Director of State of Formation at theJournal  of Inter-Religious Dialogue and founder of the first blog  dedicated to exploring atheist-interfaith engagement,  NonProphet Status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris received an MA in Religion from Meadville  Lombard Theological School at the University of  Chicago, for which he was awarded the Billings Prize  for Most Outstanding Scholastic Achievement. A  graduate of Augsburg College with a summa cum laude  B.A. in Religion, Chris writes for Huffington Post Gay  Voices, Huffington Post Religion, The Washington Post  On Faith, Religion Dispatches, Relevant, and more.  Previously a Content Developer and Adjunct Trainer for Interfaith Youth Core, Chris is an atheist working to  foster positive and productive dialogue and  collaborative action between faith communities and the nonreligious. He speaks on this  topic across the United States and around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2011, the Huffington Post listed  Chris's work as one of the Top 11  Religion Stories of the year and named  him one of the top interfaith activists on Twitter, Religion Dispatches listed him  at #5 in a list of the Top 10 Peacemakers  in the Science-Religion wars, and  the University of Oregon Alliance of  Happy Atheists recognized his work with  their first annual Happy Heathen! Award.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris served on the initial Leadership Team of the Common Ground Campaign, a  coalition of young people who stood up in response to the wave of anti-Muslim rhetoric  and violence in the U.S. surrounding the Park51 controversy, and continues to advise it in its current form, Groundswell. He also sits on the Board of Directors of the interfaith  global development organization World Faith and is an advisor to the Foundation  Beyond Belief's "Challenge the Gap" charitable initiative. Portland, Oregon's Just Out called his work "brilliant" and labeled him an "emerging... vibrant  and youthful queer voice for the secular humanist movement.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1358966704000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357672923000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name> Luncheon and talk by Chris Stedman at Paulist Center</name><id>98590162</id><duration>5400000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1358960400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/98590162/</event_url></item>