<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;IT'S ANOTHER FUN IN THE SUN DAY AT THE JULY PUG SUNDAY MEETUP!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us for the July Sunday meetup at Assistant Organizer Sharon's home in Carver - where Buford, Millie, and Max hang out. This is our favorite location - a quiet, rural side street with plenty of parking, a HUGE fenced yard, plenty of chairs, and lots and lots of flat grassy green space to run and run and run!  Don't worry about your dog overheating.  There is PLENTY of shade, and Sharon puts out a kiddie pool and a hose to cool off our Pugs' outsides, as well as plenty of bowls of water to cool off their insides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember that your host provides the soft drinks and paperware for each meetup, but we count on our members to bring the snacks. Feel free to bring snacks for the Pugs, but try to bring soft snacks so that Clovis can have some too! If you are coming to your first meetup, please be sure to let us know, so we can introduce you to everyone and make you and your Puggies feel welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WOULD YOU LIKE TO HOST A MEETUP?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please let your organizer know! We try to schedule the meetups for the 2012 calendar far enough in advance so that you can plan your Puggies' social calendar! Please note that most of the Sunday meetups take place at at Assistant Organizer Sharon's home in Carver - where Buford, Millie, and Max hang out - and an occasional Saturday Meetup takes place at your Organizer Charlotte Creeley's home in Brockton - at Casa Clovis and Cletus. However, we are always delighted to change the venue when someone else wants to host a meetup! For those who haven't hosted before, but would like to try, and if you do have a fenced yard large enough to accommodate anywhere from 30 to 60 Puggies and a few assorted other small breeds, please let your organizer know. We would like to give everyone a chance to host who would like to host! It's fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ABOUT THE MEETUPS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We're all responsible Pug owners here, so don't be concerned about your babies. Wherever we meet, we'll make sure to have shade and plenty of water for keeping Pugs cool. There will be soft drinks and something to snack on for the people attending! If you bring treats for the Pugs, please ONLY hand out treats around the central table where everyone can keep an eye on the dogs, DON'T FEED CLOVIS, and PLEASE BE SURE that nothing gets dropped - your organizer has a Pug (yes, that would be Clovis...) who has brain damage which makes it very difficult for him to swallow. I don't want Clovis to choke to death on a stolen treat, and I'm sure no one else does either.. Thank you for your consideration!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other small dogs are welcome, but please ask in advance if you can bring dogs other than Pugs. If you have a little Puggie roughneck on your hands, you can bring him too - but be prepared to keep an eye on him. If he starts bullying or being too rough with another dog, give him a time out until he can get himself under control. We want everyone to have fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your organizer pays $72.00 twice a year in January and July for the privilege of organizing the South of Boston Pug Meetups, and believe me, it's worth every penny for the fun we have. If you would like to help defray the costs, please make a voluntary contribution of $1.00 to Charlotte Creeley each time you attend. Remember, it's VOLUNTARY - even if I had to pay twice as much, it would be worth it for the just to see the smile on Clovis's and Cletus's faces when the Puggie meetups roll around.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte Creeley</member_name><member_id>2129718</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>shar</member_name><member_id>2833949</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343063422000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Pug People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>SouthofBostonPugs</urlname><id>226623</id><group_lat>42.0800018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South of Boston Pug Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341147975000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The South of Boston July Pug Sunday Meetup</name><id>71492522</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342980000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/SouthofBostonPugs/events/71492522/</event_url></item>