<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Davis Square</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.395359</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>Please Send Me A Message on Meet</phone><name>Davis Square</name><city>Somerville</city><id>735132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122574</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This meetup is cancelled due to lack of interest when 1 RSVP&amp;nbsp;has no photo and the other&amp;nbsp;is unrecognizable.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best way to play Honk Fest is to check out the Band Schedule on line and proceed to your favorite bands hourly. It is a special treat at 12 Noon to be in the Square and watch all of the bands converge on 7 Hills Park for the opening ceremonies. Or just show up later as there is no way to keep a group together with so much talent to catch. On Saturday, October&amp;nbsp;1 from Noon to 9pm over 25 activist street bands from around the country and beyond, perform outdoors in multiple locations in Davis Square for free. More information, schedules and updates will be available at www.honkfest.org [url=www.honkfest.org][/url] or 617-383-4665. I can not properly describe the Honk! Fest. You must go to their web site for more information. It's a long day. Arrive early, later or in the middle of the mayhem. I will be attending Honk Fest with some friends as I have since its birth. We will be taking a break for dinner at Mike's Restaurant in the heart of Davis Square. Maybe we will catch part of one of the American or National League Playoff Games too. Those who want to meetup e mail other attending Natives to meet. Fenway Frank&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Red Sox Natives</member_name><member_id>12040580</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1317489730000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Natives</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>natives</urlname><id>1098392</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Red Sox Natives</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1293595324000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Honk! Fest in Davis Square Meetup Cancelled Due to Lack of Interest.</name><id>15845465</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1317484800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/natives/events/15845465/</event_url></item>