<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Foster St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01608</zip><lat>42.265118</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 755-6800</phone><name>DCU Center</name><city>Worcester</city><id>732028</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.798937</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>WHAT: MARC protests against Ringling in Worcester.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Saturday, October 9 at 1:30pm and 5:45pm (show times are 3 &amp;amp;&lt;br /&gt;7). Each protest is an hour and a half long. We will be having a&lt;br /&gt;vegan meal at Loving Hut restaurant between shows; all are welcome to&lt;br /&gt;join us!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: Worcester DCU Center (formerly called the Centrum), 50 Foster&lt;br /&gt;Street, Worcester, MA 01608. Directions/Parking info below. If you&lt;br /&gt;need a ride or can give a ride, please let us know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RSVP/INFO: rayshick@msn.com or just show up. Signs and literature&lt;br /&gt;provided. Both demos are weather dependent---check emails day of event&lt;br /&gt;or call our cell at 978-257-7062. Be sure to take our cell number if&lt;br /&gt;you need help on the road with directions. If you need a ride or can&lt;br /&gt;share a ride, please let us know asap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHY: The Ringling Brothers and Barnum &amp;amp; Bailey circus is currently&lt;br /&gt;facing a federal investigation because it allowed a young lion to&lt;br /&gt;die in a sweltering animal train crossing the Mojave desert and then&lt;br /&gt;tried to keep key information from the government. Soon after the&lt;br /&gt;investigation was launched, a recently fired Ringling Brothers lion&lt;br /&gt;handler delivered an affidavit to Agriculture Department officials&lt;br /&gt;contending that the lion died because the boxcar he was riding in&lt;br /&gt;was extremely hot and the animal needed water. He said circus&lt;br /&gt;officials would not stop the train to cool the animal off despite&lt;br /&gt;reports by him and another handler that the 2-year-old lion, named&lt;br /&gt;Clyde, and other animals were suffering from intense heat. Frank&lt;br /&gt;Hagan, the veteran Ringling Brothers employee who wrote the&lt;br /&gt;affidavit, also said that circus lawyers told him and others&lt;br /&gt;familiar with the incident not to talk with Agriculture Department&lt;br /&gt;officials who were coming to the circus train to ask questions.&lt;br /&gt;Hagan said in the affidavit that the circus fired him soon after on&lt;br /&gt;what he contends was a pretext.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is just the latest in Ringling's long history of animal abuse.&lt;br /&gt;Ringling has been sued for alleged mistreatment, including beating&lt;br /&gt;its Asian elephants with bull hooks, constant chaining, and forcible&lt;br /&gt;separation of babies from their mothers. Evidence includes undercover&lt;br /&gt;video, testimony from former circus workers who have come forward&lt;br /&gt;about the abuse, and USDA documents. And now Peta has gone undercover&lt;br /&gt;and gotten new elephant training footage:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ringlingbeatsanimals.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ringlingbe...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DIRECTIONS/PARKING TO WORCESTER DCU CENTER (FORMERLY THE CENTRUM):&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DCU Center, 50 Foster Street, Worcester, MA 01608. This is a fairly&lt;br /&gt;big arena so you must find the main box office and other Foster&lt;br /&gt;Street entrances. Foster is perpendicular to Worcester Center&lt;br /&gt;Boulevard.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PARKING: Parking on the street in the area around the DCU Center&lt;br /&gt;(formerly called The Centrum) is usually easy and is free after 5&lt;br /&gt;and on Saturdays and Sundays. The Outlet Mall Parking Garage is&lt;br /&gt;located across the street from the main entrance of the DCU. It is on&lt;br /&gt;the corner of Foster and Main Street. Additional parking can be found&lt;br /&gt;at area lots and garages near the facility. Call on our cell if you&lt;br /&gt;need help.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Stephen Dunne</member_name><member_id>1339538</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1286752342000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-365</urlname><id>225364</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Worcester Vegan MeetUp &amp; EatUp</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286196845000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ringling Bros Circus Protest at the DCU (after Loving Hut Buffet at noon)</name><id>14992934</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1286645400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-365/events/14992934/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/5/8/global_5060136.jpeg</photo_url></item>