<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Pell Chafee Performance Center </address_2><address_1>87 Empire Street</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.821562</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(401) 351-4242</phone><name>Citizens Bank Theater</name><city>Providence </city><id>872241</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.415479</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>For this Meet-up we will head to the Citizens Bank Theater at the Pell Chafee Performing Arts Center,  87 Empire Street in Providence.  Here is a brief description of the play from the Trinity Rep website:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Director Michael Perlman has focused on Chekhov’s use of nature in this turn of the century Russian comedy about the disruptive effects of a summer gathering at a country estate run by Uncle Vanya and his niece Sonya. When the beautiful Yelena comes to visit, she creates a tangle of romantic chaos. As Uncle Vanya and the local country doctor declare their love for the married Yelena, Sonya secretly watches on, pining for a love of her own.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Uncle Vanya tells an all too familiar story: we live our lives, guests come, they cause utter destruction, and then they leave and we attempt to go back to life,” states Perlman. “Doctor Astrov asks: ‘What will people think of us in a hundred, two hundred years?’  A hundred years later, this story of one family's attempt to break out of the routine of their lives still asks us to question our own choices, and what choices we really have in life.” &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ticket Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $10. Seating is General Admission.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Each person is responsible for purchasing their own ticket.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; For reservations, please call the Trinity Rep Box Office at 401-351-4242.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: darkred"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please Note that this theater only holds 80 people and it will likely sell out early.  Please do not wait to order your tickets! I strongly recommend that you order your tickets now.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will send an e-mail including my cell phone number to all who RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;.  &lt;b&gt;Please plan to meet at the theater by 7:00 PM so we can sit together.&lt;/b&gt;  Seating is General Admission and therefore &amp;quot;first come; first served.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meet-up Logistics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be just inside the theater's main entrance at 7:00 and will be holding a small MEET-UP sign. Seating is first-come;first-served, so please be prompt so we can all sit together. When you RSVP, I will provide my cell phone number in case you're running late or get lost.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Inside front entrance holding MEET-UP Sign</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ron Correia</member_name><member_id>8033800</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272236677000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>theater lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ritheatre</urlname><id>790390</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4100036621</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Theater Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269900701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Uncle Vanya: Scenes from a Country Life</name><id>13029747</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272063600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ritheatre/events/13029747/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/b/3/global_6290483.jpeg</photo_url></item>