<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 127</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01930</zip><lat>42.623570</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Ravenswood Park</name><city>Gloucester</city><id>833086</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.665918</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Angela will lead this hike now as Victoria has flood problems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are various trails in this park, so we will determine our path the morning of the hike taking into account the weather. I have added a link to the TTOR website for Ravenswood so that you may review the trails at your convenience. Hope to see you there!  &lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/northeast-ma/ravenswood-park.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thetrustee...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore a shrouded landscape of hemlock groves, a magnolia swamp, and other trees species where you’ll find remnants of Colonial habitation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What makes Ravenswood Park a special place? &lt;br /&gt;Ravenswood Park offers 600 acres for solitude and quiet contemplation of nature. Whether you prefer to surround yourself with snow-covered hemlocks, experience spring emerging in a burst of color and aroma, or escape the summer’s heat – you’ll find a refuge here. The park is a testament to one man’s conservationist philosophy, and to all those who have cared for this special place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With 10 miles of carriage paths and trails that meander through the park, you can find plenty of room to picnic, bird watch, walk, cross-country ski, and simply appreciate the outdoors. Children love the Ledge Hill Trail – a 2-mile round-trip walk among magical-looking, fern-covered boulders. You don’t want to miss trekking to the overlook to Gloucester Harbor or traversing the boardwalk through the Great Magnolia Swamp, home to native sweetbay magnolias (Magnolia virginiana). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trails &lt;br /&gt;10 miles of trails and former carriage roads. Moderate hiking. Carriage roads are covered with dense crushed stone and are generally wheelchair accessible. We will hike for up to 2 hours  - lunch after is a possibility. I can't attend myself as I'd already volunteered for something in M'head and have to change to a later time so won't be able to do lunch also.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Subaru in the parking lot - if anyone wants a ride from Salem or M'head let me know. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Victoria &amp; her black PT Cruiser - 617-285-9385</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ange</member_name><member_id>7061103</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>19</waitlist_count><updated>1269309650000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers</urlname><id>1336846</id><group_lat>42.5</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8700027466</group_lon><name>North Shore Not Too Intense Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>16</yes_rsvp_count><created>1267716407000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ravenswood Park, Gloucester, MA</name><id>12781588</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1269093600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/North-Shore-Not-Too-Intense-Hikers/events/12781588/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/3/c/global_13071644.jpeg</photo_url></item>