<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This is a Pot Luck Dinner Event at a Geological Feature.&lt;br /&gt;Crosslisted between the kayak group and the Not-Married anymore (or never)...members group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some of you know what the &amp;quot;features&amp;quot; may be (sometimes not) and how the event may be more enjoyable than you would think, but there also tends to be lot more to the event than what is listed in the title.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pot Luck Events do have some hiking but not very far because of the stuff that has to get taken to a table or other location. There is some exploration of the feature that is an optional hike to see the entire feature..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring what you like...&lt;br /&gt;I dont always know what im bringing, its usually something on the way to the event from the store, (i will have my little portable grille) sometimes i get Hebrew National Hot dogs, sometimes Polish Killbassa, maybe this time Sweet and/or Hot Italian sausage, peppres onions and chez......soft buns too.....well maybe...dont know yet...Mmm sliced roast beef, green and red peppres, onions, a few little hot peppers cooked in olive oil on the grill, yep, good american chez on top...a philly chez steak sandwitch...??????&lt;br /&gt;Na, just teasing...but with me ya never know.... so there...&lt;br /&gt;White zinfendel, or something that looked interesting that i never had before....&lt;br /&gt;(what ever i pull out of the tray)&lt;br /&gt;belgum super dark chocolate.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;so you can use your imagination on what else to bring.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ok, Getting There:&lt;br /&gt;From Hartford, go 91 south to exit # 20 (Country Club Road),&lt;br /&gt;at the end of the ramp take a left on to Middle st just for a short distance,&lt;br /&gt;then take a left onto Country Club Road, go up the hill, cross over the highway, pass the 91n on ramp , then the first left is Miner St.&lt;br /&gt;Take that left onto Miner St.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Meriden, go 91 north to exit # 20, take a right and very first left onto MinerSt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take Miner st for 1 mile untill you get to the sharp right.&lt;br /&gt;at that right there are a few parking spots, (i guess 5or 6 cars) park so there is room for everyone else if possible, if it looks like its all full go a bit further and try to get onto the corner but pull off the road for safety..&lt;br /&gt;I will put a orange traffic cone on the road for finding us and for safety..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Mapquest, GPS, and other maps/travel in points ...use 200 Miner Street, Middletown , CT, that should get you close enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Back Up Plan:&lt;br /&gt;Dinner at AL's...details and updates listed if needed...&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Entertainment CT .com  VIP Club</member_name><member_id>5041325</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1182466864000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Connecticut Arts - Theatre Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>CT-Theatre-Group</urlname><id>326612</id><group_lat>41.7099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5599975586</group_lon><name>Connecticut Theatre Group Arts-Theater Events Group Discount</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182089522000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pot Luck Dinner at a Geological Feature, Middletown CT</name><id>5901186</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182294000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/CT-Theatre-Group/events/5901186/</event_url></item>