<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>9th anniversary of 9/11 benefit for 9/11 First Responders. All proceeds go to &lt;a href="http://fealgoodfoundation.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://fealgoodfounda...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For current list of events and details go to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://wearechange.org/91110/" target="_blank"&gt;http://wearechange.or...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is the event list as of 7/23/10. Please check above link for a more up to date schedule as the date approaches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Mark O'C&lt;br /&gt;617 652 0121&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   We encourage all who would like to attend our events to RSVP and buy tickets asap. Due to limited seating at our current venue, we will only have space for 300 persons. If we have an overwhelming response we will move venues to accommodate. We can only do this if you let us know!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 4 pm, join WeAreChange &amp;amp; The Love Police for street action at the Council on Foreign Relations, located @ 58 East 68th St. on the corner of Park Ave. (tentative)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 5 pm we will march down Park Ave. to 59th St. past Central Park S. and end at Columbus Circle. This march will end approx 7 pm. Material to hand out will be provided but we welcome others to bring material as well (please refer to code of conduct).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8:30 pm join us at INN Studios for an Activist Art Gallery and Activist Learning Seminars &amp;amp; Presentations. Artwork and Photography will be displayed by WeAreChange photographers Scott Star &amp;amp; John Long Tan, Brian Reeves of Slop Art &amp;amp; Graffiti Art by Duke and Duchess Creations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Learning seminars &amp;amp; presentations will kick-off @ 9 pm on the Main Stage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 10:15 join us for Activist Idol- inspired by PorcFest Soap Box Idol, this will give contestants the chance to rant for 1 minute straight, winner will be chosen by 3 professional bullhorning panelists and awarded a golden bullhorn as well as a chance to present their speech during our main event on Saturday evening!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then... hear what some of NYC's coolest stand-up comics are ranting about in the Truther Comedy Hour... a comedy show for the ages, for ages 18 and up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will be a party, concert and much more! Let's kick-off the weekend right. This event is open, no one will be turned away; suggested donation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;meetup rsvp &amp;amp; more details&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On Friday at 2 pm please join us at Union Square for a street action, at 4 pm we will march to Washington Square. Then we'll go to a venue for speeches and presentations, check back for a detailed schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;meetup rsvp &amp;amp; more details  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8 am sharp we will meet on Vessey St. against the cemetery fence off Broadway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 8:30 am we will peacefully and respectfully march in formation towards the Path Station, down Vessey towards Building 7. It is there where we will wait through the moments of silence paying respect to the victims &amp;amp; grieving family members. The name calling ceremony usually lasts from 8 am - 12 pm with two moments of silence at 8:45 am and 9:03 am. During this time it is important to show the utmost respect for those who lost their lives that day and their grieving families, friends, brothers &amp;amp; sisters from FDNY, NYPD, and PAPD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year to symbolize light and love we would like for all participants of the march to wear light colors for we are not mourning anymore, we are growing, and light signifies growth. On such a dreary &amp;amp; emotional day we would like to keep the morale up with positivity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At approximately 12:30 am we will start our name calling ceremony for those First Responders who have lost their lives since September 11th and aren't recognized as heroes. The ceremony will take place at the fountain with the giant red bulbs in front of Building 7.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 2 pm come join us for our final day of speeches, presentations &amp;amp; performances. Stay tuned for updates to the schedule. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1284078170000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279925039000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>9/11/10 activism in NYC. Benefit events for fealgoodfoundation 9/9 - 9/12</name><id>14194878</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1284073200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/14194878/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/6/global_12798054.jpeg</photo_url></item>