<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>RT-135</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.227803</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Whitehall State Park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>762729</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.540063</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;IT IS GOING TO BE WINDY THIS EVENING.  WHITEHALL WILL BE WINDY WITH SWELLS.  ONLY YOU CAN DECIDE IF THE CONDITIONS ARE SAFE FOR YOU.  DO NOT PLAN ON PADDLING IF YOU DO YOU KNOW HOW YOU OR OR BOAT HANDLE THE WIND.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning on launching at 6:15, or a bit earlier if every one is there.  We'll head out across the lake to the big island and then meander through coves and boggy areas to look for wildlife. Bring a headlamp or flashlight since we will be out past sunset.  We will only use our lights as needed and will not be paddling with them on. This is not a trip for beginners who have no experience paddling and staying with a group.  Moon rise is at 7:05 PM, 99.4% illuminated, so we should have a nice moon, once it climbs above the trees.  Expect partly cloudy skies and temps in the mid 80s dropping to the mid 70's as we paddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to bring munchies. If the moon is nice we may just sit in the middle or on an island and watch it for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The parking and launch is on Route 135 between Hopkinton and Westborough centers, approx 42.24166 North and -71.57316 West.  Do not program "Whitehall State Park" into your GPS. That will not take you to the launch site.  The nearest side road is Dale Road in Hopkinton, just west of the parking lot entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to your headlamp or flashlight you should have a whistle and wear a properly fastened PFD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(PLEASE NOTE - The organizers in this group are NOT trained leaders or instructors.  The organizers only set the time and place, each person participating in any group trip is responsible for their own safety.  Each participant is responsible for evaluating all relevant conditions for the trip and determining if their skills and equipment are appropriate for those conditions.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Kayaks at Boat Launch</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Susan L</member_name><member_id>7773139</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1346465056000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Paddlers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>paddling-33</urlname><id>505356</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>The Worcester Paddling Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346367372000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>ONCE IN A BLUE MOON full moon at Whitehall</name><id>80151752</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1346451300000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/paddling-33/events/80151752/</event_url></item>