<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;24 City&lt;br /&gt;5:30 — 7:20 pm&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, August 27, 2009&lt;br /&gt;Remis Auditorium&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An experimental fiction-nonfiction hybrid, the film follows the transformation of a state-owned factory building into a luxury, high-rise apartment complex. The lives of six retired factory workers—living monuments of the era of Mao's China, when the country turned into a global power—are supplemented by monologues delivered by professional actors including Joan Chen, to create an oral history of post-revolutionary China. Like Zhang-ke's previous film &lt;u&gt;Still Life&lt;/u&gt;, &lt;u&gt;24 City&lt;/u&gt; is artfully composed, rich in offbeat details, and punctuated with pop songs. An ambivalent exercise in Communist nostalgia as well as a moving collective portrait, the film was a New York Times critic's pick. In Mandarin and Shanghainese with English subtitles. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;Named by James Naremore of &lt;u&gt;Film Quarterly&lt;/u&gt; as the #1 Film of the Year, 2008 (My Winnipeg was #2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the 89% rottontomatoes rating:  A masterful new documentary from Jia Zhang-ke – &amp;quot;Not only is the 38-year-old director the most prominent Chinese filmmaker of his generation, he also has come to assume the role of witness and conscience in a society characterized by rapid modernization and a growing amnesia.&amp;quot; (Dennis Lim, LA Times, 2008) – 24 City recounts the dramatic and thunderous fall of the state-owned Factory 420, exploring both its physical demolition and its powerful symbolic echo of a half-century of communist rule. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots to talk about following the film.  As this will be a weeknight, please indicate whether you can stay for the post film discussion at a nearby eatery.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will stand in the hallway outside the theater holding a Meetup Sign after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250302253000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>24 City</name><id>11115731</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1251408600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/11115731/</event_url></item>