<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sturtevant Building, 1st Floor</address_2><address_1>197 Herrick Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02459</zip><lat>42.327873</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-454-2261</phone><name>Andover-Newton Theological School</name><city>Newton Center</city><id>208543</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.192406</lon></venue><fee><label>event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Thanks to all of you who attended the October NLP meetup. It was another great meeting, this time focusing on the topic of submodalities, the building blocks of our experience.  We explored what some of our own driving submodalities were, and then we learned the visual swish technique, which the group paired up to do with each other.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For November: the concept of submodalities is such a powerful one that we will look at additional aspects of it this month.  This is ?Submodalities ? The Sequel?; attendance at last month?s meetup will be helpful but not necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To recap our overview of submodalities: Every sensory modality (sight, hearing, feeling, taste and smell) has an infinite number of submodalities within it.  Examples of submodalities for sight are: image size, brightness, color versus black and white, and transparency.  For hearing, a few submodalities are: volume, direction, tone, and rhythm.  What?s really interesting about submodalities is that by changing them, you change the experience associated with them.  For example, many people have found that by making an unpleasant visual memory partially transparent, they reduce the intensity of the memory (try it!).  Similarly, someone else may find that moving a ?critical voice? from the inside of their head to the outside completely transforms their reaction to it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will be learning several new techniques that use submodalities as their basis.  This includes a great new technique from Richard Bandler (that I just learned last weekend) for reducing anxiety (or almost any other ?negative? emotion).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;November?s NLP meetup does not presuppose that you know anything about NLP. Everyone is welcome, from beginners to experts.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;Adam.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PS A reminder about the venue: &lt;br /&gt;Andover-Newton Theological School is conveniently located in Newton Center, with free parking. You can get directions here: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a map of the campus: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://ants.edu/about/mapcampus.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://ants.edu/about...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that this location is NOT handicapped accessible, as it entails climbing a short flight of stairs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx &lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner &lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Helping you to become the you that you want to be&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training &lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1195344383000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1192752594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston Neuro Linguistic Programming November Meetup</name><id>6576431</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1195171200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/6576431/</event_url></item>