<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/d/c/6/event_61908582.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;We will hike along the Goffstown Rail Trail that runs in between Henry Bridge Road and Davis Park Road. It runs behind a field opposite the Hillsborough Nursing Home and right behind the Woman's Prison and related buildings there. Behind one of the buildings in the Prison Complex is a road that takes you down to the trails and roads that run along the Piscataquog River. Dogs who like water will be able to swim in the river in some of the more shallow areas. The Piscataquog Trail section runs in between Henry Bridge Road and the field in between the river and the Rail Trail that is opposite the nursing home that looks some what like a triangle. &amp;nbsp;With the point of the triangle (top) pointed towards the river(right side, middle of photo) . &amp;nbsp;Although the rail trail is relatively flat there is some uphill and downhill for the trails along the river in terms of getting back to the rail trail. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;I am not sure of the exact&amp;nbsp;mileage of the hike but it took me two hours to hike it at a slower pace.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will park along the side of the road near the entrance to the Irving Gas Station on Henry Bridge Road and the Goffstown Rail Trail sign that is on Henry Bridge Road.  The sign and entrance are only about 200 feet  away from the traffic light.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Bigelow &amp;  Kaitlyn</member_name><member_id>8806889</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1318803025000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318131803000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Goffstown Rail Trail and Piscataquog River Trail</name><id>36687722</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1318773600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/36687722/</event_url></item>