<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Old Mountain Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03458</zip><lat>42.854801</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone> 603-431-4511 </phone><name>North Pack Monadnock</name><city>Greenfield</city><id>1043956</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.896684</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Where: Trail Head at Old Mountain Rd in Greenfield, NH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When: Saturday, July 17th 9am. I will be heading to Lee to camp with the NE Camping and Outdoor Group afterwards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;North Pack Monadnock (2,278') has trails that I have found listed variously as Easy and Moderate. I expect it to be easier than Pack Monadnock, but please understand that I have not climbed it from this trailhead.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more info: &lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/PackMonadnock071103.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was at the summit two weeks ago and there are BLUEBERRIES! They were pretty close to being ripe already. So bring a container and pick some wild blueberries when you reach the top. I am hoping they will still be there by the 17th!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I have plagiarized the following information: &lt;br /&gt;---------------------------------------- &lt;br /&gt;North Pack Monadnock or North Pack Monadnock Mountain is a 2,276 feet (694 m) monadnock located in south-central New Hampshire, at the northern end of the Wapack Range of mountains. It lies within Greenfield and Temple, New Hampshire; the 22 mi (35 km) Wapack Trail traverses the mountain. Ledges on the summit offer long views north to the White Mountains and west to Mount Monadnock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 3-mile round trip (if we use the Wapack Trail) will take less than 2 hours if you are in good shape, but it will be tough to resist spending more time on the mountain to soak in the views and maybe continuing on Cliff Trail, beyond the large cairn that materializes the North Pack summit. Overall, you can easily spend an entire day there if you bring your lunch and hike at a comfortable pace. The summit itself is a good place for a snack or a picnic, with large, flat rocks to rest (and BLUEBERRY BUSHES!).&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for the Green Honda Civic with the Meetup Sign in the windshield</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279376971000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278944945000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>North Pack Monadnock &amp; BLUEBERRIES!</name><id>14076180</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279371600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/14076180/</event_url></item>