<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>292 Centre Street </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02458</zip><lat>42.358246</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-527-7726</phone><name>Prana Restaurant</name><city>Newton Corner</city><id>1033348</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.184700</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.freshandalive.com/fresh_and_alive_images/header.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think eating organic, vegan, or raw/living food  is all you need in our diet to stay healthy? Think again! Even organic food is sadly lacking  in&amp;nbsp; nutrients these days, and most raw food supplements and  "superfoods" contain&amp;nbsp; mold. Ken Rohla will show you how to test your own food in your  own kitchen&amp;nbsp; to see for yourself what you are actually eating, or rather, what  you're&amp;nbsp; not! So what can you do about it? If you have the time and the  land, you can grow your own food. You can grow sprouts to help. You can buy  food-based&amp;nbsp; supplements and superfoods, but in sufficient quantities, that can  get quite&amp;nbsp; expensive. Or you can make gallons of your own fresh supplements  and&amp;nbsp; superfoods for pennies, including probiotics, enzymes, and  antioxidants,&amp;nbsp; with high amounts of extremely regenerative ORMUS minerals, and  imbue them&amp;nbsp; with very healing subtle scalar and other energies. Ken will also  tell you how to use the same techniques to make your own kombucha (healing  tea), pet&amp;nbsp; supplements, plant food, plant growth accelerator, compost  accelerator,&amp;nbsp; nontoxic household cleaner, odor eliminator, mold and mildew  remover, and more. Bring paper and writing instrument, Ken always gives out  lots of very specific useful info! &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; There is a sample recording of two-hour talk Ken gave in Houston  about ORMUS and growing nutrient-dense food: &lt;a href="http://sampletalk.freshandalive.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://sampletalk.freshandalive.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ken Rohla is a Hippocrates Health Institute certified natural  health&amp;nbsp; educator from New Smyrna Beach, Florida, and has been teaching  classes and&amp;nbsp; retreats since 1993 on rejuvenation and cellular regeneration  using raw and&amp;nbsp; sprouted vegetarian food, herbs, food-based supplements,  detoxification, emotional healing, ancient esoteric techniques, and cutting edge  science. With a background in engineering, physics, and computer science,  for 23 years he worked a variety of jobs in the medical industry, from  the patient level to the national policy level. A cutting edge researcher, Ken  has studied with many pioneers in the natural health movement,  including Gabriel Cousens, MD; Drs. Brian and Anna Maria Clement; David Wolfe;&amp;nbsp; Dr.  Robert Morse; Viktoras Kulvinskas; Brenda Cobb;&amp;nbsp; and many others. In  2005, Ken became certified as a natural health educator by Hippocrates  Health Institute in West Palm Beach, Florida, and is a guest lecturer  there. In 2006 Ken was honored to work with Coretta Scott King, wife of the  late Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. He may be contacted at &lt;a href="http://www.freshandalive.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.freshandalive.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to print a Name Tag and contact members to carpool. &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags/"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use our Message Boards for more events and information.&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/messages/boards/"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/messages/boards/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Feel free to print a Meetup Name Tag and contact members via Meetup messages to carpool. http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/grow/nametags/</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Prana</member_name><member_id>12763494</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1303095439000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>It's rawducational!</why><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>24</yes_rsvp_count><created>1300316258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE Talk @ PRANA: Ken Rohla - How to Make Probiotic Antioxidant Superfoods</name><id>16948630</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1302818400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/16948630/</event_url></item>