<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>83 Main St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03824</zip><lat>43.135017</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-312-6735</phone><name>Memorial Union Building</name><city>Durham</city><id>371528</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.928330</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Thursday, April 29th, 11am-3pm &lt;br /&gt;Energy Networking with UNH &lt;br /&gt;MUB Strafford Room &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UNH Parking Info: &lt;a href="http://www.unh.edu/transportation/visitor/visitorparking.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.unh.edu/tr...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join the the Seacoast Energy and Sustainable Meetup club at a FREE networking event. &lt;br /&gt;Refreshments provided, open to the public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The University of New Hampshire Energy Club has been committed to connecting students and community members to experts in the field for over a year.  Our latest event, the Energy Networking Day, seeks to draw local professionals in the energy sector into an informal and conversational setting with interested individuals.  Students interested in pursuing a career in energy technology and community members who are interested in energy issues will benefit greatly from this event. We welcome you to join us on Thursday, April 29th, 11am-3pm in the Strafford Room of the Memorial Union Building as a participant and as a resource for interested students. The venue is informal and structured to allow discussion over light refreshment and the displays of Undergraduate Research Conference poster presentations of student energy research.  This event is free to attend and open to the public. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please forward this email to anyone you may think is interested in the event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;STUDENTS:  Come build your network and learn more about the energy industry.  You might just line up an internship or job!  If you are working on an energy related project, send us some information about it by clicking on the link below!  Get some publicity by bringing your project posters to the event for all to see! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/viewform?formkey=dGh1TmFoZExOVmNlZXVqUXpTZEVUN2c6MA" target="_blank"&gt;https://spreadsheets....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROFESSORS: Connect with the community!  Converse with past, present and future students!  If you are working on an energy related project click on the link below to tell us about it!  We encourage you to bring posters or information about your research to the event! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/viewform?formkey=dGh1TmFoZExOVmNlZXVqUXpTZEVUN2c6MA" target="_blank"&gt;https://spreadsheets....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUSINESS REPRESENTATIVES:  Come build a network with UNH.  Businesses can rent a table for a display for $25.  Have some jobs or internship positions to be filled?  Want to get some publicity?  This is a great opportunity.  We will have 20 tables available for companies willing to pay a twenty five dollar table fee. Your organization's representatives will be entitled to refreshments, convenient on campus parking, connection with the community and a chance to interact with an excited student body that wants to learn more about your company and what you do.  Spaces are limited and are reserved on a first registered first served basis.  To reserve a table, please click on the following link: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://spreadsheets.google.com/viewform?formkey=dGh1TmFoZExOVmNlZXVqUXpTZEVUN2c6MA" target="_blank"&gt;https://spreadsheets....&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;COMMUNITY MEMBERS:  Have a passion for energy on the side?  Come converse with like minded people about your thoughts!   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We look forward to seeing you there! &lt;br /&gt;Peter&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter</member_name><member_id>486997</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272727235000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Green Earthlings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>oilawareness-286</urlname><id>459660</id><group_lat>43.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9899978638</group_lon><name>Seacoast  Energy and Permaculture Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271762312000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Energy Networking at UNH</name><id>13234700</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272553200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/oilawareness-286/events/13234700/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/3/global_14521011.jpeg</photo_url></item>