<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I’m in 'the rest of us’ category.  The big question concerning questions about ‘God’ is not whether s/he/it  &lt;i&gt;exists&lt;/i&gt; but  about what the word &lt;i&gt;means&lt;/i&gt;.  If we do not agree on what ‘God’ means then how are we going to form an opinion about whether or not God exists.   And, if the question is not so much a question about &lt;i&gt;existence&lt;/i&gt; than it is about &lt;i&gt;meaning&lt;/i&gt; then the distinctions between atheism, theism and deism become very muddled.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Atheism, therefore, seems to me to be just as muddled as the various forms of belief in God.  What is it that the atheist does not believe in?  The atheist has just as much need for clarity on the meaning of ‘God’ as do religionists if only because you cannot disbelieve in something that you cannot define, because if you cannot define your term you cannot put it into a statement which you think you want to refute.  Hence, the statement, “God does not exist” is meaningless unless you are prepared to define the thing that you want to reject.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Buddhism provides an interesting focal point.  I remember, a number of years ago, listening to a radio interview with Michio Kaku, the well-known physicist and writer of popular books on the subject.  I don’t recall the exact context, but a question about God or spirituality came up and he said that he was raised in a Buddhist home and that Buddhists are 'atheists’.  That comment struck me because I don’t really think of Buddhism as being an atheist religion which, anyway, I think is an oxymoron.  At the same time, I can see how at least  some strains of the Buddhist religion might be argued to be atheist because the spiritual view of transcendence is so very different than that of the so-called Western “monotheistic” religions.  So, what is atheism?   I’m not a student of the atheist movement, but my impression is that most people who today call themselves 'atheist' refer to a very scientific, naturalistic and radical empiricist view of reality that rejects any sense of immateriality while also embracing a humanism that deeply supports the notion that we don’t need to believe in God to be moral or good.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In conclusion,  my view is that the God issue is a big muddle that, while having speculative value,  has little else.  For my part, I do not consider myself to be an atheist, however, I do not think one needs to believe in God to be good.  My personal speculations flow more in a non-atheistic Buddhistic direction (but I do not consider myself to be a Buddhist either) of believing that there is  a transcendent Mind (of some sort) that is complementary with notions of spirituality.  This perspective can be very unscientific! But I believe in science.  I hope that I have at least provided some food for thought… &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NOTE:  WE'LL HAVE THE BIG, QUIET ROOM IN THE BACK! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This meeting is co-sponsored with the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/buddhism-625/"&gt;Eastern Philosophy Group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (please read)&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1295048731000</updated><rating><average>4.42999982834</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>27</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288710958000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atheism, Theism, Deism and the Rest of Us</name><id>15310513</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292025600000</time><rsvp_limit>30</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/15310513/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/c/a/global_15047834.jpeg</photo_url></item>