<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Avenue of the Arts</address_2><address_1>465 Huntington Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.338600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-267-9300</phone><name>Museum of Fine Arts </name><city>Boston</city><id>500439</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.093620</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color: crimson"&gt;MEET IN WEST ENTRANCE LOBBY at 12:30 p.m  I will be wearing a dusty pink baseball camp. My cell # is in the e-mail that I just sent to everyone who RSVP'd &amp;quot;yes.&amp;quot; See you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's the rescheduled field trip to see the Toulouse-Lautrec exhibition -- and anything else you want to see -- at the Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're a Bank of America customer, your BofA card will admit you to the MFA at no charge on this day (it's one of their Museums on Us weekends).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If not: I've reserved a library pass that will admit up to four people for $5 apiece (a huge discount over the MFA general-admission fee of $20/person). The first four people to RSVP &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot;--and to indicate that they aren't BofA customers--can claim these $5 slots from the Braintree library.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beyond that: Nearly every library in eastern Massachusetts offers a similar deal. Check your town library's Web site to see whether it has MFA passes. If so, just reserve them for that day, pick them up beforehand and bring them to the museum. Typically, each pass that you provide will let 2-4 people into the MFA for $5 apiece, which you just pay as you arrive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The key is using the discounted library passes is to reserve early--from experience, I can tell you that these passes go fast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's see whether we can make this happen. RSVP now!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in lobby </how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anne</member_name><member_id>2718718</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272991283000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>ATC &amp; Altered Art Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ne-atcs</urlname><id>236124</id><group_lat>42.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-71.3499984741</group_lon><name>New England Artist Trading Cards Plus (ATCs+) Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1266174422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NE ATC+ Field Trip to MFA for Toulouse-Lautrec exhibition </name><id>12602810</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272817800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ne-atcs/events/12602810/</event_url></item>