<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>6 William St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02144</zip><lat>42.399172</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.623.1212</phone><name>Unity Church of God</name><city>Somerville</city><id>790021</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.119963</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Proceeds from this concert help support &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandfolkmusic.org/" target="_blank"&gt;The New England Folk Music Archives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and its programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Featuring:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sam Weiser&lt;/b&gt; on violin &amp;amp; viola,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SONiA&lt;/b&gt; Guitar and Vocals,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Phoebe Hunt&lt;/b&gt; Violin and Vocals,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Seth Kibel&lt;/b&gt; on Clarinet and Saxaphone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Laura Cerulli&lt;/b&gt; on percussion,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Saso Sver&lt;/b&gt; on Guitar and Mandolin&lt;br /&gt;and &lt;b&gt;Nathaniel Smith&lt;/b&gt; on Cello&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General Admission $15.00&lt;br /&gt;Doors open 7:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Concert 8:00 pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets ~ &lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/95538" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.brownpaper...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Production coordinated by notloB Folk Concerts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fifteen-year-old Sam Weiser began playing the violin at three. By ten, Sam was concertmaster and soloist at the Norwalk Youth Symphony. He is the first Manhattan School of Music pre-college student to double-major in classical and jazz violin. He studies classical violin with world-renowned educator Patinka Kopec and jazz violin with Sara Caswell. Sam was the 2008/2009 recipient of the Daniel Pearl Memorial Violin, honoring the journalist and musician murdered in Pakistan in 2002, and was honored to be an emissary for music as a universal communication between all people. Sam was also the 2009/10 winner of the National American String Teachers' Association Alternative Styles Award.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam attended his first Mark O'Connor Fiddle Camp in Nashville in 2002, where he was introduced to string music of multiple genres. His exposure to the variety, talent and vitality there began an artistic journey that frees him to embrace all music on the violin without boundaries. He has continued to attend O'Connor's camps ever since, and has made lasting friendships and created deep musical bonds there with world-famous instructors and musicians of all ages, backgrounds and interests. Sam also performs with Mark in the American String Celebration Tours and at fundraisers for the camps.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam met Grammy® nominee and world music artist SONiA of disappear fear on the FODfest (Friends of Danny Pearl) tour in 2008, along with many other talented musicians who donate their time. After just a few shows, Sam and SONiA bonded musically and personally. Sam wanted to record a CD to raise money for charity, and was thrilled to have SONiA help translate the diverse genres of music he hears in his head into reality. Sam signed with disappear records, and his debut CD, 'Sam I Am', will be released Feb 16, 2010. Guest artists on the CD include Phoebe Hunt of Belleville Outfit, Sara Caswell of The Caswell Sisters, Mike Block of the Mike Block Band/ Appalachia Waltz Trio, Lulo Reinhardt of the Lulo Reinhardt Project (Django Reinhardt's great-nephew), and Dennis Chambers of Santana and SONiA of disappear fear. All profits will go to the Daniel Pearl Foundation and FODfest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam is a tenth grade honors student. He is a fanatic Mets fan, a NY Giants lover, a crazed Madden game aficionado and a rabid fantasy football and baseball team enthusiast. He is also a Fishman-endorsed artist, the youngest ever, and only uses Fishman pickups and amplification equipment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sam Weiser's Instruments: Violin, 5 String Wood Viper Electric Violin, 2009 artisan-made Jonathon Cooper 5 String Viola, David Segal Viola, Mandolin, Guitar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More info / purchase tickets at&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newenglandfolkmusic.org/EVTSamWeiser.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.newengland...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Artist's website: &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/samweisermusic" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>J. Boudreau</member_name><member_id>2060733</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1266195796000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Live Music Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Mass-Live-Music</urlname><id>1303540</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Mass Live Music n More</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263264445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sam Weiser Band ~ Benefit for NEFMA</name><id>12294312</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1266022800000</time><rsvp_limit>175</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Mass-Live-Music/events/12294312/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/a/a/global_12596218.jpeg</photo_url></item>