<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Rt 27</address_2><address_1>317 North Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.313030</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-315-8088</phone><name>Roots &amp; Wings</name><city>Natick</city><id>1075150</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.360298</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Welcome to everyone intrigued by Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP). Here are the details of the April meeting of the Greater Boston NLP group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month’s topic: Using NLP to Be an exceptional parent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those of us who are parents know that it's one of the most challenging roles we can take on.  Luckily, NLP has a range of tools and techniques that can help us meet those challenges in very effective ways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start by determining what &amp;quot;state&amp;quot; we most want to parent from (groundedness, humor, love, etc) and anchor those states so that we can easily access them when needed.  We'll then look at one or more language patterns that can be very useful in guiding our children with a minimum of conflict. Finally, we'll explore the multiple points of view that can give you a greater understanding of what's going on for you, your child(ren), and the family system.  Note that all of these techniques will work _on_ parents as well, for those of you who have parents but no children yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everyone is welcome to this meetup, from beginners to experts. Feel free to contact me if you have any questions about the group in general or this meeting in particular. I will stay for a while after the meetup, if you want to discuss specific issues that were not addressed during the session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking forward to seeing you there!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Adam Marx&lt;br /&gt;NLP Master Practitioner&lt;br /&gt;New Light NLP&lt;br /&gt;317 N Main St, Natick MA 01760&lt;br /&gt;(617) 329-1657&lt;br /&gt;adam@NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;www.NewLightNLP.com&lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;Helping you to become the you that you want to be:&lt;br /&gt;Coaching, Counseling, and Training&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Go straight back to the large studio (after 7pm)</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Adam Marx</member_name><member_id>2037274</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1271546794000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Transformational Individuals</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nlp-100</urlname><id>300638</id><group_lat>42.7299995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1800003052</group_lon><name>The Greater Boston NLP and Hypnosis Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1269010004000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Greater Boston NLP Meetup - Using NLP to Be an exceptional parent</name><id>dlfdnyngbtb</id><headcount>1</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1271373300000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nlp-100/events/12932337/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/4/d/0/global_11885328.jpeg</photo_url></item>