<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Jewell Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06103</zip><lat>41.765079</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Bushnell Park</name><city>Hartford</city><id>1586824</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.676476</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;What's better than an OUTDOOR concert with FREE music!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What: Black-eyed and Blues Fest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When: Friday, June 3, 2011&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 5:00 - 11:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where: Bushnell Park in Hartford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 12th Annual Black-eyed and Blues Fest is a free event with great music! Just bring a chair or blanket, bug spray and your favorite food and beverages!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to come anytime and stay as long as you want. You'll find us sitting on the back lawn of the Capitol beside the small grove of trees, up on the left as your facing the band shell. There are a few other Meetup groups that also posted this event so it will be nice to all hang out together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although it's advertised as "All Ages - No Coolers - No Food - No Dogs".&amp;nbsp; We've found that&amp;nbsp;as long as you stay outside of the roped off area, you can pretty much bring whatever you want to eat or drink.&amp;nbsp; However, if you decide to bring any alcoholic beverages, please make sure that you're very discreet and of course, please drink responsibly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Black-eyed Sally's will be selling food and beverages inside the roped area.&amp;nbsp; You must show ID to enter and keep in mind that you can't bring anything in or out of the roped area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking:&amp;nbsp; If you come early enough, you should be able to find plenty of free parking at the Capitol.&amp;nbsp; If not, metered on street parking is free after 6:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is typically a&amp;nbsp;rain or shine event (but I'm not going if it rains!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Musical lineup (subject to change without notice):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eran Troy Danner 5:00-6:00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johnny Rawls 6:15-7:30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine Ohlman 7:45-9:15&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthony Gomes 9:30 -11:00&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>back lawn of the Capitol beside the small grove of trees, up on the left as your facing the band shell. There are a few other Meetup groups that also posted this event so it will be nice to all hang out together!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy</member_name><member_id>4345102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307225671000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><why>it is free and fun</why><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1305024318000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>FREE BLUES CONCERT</name><id>17824351</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307134800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/17824351/</event_url></item>