<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Kingston Station</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02892</zip><lat>41.482063</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>South County Bike Path</name><city>West Kingston</city><id>903506</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.560204</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: orangered"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLEASE TAKE THE POLL TO LET US KNOW WHAT YOU ARE GOING TO DO...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;WALK, JOG, RUN, BIKE or ROLL. Click the link below to vote&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Bicycling/polls/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My meetups are just for fun and pleasure.&lt;br /&gt;Anyone and everyone is welcome.&lt;br /&gt;So don't get stressed about having to complete the whole path, just come on out, enjoy the outdoors and meet some new folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;South County Bike Path: 5.6 miles between the Kingston RR Station and Rte. 108 in Wakefield.&lt;br /&gt;Go at your own pace&lt;br /&gt;Go as far as you want&lt;br /&gt;Stop where ever you want&lt;br /&gt;Stay for as long as you want &amp;amp; leave whenever you want.&lt;br /&gt;NO STRESS!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grade: Gentle hill in middle of trail from Kingston Station to Peace Dale. The Peace Dale to Wakefield section has moderate ups and downs throughout. A switchback built where an old trestle was removed requires great caution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail condition: Excellent. Eastern 2-mile segment opened summer 2003.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Special characteristics: This path served as a rail spur from the main line to Narragansett Beach. It begins at historic Kingston Station and passes through sections of the Great Swamp. It then connects to Peace Dale and Wakefield, passing many commerical areas as it makes its way into Narragansett.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Natural attractions nearby: Wildlife observation, hiking and paddling in Great Swamp Management Area, Tri-Pond Park and Saugatucket River, recreation fields, beach with swimming at Narragansett Town Beach.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Historical attractions nearby: Kingston Station, Kingston village, main street area of Wakefield, South County Museum, art galleries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Services nearby: Shops, restaurants, grocery stores, schools, college, library, bike shop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: From Route 95, take Exit 9 to Rte. 4 south. Follow until junction with Route 1 south. Follow to Rte. 138 west. Pass University of Rhode Island, look for signs for Kingston Station. Trail begins from back of parking lot. Alternative is Rte. 4 south to Rte. 2 south to Rte. 138 east to Kingston Station.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is available:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Kingston Station (AMTRAK) Station, on Railroad Ave., south of Route 138 in Kingston. Parking and entrance to the bike path at the southern end of the train station parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;* Intersection of Railroad St. and Route 108 in the Village of Peace Dale.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I drive a white Toyota Highland meet me by my car. We won't leave until 10 AM&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;If it is raining – I will reschedule for another day.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a White Toyota SVU. I will have a Red Towel unfold over the hood</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1248017356000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>awesome people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group</urlname><id>1300868</id><group_lat>41.8300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Providence Biking and Recreational Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1241201713000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>South County Bike Path - 5 Miles Long - 10 Miles Total Trip Back &amp; Forth</name><id>10313057</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244383200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Providence-Biking-and-Recreational-Group/events/10313057/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/d/global_5864541.jpeg</photo_url></item>