<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>2.2 miles on Rte 302 past Rte 3</address_2><address_1>At the end of Zealand Road</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03595</zip><lat>44.270813</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Zealand Parking Lot</name><city>Twin Mountain</city><address_3> drive to the end and park in the lots</address_3><id>292754</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.539917</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Leaving the Zealand Parking area, the trail follows the railroad grade, then a bypass that is somewhat rough. It then returns to the grade and approaches the Zealand River, near some ledges in the stream. Here it diverges right from the grade and continues on the west bank, then rejoins the grade and makes the first of several brook crossings. The trail now passes through an area of beaver activity with a boardwalk, but otherwise stays mostly on the railroad grade. The A–Z Trail enters from the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  From the Zealand Trail, the A-Z Trail skirts a beaver pond and starts up at easy grades. It descends down a low ridge and then climbs to cross a brook. It crosses several smaller brooks as it ascends moderately through a beautiful birch forest. It crosses a snowmobile trail and traverses a long easy section with a slight descent. It crosses two branches of Mt. Field Brook and recrosses the snowmobile trail. It now ascends steeply with rough footing to the junction of Willey Range Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  The Willey Range Trail enters on the right and the trail begins to ascend gradually.&lt;br /&gt;to the junction of Mt Tom Spur. The Mt. Tom Spur diverges left and the A-Z Trail bears right to reach the height-of-land. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail then begins to descend steeply, swinging left to cross a brook. It follows along side this brook valley that has its head at the Field-Tom col. It descends steadily, crosses a steep-walled gully and terminates at the Avalon Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The A–Z Trail to Zealand Falls Hut diverges left. The Avalon Trail continues to descend moderately and crosses Crawford Brook. It then continues at an easy grade and arrives at a loop path that diverges right, passing by Beecher and Pearl Cascades. It shortly rejoins the main trail and recrosses the brook to Beecher Cascade  to the junction of Mt Willard Trail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After crossing Crawford Brook, the Avalon Trail descends gradually. The Mt. Willard Trail enters right and the trail terminates at the information center to Avalon Trailhead (HiCtr) and Mount Willard Trailhead (HiCtr)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Totals&lt;br /&gt;Distance  7.30 mi&lt;br /&gt;Time  4 hr 55 min&lt;br /&gt;Elev Gain  +2088 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Loss  -1961 ft&lt;br /&gt;Elev Change  +127 ft&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We would like to see at least 3 &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; RSVP's to create a meetup. Your assistance on the trail is always welcome and helps in making a Meetup. In the case of a full event and waiting list, maybe RSVPs will be moved to the waiting list 3 days before the hike. All hikers need to watch for changes and cancellations.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Please keep your rsvp's up to date. Its very important that we have a true headcount, and not worry that  your late or lost.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every hiker is important on a hike, especially if we divide the hike into a fast and slow group, or if there is an injury. Review the trail maps and itinerary available in the White Mountain Guidebook. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This group will average a 1pm turn around time. If trail or hiker conditions slow the group, you need to understand that the goal for the day can change and we must start back to end the hike safely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make sure your hiker profile is complete so we can verify that your qualified to join us on this White Mountain hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is always advised and a great way to get to know your fellow members.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Diane Mancino</member_name><member_id>2347621</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1244550942000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242087507000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Avalon to Zealand Trail  loop hike</name><id>10389953</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1244377800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10389953/</event_url></item>