<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>How can you easily have the body and health you desire?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's SO much we can talk about on this subject!  (Maybe we'll have more than one night on this topic.  We'll see.) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll begin by watching part of the&lt;b&gt; Abraham/Hicks new DVD: &lt;u&gt;Think and Get Slim: Natural Weight Loss&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;.  The discussion can extend beyond weight issues, however; so &lt;b&gt;bring all your questions and concerns regarding health, your body, etc&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;This meeting will be in our beautiful home nestled in the woods in Framingham&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt; We welcome you to come early for extra social time, and to stay after the meeting for a campfire in our backyard.&lt;/span&gt;  If you want to stay for the fire, we advice you bring appropriate clothing for the nighttime weather and possible bugs.  We'll intend for the best, most comfortable unfolding!  If you play an instrument appropriate for quiet fireside playing, please bring it!  The evening will end by 10:00pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is limited parking in our driveway.  &lt;b&gt;Please look for possible spots along the sides of the long driveway; and park as efficiently as possible to allow for the most cars.  You can also look for spots along Edmands Rd, and we encourage carpooling, too.&lt;/b&gt;  You might be more comfortable using a flashlight to walk down our driveway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are expecting this to be a most informative and enjoyable evening!  Great discussion and learning, aligning, wonderful people, yummy snacks, and good vibrations!  &lt;span style="color: indigo"&gt;PLEASE only rsvp if you know you can really attend, and be considerate to let us know if your plans change.  Our goal is to have zero no-shows! &lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Warm hearts,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ann and Mark&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Across from a big old white house.  Look for our mailbox at end of long driveway</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mark</member_name><member_id>6516126</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ann Ide</member_name><member_id>7915265</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1247702591000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>deliberate creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up</urlname><id>1276745</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>"Good Vibrations" Metro West Law of Attraction Community</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1242777811000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Our bodies, our health, and feeling good about them</name><id>10450522</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245193200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/MetroWest-Law-of-Attraction-Good-Vibrations-meet-up/events/10450522/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/2/b/global_6751323.jpeg</photo_url></item>