<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>216 Crown Street</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06510</zip><lat>41.310001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hula Hanks</name><city>New Haven</city><id>240174</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919998</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>ever been served a vodka tonic by a pro wide receiver?? didn't think so. well, here's your chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;blow off work a little early and come out to Hula Hanks for celebrity bartending, where between 4pm and 6pm NFL players from all over the country will be pouring drinks. all the tips benefit united way charitable programs in the greater new haven area. word is that some of the cast of &amp;quot;Beauty and the Geek&amp;quot; will also be there to mingle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;this is part of the NFL Players Weekend as put on by the United Way of Greater New Haven, which just happens to be the largest annual sports charity event in Connecticut. more than 30 players will be here to participate in various volunteer and fundraising events, including an auction (lots of sports memorabilia), a bowl with the pros event and of course celebrity bartending at Hula Hanks. for more information on the weekend, &lt;a href="http://www.uwgnh.org/nfl/" target="_blank"&gt;click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the bartending event is open to the public, and there is no cover charge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;your contact person for this event is J.R., 248-563-4557&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273541100000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173120363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Fri. 3/9 - Celebrity Bartending at Hula Hanks! Benefits United Way!</name><id>5539088</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1173474000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/5539088/</event_url></item>