<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Science Park</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.360001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Museum of Science</name><city>Boston</city><id>241405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070000</lon></venue><fee><label>admission fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>16.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll be visiting the Museum of Science to investigate a traveling exhibit about the scientist who's articulate explanation for the apparent design of life provided an intellectually respectable reason to dispatch with theories of special creation: DARWIN.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From MoS.org: &amp;quot;The most in-depth exhibition ever mounted on the highly original naturalist and his groundbreaking theory... find out how this scientific genius realized that biological life is not static, but changing through ongoing natural selection ... In this exhibit, a lush array of fossils, mounted specimens, and collections of beetles, butterflies, and moths suggest the astounding diversity Darwin encountered in his travels around the world. Complementing the assortment, live organisms (two 50-pound Galapagos tortoises, a five-foot-long green iguana, ornate horned frogs from South America, and carnivorous plants) evoke the sense of wonder that Darwin felt when first seeing so many magnificent, unfamiliar living things.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What a way to spend a Sunday! Families are welcome. Ticket prices are standard, $16 adults, $13 children, $14 seniors. If there is sufficient interest (20 or more coming) I will be putting in an inquiry about getting a group discount. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Zachary Bos</member_name><member_id>83909</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1174406750000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Freethinkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>bostonatheists</urlname><id>12763</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>The Boston Atheists Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1173281436000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunday with Mr Darwin</name><id>5545556</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1174233600000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonatheists/events/5545556/</event_url></item>