<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>This will be our last meetup on Nietzsche for a while. We decided to skip the 4th (last) part of Thus Spoke Zarathustra and to discuss On the Uses and Misuses of History for Life at our last meeting on Nietzsche. You probably noticed that in the title and in the text I have already referred to this work in two different ways. Yes, so it seems that the title of this work has been translated many different ways nevertheless it is unambiguous what text those different titles refer to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is about a 60 page long work. Since we have begun to meet twice a month instead of once in every three weeks it has been the observation of many of us that we need smaller amount of readings for each meetup. The approximately 60 page long suggested reading sounds about right while the 150 pages selected for the last meetup seemed to much. In the future we will consider this when we (the participants of each meeting) decide the suggested reading for the next time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This work does not appear in the two books that were suggested for the previous Nietzsche meetings. There are web sites where one can access the entire text. One such web page is:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geocities.com/thenietzschechannel/history.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.geocities....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is within the web site:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geocities.com/thenietzschechannel" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.geocities....&lt;/a&gt; (In the &amp;quot;Text: English&amp;quot; session.)&lt;br /&gt;On the Advantage and Disadvantage of History for Life (yet an other translation) is also available in hard copy:&lt;br /&gt;1. On the Advantage and Disadvantage of History for Life, ISBN 0-915144-94-8  for $6.95 from Hackett&lt;br /&gt;2. Also as part of Nietzsche's 4-part Untimely Meditations, (ISBN 0-521-58584-8 for $19.99 from Cambridge University)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remember that in a case of an unexpected setback at our selected location (Rendang) the backup location is the Bombay Club next door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Andras</member_name><member_id>2044995</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1170547646000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-philosophy</urlname><id>119696</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Boston Philosophy Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1169314304000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nietzsche: On the Use and Abuse of History for Life</name><id>5410254</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1170374400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-philosophy/events/5410254/</event_url></item>