<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Note -  There is still plenty of room to stay here in the Adirondaks and Campsites.  After reading the details of this event below,  you can click on this link to sign up for the campsite portion of this meetup:  &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/calendar/9876505/"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/calendar/9876505/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a link to see more about the &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/pages/Wilton_Meet_Up_Details_and_Photos/"&gt;LOWER CAMP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pack up your pooch,  your favorite toothbrush and pajamas because we have planned an exciting overnight stay at Camp Anne Jackson in wonderful Wilton New Hampshire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;When&lt;/b&gt;: Saturday May 9th -  Full Moon Event (Rain or Shine) and Sunday morning May 10th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost&lt;/b&gt;: Such a deal.  Oye vey !    Let me tell you.....this vacation wonderland normally rents out for $1,200 for the weekend.   We have negotiated the deal of the summer.  For the special low price of &lt;b&gt;ZERO&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and with just a little bit of volunteer effort,  we can stay at this glorious camp with our four legged friends and family.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&lt;/b&gt;: There will be opportunities galore for all types of interests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;79 Acres of land for your puppies frolic, fun and enjoyment&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Campfires&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hiking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swimming&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fishing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doggie Frisbee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Board Games&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating (did we mention....LOTS of eating&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doggie Agility Play&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ghost stories around the camp fire (bring flashlight to hold under you chin)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why&lt;/b&gt;: To help out Girl Scouts of America and get their camp open for the summer while also having a great time with our dogs and friends..  This will definitely earn us Brownie Points  ;-) if you catch our drift (Yes Girl Scout cookies will be provided and in the proper ratio of Mint Chocolate to all others) and we hope will lead to many more play dates on the Camp grounds&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to Bring for the fun part:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of doggie Toys&lt;br /&gt;Your favorite board and card games&lt;br /&gt;Fun lawn games (anyone have a Volleyball or croquet set)&lt;br /&gt;A food dish or two for our smorgasbord&lt;br /&gt;Beverages (let's shoot for sodas, water, juice, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;Smores Fixings required (there will be a contest with doggie prizes)&lt;br /&gt;Free Pizza and Salad will be provided by the Girl Scout Council&lt;br /&gt;Sleeping bag, flashlights, headlamps, lanterns, bug spray, bug lights, toothbush (no sharing), towels, garbage bags, DOG POOP PICKUP BAGS, etc.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Main Lodge&lt;/u&gt; -  Indoor sleeping on floor mattresses for &lt;b&gt;16 peeps max&lt;/b&gt; in the loft&lt;br /&gt;(Yes....Pooches included)&lt;br /&gt;Full HUGO size kitchen....HUGE....with large refrigerator, oven, stove, microwave, sinks, coffee pot, toaster oven, utensils, plates.  Yaddy yaddy yadda.  Basically full kitchen ammenities.  Okay....no need to worry we are not really roughing it.&lt;br /&gt;Large bathroom (accomodates three at time unisex)&lt;br /&gt;No showers so bring your perfume &lt;br /&gt;Dining room with large tables to accomodate our group&lt;br /&gt;covered porch&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lower Camp&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;WIIIIIIDDDDDE  OPEN ACREAGE&lt;br /&gt;79 acres of woods, fields, trails, water (for Barney).  You name it,  we got it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Pavilion&lt;/u&gt; - Campground Central Meeting Point&lt;br /&gt;Electricity and huge covered stone fireplace (think Huge Smores)&lt;br /&gt;Refrigerator (no need for coolers and ice)&lt;br /&gt;Picnic tables&lt;br /&gt;bathrooms (natural composting)&lt;br /&gt;huge outdoor fire pit (can we spell Pig roast????)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Adirondacks&lt;/u&gt; - There are Six lovely enclosed lean-to's&lt;br /&gt;Each adirondack has a firepit and picnic table with smoke detector on the inside and screen front doors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Swimming Hole&lt;/u&gt; Bring towels because your dogs will love this pond and will need a&lt;br /&gt;toweling after their swim&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What to Expect:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Checkin anytime after 8:30 am Saturday May 9th&lt;br /&gt;Departure time by 1:00 pm sharp Sunday May 10th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please carry in, carry out&lt;/u&gt;, dumpster provided, bring garbage bags.&lt;br /&gt;Parking for up to 50 cars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will further discuss our volunteer effors which will encompass brush clearing and pickup for a couple of hours max (the rest of the weekend will be pure fun and schenanigans).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring working gloves, rakes, loppers (anything that might help us along with brush pickup considering the rough winter we have had)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By the Way: For those of you that want to rough it or if we fill up the main lodge and you still want to join us,  there is plenty of room on the grounds for tent camping...as many as 110 +&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So if camping out is your preference,  there is plenty of room to pitch a tent or sleep in one of the Adirondacks.  Each Adirondack accomodates up to 4 people in sleeping bags.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the meetup at the Lodge is filled up you can also sign up for the waiting list for lodge accomodations based on cancellations.  Or you can &lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/calendar/9876505/"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; and sign up for the Really Roughin' It Sleeping Under the Stars portion of the meetup.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>There is still PLENTY of room to stay here in the Adirondaks and Campsites.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judi-Judi-Judi</member_name><member_id>7477606</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gabriella Lopez</member_name><member_id>8643209</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1242437083000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>SDS - Super Doggie Soles</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Doggie-Paws</urlname><id>1101339</id><group_lat>42.9700012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4400024414</group_lon><name>Human Soles &amp; Doggie Paws Hikers &amp; Walkers of Manchester, NH</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1236137243000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wilton Wilderness Weekend Dog and Peeps Overnight Adventure - Stay in the Lodge </name><id>9876253</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1241872200000</time><rsvp_limit>16</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Doggie-Paws/events/9876253/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/b/f/a/global_7035066.jpeg</photo_url></item>