<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>We will walk to the reservoir and around it.  Meet at 7pm in front of the Coolidge Corner Starbucks. &lt;br /&gt;There is plenty of free parking in the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview:&lt;br /&gt;The Brookline Reservoir property is a man-made body of water approximately one mile in circumference. A jogging/walking track encircles the reservoir. The entire park is visible from perimeter, while the details of the property become observable when walking along the circular path. The architecturally significant gatehouse is a prominent feature. Most of the park is set below the surrounding roads, creating a feel of separation between the park and abutting lands. Swimming and skating are not allowed on the property. The reservoir is on the National and State Registers of Historic Places. The reservoir is stocked annually with fish by the Massachusetts Department of Fish and Wildlife. Fishing is allowed by permit from the Town Clerk's Office. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Park History:&lt;br /&gt;The reservoir was originally built as a drinking water supply for the City of Boston. This area was once low-lying pasture land with a marsh in the center and a stream running through it. The reservoir was part of the Cochituate water system and was built to feed the Beacon Hill Reservoir that stood at the intersection of Hancock, Derne and Temple Streets. The Brookline Reservoir was filled to capacity in 1848. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 1902, the City of Boston decided to sell the reservoir and its surrounding land. Prompted by rumors of undesired development, the neighbors, including Amy Lowell, John C. Olmsted, Walter Channing, Edward Atkinson, and George Lee, contributed more than $50,000 towards the purchase price of $150,000. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although there were plans in the 1920's to build a beach and a bathhouse near Lee and Dudley as well as a wharf near the gatehouse, they were not realized. In 1926, the gatehouse was altered to provide rooms and toilet facilities for swim meets, skating and other occasions. The Reservoir Park was considered briefly in 1956 as a possible location for a new Town Hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Deed/Title Restrictions&lt;br /&gt;The land was purchased from the City of Boston with the condition to &amp;quot;operate and maintain to flow water through.&amp;quot; The property is individually listed on the State and National Register of Historic Places and is within the Town Green Historic District.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nancy M</member_name><member_id>3233594</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1227370673000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224971626000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brookline Reservoir </name><id>9031077</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1227139200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/9031077/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/f/0/global_6019008.jpeg</photo_url></item>