<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>14 Hancock Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03801</zip><lat>43.075081</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Strawbery Banke Museum</name><city>Portsmouth</city><id>10419692</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.753067</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;33rd Annual Candlelight Stroll at Strawbery Banke Museum&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Lights Up Vintage Christmas in Portsmouth Holiday Celebration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portsmouth, New Hampshire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; (December 9, 2012) – Candlelight Stroll at Strawbery Banke Museum, now in its 33rd year, offers visitors &lt;strong&gt;a glimpse into an authentic “Winter’s Eve on Puddle Dock.”&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/9/4/event_181808852.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The experience that is one of New Hampshire’s most-treasured holiday events is a family tradition for many who return year after year to savor what’s new as well as their favorite details.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Families are drawn to the &lt;strong&gt;magic of an authentic “old-time” Christmas&lt;/strong&gt;, when night watchmen walked and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;cheery bonfires&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; warmed passersby. Visitors travel in a horse-drawn carriage along the lanes lit with &lt;strong&gt;real candle lanterns&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;strong&gt;historic houses are decorated to their eras&lt;/strong&gt; with fresh greens and dried herbs and flowers collected from the Museum gardens. &lt;strong&gt;Music accents Candlelight Stroll&lt;/strong&gt; in multiple ways: an &lt;strong&gt;18th century harpsichord in Chase House&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;folk music in the Cider Shed&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;carolers strolling&lt;/strong&gt; the 10-acre grounds or gathering by the bonfire and a &lt;strong&gt;pianist presenting holiday favorites&lt;/strong&gt; in the Visitor Center for visitors admiring the Gingerbread House Contest display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 The most popular feature of Candlelight Stroll are the &lt;strong&gt;role-players&lt;/strong&gt; celebrating the holidays. Mrs. Goodwin welcomes callers to her &lt;strong&gt;lavishly decorated Victorian mansion&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/2/d/a/event_181808922.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt; Mrs. Shapiro prepares potato latkes and applesauce for Hannukah in her 1919 kitchen. Mrs. Abbott sells &lt;strong&gt;penny candy&lt;/strong&gt; in the 1940s Abbott Store. Museum volunteers and junior role-players help depict the “Winter’s Eve” in their houses while &lt;strong&gt;craftsmen demonstrate tinsmith, coopering and hearth-cooking&lt;/strong&gt; in different locations around the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;33rd Annual Candlelight Stroll TICKETS NOW ON SALE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$2 discount for tickets purchased in advance,  November 1-30. &lt;a href="http://www.strawberybanke.org/index.php?option=com_virtuemart&amp;amp;Itemid=95"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to purchase tickets online.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets are $20 for adults; $10 for children 5-17 and free to children under 5. Tickets are available on the Museum website starting November 1. There is a $2 per ticket discount for tickets purchased between November 1 and November 30. Tickets may also be purchased in the Strawbery Banke Museum Store, open daily 10-4. Free parking and free admission at all times for the Museum Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #008000"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy your ticket now! Meetup location will be announced soon!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meetup @ 4:00 PM @ the entrance to the Museum (see map). FREE parking @ corner of Parrott Ave &amp; Junkins Ave. My phone # (603) 759-9876.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1355112657000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fun People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>funstuff40</urlname><id>330793</id><group_lat>42.1500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5199966431</group_lon><name>Fun Stuff</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353473515000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>33rd Annual Candlelight Stroll</name><id>92275792</id><headcount>8</headcount><duration>14400000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1355086800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/funstuff40/events/92275792/</event_url></item>