<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Intermediate hike:  Fun, varied, with great views.   From Hike-New England.com:  This is a loop hike across the summits of Welch and Dickey Mountains, providing many views along the way as the trail winds its away across open ledges. It follows the yellow-blazed Welch-Dickey Loop Trail all the Claudette and slab (photo by Sue Murphy) way. The different branches of the loop are commonly referred to as Welch Mountain Trail (the right-hand fork which leads most directly to Welch); and Dickey Mountain Trail (the left-hand fork which goes directly to Dickey Mountain.) &lt;a href="http://www.hikenewengland.com/WelchDickey080816.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.hikeneweng...&lt;/a&gt;  Total elevation gain is 1650'.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.5 miles&lt;br /&gt;Approx. 3 hours&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring lunch and water.  Social gathering after, location TBD.From I-93:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Take exit 28 off I-93, and head east toward Waterville Valley on Rt. 49.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn left onto Mad River Road (at the traffic signal) and bear right when Mad River Road goes that way.&lt;br /&gt;    * Then turn right onto Upper Mad River Road, which is both paved and dirt.&lt;br /&gt;    * Turn left onto Orris Road (there is a hiker sign at this intersection).&lt;br /&gt;    * Follow Orris Road for 0.6 mile and then take a short fork to the right to reach a large parking area.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet in the parking area off Orris Road</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tracy</member_name><member_id>6940492</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256243506000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Snow &amp; Outdoor Sport Enthusisats</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NESeacoastOutdoorSports</urlname><id>1298081</id><group_lat>42.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-70.8199996948</group_lon><name>NE Seacoast Snow &amp; Outdoor Sports</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246106476000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Foliage Hike Welch Dickey Loop</name><id>10746467</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255788000000</time><rsvp_limit>25</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NESeacoastOutdoorSports/events/10746467/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/8/5/global_5803669.jpeg</photo_url></item>