<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Faneuil Hall Market Plaze</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.359657</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mija Cantina</name><city>Boston</city><id>1940561</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.055946</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate summer and join Smiling Stiletto Shoe Club for a ladies night cocktail party on the outdoor patio at Mija. Conveniently located in Faneuil Hall markeplace, Mija is known for its Mexican food and delicious cocktails. Enjoy complimentary appetizers, delicious cocktails, prizes and mingling with other shoe loving fashionistas! Be sure to break out your sexy summer shoes for the pink carpet walk-off competition for the title of Best-in-Shoe. There is also plenty of indoor, covered space at Mija- so even if it rains, we will still be partying!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling Stiletto Shoe Club is a social organization for shoe and fashion lovers with 2,800 members in the Boston area. We get together monthly for cocktail parties, fashion shows, shopping events and other fun activities!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joining us will be Avni Fashions by Boston based designer Avni Trivedi. Avni will be displaying her latest looks and there will also be a mini fashion show on the pink carpet. Also joining us will be the authors of the hilarious new book &lt;a href="http://dictionaryofmen.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Dictionary of Men&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have you ever met a guy and realized that you've dated him before... even though, you technically haven't? Authors Maria Blanco and Jane Black have taken some out the guess work out of and put some humor into the dating process by categorizing some common types of men in their book Dictionary of Men. Based on conversations with real women out there in the dating trenches, Dictionary of Men defines over 300 men plus it includes true, hysterical stories from women about their experiences with men. So, come and meet the authors, pick up a copy of their new book, have a few cocktails and appetizers and enjoy a lovely and stylish summer night with friends!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Catherine (see photo) inside the venue or call 774 232 0000! I am hosting the event!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Catherine </member_name><member_id>6146290</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342626885000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1341933720000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ladies Night: Cocktail Patio Party at Mija, Faneuil Hall</name><id>72736572</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342564200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/72736572/</event_url></item>