<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;First off, just a small plug for any volunteers interested in becoming assistant organizers. If you want to get out of the house and have ideas (gallery openings, movies, ice-skating, etc.) but don't necessarily know that many people, then this network is perfect. Please contact Matt via email or find me Friday night to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday Night Downtown exploration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9pm - The Congress Tavern&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10pm - The Salon - DJ Nick DeParis (spins house/electronic - probably upstairs but if you don't see us try the basement dancefloor)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11:30pm - Local 121 - Handsome Pete 80s night (never know what you are gonna get but it is usually fun. doesn't start until 11).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stop by at any of the venues. Don't feel the need to leave for the next spot if you are having fun. This is really meant to be informal and allow some of us to have a familiar face or two in the Providence social scene. For others, you may be interested in checking out these venues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared to dance! * not required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please make sure to look at our pictures before heading to the spaces - due to the nature of the crowds we cannot pre-determine where we'll be standing. The times are approximations on when we will arrive/depart. Don't forget that it could get very loud which is not conducive to large group conversations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Val</member_name><member_id>7362863</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1330810026000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>providence-newcomers</urlname><id>530714</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>Newcomers to the Providence Area</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330294327000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Friday Night Downtown</name><id>53930092</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1330740000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/providence-newcomers/events/53930092/</event_url></item>