<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Louder Than A Bomb&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a film about passion, competition, teamwork, and trust. It&amp;rsquo;s about the joy of being young, and the pain of growing up. It&amp;rsquo;s about speaking out, making noise, and finding your voice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also just happens to be about poetry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every year, more than six hundred teenagers from over sixty Chicago area schools gather for the world&amp;rsquo;s largest youth poetry slam, a competition known as "Louder Than a Bomb". Founded in 2001, Louder Than a Bomb is the only event of its kind in the country&amp;mdash;a youth poetry slam built from the beginning around teams. Rather than emphasize individual poets and performances, the string, critiquing, and rewriting their pieces. To succeed, teams have to create an environment&amp;nbsp;ucture of Louder Than a Bomb demands that kids work collaboratively with their peers, presentof mutual trust and support. For many kids, being a part of such an environment&amp;mdash;in an academic context&amp;mdash;is life-changing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Louder Than A Bomb&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;chronicles the stereotype-confounding stories of four teams as they prepare for and compete in the 2008 event. By turns hopeful and heartbreaking, the film captures the tempestuous lives of these unforgettable kids, exploring the ways writing shapes their world, and vice versa. This is not "high school poetry" as we often think of it. This is language as a joyful release, irrepressibly talented teenagers obsessed with making words dance. How and why they do it&amp;mdash;and the community they create along the way&amp;mdash;is the story at the heart of this inspiring film.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.coolidge.org/sites/default/files/thumbnail_6.jpg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;



Special Screening

&lt;p&gt;Director Greg Jacobs will be on hand after the screening for a Q&amp;amp;A at the showtimes below&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=f740e0c1-ba1c-4632-b43d-0f9f0a474d69&amp;amp;evtcode=15841~2227d6a5-68f5-41c2-b22e-813c872c64f4&amp;amp;"&gt;Saturday, June 4 at 7:10pm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;




&lt;p&gt;From AV Club:The documentary&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Louder Than A Bomb&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a different kind of high-school movie, brimming with life and hope instead of social-climbing, bullying, and furtive first kisses. It should hit home with anyone whose experience of adolescence involved creativity, intellectual exploration, and getting to know and love people outside their immediate social circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the film is showing in the Screening Room, I &lt;strong&gt;STRONGLY&lt;/strong&gt; suggest you pre-purchase your tickets. This special screening &lt;strong&gt;WILL&lt;/strong&gt; sell out:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=f740e0c1-ba1c-4632-b43d-0f9f0a474d69&amp;amp;evtcode=15841~2227d6a5-68f5-41c2-b22e-813c872c64f4&amp;amp;"&gt;http://store.coolidge.org/WebSales/Pages/TicketSearchCriteria.aspx?epguid=f740e0c1-ba1c-4632-b43d-0f9f0a474d69&amp;amp;evtcode=15841~2227d6a5-68f5-41c2-b22e-813c872c64f4&amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we'll go to a nearby eatery/drinkery (Finale? &amp;nbsp;Zaftigs? The Pub (will the Bruins be playing??!!) to talk about the film and the best part of our high school experiences. &amp;nbsp;Remember when people told us it was 'The best times of our lives?' &amp;nbsp;How many of us are still in touch with our high school friends? &amp;nbsp;How many of us competed in creative and intellectual competitions? &amp;nbsp;How embellished will the memories get after we've hoisted a few?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you at the movie,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>John will be holding a Meetup Sign reciting poetry every bit as powerful as what we see in the film</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>John</member_name><member_id>2321575</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307827096000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1306586175000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Louder Than A Bomb</name><id>20044371</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307228400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/20044371/</event_url></item>