<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>85 East Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01366</zip><lat>42.489315</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Brooks Woodland Preserve (Roaring Brook Tract)</name><city>Petersham</city><id>868433</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.186780</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Here is a hike that the meetup hiking group may be interested in. &lt;br /&gt;Saturday, March 26 at 9:30 am. Swift River hike in Petersham. 6 mile moderate hike. Meet at the Petersham common near the old country store. Bring lunch, water, snacks. Wear weather appropriate clothing. Depending on snow cover, stabilizers, microspikes, snow shoes, may be neccessary. Good water resistant sturdy boots will likely be needed at the least. Mud season. This is a nice scenic hike. It includes meadow, scenic forest, nice views of the Swift River, and the Indian Grinding Stones. This is a day hike. Heavy rain or snow/ice storm cancels hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please note***This hike is limited to 30 attendees with a waiting list for any canceled spots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You can check out this link for Brooks Woodland Preserve and North Common Meadow and directions to the Petersham Common....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/north-common-meadow.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/north-common-meadow.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/brooks-woodland-preserve.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/central-ma/brooks-woodland-preserve.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.google.com/search?q=petersham+common%2C+petersham%2C+ma&amp;amp;ie=utf-8&amp;amp;oe=utf-8&amp;amp;aq=t&amp;amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;amp" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.google.com/search?q=petersham+common%2C+petersham%2C+ma&amp;amp;ie=utf-8&amp;amp;oe=utf-8&amp;amp;aq=t&amp;amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;amp&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Carolyn has very sweetly invited hikers attending this event to come to her home in Petersham following this hike for a pot luck gathering. The address will be provided at the hike. Anyone planning on attending should bring a favorite dish, small sandwich platter, homemade soup or desert (enough for 6+ people) stored in a cooler if needed for food safety since we will be hiking first. Suggestion: if you don't cook or want to bother making a sandwich platter, maybe bring a couple bottles of quality juice or some nice cheese or fruit on a platter. Thank you for welcoming the group to your home Carolyn!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Meet at the Petersham Common in the Center of Petersham</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dan Bolton</member_name><member_id>11623335</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301249617000</updated><rating><average>4.61999988556</average><count>8</count></rating><why>Dan Bolton will be leading this hike. He is an experienced hiker and leader through the AMC. Petersham is a gorgeous place to explore.</why><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>30</yes_rsvp_count><created>1297996164000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Brooks Woodland Preserve Hike along the Swift River with Dan Bolton</name><id>16608800</id><headcount>27</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301146200000</time><rsvp_limit>35</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/16608800/</event_url></item>