<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a challenge?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How about hiking 17 miles, nearly 6,000 feet of elevation gain, and getting four 4K peaks and a NE Hundred Highest peak?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a long day, so we'll meet &lt;em&gt;early&lt;/em&gt; (7am) at the Oliverian Brook trailhead on the Kancamagus Highway (Rt 112) to spot a car, then head back down the Kanc to begin our hike up Pine Bend Brook trail to the Tripyramids. Then we'll&amp;nbsp;head over to the Kate Sleeper trail and across the Sleepers&amp;nbsp;to Whiteface and Passaconaway and out the Oliverian Brook trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hike is considered &lt;strong&gt;advanced&lt;/strong&gt; due to distance, pace and elevation. To sign up for this hike, you should be an experienced hiker who has recently done trips of this length--15+ miles--and elevation gain and be able to hike faster than book time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting time/place&lt;/strong&gt;: 7am at the Oliverian Brook Trailhead (GPS coordinates are: N43&lt;span style="color : #003500"&gt;&amp;deg;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;59.642 | W071&amp;deg; 21.025) Rt 112/Kancamagus Highway - about 21 miles east of Lincoln.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Google Maps indicates this is a&lt;em&gt; 3 hour drive from Boston&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two before this event.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please answer the RSVP questions in full.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you and your guests acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the Hiker Responsibility Code described at www.hikesafe.com; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Gray Subaru</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307676710000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><why>It's a great hike!</why><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304561817000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Tripyramids, Sleepers, Whiteface &amp; Passaconaway (Advanced+)</name><id>17550668</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1306666800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/17550668/</event_url></item>