<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ludcke Auditorium (looks like a church)</address_2><address_1>716 Stevens Avenue</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.683291</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>University of New England</name><city>Portland</city><id>1388103</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.293858</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Please join us for a potluck supper (still &amp;quot;best-in-town&amp;quot; by all accounts:) and a meet-and-greet with the City of Portland's Sustainability Coordinator, Ian Houseal.   We'll hear a bit from Ian on what his job is all about, what he has been working on and what he would like to accomplish.  Then we'll try some Q&amp;amp;A.  Submit a question or two when RSVPing to get the ball rolling...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The potluck/meet-and-greet &lt;b&gt;will be followed by our 3rd film in the Bad News / Good News Movie Series&lt;/b&gt;: FUEL.  This promises to be a lively film followed by an incisive group discussion as usual!  Here's the trailer:  &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=upTCSSkxlxE" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6:00 Potluck Supper (bring a dish/beverage/dessert to share + your potluck kit)&lt;br /&gt;6:30 Remarks + Discussion by Portland's Sustainability Coordinator&lt;br /&gt;7:15 FUEL The Film&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Join us for the potluck/meet-and-greet or the movie, or both.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's Ian's Bio:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ian manages the City’s energy using assets and seeks to improve the energy-efficiency of City through long-term policy, practice changes, and technology improvements as well as through energy saving projects. He is project manager for the Energy Service Contract that the City is undertaking as well as coordinator for the City’s Capital Improvement Plan.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ian came to the City of Portland from the City of Lewiston where under his direction; the City saved approximately $90,000 in energy related costs in 2009, a reduction of 5% in total energy costs. Previously to the City of Lewiston, Ian was a sustainability consultant with Stantec (formerly Jacques Whitford) working in sustainability and carbon consulting as well as in environmental site assessment and remediation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ian holds two concurrent Masters Degrees in Architecture and Regional Planning from North Carolina State University and the University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill. Ian received his undergraduate degree in Environmental Studies from Bates College. Ian is a LEED Accredited Professional, sits on the finance board of the Maine Chapter of the US Green Building Council, and is an Eagle Scout.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292026572000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>44</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285696044000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meet Portland's Sustainability Coordinator + FUEL, The Movie</name><id>14926458</id><headcount>42</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1291762800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/14926458/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/7/4/e/global_19963870.jpeg</photo_url></item>