<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>175 State Road East</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01473</zip><lat>42.558624</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wachusett Brewing Co</name><city>Westminster</city><id>4246532</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.871529</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;History &lt;br /&gt;

Wachusett Brewery founders Ned, Kevin and Quinny developed a significant appreciation for beer while attending Worcester Polytechnic Institute. Adventures in biking, canoeing, and hiking that led the trio to the northern New England states allowed them to visit some of the first operating craft breweries. Armed with a "we can do this" attitude the three cast off from their careers in engineering and biology to found the Wachusett Brewing Co. in 1993. Wachusett Country Ale was introduced to beer fans of Massachusetts the next year after lots of experimenting to get the formula just right. When Wachusett opened, the three designed and built most of the equipment; did the brewing and filling, selling and delivering, and everything else that a small startup brewery needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ned, Kevin and Quinny are now backed by some of the most passionate and capable co-workers in the industry. Wachusett Ales continue to be hand crafted with the finest ingredients available, bottled and kegged in our Westminster facility. The three have never strayed from their plan to brew and sell the freshest, highest quality beers possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founders &lt;br /&gt;

Ned LaFortune / Founder President&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Buckler / Founder Plant Engineer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Quinn / Founder Sales Manager&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tours and Tastings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Tours: &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday &amp;amp; Thursday &lt;br /&gt;

Noon - 4:00 (last tour at 3)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday &amp;amp; Saturday &lt;br /&gt;

Noon - 5:00 (last tour at 4) &lt;br /&gt;

Brewery Store Hours: &lt;br /&gt;

Wednesday &amp;amp; Saturday &lt;br /&gt;

Noon - 5:00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday &amp;amp; Friday &lt;br /&gt;

Noon - 6:00 &lt;br /&gt;

The walking tour of the brewery begins every hour on the hour. The full brewery tour takes about 30 - 45 minutes and is offered on Saturdays. The condensed tour averages about ten minutes and is offered on weekdays. Your tour guide will give you a brief history of the brewery and walk you through our brewing, cellaring and packaging. Children are welcome, but of course may not taste beer during our tasting session, which follows the walking tour. Altogether, the tour and the tasting last for about 1 hour, and tastings are limited to two (2) 2oz. samples. &lt;br /&gt;

We recommend that you call us as early as possible to make reservations for parties of more than ten. Private tours are available for larger groups. &lt;br /&gt;

Wachusett Brewery is delighted to offer this tour to our guests free of charge. However, voluntary contributions are welcome with all proceeds being donated to the Westminster Benefit Fund, a local charity helping families in need for over 19 years.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Carol Lielasus</member_name><member_id>11490496</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1341197707000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339589269000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>WACHUSETT BREWERY TOUR... Steamline Tr(1.2mi) and S.S. Lobster</name><id>68974292</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1341086400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/68974292/</event_url></item>