<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Let's get together and play these three great card games that are perfect for 7 players:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.  Bang!  --  In the wild West, the Outlaws hunt the Sheriff, the Sheriff hunts the Outlaws, and the Renegade plots in secret, ready to join one side or the other.  Before long bullets start to fly!  Which gunmen are Deputies, ready to sacrifice themselves for the Sheriff?  And which are the merciless Outlaws, looking to gun him down?  &lt;a href="http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/3955/bang"&gt;http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/3955/bang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.  Pit  --  In this loud, real-time trading game, players are given the task of cornering the market in one type of commodity. There are as many suits as there are players, and all the cards are dealt out at the start of each round. When the trading begins, players offer sets of cards to each other in the hopes of completing a set for themselves. If you're successful, you ring the (optional)bell and yell out, "Corner on wheat!" (or whatever your commodity is). You then score points depending on which it was - some are more valuable than others. Two cards labeled Bull and Bear may be used to add wild/penalty cards to the gameplay. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/140/pit"&gt;http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/140/pit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.  Wizard  --&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shades of &lt;a href="http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/1116/oh-hell"&gt;Oh Hell!&lt;/a&gt;. With a 60 card deck comprising a standard deck plus 4 Wizards (high) and 4 Jesters (low). In the first hand 1 card is dealt to each player. In the second 2 and so on. The game is over after the hand in which all cards are dealt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After examining your cards you state the number of tricks you will win. Each round each player puts down one card. The first Wizard played wins the trick, followed by the highest trump card, followed by the highest card in the suit of the first card played. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;a href="http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/1465/wizard"&gt;http://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/1465/wizard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a game or two of your own, if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the usual skinny:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to limited space, each member can RSVP only for themselves +1 guest.  There will be a waiting list if we fill up, so please, please change your RSVP if your plans change so someone else can take your spot.  Please bring $1 for Nina to keep this awesome Meetup group going.  BYOB -- alcohol or not is fine.  I'll have some chips, etc. on hand, but feel free to bring a snack to share if you wish.  Please provide your phone number when you RSVP so I can call you in case of any last minute changes.  My number will be provided as well.  Please make a note of it and USE it if your plans change at the last minute, if you're running late, or if you just have questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look forward to seeing you on the 10th!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll send parking instructions and further info to "yes" RSVPs a few days before the event.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1340157676000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>CardBoard Players</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-CardBoard-Players-Club</urlname><id>1390924</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The CardBoard Players Club of Connecticut</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339198129000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Bang!, Pit, and Wizard (Three Great Card Games) at Mitch's Place</name><id>68378952</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1340058600000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-CardBoard-Players-Club/events/68378952/</event_url></item>