<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>[We're all set with the birds (not nesting anymorein the part of the beach we're walking on), so this trip is a go...]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS WILL BE A AFTERNOON/EVENING EVENT.     Plum Island is an island next to Newburyport on the North Shore.  The island includes a town on one half, and a nature reservation on the other called the Parker River National Wildlife Refuge.   We will meet with our cars in front of the gate to the refuge, prior to the refuge pay gatehouse (its $5 to enter reservation per car) at 3:30 pm.  We will then enter the reservation, we will drive several miles down a dirt road, and park at parking lot 6.   The walk will begin there.  We will walk along the beach around the tip of the island (going south), and then return.  I did this last year, and it was a beautiful beach walk-the tip of the island is really cool with pools of water and rocks and a view of Crane's beach.  Depending on what people want to do, we can hang out for a little bit on the beach after the walk.  What I'm hoping is people will want to hang out until 7pm at the reservation - it is really beautiful at the time.    Afterwords, we will then have dinner at the Grog in Newburport, which is a fun restaurant/bar with seafood and other food.  Carpooling strongly encouraged.  I can take up to three others in my car. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I suggest bringing bug repellant (for flies, mosquitos in the evening).  Bring a bathing suit etc. if you want to swim after the walk.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After the group walk, if we have time, and people want to wander around on their own for a bit,  that's fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link with some details on Plum Island and the reservation: &lt;a href="http://www.plum-island.com/description.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.plum-islan...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a link to a map of the reservation.  &lt;a href="http://www.fws.gov/northeast/parkerriver/map.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.fws.gov/no...&lt;/a&gt;  We'll probably drive from the gatehouse to beach #5, and walk from there to the South edge of the island and back, but that plan may change depending on where the birds decide to nest....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Boston to the refuge gatehouse: Distances approximate: the refuge is located 35 miles (56.3 kilometers) north of Boston near the City of Newburyport. From Route 95 take exit 57 and travel east on Route 113, then continue straight onto Route 1A South to the intersection with Rolfe?s Lane for a total of 3.5 miles (5.6 kilometers). Turn left onto Rolfe?s Lane and travel 0.5 miles (0.8 kilometers) to its end. Turn right onto the Plum Island Turnpike and travel 2.0 miles (3.2 kilometers) crossing the Sgt. Donald Wilkinson Bridge to Plum Island. Take your first right onto Sunset Drive and travel 0.5 miles (0.8 kilometers) to the refuge entrance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's some info on the Grog:&lt;br /&gt;Address:&lt;br /&gt;13 Middle Street&lt;br /&gt;Newburyport, MA 01950&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 978.465.8008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thegrog.com/main.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.thegrog.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Greg</member_name><member_id>2750937</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1185924410000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>social walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Boston-Walking</urlname><id>341292</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1200027466</group_lon><name>The Boston Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1181959127000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Plum Island/Wildlife Refuge Beach Walk</name><id>5896835</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1185651000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Walking/events/5896835/</event_url></item>