<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Route 9 and Pleasant St.  </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01002</zip><lat>42.373192</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Amherst Common</name><city>Amherst</city><id>4488402</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.519783</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This will be our way of keeping Christ in Christmas.&amp;nbsp;We would like to have volunteers to show up in costume so that we can represent the Nativity. If possible, we could use people who would be willing to portray Mary, Joseph, the 3 wisemen, shepards and maybe some angels. There will be no speaking parts. It would be great if we could have enough volunteers to portray a kind of "living" Nativity. Along with that, some folks could bring signs relating to the Christmas message. It is a wonderful opportunity to show those people who are attempting to destroy our Christian heritage, that we will not tolerate their bullying. It is also a great way to witness our faith to the GP. Hopefully we can get someone to bring a boom box with a CD of the traditional Christmas songs&amp;nbsp;;ieSilent Night, etc, that we can either sing to or just listen. This is NOT a political rally, but a celebration of the real meaning of Christmas. We also have access to costumes through the Abbey Theatre in Hardwick.&amp;nbsp; Let's bundle up, have some hot cocoa and cookies and enjoy our time together for this special rally.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will meet and have our standout at the intersection of Route 9 and Pleasant St.  There is parking available along the side street by the common.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Denise Baran</member_name><member_id>9211691</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1324149531000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>We Surround Them</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>The-Western-Mass-912-Project</urlname><id>1394602</id><group_lat>42.2000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6299972534</group_lon><name>The Original WMass 912 Project</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1321586344000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CHRISTMAS RALLY FOR JESUS</name><id>41589922</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1324144800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Western-Mass-912-Project/events/41589922/</event_url></item>