<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Note that the actual starting time is 3:50. I'm not familiar with this play, but I'm intrigued by the premise and background. As with all French Film Festival movies, getting your ticket in advance is always advised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About the film:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Screen Illusion (L’Illusion comique)&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span&gt;by Mathieu Amalric (2011, 77 min.). Amalric accepted La Comédie-Française’s challenge to adapt a classic French play in 12 days without changing a single line of dialogue. Amalric’s clever update of Pierre Corneille’s 17th-century tragicomedy follows a hotel concierge (a magician in Corneille’s text) on the trail of a missing young man. By finding ingenious solutions for the play’s characters, Amalric succeeds in maintaining the spirit of the 1636 five-act play. “French acting at its very best . . . a perfect fusion between screen and stage modes” (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Screen Daily&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;). Jeff Kline, Professor of French at Boston University, introduces the July 15 screening.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The action takes in near-farce in hotel rooms and bars, a rooftop shootout, and a nightclub climax in which a last-minute reveal whisks away the screen of dramatic illusion. Throughout, the dialogue is delivered immaculately in Corneille’s formal verse, and despite much playful anachronism, Amalric’s vision never feels forced onto the play. Whether characters type out their soliloquies as emails, or perform them while smashing up luxury cars, the film offers a fresh and fitting rethink of heritage material." - ScreenDaily.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the film we'll go to an area restaurant for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>After the film I'll be near the front of the theater with a Meetup sign.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa</member_name><member_id>1230356</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342393016000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1342147258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Screen Illusion -- French Film Festival @ MFA</name><id>73146762</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342381500000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/73146762/</event_url></item>