<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>270 Tremont St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.350281</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 482-9393</phone><name>Wang Theater</name><city>Boston</city><id>746723</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065140</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Fab Faux are without a doubt the most musically satisfying Beatles tribute band on the scene today. Boasting the high visibility of TV star/musicians Will Lee from The Late Show with David Letterman and Jimmy Vivino from Late Night with Conan O'Brien; five strong lead vocalists (including Rich Pagano, Frank Agnello, Jack Petruzzelli) and a commitment to the accurate reproduction of The Beatles' repertoire; this is the band to see if you want to know what it might have been like if The Beatles toured behind their later albums (with a healthy portion of the early guitar-based stuff that most tribute bands play.) Imagine hearing complex material like &amp;quot;Strawberry Fields Forever&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;I Am the Walrus&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;Being for the Benefit of Mr. Kite&amp;quot;, performed in complete part-perfect renditions; or such harmony-driven songs as &amp;quot;Because&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Nowhere Man&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;Paperback Writer&amp;quot;, reproduced not only note-for-note, but with extra vocalists available to achieve a double-tracked effect!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since their formation in the spring of '98, the Fab Faux have created a buzz among Beatles fans in the New York City area; packing The Bowery Ballroom, Webster Hall, Irving Plaza, The Bottom Line, and The China Club with high energy shows; for an audience liberally sprinkled with fellow musicians, celebrities, and fans alike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apparently, people have taken notice, as the group was featured in a full-length profile on CNN that was broadcast all over the world on several of that network's programs; and participated in a CD of original material by Beatles tribute bands, recorded in London at Abbey Road Studios! Since August '99, the group has performed multiple times in Liverpool, England, where they play three shows each year for that city's annual Beatle Week festivities, including outdoor concerts for over 35,000 people on the Apple-sponsored Yellow Submarine and Let It Be stages.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, for Beatles fans (and music fans), the choice is clear: If you want to hear songs recreated that were written, arranged, and performed with a genius and talent sadly missing from today's music scene; if you're too young to remember what all the fuss was about; or if you just want to see one of the best live rock bands performing today, look no further than The Fab Faux....&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>RSVP</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael </member_name><member_id>8251672</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256601980000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Brunch Lovers</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Brunch-Lovers-Wanted</urlname><id>1307817</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Brunch &amp; More (20/30-Somethings for brunch &amp; more, etc...)</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255231233000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Fab Faux  - One of the Best Beatles tribute bands on the scene today!</name><id>11598964</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1256428800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Brunch-Lovers-Wanted/events/11598964/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/4/global_11150276.jpeg</photo_url></item>