<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>71 Cedar St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01748</zip><lat>42.244067</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508) 435-4303</phone><name>hopkinton state park</name><city>Hopkinton</city><id>682991</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.525779</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join us for Baypath's 3rd annual Paws &amp;amp; Claws 5K Run/Walk, Sunday, October 23rd, 2011 11am... Enjoy the gorgeous USATF certified 5K course at Hopkinton State Park... There is truly no better place to be on a lovely Fall day, while supporting Baypath, a no-kill animal shelter proudly serving the region for over 30 years... We welcome participants of all skill levels, from walkers through to elite runners - including those who run with their (leashed) dogs! NEW: Register &amp;amp; Help Us Fundraise!! This year when you Register online you will also get a personal Sponsorship page so your Friends and Family can sponsor you for the 5K online! It's Easy! You can set your Fundraising goal, Add a Picture, and personalize a message, and send Email requests to all of your friends, family and colleagues to Sponsor you! You can bring in your daily email contact list from Outlook, Yahoo or Gmail! Promote your Walk page on Facebook and Twitter! Check your page often. It's FUN watching your personal fundraising goal thermometer go up toward your goal knowing you are helping the wonderful animals of Baypath!... 5K Event Questions: Contact Brenda- BrendaHD@BaypathHumane.org Any Questions with online Registration or Sponsorship: Contact Jeff- jeffm@baypathhumane.org... Visit www.baypathhumane.org for more info!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Cassie-Leigh Stock</member_name><member_id>8663419</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1320506887000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Responsible Bully Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nebbc1</urlname><id>1356904</id><group_lat>42.2200012207</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5299987793</group_lon><name>New England Bully Breed Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314140585000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BayPath Humane Society's 3rd Annual 5k Walk/Run Event</name><id>30631811</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1319382000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nebbc1/events/30631811/</event_url></item>