<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Walk off the calories before you even consume them with this fairly easy 2-3 mile jaunt at the Belding Wildlife Management Area in Vernon.  This is a very pretty property, with a couple of streams and a pond where the doggies can swim.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have not been there, the trail head I use can be hard to find, so we will meet at the 7-11 on Route 30 in Vernon at 9:00 and proceed to the trailhead on Tamarack Lane at 9:15.  If you know where the trailhead is, feel free to meet us there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dogs and kids are welcome.  I will have my very energetic and very large 6-month-old puppy with me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gloria&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;=== Legal Stuff === &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Gloria</member_name><member_id>1099810</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1246885748000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1246627880000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A pre-holiday barbecue walk</name><id>10795630</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1246712400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/10795630/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/a/e/a/global_5696794.jpeg</photo_url></item>