<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>First, THANKS everybody who braved one of the chilliest, windiest nights&lt;br /&gt;to join us at our March meetup. Your heartfelt presence and enthusiastic&lt;br /&gt;participation warmed us right away!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THANKS much again to Diane D'Souza and Leah Shapiro&lt;br /&gt;( &lt;a href="http://www.law-of-attraction-coach-boston.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.law-of-att...&lt;/a&gt; ) for leading us &lt;br /&gt;in wonderful discussions and activities.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wow, it's great that we'll be seeing a lot of you next week who've&lt;br /&gt;enthusiastically being there for each other from the beginning of our&lt;br /&gt;Boston LOA meetup. Was it only 3 months ago that we first met?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're doubly blessed that you're sharing our meetup with others&lt;br /&gt;and bringing them along too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and YES, a BIG WELCOME to our new members. We look forward to&lt;br /&gt;supporting you in your LOA journey as we appreciate your support for us too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;========&lt;br /&gt;AGENDA for our APRIL meetup next Tuesday, April 3rd, 7 pm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(1) Dave Buck will unveil our first &amp;quot;virtual&amp;quot; study group &amp;amp; topic.&lt;br /&gt;Folks who's at meetup will have first dips to sign up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(2) We are delighted to have a special guest, Rob Kanzer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Topic: Ask, Believe, Receive: Find Your Voice Inside and Out to&lt;br /&gt;Deliberately Create What You Want&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you suffer from unclear vision and frustration or&lt;br /&gt;you simply want to be more powerful in deliberately manifest your desires...&lt;br /&gt;Life and Business Coach Rob Kanzer can help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your ability to connect and engage your inner power&lt;br /&gt;starts with your own passion and beliefs. Come with the&lt;br /&gt;desires you want to deliberately create and be willing to try&lt;br /&gt;really fun ways to give voice to your desires simply yet&lt;br /&gt;powerfully.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be ready to receive ... don't be surprised to get what you&lt;br /&gt;want this evening! :-)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our time together is always one of engagement... inspiring and safe,&lt;br /&gt;to have you learn, feel and give voice to your desires.&lt;br /&gt;Be willing to ask, share with each other and receive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Kanzer, President of The Cambridge Coaching Collaborative,&lt;br /&gt;since 1981 continues to provide powerful, life changing&lt;br /&gt;improvements for companies and individuals that seek true&lt;br /&gt;personal and professional transformation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A successful entrepreneur in his own right, Rob is a Crisis Intervention&lt;br /&gt;Counselor, certified mediator and Master Presenter.&lt;br /&gt;He combines traditional and his own &amp;quot;true life curriculum&amp;quot; that&lt;br /&gt;you can adapt to your own needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You're welcomed to contact Rob directly for some free coaching&lt;br /&gt;prior to our meetup.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RobKanzer@RobKanzer.com&lt;br /&gt;(617) 491-8939&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.RobKanzer.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.RobKanzer....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Seating is limited, so please remember to RSVP Today!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Buck</member_name><member_id>2466801</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>18</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1175964857000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>Law of Attraction Co-Creators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>lawofattraction-us</urlname><id>368525</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>The Boston Law of Attraction Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>64</yes_rsvp_count><created>1172712047000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April MeetUp</name><id>5524195</id><headcount>48</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1175641200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/lawofattraction-us/events/5524195/</event_url></item>