<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>suggested donation</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per adult</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;We have been invited by David Spahr (illustrious and prodigious contributor to our message boards) to visit his place in Washington, Maine for a garden/forage/mushroom walk&lt;/b&gt;.  As many of you know, David has years of experience and experimentation under his belt with regard to mushrooms,edible perennials and annuals as well as wild foraging in general.  He looks forward to sharing much of that with us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Suggested agenda:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:00am Arrival / Introductions / General background from David &lt;br /&gt;9:30am Begin walk/forage &lt;br /&gt;Noon - Potluck Lunch (don't forget your potluck kit of dish/bowl/utensils/napkin/cup) &lt;br /&gt;1:00pm-ish Depart back to Portland &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please dress in layers for the weather.&lt;/b&gt;  Bring good walking shoes/boots as well as any desired sunscreen and bug repellent.  I recommend bringing drinking water and possibly a little snack to carry on the walk if you think you might need that.   &lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bring digging stuff and empty pots if you would like to take away some plants, shrubs and trees that David can spare from his property.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;David is moving in the direction of doing this sort of thing for a living.  There is a suggested donation of $15 for adults and $10 for 18 and under.  Free for 12 and under.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility note:&lt;/b&gt;  This particular walk/forage will be fairly &amp;quot;hardy.&amp;quot;  If you have some mobility challenges, you are welcome to join us for the brief discussion at the beginning and the potluck lunch to follow, but the walk itself may not be feasible or comfortable for you.  Contact LisaF with questions regarding this. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carpooling:&lt;/b&gt;  I encourage people to carpool from Portland as this is a little bit of a drive.  I suggest meeting at the Marginal Way Park-and-Ride (adjacent to Franklin Arterial) at about 7:20 for an 7:30 departure.  Please post to the carpool thread on the message boards if you would like to hook up with someone to give/get a lift.  Don't forget to exchange mobile phone numbers if applicable and I suggest sharing the cost of fuel.  Here is a google driving map: &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;saddr=portland+maine&amp;amp;daddr=16+nelson+ridge+road+south,+washington+maine&amp;amp;sll=43.969175,-69.812105&amp;amp;sspn=0.847032,1.636963&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=43.969098,-69.822235&amp;amp;spn=0.847032,1.636963&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=10" target="_blank"&gt;http://maps.google.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Lisa Fernandes</member_name><member_id>2324592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216721078000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1214252810000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Garden/Forage/Mushroom Walk with David Spahr in Washington, Maine</name><id>8199200</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1216472400000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/8199200/</event_url></item>