<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Summer is nearing its end so let's get out and hiking while we still can! The first hike of the Wedeln late summer season will be the Welch-Dickey loop near Campton NH. We will follow the Welch-Dickey Loop trail up Welch Mountain,across to Dickey Mountain, and then down Dickey to the trailhead. Along the way there are multiple great views on the way up of the Waterville Valley area and Sandwich Range Wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will begin the hike from the Welch-Dickey Trailhead (there will be a Forest service fee of a couple dollars per car) around 10:00 AM. The trailhead is approximately 125 miles from Boston MA and will take about 2 hours to travel to. To get to the trailhead, take I-93 North into NH to Exit 28, Rt. 49. Head east on 49 for about 5.5 miles and take a left onto upper Mad River Rd. Follow Upper Mad River Road for .7 Miles and turn Right on Orris Rd. The trailhead Perking lot will be a little more than half a mile on the right. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This moderate pace loop hike will cover 4.5 miles and climb about 1,800 feet. It is considered an INTERMEDIATE hike due to the pace, distance, and some of the rock scrambles on the ascent.  If you have ANY questions about your ability to participate in and complete this entire event please contact me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start as a group, stay as a group, and finish as a group. Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker in the group. If you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us or want to head off on your own, this isn't the trip for you. Likewise, this trip isn't for you if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you or want us to go on without you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dangerous weather conditions will cancel this hike - I will email all confirmed participants a day or two before the hike to update everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.weather.com/weather/today/USNH0027" target="_blank"&gt;Click here for the current weather forecast for this trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a list describing the highly recommended clothing and equipment for participating in this event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    * Footwear: Hiking boots/Trail shoes.&lt;br /&gt;    * Clothing: Dress in layers to easily regulate body temperature. Wear synthetic shirt/pants and bring a fleece jacket/wool sweater.&lt;br /&gt;    * Food and Water: High-energy snacks, food for lunch, and at least two quarts of water.&lt;br /&gt;    * Other Essential Gear: Map and compass. Plastic whistle. Headlamp with spare batteries. An emergency space blanket (e.g. mylar). Small pocket knife or multi-purpose tool. Trekking poles (optional). Toilet kit (e.g. hand sanitizer, toilet paper and a zip-lock bag to pack out your used personal hygiene items). Sunscreen. Lip balm. Waterproof cover for your pack. Camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will bring a group first aid kit that contains basic items but you will need to bring any medications or medical supplies that you may need during the trip. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>George Fraley</member_name><member_id>10925592</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1283008579000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1282094279000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Welch-Dickey Hike</name><id>14456904</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1283004000000</time><rsvp_limit>15</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/14456904/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/8/global_14726280.jpeg</photo_url></item>