<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions will follow soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm planning to trek in to Owl's Head as a very long day hike on &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, June 11th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will likely camp in the area on Friday night to get an early start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be a moderately paced hike - &lt;strong&gt;I'm not a fast hiker but I do keep moving&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the distance involved, please demonstrate (via the RSVP questions) that you have been hiking long distances recently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a very wet trail&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;nbsp;I've also been told it's "boring" because of the lack of views and relatively easy grade (until you reach the Owl's Head Path, which is steep). &amp;nbsp;For that reason, I'm considering doing the full route around Owl's Head instead of making this an out-and-back. &amp;nbsp;The group can decide what they want to do when they complete the ascent to the summit. &amp;nbsp;Doing it this way would add 3.6 miles and two hours at a pace of about 1.5 miles per hour. &amp;nbsp;Be prepared to come out in the dark. &amp;nbsp;I'm hoping that given the minimal elevation gain, we will exceed 1.5 miles per hour, but this is the pace I use to calculate for my hikes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My hikes are always dog-friendly, however, since this is a long day, please make sure that your dogs are experienced hikers and not disruptive when camping or climbing. &amp;nbsp;I will have both my "boys" with me - they need this peak too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will post trail descriptions from the AMC guide shortly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a traverse, so we will not have to carpool. &amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;We will meet in the lot of the Visitor's Center at Lincoln Woods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be prepared for cold and potentially poor weather conditions. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&amp;nbsp;This is a very WET trail, so come prepared to stay dry. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;DO NOT WEAR COTTON OR DENIM. This is dangerous especially in cool/wet weather. If you have questions about how to prepare or how to dress, ask them in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Answers to FAQs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunset on Saturday will be at 8:26 pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because this is a LONG hike, headlamps are require&lt;/strong&gt;d.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This hike is not very exposed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no hut along this trail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will START AND FINISH TOGETHER. If you cannot hold your speed down to match that of the group (if necessary), this is not the hike for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I (Kate) am not a speedy hiker, but I do keep a steady pace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the conditions are prohibitive, I have no qualms about turning around. The mountain will be there another day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will watch the weather carefully and post weather updates during the week leading up to the hike. Il rely on NOAA and MWObs for my forecasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most of the payoff comes in the form enjoying the outdoors (Owl's Head does not have fabulous views), SO if the weather looks like it will be miserable, we will reschedule to Sunday if possible. Please plan accordingly.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000080"&gt;RSVP Questions are not optional - I may delete your 'going' RSVP and/or will not take you from the waiting list if I don't see your answers. &amp;nbsp; If you do not provide me with a phone number to try and contact you on the morning/evening of the hike (if necessary), we will NOT wait for you at the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I &amp;nbsp;will provide attendees with my cell phone number in advance of the hike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book time is about &amp;nbsp;12 or 14 hrs &amp;amp; &amp;nbsp;18 or 21.6 miles depending on the route taken&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plagerized Trail Descriptions for your benefit&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;----------------------------------------------------------&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; the Appalachian Mountain Club. All rights reserved do not distribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lincoln Woods Trail to Franconia Brook Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.9 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;300 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 hr 35 min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Franconia Brook Trail to Lincoln Brook Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.7 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;300 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 hr&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lincoln Brook Trail to Owl's Head Slide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.4 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;800 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 hours 10 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Owl's Head Path&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 mile&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1500 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 hr 15 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total to the summit: &amp;nbsp;9 miles - 6 hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total out-and-back (returning the way we came): &amp;nbsp;18 miles - 12 hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXIT ROUTE IF WE TAKE THE LOOP AROUND THE BASE OF THE MOUNTAIN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Owl's Head Path&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 mile&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1500 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 hr 15 minutes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lincoln Brook Trail to Franconia Brook Trail (northern junction)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.5 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;650 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Franconia Brook Trail (East side of the base of the mountain) to Lincoln Woods Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.2 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;750 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 hours&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lincoln Woods Trail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.9 miles&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;300 feet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 hr 35 min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total route round the base of the mountain: &amp;nbsp;21.6 miles &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14 hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;DISCLAIMER: MY ROLE AS ORGANIZER IN THIS HIKE IS SOCIAL. I AM NOT TRAINED TO BE A GUIDE, NOR HAVE I RECEIVED TRAINING OR INSTRUCTION IN HIKING SAFETY OR WINTER HIKING. WHILE I TRY TO HEAD OFF SOME OF THE PROBLEMS I HAVE SEEN (OR EXPERIENCED OR EVEN CAUSED) IN THE PAST, MY UNDERSTANDING IS THAT YOU WILL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY. IF MY DISAPPEARANCE DURING THIS TRIP WOULD CAUSE YOU MORE THAN ANNOYANCE AND INCONVENIENCE, THIS IS NOT THE TRIP FOR YOU. THERE ARE ALWAYS RISKS IN HIKING IN THE MOUNTAINS. IF YOU ARE NOT CONFIDENT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THE RISKS, PLEASE DO NOT SIGN UP (or change your RSVP to no). I HAVE NOT CLIMBED THESE PEAKS BEFORE AND HAVE DONE ALL MY RESEARCH VIA GUIDEBOOKS, INTERNET AND ADVICE FROM OTHER HIKERS, SO IT IS POSSIBLE THAT SOME INFORMATION IS NOT ACCURATE. I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING STUPID OR MINDLESS MISTAKES, SO PLEASE DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH AND COME PREPARED WITH APPROPRIATE KNOWLEDGE, EQUIPMENT AND JUDGMENT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Green Honda Civic, usually a Meetup Sign in the window &amp; 2 dogs</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kate K </member_name><member_id>9984045</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1307891208000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><why>You've seen it from every possible vantage point in the Pemi, but you still haven't been there yet! Plus, I/you need it for my/your 48 4kers!</why><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1304945970000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH 48:  Owl's Head</name><id>17690461</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1307790000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/17690461/</event_url></item>