<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Boston</address_2><address_1>Huntington Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.337310</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Museum of Fine Arts</name><city>Boston</city><id>161132</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.096830</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Draughtsman?s Contract is the movie that established Peter Greenaway?s reputation as one of Britain?s foremost and most original filmmakers.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Made in 1982, Draughtsman is set in late Seventeeth century England. A young painter called Mr. Neville is commissioned by a lady Hebert to make 12 drawings of her countryside estate. Neville agrees in return for free sexual favors from Lady Hebert. The arrogant and meticulously naturalistic painter, bent on drawing the estate exactly how his eyes see it down to the very last details, imposes strict, almost despotic rules on the estate?s owners and guests: they?re instructed where to exactly stand and what to wear, and asked not to move even the most trivial and inconspicuous object out of the scenery. But the painter?s plan slowly goes astray as mysterious articles start making their way into his true-to-life canvas. As rumors of Mr. Hebert?s murder start circulating, sinister and hidden motives are progressively revealed.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Draughtsman is a dense and multi-layered work. It is an intricate and mind-boggling erotic murder mystery, a study of class, family and religious relations in Restoration-era England, and an incisive critique of naturalistic tendencies in art, all rolled into one. It combines a deliberately artificial visual style (mannerist acting, excessive makeup, gorgeous and deliberate framing, sumptuous surroundings, baroque music, and lots of wigs, fancy dresses and exquisite banquets) with witty, incisive and almost delirious dialogue, written by Greenaway himself. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everybody?s favorite critic, Roger Ebert, gives it four stars and declares ?I have never seen a film quite like it? But after it's over you may need hours of discussion with your friends before you can be sure (if even then) exactly what happened.?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The MFA is playing Draughtsman in a new, restored print. A Zed and Two Noughts, another Greenaway classic (and a movie that makes Draughtsman seem like a Disney family attraction) will also be shown on that same weekend.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mfa.org/calendar/event.asp?eventkey=31117&amp;amp;date=12/8/2007" target="_blank"&gt;Link to MFA Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom Green</member_name><member_id>1984564</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198308785000</updated><rating><average>4.19999980927</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196009272000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Draughtsman?s Contract - A Film by Peter Greenaway</name><id>6799708</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197139500000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/6799708/</event_url></item>