<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>294 Cabot Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01915</zip><lat>42.551907</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-922-0004</phone><name>Organic Garden Cafe</name><city>Beverly</city><id>598589</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.879082</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Why We Love Dogs, Eat Pigs, and Wear Cows: An Introduction to Carnism

[img]&lt;a href="http://www.dovertownlibrary.org/why-we-love-dogs-eat-pigs-and-wear-cows-an-introduction-to-carnism.jpg[/img" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.dovertownlibrary.org/why-we-love-dogs-eat-pigs-and-wear-cows-an-introduction-to-carnism.jpg[/img&lt;/a&gt;]

In her groundbreaking new book, Why We Love Dogs, Eat Pigs, and Wear Cows, Melanie Joy explores the invisible system that shapes our perception of the meat we eat, so that we love some animals and eat others without knowing why. She calls this system carnism. Carnism is the belief system, or ideology, that allows us to selectively choose which animals become our meat, and it is sustained by complex psychological and social mechanisms. Like other “isms” (racism, sexism, etc.), carnism is most harmful when it is unrecognized and unacknowledged. Why We Love Dogs, Eat Pigs, and Wear Cows names and explains this phenomenon and offers it up for examination. Unlike the many books that explain why we shouldn’t eat meat, Joy’s book explains why we do eat meat—and thus how we can make more informed choices as citizens and consumers.

Melanie Joy is a Harvard-educated psychologist, author, and personal/relationship coach. She teaches psychology and sociology at the University of Massachusetts, Boston. Dr. Joy has written a number of articles on psychology, animal rights, and social justice, which have been published in academic and popular journals and magazines. Dr. Joy is the leading researcher on carnism, the psychology and ideology of meat, and she has been interviewed for numerous magazines, books, and radio on her work, including the BBC, NPR, PBS, ABC Australia, and the prestigious Le Scienze, the Italian edition of Scientific American. She has also presented her work at national and international academic and grassroots conferences. Dr. Joy is also the author of the activist handbook, Strategic Action for Animals. Refreshments for this event will be served at 6:30 pm, and the presentation starts at 7 pm. 

[url=&lt;a href="http://www.carnism.com][b]www.carnism.com[/b][/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.carnism.com][b]www.carnism.com[/b][/url&lt;/a&gt;]

&lt;xobject width="467" height="281"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/v3CsceN26_E&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;fs=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="467" height="281" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

[url=&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3CsceN26_E]www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3CsceN26_E[/url" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3CsceN26_E]www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3CsceN26_E[/url&lt;/a&gt;]</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292880387000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1291180287000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Melanie Joy, PhD, Author; FREE Talk</name><id>15604761</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292076900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/15604761/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/7/2/1/global_12599921.jpeg</photo_url></item>