<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>727 East Avenue</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02860</zip><lat>41.858219</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Rasoi Restaurant</name><city>Pawtucket</city><id>7882582</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.391556</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;From the RIVA Website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come Celebrate the New Year with Rhode Island Vegan Awareness!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~Rhode Island Vegan Awareness will be hosting our annual totally Vegan &amp;amp; Gluten Free New Year's Brunch at Rasoi!!! Rasoi is a delicious Indian restaurant located at 727 East Avenue in Pawtucket, RI 02860~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details….&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brunch will be served buffet style and the cost is $11.99 a person. Please note that this is the price for the delicious buffet only and does not include gratuity or additional beverages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, RIVA will be asking for a $3.00 suggested donation as a way to raise addition funds for our outreach events and programs. This is totally optional!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will be held on Saturday, January 5th, 2013 and will begin promptly at 12:00pm!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important Note: The doors for the event will open at 11:30am and the buffet will begin very promptly at noon. We are asking that everyone arrive between 11:30am-11:45am. We want to ensure that all those in the RIVA Party get seated next to each other and late arrivals in the past have made this difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come see old friends and meet new friends! This is an open event, open to RIVA members and non-members (as well as vegans and non-vegans alike). We would love to make this our biggest New Year's Celebration yet!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The celebration will also include some special holiday fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secret Santa!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone attending the event is encouraged to bring a wrapped “Secret Santa” gift valued at around $10.00. The gift can be anything and can even be something totally silly! Perhaps something you received as a holiday gift and would like to re gift? There is no need to purchase something (unless you would like to) this meant to be silly fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please RSVP for this event no later than December 31, 2012 by calling RIVA at 401-919-2058 or e-mailing RIVA@veganawareness.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also post on our Facebook event wall if you plan to attend and how many people will be attending however; simply joining the Facebook event is not a sufficient RSVP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please remember that the success of this event depends on the accuracy of the RSVP count. If for some reason you are not able to attend we ask that you give us as much notice as possible so that we may plan accordingly and provide the restaurant with appropriate numbers. Thank You for your cooperation and we are looking forward to seeing you in the New Year!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhode Island Vegan Awareness, the non-profit organization hosting the event, is dedicated to raising awareness about the benefits of a vegan diet and how it is one of the most powerful ways to improve health and reduce animal suffering and environmental devastation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin</member_name><member_id>7947968</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357414667000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1353549517000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Celebrate the New Year with Rhode Island Vegan Awareness</name><id>92380272</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357403400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/92380272/</event_url></item>