<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>amazon</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>26.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to The Nation's Premier Hiking Event! &lt;br /&gt;

 Seek the Peak welcomes hikers of all ages and abilities from around the world to the rugged, windswept trails of Mount Washington, New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boasting world-class alpine trekking and stunning views to the Atlantic Ocean, Canada, the Adirondack mountains and beyond, Mount Washington is the pinnacle of the New England hiking scene. Scaling its windswept summit as a participant in Seek the Peak offers an immensely rewarding physical challenge, while benefitting a great cause: the legendary Mount Washington Observatory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsored by Subaru and Eastern Mountain Sports, Seek the Peak is Mount Washington Observatory's largest fundraiser. Since the event was founded in 2001, Seek the Peak has raised nearly $1,000,000 for the nonprofit institution, helping it maintain its famous weather station on the summit of Mount Washington and continue its important work collecting weather data, performing research, and educating the public about the science of climate and weather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participating in Seek the Peak is not only fun, but rewarding, too. Participants are thanked for their efforts with awesome freebies, a kick-off party, tours of our famous mountaintop weather station, and a huge after party with live music, great food, and thousands of dollars in prize giveaways. It's easy to see why Seek the Peak has grown to become the nation's premier hiking event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab your pack and join us: Mount Washington is calling!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.seekthepeak.oirg"&gt;http://www.seekthepeak.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Note - You must visit the seek the peak website to sign up to hike Mount Washington.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Costs here only reflect guest fees at the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Karen will be leading you from the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club base located on the North Conway / Bartlett line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accommodations are $25 per guest per night - 1 Night $25 Minimum + $1 Amazon Payments Fee - &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #99be87"&gt;Total $26 due now. If you stay an extra night, you must pay in cash or check&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;No Refunds!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Rooms are separated by gender and are dorm style. Shared bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is NOT a hotel. You are expected to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bring your own sheets, blanket pillow or sleeping bag and pillow&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bring Flip Flops for shower, towel, tolietries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You may use our kitchen - but you are responsible to bring your own food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- You will be responsible to help keep the club clean. This may consist of a light duty like kitchen clean up, vacuum a hallway, or bathroom cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For any questions, please contact Jonathan Magsino @ jonathan.magsino@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agenda &lt;br /&gt;

 2012 Schedule &lt;br /&gt;

 Friday, July 20, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12:00 – 7:00 PM: Registration &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: Mount Washington Observatory Weather Discovery Center, North Conway Village &lt;br /&gt;

 Stop by our Weather Discovery Center anytime between 12 and 8 PM on Friday to turn in any remaining donations, pick up your goodie bag and t-shirt, and discuss trail options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 - Check in at the Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5:00 – 8:00 PM: Kick-Off Party (Optional) &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: Mount Washington Observatory Weather Discovery Center, North Conway Village &lt;br /&gt;

 Join us for appetizers, refreshments and mingling in our interactive science museum. Bring the family and stay as long as you like: there are hands-on exhibits for kids of all ages!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, July 21, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6:00 – 9:00 AM: Trailhead Send-Off &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: AMC's Pinkham Notch Visitor Center &lt;br /&gt;

 If you missed registration on Friday, you can drop off your donations right at the trailhead and get underway! We'll bring your t-shirt and goodie bag to the after party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9:30 AM – 3:00 PM: Weather Station Tours &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: Summit weather station &lt;br /&gt;

 When you make it to the summit, pop in to our legendary summit weather station for a complimentary behind-the-scenes tour and refreshments with the crew!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4:00 – 7:00 PM: Outdoor Expo, After Party &amp;amp; Annual Meeting &lt;br /&gt;

 Location: Base of the Mt. Washington Auto Road &lt;br /&gt;

 Celebrate a great day with good friends, live music, great giveaways, and a sumptuous dinner! The party also includes an outdoor expo with gear presentations and activities from event sponsors, as well as the famous awards ceremony, featuring hundreds of prizes worth thousands of dollars! Bring the family and plan to stay a while; this is one event you don't want to miss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7:00 - Head back to the Wedeln SKi and Outdoors Club.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seek the Peak hikers who meet the $200 fundraising minimum will receive free entry into the expo, after party and meeting. Friends and family are invited to purchase a ticket and join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Check out by 11 AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Directions will be given out to Meetup Guests who have RSVP'd Yes and paid up in advance by July13</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Karen Jill</member_name><member_id>3865199</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mags</member_name><member_id>5575742</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dave Poirier</member_name><member_id>8205389</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1343143502000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Wedelns</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Wedelns</urlname><id>687583</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Wedeln Ski and Outdoors Club</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1340970126000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Seek The Peak</name><id>71259102</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>147600000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342825200000</time><rsvp_limit>40</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Wedelns/events/71259102/</event_url></item>