<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>215 Charles St. </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02114</zip><lat>42.362024</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-244-4000</phone><name>Liberty Hotel</name><city>Boston </city><id>1436840</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.070815</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>A free and public reading from three local authors, each of whom deserves more praise and appreciation than may easily be fitted into this measly event description. Part of the Poetic Justice series, curated by Harris Gardner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Erica Funkhouser is the author of four collections of poetry, including Pursuit, Sure Shot and Other Poems, and Natural Affinities (1983). Her poems have been published in numerous magazines and literary journals including The Atlantic Monthly, The New Yorker, The Paris Review, Ploughshares, and Poetry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Melissa Green is the recipient of both the Norma Farber Award from the Poetry Society of America and the Lavan Award from the Academy of American Poets. In addition to her collection The Squanicook Eclogues, brought back to print as a reissue by our own Pen &amp;amp; Anvil Press, she is the author of a memoir, Color is the Suffering of Light, and the collection Fifty-two. She was recorded reading her own poems for The Ottoman Estate, at &lt;a href="http://theottomanestate.wordpress.com/2010/09/24/melissa-green-a-place-from-words" target="_blank"&gt;http://theottomanesta...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;George Kalogeris teaches humanities and literature at Suffolk University. His book of poems based on the notebooks of Albert Camus, entitled Camus: Carnets, was published by Boston small press publisher Pressed Wafer. Hear poems in his own voice, at &lt;a href="http://theottomanestate.wordpress.com/2010/06/27/george-kalogeris-poetrys-pacific-voice" target="_blank"&gt;http://theottomanesta...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more about the series at &lt;a href="http://poetmom.blogspot.com/2010/06/poetic-justice-series-franz-wright-and.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://poetmom.blogsp...&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://miriamlevine.blogspot.com/2010/10/poetry-party-at-liberty-hotel.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://miriamlevine.b...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nora</member_name><member_id>2725784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1294965532000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Poets</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>bostonpoetry</urlname><id>122206</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0999984741</group_lon><name>Boston Poetry</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1294014578000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A don't-miss reading: Erica Funkhouser, Melissa Green, and George Kalogeris</name><id>15889605</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1294961400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/bostonpoetry/events/15889605/</event_url></item>