<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The group discussed this topic back on 12/10/2010 in what was a memorable fiasco because the restaurant that we used at the time did not honor our reservation for a private room despite three confirmations including the day of the event!&amp;nbsp; We ended up being seated at individual tables and there wasn't a group discussion.&amp;nbsp; But now we have very dependable arrangements with a different restaurant, the group has doubled in size, it's a very popular topic, so let's do it again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m in 'the rest of us&amp;rsquo; category. The big question concerning questions about &amp;lsquo;God&amp;rsquo; is not whether s/he/it &lt;em&gt;exists&lt;/em&gt; but about what the word&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;means&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; If we do not agree on what &amp;lsquo;God&amp;rsquo; means then how are we going to form an opinion about whether or not God exists.&amp;nbsp; And, if the question is not so much a question about&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;existence&lt;/em&gt; than it is about &lt;em&gt;meaning&lt;/em&gt; then the distinctions between atheism, theism and deism become very muddled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atheism, it seems to me, is just as muddled as the various forms of belief in God.&amp;nbsp; What is the God that&amp;nbsp; atheism rejects?&amp;nbsp; The atheist has just as much need for clarity on the meaning of &amp;lsquo;God&amp;rsquo; as do religionists if only because you cannot disbelieve in something that you cannot define, because if you cannot define your term you cannot put it into a statement which you think you want to refute.&amp;nbsp; Hence, the statement, &amp;ldquo;God does not exist&amp;rdquo; is meaningless unless you are prepared to define the thing that you want to reject.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buddhism provides an interesting focal point.&amp;nbsp; I remember, a number of years ago, listening to a radio interview with Michio Kaku, the well-known physicist and writer of popular books on the subject. I don&amp;rsquo;t recall the exact context, but a question about God or spirituality came up and he said that he was raised in a Buddhist home and that Buddhists are 'atheists&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp; That comment struck me because I really do not think of Buddhism as being an atheist religion which, anyway, is probably an oxymoron.&amp;nbsp; I have since come to understand that Buddhism is considered non-theistic (Kaku's comment aside) because while it rejects deities it is distinguishable from atheism.&amp;nbsp; I am not a student of the atheist movement, but my impression is that most people who today call themselves 'atheist' refer to a very scientific, naturalistic and radical empiricist view of reality that rejects any sense of immateriality and not merely theism, while also embracing a humanism that deeply supports the notion that we don&amp;rsquo;t need to believe in God to be moral or good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, my view is that the God issue is a big muddle that, while having speculative value, has little else.&amp;nbsp; For my part, I do not consider myself to be an atheist, however, I do not think one needs to believe in God to be good.&amp;nbsp; My personal speculations have some complementarity to non-atheistic Buddhism and some forms of mysticism that posit a transcendent Mind (of some sort).&amp;nbsp; This perspective can be very unscientific!&amp;nbsp; But I believe in science.&amp;nbsp; I hope that I have at least provided some food for thought&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***********************************************&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.greenteanewton.com/GreenTea_Newton_Chinese_Food_Menu_2010.pdf"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : small"&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;enu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FORMAT:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; When both big round tables are used, a designated half of each will move to the other table at approximately 8:45 pm in order to encourage mixing between the tables (each table accommodates up to 13 people). &amp;nbsp; After all, our events are as social as they are intellectual, and this format encourages the flourishing of both!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOOD AND BEVERAGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp; This restaurant is extremely accommodating and allows us to stay until closing (11:00pm) if we choose.&amp;nbsp; It is not fair if they are not fairly compensated&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp; And we use a large percentage of the total seats in the house!&amp;nbsp; While a &lt;strong&gt;minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; expenditure of $10 on food and/or drink is a group requirement, you are strongly encouraged to purchase a meal or its equivalent in cost (if your bill is under $10 the balance will be added to the gratuity).&amp;nbsp; Generally $20 (or a little less) will cover your entree, some shared appetizers, tax, and the gratuity but not drinks.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;By attending this event you hereby agree to this policy&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes some of us head out for a late night prolongation of the evening at a nearby pub.&amp;nbsp; However, during these occasions please do not carpool to the pub: drive your car down the street and re-park it at the pub because there is TOWING after the restaurant and the little mall area close for the night. &lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/pages/No_Show_Policy/"&gt;No Show Policy&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;PLEASE READ&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'm the guy in the picture.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Arthur</member_name><member_id>3026120</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>11</waitlist_count><updated>1330131639000</updated><rating><average>4.88999986649</average><count>9</count></rating><group><who>Philosophers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Philosophy-Discussions</urlname><id>1422684</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1900024414</group_lon><name>Boston Area Philosophy Discussions</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1325264087000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Atheism, Theism, Deism and the Rest of Us</name><id>45967662</id><headcount>22</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1327708800000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Philosophy-Discussions/events/45967662/</event_url></item>