<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;If interested in the following, please put yourself on the established waiting list. A yes list will be provided as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Criteria: NO WHINING, COMPLAINING, ETC. All hikers must be able to maintain a minimum pace of three miles an hour for a minimum of four hours. All hikers must have cold weather gear and be experienced above treeline in winter conditions. All hikers must have map &amp;amp; compass skills along with being prepared to spend an emergency night out in the woods. All attendees must read, understand and agree to the waiver/liability as outlined by this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;starting at Falling Waters Trailhead and Old Bridle Path (Franconia Range) Back to here hike 0.20 mi/8 min/+62 ft on the Old Bridle Path The trail leaves the parking lot (which is a stop for the AMC&amp;rsquo;s Hiker Shuttle) on the east side of the parkway (reached from the west side by a paved path 0.1 mi. long) near the hiker information kiosk, in common with the Falling Waters Trail, and passes through a clearing into the woods. to the junction of Falling Waters Trail hike 1.40 mi/1 hr 55 min/+982 ft on the Falling Waters Trail The trail turns sharply right away from the Old Bridle Path and immediately crosses Walker Brook on a bridge, then leads away from the brook heading east, then turns south. It crosses Dry Brook (use care if the water is high), turns left, and follows up the south bank to a beautiful cascade known as Stairs Falls. Above the falls, the trail passes beneath Sawteeth Ledges and crosses the brook to the north bank just below Swiftwater Falls, which descends 60 ft. in a shady glen, then climbs a steep rock staircase to the north bank and follows an old logging road that rises gradually in the narrow gorge of Dry Brook. The trail leaves the old road at a steep embankment and ascends more roughly to Cloudland Falls (80 ft.). It then climbs steeply up the steep bank of the brook with a ledgy scramble to the top of the falls. Here there is a viewpoint looking out over the valley toward Mt. Moosilauke on the skyline. At the head of Cloudland Falls are two small (25 ft.) falls practically facing each other. The one to the south, which emerges from the woods, is on the branch of Dry Brook that runs down from Little Haystack, while the other is on the Mt. Lincoln branch. The trail continues steeply on the north bank of the Mt. Lincoln branch, soon crosses to the south bank, crosses back to the north side, climbs to and follows an old logging road, and recrosses to the south bank. entering alpine zone hike 1.20 mi/1 hr 16 min/+1306 ft on the Falling Waters Trail Here it swings to the right, away from the brook, and angles uphill on an old logging road. Soon the trail takes the left fork of the old road, then diverges to the left off the road and ascends the ridge via a series of switchbacks. At the south end of the last switchback, a side trail leads south downhill about 100 yd. to the northeast corner of Shining Rock, where there are fine views south and west over Franconia Notch. This steep granite ledge, more than 200 ft. tall and nearly 800 ft. long, is usually covered with water from springs in the woods above and, seen from the mountains across the notch, shines like a mirror in the sunlight. Caution: Climbing Shining Rock without rock-climbing equipment and training is extremely dangerous. This steep ledge is wet and very slippery; several accidents involving serious injuries have occurred here to hikers who tried to scramble up the rock. to Shining Rock hike 0.40 mi/30 min/+590 ft on the Falling Waters Trail From the Shining Rock spur junction, the main trail continues north for a short distance, then turns right and climbs in a nearly straight line to the Franconia Ridge Trail at the summit of Little Haystack. to Little Haystack Mtn hike 0.70 mi/25 min/+324 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail The trail continues down and then up the long, gradual ridge, becoming rather steep over ledges as it approaches the treeline on Little Haystack. It reaches the junction with the Falling Waters Trail on the left, just under the summit rock of Little Haystack Mountain. to Mt Lincoln Totals Distance 3.90 mi Time 4 hr 14 min Elev Gain +3522 ft Elev Loss -259 ft Elev Change +3263 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 1.00 mi/39 min/+162 ft on the Franconia Ridge Trail From Little Haystack, the trail follows a broad, nearly level ridge crest in the open to the foot of Mt. Lincoln, then ascends sharply, keeping mostly just to the east of the crest of the knife-edged ridge between Mt. Lincoln and Little Haystack Mountain, which has steep slopes on both sides. After passing over the summit of Mt. Lincoln, the trail descends to a sag, climbs across a prominent hump, then descends to another sag, where it passes through a small scrub patch that might provide some shelter in bad weather. The trail then climbs at a moderate grade to the summit of Mt. Lafayette, where it meets the Greenleaf Trail on the left (west) and the Garfield Ridge Trail, which continues straight ahead along the north ridge. to Mt Lafayette Totals Distance 4.90 mi Time 4 hr 53 min Elev Gain +3990 ft Elev Loss -565 ft Elev Change +3425 ft Driving Directions Show in Google Earth Download to GPS Back to here hike 1.10 mi/1 hr 5 min/-1026 ft on the Greenleaf Trail At the summit of Mt. Lafayette, the Greenleaf Trail begins at the junction with the Garfield Ridge Trail (north) and the Franconia Ridge Trail (south). The trail descends the West side of Mt. Lafayette and bears right around a ledge on the left side from which a remarkable spring issues, very small but fairly reliable. The trail continues in the open at a moderate grade, sometimes on rock steps between stone walls. The trail enters the scrub, passes a sandy area on the left, and then descends, passing over several minor knobs. The trail passes south of the Eagle Lakes, two picturesque shallow tarns (though the upper lake is rapidly becoming a bog). The Greenleaf Trail then passes the Greenleaf Hut where the Old Bridal Path leaves to the left. to AMC Greenleaf Hut leaving alpine zone hike 2.70 mi/2 hr 34 min/-2337 ft on the Old Bridle Path From Greenleaf Hut, the Old Bridle Path descends through a patch of dead trees and then crosses a small sag. It reaches a grassy spot with a nice view to Cannon Mountain, Kinsman Mountain, and Mt. Moosilauke. Still descending, an unmarked side path leaves the main trail and diverges left and passes two fine outlooks. In about 40yd. it rejoins the main path. The trail then reaches the top of Agony Ridge (a name that originated with hut people who had to pack heavy loads up this steep section) and begins to descend the steep portion. In one pitch, the trail struggles down a steep basalt dike with somewhat slippery footing. The first of the spectacular outlooks from the brink of the ravine is reached, and several more are passed. The trail leaves the ridge and there is a view of Mt. Lincoln through the trees and follows rock steps down the edge of teh ravine. The trail then makes a sharp left turn and swings toward Walker Brook. It comes to the edge of the bank, high above the brook and leaves the WMNF (sign). The trail swings toward the brook again and descends at a moderate grade. The trail then continues along the brook, while the Falling Waters Trail crosses the brook on a bridge. to the junction of Falling Waters Trail hike 0.20 mi/8 min/-62 ft on the Old Bridle Path The Falling Waters Trail joins the Old Bridle Path through the woods and into a clearing. It passes the hiker information kiosk and terminates at the parking lot on the east side of the parkway (reached from the east side by a paved path 0.1 mi. long) The parking lot is also a stop on the AMC's Hiker Shuttle route. to Falling Waters Trailhead and Old Bridle Path (Franconia Range) Totals Distance 8.90 mi Time 8 hr 40 min Elev Gain +4154 ft Elev Loss -4154 ft Elev Change 0 ft&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We will be in a silver four door Legacy Subaru with Maine plates</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>DIANNE AND PAUL</member_name><member_id>4968533</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>1</waitlist_count><updated>1310598042000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1309269539000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>MT LAFAYETTE AND LINCOLN</name><id>23808931</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310301000000</time><rsvp_limit>4</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/23808931/</event_url></item>