<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>/person ($5 if WRNEC mem)</description><amount>10.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Special RSVP instructions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;To RSVP, please use &lt;b&gt;BOTH&lt;/b&gt; the Meetup system &lt;b&gt;AND&lt;/b&gt; call Betsy Bragg, Health Educator &amp;amp; Coach, at 781-899-6664, (cell) 617-835-2913 or email Betsy@rawnewenglandcommunity.com (specify which event). If you only use the Meetup RSVP system, then you won't be registered. If you only contact Betsy and don't use Meetup, your Meetup member stats and our group's Meetup stats won't be correct. Thank you for understanding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Raw Food Author Paul Nison Speaking in Waltham&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There will be a DVD shown on The Principles of Health at 5 PM.  &lt;br /&gt;Paul's DVDs are at: &lt;a href="http://www.rawlife.com/store/home.php?cat=391" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawlife.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Raw Luck 6-7 PM (Raw Pot Luck)&lt;br /&gt;Speaker 7:00 PM to 9:00 PM &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In his books and lectures, Paul explains how to make an easy transition to a raw diet, how to be happy, healthy and positive and move forward in life. Although his message is serious, his style of lecturing, combining humor and boldness is enjoyable to everyone. If you want to live your life to its fullest, Paul can help you. NOTE: Paul talks from a Christian perspective and references the bible during his talk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Nison will present his newest revolutionary lecture based on his latest book ?The Health Formula? If you are confused about health, want more energy or struggle with a raw food diet, this lecture is for you! Paul will teach you how to overcome disease and stay healthy while having fun with your diet. He has a unique style combining humor and boldness to get his message across.  From children to seniors, men and woman, everyone stands to benefit from Paul?s message. See his website www.paulnison.com .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul has lectured and conducted classes nationally and internationally. He is the author of five books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At all his lectures, Paul answers questions and does a book signing before and after the events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;------------------&lt;br /&gt;All those attending are requested to bring a raw, organic, unprocessed, non-animal based (vegan with no honey) ready- to-serve dish for 6 - 8 people.  Please bring serving utensils labeled with your name on them. Bring a typed or neatly printed recipe to display next to your dish.  For recipe ideas, go to &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawnewengl...&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are some ideas to help you find something raw to bring:&lt;br /&gt;1. you could bring an organic salad;&lt;br /&gt;2. there is a source for raw recipes listed in the invitation at &lt;a href="http://www.rawnewenglandcommunity.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawnewengl...&lt;/a&gt; ;&lt;br /&gt;3. there are plenty of raw recipes available online&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.living-foods.com/recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.living-foo...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://goneraw.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://goneraw.com...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawsacramento.net/recipes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawsacrame...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawfoodlife.com/raw_food_recipes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawfoodlif...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shazzie.com/raw/recipes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.shazzie.co...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.healthfree.com/raw_food_recipes.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.healthfree...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rawganique.com/recipes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.rawganique...&lt;/a&gt; ; &lt;br /&gt;4. most raw food books have raw recipes; and&lt;br /&gt;5. organic fruit or fruit salad.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Daryl Elliott</member_name><member_id>5267372</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278895367000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1199653223000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Raw Food Author Paul Nison Speaking in Waltham</name><id>7046507</id><headcount>18</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1203458400000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/7046507/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/0/global_2923264.jpeg</photo_url></item>