<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>100 Institute Road </address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01609</zip><lat>42.272816</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>WPI - Olin Hall 107</name><city>Worcester</city><id>1062193</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.808204</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>15.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Greater Worcester Humanists is welcoming renowned folk musician and satirist Roy Zimmerman to Worcester.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tickets are $15 regular and $8 for a student and can be purchased through Meetup or by following this link:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://worcester.humanists.net/events/zimmerman.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://worcester.huma...&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Students with a current ID card at a Worcester Consortium College can also buy tickets at a student discounted price while supplies last by sending e-mail to Steve Jasperson at &amp;quot;snj@wpi.edu&amp;quot; prior to October 13 -- one ticket per current ID only -- instructions for ticket pick-up will arrive via return e-mail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The show starts at 8:00 pm.  &lt;b&gt;Show up at least 15 minutes early for seating.  Please print out and bring your receipt from the transaction on Paypal, Meetup.com or email from Steve for entry to the show. &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zimmerman is one of those rare individuals who combines great musical talent and sharp satirical humor with a clear social and political message.  He's performed all around the country, including playing at the Democratic National Convention.  His original music and lyrics will remind you at times of Pete Seeger and Bob Dylan, but his material is even more contemporary, addressing issues that are in today's headlines such as gay marriage, the war on terror, the economy and the religious right, almost always with a wit that seems to thrive on the hypocrisy and lunacy of neocons and social conservatives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A sampling of Roy's music includes titles such as Abstain with Me (his ode to abstinence-only education), Chickenhawk, My Conservative Girlfriend, Defenders of Marriage, and Creation Science 101.  One of our members had a chance to see Roy's show in Arizona a few months ago, and his songs had people almost falling off their chairs. It's a show you won't want to miss!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check out his work at &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/RoyZimmerman" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.youtube.co...&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a map of the WPI campus.  Olin Hall is shown in red&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.socialweb.net/WPI/olin.gif" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>We'll be greeting people at the front door, park in the main lot of WPI.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Moran</member_name><member_id>7617544</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1258337534000</updated><rating><average>4.86000013351</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>Humanists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>worcesterhumanists</urlname><id>1218349</id><group_lat>42.3100013733</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8000030518</group_lon><name>Greater Worcester Humanists</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>23</yes_rsvp_count><created>1252631910000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Roy Zimmerman - Real American: funny songs about ignorance, war and greed.</name><id>11343375</id><headcount>26</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255824000000</time><rsvp_limit>100</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/worcesterhumanists/events/11343375/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/2/8/global_10744392.jpeg</photo_url></item>