<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>150 Ash St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03104</zip><lat>42.997272</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-669-6144</phone><name>Currier Museum of Art</name><city>Manchester</city><id>761744</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.455039</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Frank Lloyd Wright designed the Zimmerman House in his classic Usonian style in 1950, planning its gardens, its built-in and freestanding furniture, its textiles, and even the mailbox.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Zimmerman House offers a glimpse into the 1950s - 1960s, and the private lives of Isadore and Lucille Zimmerman, who lived in the home for 36 years.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 1 ½-2 hour private tour of the house can be tailored to meet the group's specific needs. So, let me know what you would like the tour to cover, in your RSVP.  &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: seagreen"&gt;Group Rate of $75.00 will be divided by the number of people attending. &lt;b&gt;By the way this rate includes museum admission&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: teal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Currier Museum opens at 11:00am on Sundays.  For those who would like to go into the galleries prior to the tour, stop at the VS desk and identify yourself as part of &amp;quot;ZH private tour at 1:00&amp;quot;. You will be given a special tag that will allow you to go into the galleries&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at the museum at least 15 minutes prior to your scheduled tour time and check in at the museum's admission desk.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;Tours depart promptly by shuttle van &lt;/b&gt;from the Currier Museum of Art's front lobby. Please note that there are no restrooms at the Zimmerman House. You may use the facilities in the museum prior to your tour. Children under age 7 are not permitted on Zimmerman House tours. &lt;i&gt;Photography is not permitted inside the house. (Photographs of the exterior may be taken.)&lt;i&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;3:00 PM - 5:00 PM:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ARTalk:  Frank Lloyd Wright - Usonian Architecture : &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get an insider perspective from Roland Reisley, author of Usonia New York: Building a Community with Frank Lloyd Wright. Reisley is one of the original residents of Usonia - a community planned by Wright - and has lived there for more than fifty years.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will meet you at the admission desk at 12:45. I will be wearing a Meet-Up - FAN pin.  The tour starts at 1:00.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Charlotte V.</member_name><member_id>3105127</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212512986000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1209506727000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Zimmerman Museum - (Private Tour)</name><id>7838118</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1212339600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/7838118/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/d/f/global_3972479.jpeg</photo_url></item>