<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join P-Collective member Christopher for this annual West Side tradition! We will be meeting at Louie Fullers with the other revelers, and go from there! Its always a great time! More details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Spread warmth and merriment during one of the coldest times of the year. Join us as we joyfully carol through historic streets surrounded by beautiful Victorian architecture in Providence's Armory District. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Annually, the Sunday before Christmas! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Meet up at Loie Fuller's restaurant (1455 Westminster St) from 5-6pm before heading out at 6pm to bring holiday cheer to the neighborhood through festive holiday songs. We have planned stops with neighbors along the way for warm drinks and bathroom breaks, before&lt;/span&gt; ending at 8pm with milk &amp;amp; cookies at Fertile Underground (1577 Westminster St) &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 EVERYONE IS WELCOME regardless of any religious or non-religious beliefs. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 Spread some end-of-the-year joy through song. &lt;br /&gt;

 INVITE YOUR FRIENDS &amp;amp; FAMILY! &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

 This free festive event is sponsored by Connect Providence, Hudson Street Deli, Fertile Underground Grocery, Kidoinfo.com, Leadership Rhode Island, Loie Fuller's, the West Broadway Neighborhood Association (WBNA) and WestSide Stories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Christopher is hosting this one! Please look at his picture!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher</member_name><member_id>10240270</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1356453593000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1355883270000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>5th Annual West Side Caroling</name><id>95856152</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>10800000</duration><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1356300000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/95856152/</event_url></item>