<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite 90</address_2><address_1>45 S Main St</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06107</zip><lat>41.759000</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860 523 5260</phone><name>SunDo Mountain Taoist Center</name><city>West Hartford</city><id>489318</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.742390</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Taoist meditation is a method for cultivating, refining, and circulating internal energy within the chakras and meridian channels in the body. Taoists believe that tancheon breathing is a method of natural healing that works with the life force energy, also known as “chi” in Chinese and “prana” in Sanskrit, is the flow of energy that sustains all living beings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although it may be tempting to believe that we can heal other people, it is of utmost importance to realize that all healing is self-healing. The body has an extraordinary ability to heal itself given the right energetic, emotional, nutritional, and spiritual environments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us for a one hour meditation with light stretching followed by tea and a discussion with Taoist Master Hyunmoon Kim. Master Kim's talk will explain the core of Taoist practice, tancheon breathing, or lower abdominal breathing. By returning to this natural breath and letting it sustain us, we can understand and learn to do tancheon breathing without force, yet the result is increased energy, strength, flexibility and endurance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please wear comfy clothing. No previous experience necessary. All physical fitness levels are welcome&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a free class but a $5 donation would be appreciated. Donations help to support the work of SunDo Mountain Taoism, a non-profit organization dedicated to th eeducation of Taoist philosophy and practice.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282441501000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Conscious Co-Pollinators</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>high-vibe-tribe</urlname><id>450677</id><group_lat>41.75</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>High Vibe Tribe</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1281467091000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Energy Healing Workshop: Taoist Meditation &amp; Energy Breathing </name><id>14381018</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282084200000</time><rsvp_limit>8</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/high-vibe-tribe/events/14381018/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/5/2/global_12433362.jpeg</photo_url></item>