<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>3rd Floor</address_2><address_1>10 Boylston Place</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02116</zip><lat>42.351810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-542-7400</phone><name>Semel Theater at Emerson College</name><city>Boston</city><id>907842</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.065990</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;UPDATED!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to the generous donation of a silent donor, admission to the Second Annual Revolve Nation Entrepreneur Film Series is now &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;FREE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is life like for startup companies after 9/11?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join your fellow entrepreneurs from the Greater Boston area for a screening of the entrepreneur-focused movie: AUGUST. Starring Josh Hartnett, AUGUST centers on two brothers fighting to keep their start-up company afloat on Wall Street during August of 2001, a month before the 9/11 terrorist attacks. As the pundits continue to push the message that America is suffering the worst recession in decades, the resolve of the entrepreneur holds steady and shines in the story of AUGUST.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Distinguished Panel Shares Their Related Experiences&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AUGUST will be followed by a distinguished panel from the Private Equity and Serial Entrepreneurship communities for an engaging discussion and Q&amp;amp;A session on: &amp;quot;The Significance of Human Capital&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Rich vs. King Dilemma.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Panel will include: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Edward Melia has served as a Human Resource Executive at many international companies.  In his current role, Edward is Senior Vice President/Human Capital Advisor at P3 Ventures Group. In this role, Edward applies his global management consulting experience and proven ability to grow successful businesses to strategically develop entrepreneurs and executive teams on a wide variety of human capital issues.  Edward has served on the Board of Advisors of several successful start-up ventures and is an active volunteer, mentor and board member for various non-profit organizations.  Edward is a frequent speaker and workshop leader for major business symposia and professional groups, and has been guest lecturer for graduate-level academic programs in human resources. He is the author of several articles on assessing and selecting talent and the effects of technology on the HR profession.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark Cohen has been a Human Resource Professional and Management Consultant for over 18 years, in such companies as Polaroid, Fidelity Investments, General Mills, Apple Computer, as well as several start ups.  Over his career, Mark has partnered with top executives to find and hire world class leadership.  Mark received his MBA from Suffolk University. He is a co-author of the college text, Communicating in Business Today and is currently working on his second book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come join us for a fantastic evening celebrating entrepreneurship through film and networking!  Immediately following the panel discussion, we will continue the networking party at Felt!  Seats will be going fast, so sign up today! Looking forward to seeing all of you there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where and When:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, April 15th, from 6:30pm-9:30pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emerson College (Boston): Semel Theater, 10 Boylston Place, 3rd Floor&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;TICKETS&lt;/u&gt;: &lt;b&gt;FREE&lt;/b&gt; Seats are Limited!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sponsored By:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.exemplarcompanies.com" target="_blank"&gt;Exemplar Companies &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brought to you By: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.emerson.edu/admission/undergraduate/academics/mkt_emerson_experience_in_entrepreneurship.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;Emerson College, Entrepreneurship (E3)&lt;/a&gt; Program  (Host Sponsor)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Revolve Nation:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Revolve Nation is a national entrepreneurs organization and the largest community of entrepreneurs in the Greater Boston area!  Created by&lt;a href="http://www.revolvethis.com" target="_blank"&gt; Revolve Inc., &lt;/a&gt;the first exclusive partnership of business law, business deployment, and business capital specialized and serving companies from the start-up to exit phase of growth. Accelerate the Revolution!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1240527313000</updated><rating><average>4.55000019073</average><count>11</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>152</yes_rsvp_count><created>1237477865000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Second Annual Revolve Nation Entrepreneur Film Premiere, Panel &amp; Networking!</name><id>9988548</id><headcount>151</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1239834600000</time><rsvp_limit>200</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/9988548/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/0/f/global_1065599.jpeg</photo_url></item>