<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>9 Simon Street</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03060</zip><lat>42.750863</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-233-1058</phone><name>Balanced Health Center</name><city>Nashua</city><id>727520</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.488831</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is our fifth monthly video screening in Nashua&lt;/b&gt;. We have screenings every Tuesday somewhere in the Merrimack Valley: &lt;b&gt;1st Tuesday-Nashua&lt;/b&gt;; 2nd Tuesday-Manchester; 3rd Tuesday-Concord; 4th Tuesday-Plymouth. If there's a 5th Tuesday in a month, we'll have a special meeting!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;This month in Nashua we will see &lt;a href="http://fabledenemies.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Fabled Enemies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, by Jason Bermas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fabled Enemies by Jason Bermas is the latest film to question the events of September 11th 2001. Instead of the focus being on physical anomolies surrounding the attacks, it focuses on a vast intelligence network and how they were able to succeed almost 7 years ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It begins with footage from the morning itself reminding everyone that in the court of public opinion Osama Bin laden was convicted on day 1, there were no other suspects. We then delve into the fact that many of the alleged hijackers were trained at U.S. military facilities, and still others had ties to the FBI. When others within the FBI tried to go after Bin Laden, and his financial supporters there investigations were impeded and shut down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Able Danger the Black Ops program that identified the hijackers prior to 9/11 had also tried to move the information tot he FBI, but the FBI still was not interested for some reason. Anthony Shaffer who headed up this team later met with Phillip Zelikow, the Executive Director of the 9/11 Commission, to try and pass this information along after the fact. It was then covered up, not included in the report, and Shaffer and his team were gagged and slandered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The film then explores the mystery of those who were detained on the morning of September 11th. Several vans were stopped that morning containg Israeli citizens, who either seemed to have prior knowledge of the attacks, or had explosives in their vehicle. When investigators started looking into this network it was revealed they did indeed have a classified role in 9/11, and that two companies within the United States may have been helping them gain their intel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This network's existence is then confirmed by whistle blower Sybyl Edmonds, who came across a international spy ring containing Turks, Israelis, and member's of Pakistani Intelligence. The Pakistani operation was headed by General Mahmoud Ahmed, who had financial ties to the hijackers, and diplomatic ties to the upper echelons of Washington.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After two seperate government investigations into 9/11 you would think that the public would be satisfied with their efforts and conclusions. However we show you how both the Congressional Report and the 9/11 Commission Report were a whitewash and a scam to begin with, and how it was used to manipulate the public into believing the issue had been dealt with and thouroghly explained.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;After the video, we'll go over how each attender can become more involved&lt;/b&gt; and spread the workload of running a meetup like this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;We'll have free DVD's&lt;/b&gt; and DVD's and books for sale. Everyone should bring their collection for trading, viewing, copying, etc. Bring your favorite books, too. We've developed a collection of books for sale at these various meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please arrive at 7:00 PM&lt;/b&gt;, since this meeting is on a tight schedule. We'll start a brief business meeting at 7 and the video will begin promptly at 7:30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring snacks and/or drinks for sharing, and we suggest a donation of $1 to $5 to keep growing our library of videos and books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Parking is in the lot in front of the building. Please enter the right entry doorway and suite 135 will be directly ahead of you. After entering the office, turn left to go to the video viewing room.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Merrimack Valley 911 Truth has set up a &amp;quot;carpooling group&amp;quot; online&lt;/b&gt; at &lt;a href="http://mv911t.eRideShare.com" target="_blank"&gt;http://mv911t.eRideSh...&lt;/a&gt;. Our group nickname is &amp;quot;mv911t&amp;quot; and our password is &amp;quot;truth&amp;quot;. You can post if you are driving to one of our events and have extra seats - if you're looking for a ride to an event just logon and post that you're seeking a ride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As always, &lt;b&gt;donations to the driver for the ride-sharing are appreciated&lt;/b&gt; to cover gas costs.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be the guy fixing tea for everyone</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jaqeboy</member_name><member_id>3996281</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226253415000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>9-11-307</urlname><id>464907</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>Merrimack Valley 9/11 Questions Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1225083354000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Nashua - Fabled Enemies</name><id>9038199</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225843200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/9-11-307/events/9038199/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/4/f/global_6058431.jpeg</photo_url></item>