<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>232 Wooster Street </address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06511</zip><lat>41.302810</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>203-773-0733</phone><name>Joker's Wild</name><city>New Haven</city><id>1029660</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.919816</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, I haven't had a chance to meet a lot of the newer members, but here's a chance to fix that while having a great evening. The Joker's Wild comedy club on Wooster street is a terrific little place, and every show I've seen there has been hilarious. In addition, the Nov 10th show is also a fund-raiser for Breath 4 Life, a charity to give support to those affected by cycstic fibrosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breath 4 Life was established in May 2011 by Stephanie Gayda and Shawn Palmer shortly after their friend Melissa Gullesh, a resident of Milford, passed away in April 2011 from Cystic Fibrosis. The charity Breath 4 Life has a goal to raise over $10,000 to assist Richard Gullesh, Melissa&amp;rsquo;s father, with funeral costs/hospital bills he incurred and to place a tombstone on Melissa&amp;rsquo;s gravesite, which currently only has flowers and a wooden cross with her name. Mr. Gullesh has seen too much tragedy the last several years. His wife Lynn passed away from Cancer in 1999, his son Mark passed away in 2001 at only 17 years old, and now his only daughter Melissa lost her battle from Cystic Fibrosis on April 23, at only 24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**PLEASE PURCHASE TICKETS AHEAD OF TIME** at &lt;a href="http://www.cfbreath4life.com/#!events" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.cfbreath4life.com/#!events&lt;/a&gt; .&amp;nbsp; The organizers have to pre-sell 60 tickets before the event, or else they have to pay the difference... which would mean a deficit for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is very detailed information about this excellent organization and ticket-purchase instructions on the Bucket List Bunch website: &lt;a href="http://www.bucketlistbunch.com/events/34693452/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bucketlist...&lt;/a&gt; Please read the BLB listing and pass along info about this worthwhile event to anyone you think might enjoy a night of good will, fun, and laughter. Hope to see you there! -Neil K. 203-928-9907&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1321097720000</updated><rating><average>3.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1318535422000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Joker's Wild comdey night and charity fund-raiser</name><id>37297612</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1320969600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/37297612/</event_url></item>