<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>173 Water St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02360</zip><lat>41.962585</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 746-9751</phone><name>East Bay Grille</name><city>Plymouth</city><id>326056</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.669070</lon></venue><fee><label>Event Fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Our annual Columbus Day lunch has become an SSDOMG tradition!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year, we've chosen to visit one of Plymouth's waterfront hotspots: The &lt;a href="http://www.eastbaygrille.com/" target="_blank"&gt;East Bay Grille&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well known for its harborside location, large patio (though we probably won't be dining outside!) and above-average bar, East Bay Grill has been such a success that they've recently opened a second location in Plymouth's upscale Pinehills development. Indeed, one seldom gets very far into a conversation about Plymouth restaurants without hearing hearing the words &amp;quot;East Bay Grille&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us there on Monday, October 12th at 1:00 PM as we take forks and knives in hand to discover for ourselves what all the buzz is about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;East Bay Grille&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, October 12th, 2009 @ 1:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;173 Water Street&lt;br /&gt;Plymouth, MA&lt;br /&gt;(508) 746-9751&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.eastbaygrille.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.eastbaygri...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Organizers:&lt;/b&gt; Angela and Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Min/Max:&lt;/b&gt; Minimum of six attendees by Thursday, October 8th.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guests:&lt;/b&gt; 1 per Member&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.eastbaygrille.com/lunch.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lunch offerings&lt;/a&gt; range from $8.95 (several sandwiches) to $16.95 (King Crab Roll).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cash Only Policy:&lt;/b&gt; Please bring cash! Paying for all of our meals in cash has been SSDOMG'S policy for over three years. It allows us to avoid the confusion of having the waitstaff run multiple credit card slips and generally helps to keep things simpler for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Event Fee:&lt;/b&gt; Annual Members - None. Group Members and Guests - $2.00.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;RSVP Deadline:&lt;/b&gt; Sunday, Oct 11th @ 5:00 PM. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer. Changes to No after this point will be considered No-Shows per our guidelines on the About Us page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;East Bay Grille is located on the &lt;b&gt;waterfront&lt;/b&gt; in &lt;b&gt;Downtown Plymouth&lt;/b&gt;. From &lt;b&gt;Route 3 South (coming from Braintree)&lt;/b&gt; take &lt;b&gt;Exit 6A (Route 44 East)&lt;/b&gt;. From &lt;b&gt;Route 3 North (coming from Cape Cod)&lt;/b&gt; take &lt;b&gt;Exit 6 (Route 44)&lt;/b&gt; and head &lt;b&gt;East toward Plymouth Center&lt;/b&gt;. Starting off on Route 44, you will pass a large Hesse gas station on your left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow Route 44 until it ends at its intersection with Route 3A (you will be at a stoplight; there is a Dunkin' Doughnuts and a Mobil gas station on the far-left corner). Go straight across Route 3A, then follow the short stretch of road as it turns right, then left, heading down towards the water. After about a minute, you will come to the intersection with Water St., where you have to either turn right or go around a rotary to turn left (Al's Restaurant will be on your right). Make a left turn by going 3/4 of the way around the rotary, keeping the Cranberry House on your right.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming off the rotary, you should be able to clearly see a large sign for the East Bay Grill: The restaurant and its parking lot are just ahead on your right.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Our reservation is under both 'Mike' and 'South Shore Meetup Group'.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Mike</member_name><member_id>3444655</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256249530000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1253972497000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Land in Plymouth on Columbus Day!</name><id>11471021</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255366800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/11471021/</event_url></item>