<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;(This venue is very accessible via MBTA: just a few steps from the Outbound station - Essex Street entrance - at the Central Square stop on the Red Line, and across the street or around the block from Central Square bus stops. Attendees can PARK FREE AFTER 6 PM on-street and in the lots beside the Cafe off Bishop Richard Allen Drive and Norfolk Street- **DO NOT USE THE LOT THAT IS ACCESSIBLE FROM ESSEX STREET, as your car WILL be towed!!**)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;Refreshments at Clear Conscience Cafe range from $1.85 for a drink to ~$8 for a sandwich plate.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;There is no specified purchase minimum for refreshments,  but participants are encouraged to order &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt;thing to support the  business, in appreciation of Management's permission to meet in their space.&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Please be advised: Commercial eating establishments generally do &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;not&lt;/span&gt; permit &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;on-site &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;em&gt;consumption of refreshments brought in from elsewhere, due  to liability concerns, so please be considerate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;______________________________________________&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;excavate&lt;/strong&gt; [&amp;#712;&amp;#603;ksk&amp;#601;&amp;#716;ve&amp;#618;t] &lt;em&gt;vb &lt;/em&gt;- (Social Science / Archaeology) to unearth (buried objects) methodically in an attempt to discover information about the past &lt;em&gt;-The Free Online Dictionary.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring your calendar or datebook (wherever you maintain your schedule) AND, if possible, a photo - digital or print - of the space you'd MOST like to clear SOONEST. Start reflecting on the dream(s) that space potentially holds  for you- and the story behind all the stuff occupying the space right now, instead: what it seems to say about your journey &lt;em&gt;up to this point.&lt;/em&gt; Then come SHARE your vision and the challenges obscuring it right now- and let's put Your Dream on a &lt;em&gt;production schedule&lt;/em&gt; with You in control- not stuff.&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is rather short notice, but because our last meeting venue was &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; noisy and distracting, I've embarked on &lt;em&gt;a Quest for &lt;strong&gt;More Suitable Venues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;- and welcome your input, which I realize might be staggered throughout the evening for such an informal event ... just come for any time period between 7 and 9 pm that is most convenient for you (specifying in your RSVP Comment the particular time period you plan to participate) to join a "miniClinic"- for help to move us all in directions &lt;em&gt;we&lt;/em&gt; want to go. Please just be advised that, if nobody RSVPs to come late in the evening, I might leave before 9 pm if no other group members are on hand UNLESS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(1) I am notified of a definite late arrival by a group member on Meetup.com by 5 pm the day of the event AND&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(2) I RESPOND by stating that I will wait until a set time for the late RSVPer to arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can discuss neurolinguistic programming (and practice some EFT &amp;amp; NLP techniques) for making changes faster than we'd thought possible; find inspiration; share support, resources online and off-line, tips &amp;amp; tricks, and consider various possible sorts of &lt;em&gt;welcomed&lt;/em&gt; accountability; brainstorm programs and events (including how best to introduce our group to YOUR possible clutter-related services or products?), and sustainability of such a service and group as this could be- while enjoying the cuisine and ambiance of a restaurant(s) that particularly appeals to &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; and thus attracts people somewhat like you (some of whom might share and support your vision? &lt;em&gt;Who knows??).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since learning, recall, and success are "state-specific," from what I keep reading, let's meet in a &lt;em&gt;nurturing, nourishing environment&lt;/em&gt; that &lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;&lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; especially enjoy, to put you in a state of consciousness as peaceful and reflective as possible, discussing Dreams and how to achieve them for "Level-10 Living" &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; way- partly by &lt;em&gt;clearing precious space and time&lt;/em&gt; in your life:&amp;nbsp; the mission of our larger group. Specifically, let's figure out how to get you on track and &lt;em&gt;keep&lt;/em&gt; you there until you achieve your Dream that is currently buried within a cluttered space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How better to Go for it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;than by having FUN along the way? &lt;/em&gt;I would &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; to check out one or a few venues each week, in a range of prices (including free, which likely will preclude refreshments and amenities ... or not? Input is welcomed!) so our group members can have a range of choices, reflecting our diversity. &lt;em&gt;Do suggest favorite spots of your own-&lt;/em&gt; I am especially looking for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; QUIET restaurants with various seating capacities, cuisines, and ambiances- especially those that might flexibly accommodate our group (e.g., by turning background music down or even off, if requested, to improve a meeting program) in SAFE sections of the metro-Boston area (venues en route to Methuen would facilitate Kevin Martin's organizing more NLP Meetups jointly with us!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Accessible to public transportation on relatively high-frequency travel schedule(s), including return trips later than 9:15 pm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Free, safe (e.g., well lit) parking close by&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Private or semi-private room(s) or space(s)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come join us!&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp; (Or specify a better time and place for you to do so). &amp;nbsp;In fact-&amp;nbsp;please take this opportunity to &lt;strong&gt;Share Your Abundance: &amp;nbsp;If you have any of the following items in good condition that you'd like to release, please bring to this Meetup for me to donate &lt;/strong&gt;to my church's Gifts of the Heart&amp;nbsp;project&amp;nbsp;(Disaster Assistance in conjunction with the Church World Service):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Face towels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hand towels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nail clippers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Individual-sized soaps (3-4-oz size)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My church collects these items to pack hygiene kits for emergency response to disasters such&amp;nbsp;as the recent earthquake and tsunami in Japan, and the earthquake in Haiti ... finished kits are then sent to a central clearing house in readiness for shipment to disaster sites at a moment's notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please give the above-listed items&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;to me directly&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration : underline"&gt;DO NOT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;ask Clear Conscience Cafe staff to take any items before or after our Meetup, to give to me.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank You!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll have a red &amp; white Meetup sign at my table</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Judy</member_name><member_id>5072480</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1301516062000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Informal opportunity to meet in a small group or one-on-one to "reframe"- learn or practice neurolinguistic programming (NLP) methods, achieve a "Gestalt switch," increase accountability to facilitate decluttering...whatever YOU need to progress!</why><group><who>Accountability Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>declutter-113</urlname><id>963536</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Tools for Decluttering, Personal Change &amp; Goal Attainment</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1299989550000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Freeing SpaceTime" miniCLINIC: Excavating Dreams</name><id>16900814</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1301353200000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/declutter-113/events/16900814/</event_url></item>