<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>76 Community Drive</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04330</zip><lat>44.342453</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Augusta Civic Center</name><city>Augusta</city><id>7029142</id><country>us</country><lon>-69.798950</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend in Massachusetts and Louisiana, and Alaska, Ron Paul supporters ousted establishment insiders to win a number of National Convention delegate spots. This weekend, Maine selects her delegates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless you've been living under a rock you know that Ron Paul was the victim of blatant voter fraud in Maine earlier this cycle. If you don't know what I'm talking about type the words into google. The state GOP chair declared Romney the primary winner before all of the counties even voted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weekend is the state GOP convention where delegates are chosen and Maine could use our help. For $30, out-of-state guests can get into the state convention and help. I don't exactly know what you can do; presumably you will not be allowed on the floor. They pick 15 delegates on Saturday and 6 on Sunday. Here's more info about the convention: &lt;a href="http://www.MaineGOP.com/2012/03/2012-maine-republican-party-state-convention/" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.MaineGOP.com/2012/03/2012-maine-republican-party-state-convention/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reports from MA, LA, and AK have the establishment terrified. Mitt Romney is robocalling in Maine to ensure his people come out in numbers. The Maine GOP chairman (same guy who declared Romney the winner prematurely) has warned voters of the Paul campaign "take over" plans. Please read his email blast at the end of this message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can come up to help your neighbors either or both days this weekend remember to dress as nicely as you can, suits &amp;amp; ties, etc. You are reminded to remain courteous at all times. I have been told that if you show up you WILL be put to work. Help us show that we're not taking over the GOP we're taking it back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not be afraid to use this group's email list to coordinate ride share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More info: ericb@ronpaul2012.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To: State Convention Delegates and Alternates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: Charlie Webster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several weeks ago I attended a meeting at the Party Headquarters with a representative from the Ron Paul campaign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At that meeting I was informed that the Ron Paul campaign intends to "take over" the Republican State Convention and Republican State Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It appears that such an effort will be attempted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is my opinion that, in my role as Party Chairman, my obligation is to welcome every Republican activist to our Convention, and to guarantee that all voices are heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of us should welcome the supporters of Ron Paul, Newt Gingrich, Rick Santorum, and Mitt Romney.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These activists are critical to the election of our candidates in the 2012 elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As attendees of our convention, I write to inform you of this situation and to remind you of the importance of attending the Convention beginning with the election of the Convention Secretary when we convene at 9 a.m. ( We recommend that you arrive at 8:15, at the latest to collect your Delegate/Alternate credentials )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The very first business on Saturday will be the election of the Convention Secretary and Convention Chairman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This would be the first opportunity for anyone to "take over" the Convention by electing " their " Convention Chairman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The County caucuses will be held at 4 o'clock and this matter of business would be another opportunity to "take over" the State Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I regret the necessity of writing this message, but unfortunately there are those among us who would choose to divide us rather than unite us. Individuals who seem to believe that the overall good of the Party may not be as important as their candidate and their own personal political opinions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading this message, see you at the Convention. 8:15 a.m. on Saturday&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charlie Webster &lt;br /&gt;

Chairman, Maine Republican Party&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a response to Charlie's "Important Message" from Eric Brakey Maine State Director for Ron Paul's Campaign&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Maine Patriots,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I regret the necessity of writing this message, but unfortunately the Maine GOP leadership has desperately chosen to use “scorched earth” tactics to suppress your vote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning, Charlie Webster sent out an email to Maine Republicans which contained outright lies about a meeting he had with our campaign. &lt;br /&gt;

Perhaps the facts got lost in Charlie's spam folder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charlie Webster says we want to "take over" the Republican Convention. &lt;br /&gt;

By "taking over," he must mean we want to have our voices heard. &lt;br /&gt;

If that's the case, then count me in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to send a conservative delegation to Tampa, we need your help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not yet become a delegate, there's still time. This Saturday, any vacant delegate seats can be filled by registered Republicans who show up. That's right, you may STILL become a delegate for Dr. Paul!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maine is winnable--with your help. To become a delegate, show up to the Augusta Civic Center no later than 8:00 am to register. Fellow supporters have worked out carpooling and room-sharing options, simply respond to this email with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Charlie wants a fight, it's a fight he will get!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Liberty, &lt;br /&gt;

Eric Brakey &lt;br /&gt;

Maine State Director &lt;br /&gt;

Ron Paul Presidential Campaign &lt;br /&gt;

207-406-0897 &lt;br /&gt;

P.S. Ron Paul's been fighting for us for 30 years; fight for Ron Paul and become a Delegate, it's easy! Just show up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1336220532000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RonPaul-NH</urlname><id>527156</id><group_lat>42.9799995422</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire for Ron Paul 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336099363000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>HELP: Maine picks delegates this wknd</name><id>63361672</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1336215600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RonPaul-NH/events/63361672/</event_url></item>