<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Chestnut St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02169</zip><lat>42.249938</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617.471.4363</phone><name>Fat Cat</name><city>Quincy</city><id>884104</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.001294</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join 2012 Annual Members of the South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group for a fun Saturday lunch@ Fat Cat  in Qunicy.  Yelp states the approximate cost for one meal including drink, tax and tip is approximately $11-$30.  The Fat Cat is a small restaurant located in Quincy Center which has received great reviews from practically everyone who has dined there. As this restaurant is small and does not accept reservations, this will be an "intimate" meetup and seating will be limited to members only.  The Fat Cat does not seat incomplete parties so if you don't mind arriving on time, waiting a few minutes to be seated, and meeting up with our annual members, this is the perfect event for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring cash. You are responsible for your portion of the meal, including but not limited to, your drinks, food, tax, and tip and any shared items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Please note: As is customary with our Annual Members Only Events this event is only available for CURRENT (2012) Annual Members (who have already paid their Annual Membership).  We apologize for any inconvenience and encourage you to attend an event (that is not an AMO event) and pay your 2012 Annual Membership then.  It is now $6 for the balance of the calendar year.*&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annual Members Only Lunch!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, July 14th at 11:30am&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fat Cat Restaurant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;24 Chestnut Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quincy, MA 02169&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;617-471-4363&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.fatcatrestaurant.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Meeting Location&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Outside the front door if it's nice out. We will then go in together as a Group.&lt;/em&gt; Otherwise, inside the Lobby. If you arrive after we are seated the reservation is under "Debbi"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Organizer(s)&lt;/em&gt;: Debbi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Min/Max&lt;/em&gt;: Min of 4 people 48 hours in advance. Max of 12 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guests&lt;/em&gt;: None.  This is a Members-Only event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fees&lt;/em&gt;: None!  This is an Annual Members Only Event.  Therefore, no fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVP Deadline: 7:00PM on Friday, July 13th. Any changes made after this time may not be seen by an Event Organizer and will be considered a No-Show per our guidelines on the About Us page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;No-Show Policy on Membership Information Page:&lt;/em&gt; (Please click on the following link to be taken directly to the page.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/"&gt;http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/pages/Membership_Information/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Inclement Weather&lt;/em&gt;: This event takes place rain or shine as it's an indoor event.  Please see our Weather policy on the About page. (Simply scroll to the bottom and click on "Weather.")&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overview: Located in Quincy Center on the same street as the Quincy District Courthouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking: On-street parking as well as an inexpensive community parking lot is available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Debbi  </member_name><member_id>22304061</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1342482148000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1339687258000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Annual Members Only Lunch!</name><id>69157102</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1342279800000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/69157102/</event_url></item>