<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>123 River Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><lat>42.696285</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Wyndham Boston Andover</name><city>Andover</city><id>7250292</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.207474</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andover Ma.&lt;/strong&gt; Together Singles Dance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturday, Oct. 20th.&lt;/strong&gt; , 8pm. to 1am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wyndham Andover Hotel, Andover, Ma&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proper attire is required. No jeans or sneakers, no work boots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cover Charge goes from $12 to $15 after 9 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Host: Steve Obermiller. 603-491-1962 ob@tds.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RSVPs are incorrect. Because this event is listed with up to 10 different Groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had over 70+ at our tables at the last Dance, and everyone seemed to really enjoy themselves. Out of the 300 plus attending the TogethereNH Dance. This next one looks to &lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/6/9/5/c/event_160226972.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;be a great also. So, please join Steve Ob1. and about 20 to 70+ friends for an evening of dancing and socializing. This is one of the largest Singles Dances in Ma. or  NH, with between 200 and 400 singles, in a ballroom setting. Yet, this is not a Ballroom Dance. So, all you need to do is just shake it to dance. This Dance has the most tasteful variety of people and mix of ages that you will find anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please get there as close to 8 pm as possible.  As always, Steve Ob1. will do his best to introduces you as many people as he can. We had 5 tables + at the last Dance, and most people met at least 25 to 40 new people.   Because of the popularity of this Dance. Tables and seats will be hard to hold, much past 8:30. Plus, we have the only reserved tables there. Also, if you are late? The Cover Charge goes from $12 to $15 after 9 pm.  Ask where Steve Ob1., or where Meetup is sitting as you pay at the door. They will show you where we are sitting. Also look for our signs on our tables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also: There are some special hotel rates for people attending the TogetherNH Dance. So, ask the hotel if the are still available.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask for Steve Ob1. or Meetup at the door as you pay, &amp; the Meetup signs on our tables.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Ob1</member_name><member_id>3333572</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350788971000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SUPER FAN's</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Friends-Activity-Network</urlname><id>400492</id><group_lat>42.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The FAN Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349621209000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Andover Ma.Together Singles Dance</name><id>85892042</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350777600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Friends-Activity-Network/events/85892042/</event_url></item>