<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>703 Westfield Rd.</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06450</zip><lat>41.555537</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Guiffrida Park</name><city>Meriden</city><id>129143</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.761671</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The weather should be great for a change for this after work hike. I've made it a little later so more people can make it. This is a wonderful roughly 2 mi. vista hike which is so far my most favorite short hike!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We start out In the Giuffrida Park parking lot and hike past the dam for Crescent Lake. This part may be a little wet as we have to cross below the dam where the trail crosses the spillway. Then we hike up the steep side of the ridge and climb only an easy 15 feet or so of traprock. The path to climb like steep stairs. The reward is great though as at the top, on Chauncey Peak, is a WONDERFUL vista!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail follows the cliff edge to the north with a great view of the lake below and Lamintation Mtn. on the other side of the lake. The views get more natural and lovely as we follow the ridge. Eventually, as we get past the lake, the trail will cut down steeply from the ridge line. There is no climbing, but you need to watch your step lest you slip a little on leaves, dirt, or scree.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The path continues by the side of the lake with a pleasant walk through the old evergreens with a few benches at lakeside and back to the parking lot.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Those who wish to go need to have:   &lt;br /&gt;* A daypack - You need your hands free  &lt;br /&gt;* 1 quart of water - MUST bring!   &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate footwear - hiking boots are the best  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;Approximate location/directions to the *unmarked* park entrance can be found via MapQuest:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Meriden&amp;amp;state=CT&amp;amp;address=800+Westfield+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chauncey Peak is near the northwestern end of the Mattabesett Trail system. A good map can be found in the &lt;i&gt;Connecticut Walk Book&lt;/i&gt;, 19th Ed., in either the East or West editions, as map MB-8b as published by the Connecticut Forest and Park Association  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The link provided below takes you to a topographic map of the area centered on Chauncey Peak. A number of maps (this topo link included) list the lake as being named Bradley Hubbard Reservoir. You can zoom out on the map by changing the View Scale on the left to 1:50,000 or a little higher to get a context.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a general topographical map, see:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.topozone.com/map.asp?z=18&amp;amp;n=4603131&amp;amp;e=686860&amp;amp;s=25&amp;amp;size=l&amp;amp;datum=nad83&amp;amp;layer=DRG25" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.topozone.c...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1249599630000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1249215157000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike at Chauncey Peak in Meriden CT</name><id>11013577</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1249423200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11013577/</event_url></item>