<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Taconic Trail</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01267</zip><lat>42.722782</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Taconic Mountain Range-The Snow Hole</name><city>Williamstown</city><id>7389202</id><country>us</country><lon>-73.277626</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/1/1/c/event_122832572.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;The hike is on! No promises that we will be able to complete this due to weather, however. Please use your own judgment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(updated with distances on the bottom on 7/22)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : x-small"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;For those attending that are interested, there are a number of eatery's in Williamstown. We may be able to grab a bite if people are in agreement on the return!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;WOO HOO!!!  Finally picked a date for this!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;Now that we have a date chosen I will await more definite RSVP's. I will encourage carpooling / caravaning as well due to the distance. From the Athol/Orange area of Rt. 2 this is a 2 hour drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000 ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff00ff ; font-size : xx-large"&gt;PLEASE UPDATE YOUR RSVP'S!!!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realize it's a couple hours drive for most people, but I'm throwing the idea out there for you adventurous folks. I can't promise, with the lack of snowfall this past winter, that there will be much in the hole...  But you never know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;"snowhole"&lt;/strong&gt; is on the border of Williamstown, MA and Petersburgh NY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate or Strenuous (If you're into spelunking, you'll love it!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Main Attractions:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Cave that has ice/snow even in summer, great vistas, hardwoods, side trails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The locally-famous "Snowhole" is nestled in the portion of the Taconic Mountain Range where MA, NY, and VT come together. This rare, and intriguing geophysical treasure is essentially a 40-50 foot deep bedrock chasm that holds snow and ice well into the warmest summer months, and as of July 14th, 2004 continued to hold a fair amount of ice as it probably has done for thousands or millions of years gone by. If you'd like to really get adventuresome, there is also an explorable cave situated just at the beginning of the descent into the "snowhole" with room for up to a half dozen adults. The small entrance is on your right and is partially disguised by surrounding rocks. Bring your flashlight and wear "Mud clothes" as this cave will require you to get dirty if you wish to explore it. WORD OF CAUTION: Proper caving equipment and practices should be adhered to at all times, and &lt;strong&gt;NEVER ENTER THIS CAVE ALONE!&lt;/strong&gt; If you have an interest in caves, or if you are just looking for a really cool new place to explore this summer, this spot comes with the highest of recommendations!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;En route to the snowhole, take advantage of the numerous scenic vistas, and well maintained trail system to make your trip to the snowhole as enjoyable as the destination itself. This trail system is maintained by the Williams College Outing Club as a part of the College's Hopkins Memorial Forest and by the State of New York. The start of the walk from the parking area is fairly steep, but very short, and once you arrive at the small clearing and sign for Hopkin's Forest you have conquered the most difficult part of your trip. From that point you should follow the Taconic Crest Trail, marked by trail markers consisting of a white diamond on a blue square background, over gently rolling terrain for approximately 1-1.5 hours passing the Shepard's Well and Birch Brook side trails along the way. At the end of one of the open areas/scenic vistas you will see a sign that says "White Rocks" and from that point you continue for about 10 more minutes to a side trail on your right leading to the snowhole. Note: Some maps list White rocks much closer to the parking area, but they are inaccurate! These directions have been field checked, and "Berkshire" approved! From this clearing and sign, you will take your next right onto a small side loop that leads to the Snowhole and back again, if you miss the first, you can take the second, or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although there are several ways to access the snowhole, the route I describe here has been selected for it's moderate approach trail, abundance of parking, views, and wild berries, as well as it's simplicity for those of you who may be less than proficient map readers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This link will show you where we will be hiking. The Taconic Crest trail is on the very left edge of the map, with the snow hole in the upper left corner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hmf.williams.edu/public/trail-map/"&gt;http://hmf.williams.edu/public/trail-map/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;This trail is approximately 3 miles each way. Looking at the topographic map in the previous link, it is more of a rolling hike with not much of an actual climb.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Directions:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;Rt 2 westbound. All the way. I mean it!  All kidding aside, you DO want to take Rt 2 westbound until you get to the top of the Taconic Trail at the Williamstown MA/Petersburgh NY border. Parking area is at the old ski area on the LEFT side of the road.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Anybody interested in carpooling or caravaning can meet me at the Orange Wal-Mart on Rt 2A &lt;strong&gt;by&lt;/strong&gt; 8am.  If coming from Rt 2 East, take exit 16 and turn LEFT at end of ramp. Drive approximately 2 miles north until you come to a stop light and McDonalds on your right hand side. Turn LEFT on to Rt 2A and follow that about a mile and a half. Wal-Mart will be on your RIGHT. I will be parked near the Garden Center in a silver Toyota Corolla.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;For those needing pee breaks, coffee, or gas...  If you're coming to the carpool meeting in Orange, there is McDonalds (for pee or coffee) and Cumberland Farms (for gas or coffee) in Athol at the intersection of Rt 2A where you take a left to head towards Wal-Mart. Also, if you take that left onto 2A, about a half mile after the turn on the left is a Dunkin Donuts (for coffee or pee). And finally, Wal-Mart has a toilet if you missed the others!  Enroute to the Williamstown area we will pass another McDonalds in Greenfield as well as a couple gas stations. THAT's ABOUT IT until you reach North Adams, which is over an hours ride from there! Please plan your pee, gas, and coffee breaks accordingly!  Once you reach the downtown part of North Adams, there is a McDonalds and a Dunkin Donuts side by side on your right.  And...  I don't think there are any porta-pottys at the trail head, so... bring TP and hand sanitizer etc if needed!!!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Okay...   Because I'm OCD about details and such, I did this hike ahead of time on 7/22. This is what I have for mileage points:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Orange Wal-Mart to Rt 2 west via West River Street onramp is 2.7 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Intersection where Rt 2 west joins Rt 91 south is another 16 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Rt 91 south to Rt 2 west exit in Greenfield is another 2.7 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Rt 2 west from the Rt 91 rotary to North Adams is 35.3 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;North Adams center to Williamstown intersection with Rt 7 south is 5 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Rt 7 south/Rt 2 west to intersection with Taconic Trail is 2.5 miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;And Rt 2 west up the Taconic Trail is 4 more miles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #3366ff ; font-size : large"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000 ; font-size : small"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #800080"&gt;Grand total from Wal-Mart in Orange to the parking spot in Petersburgh NY is 68.2 miles. (Just over an hour and a half, depending on traffic) &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1344915880000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>kindred spirits</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group</urlname><id>1282371</id><group_lat>42.5299987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.75</group_lon><name>Northern Central MA, Southern NH Hiking Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337987568000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike to the "Snowhole" - snow in August?</name><id>66371292</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1344693600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Northern-central-MA-Hiking-Group/events/66371292/</event_url></item>