<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Quincy St.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.374475</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 495-1573 </phone><name>Harvard University - Sever Hall</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>1133541</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.114562</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;Jenna Norwood to Present Award-Winning Health Documentary &amp;amp; Lecture at Harvard University&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have seen &amp;quot;Super Size Me,&amp;quot; the junk food documentary, get ready for a stunning look at the other side of the dining table. Independent filmmaker Jenna Norwood will screen her feature documentary, &amp;quot;Supercharge Me! 30 Days Raw&amp;quot; at Harvard University on Tuesday, December 8th, 5 p.m. at Sever Hall, Harvard Yard. The event is part of Norwood's &amp;quot;Supercharged Living&amp;quot; College Tour. The film will be followed by a lecture and discussion about food choices and their relationship to sustainability. The event is sponsored by the Harvard University community and is FREE to the public.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following day, Norwood will present a healthy food demonstration to students, parents and teachers at the Warren Prescott Elementary School in Charlestown, MA as part of the Meatless &amp;quot;Carbon Offset Program,&amp;quot; initiated by the Oceanic Society (a marine conservation non-profit) and, Quen.ch, an environmental education outreach group from the Harvard University Extension.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;This vital interconnectivity among our food, our health and our environment is every reason for communities and schools to come together to gain knowledge and share resources to improve our future,&amp;quot; said Alisyn Johnson, event organizer. &amp;quot;That is the intention of these events.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Supercharge Me!&amp;quot; is a &amp;quot;rawcumentary&amp;quot; -- a film that shows what happens when one volunteer human guinea pig (Jenna Norwood) eats only raw, organic food for 30 days. The original inspiration was weight loss, but the results went beyond the visible to those which were more profound.; including lower cholesterol, lower blood sugar, elimination of chronic pain, better mental clarity, enhanced spirituality and happier disposition.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Norwood's odyssey took her from Sarasota, Florida to San Diego, California where she enrolled in a 30-day raw food detox program where she consumed only uncooked &amp;quot;living&amp;quot; foods. Generally, these foods include organic fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds, sprouted grains and juices. Many believe that food in its raw state has greater nutritional value and contains more enzymes. And the lifestyle is regarded as having the smallest ecological footprint.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Documentary cameras followed Norwood as she transformed her life with a raw food diet and interviewed doctors, raw food experts, celebrities (Ben Vereen and Kathy Sledge) and a variety of others from around the world who follow the raw food lifestyle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Supercharge Me!&amp;quot; is pending wide international release. Currently, the film is only available at JennaNorwood.com. The site also has videos, recipes and resources for the raw food lifestyle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; About Jenna Norwood&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After her dramatic transformation on raw food, Norwood became passionate about sharing her experience. She switched careers from public relations consultant to raw food educator and chef. She has a recipe book in the works and is in negotiations for a healthy living television show.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Norwood currently serves as Chair of the Healthy Start Coalition of Sarasota County. She is a native of Washington, D.C. where she founded her public relations consulting business in 1993. In her former PR career, she worked exclusively with socially conscious clients. Norwood holds a B.S. in Journalism from the University of Maryland. She received her nutrition and culinary education through the Optimum Health Institute and the Living Light Culinary Arts Institute.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?f=q&amp;amp;source=s_q&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=sever+hall+harvard+cambridge+ma&amp;amp;sll=42.842474,-70.99293&amp;amp;sspn=0.007835,0.01929&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;hq=&amp;amp;hnear=Sever+Hall&amp;amp;ll=42.37443,-71.115993&amp;amp;spn=0.003947,0.009645&amp;amp;z=17&amp;amp;iwloc=A" target="_blank"&gt;Google Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;# # #&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media Note: Members of the media are encouraged to attend. Interviews are welcome. For film trailer, more information &amp;amp; images, please see &amp;quot;Media&amp;quot; page at &lt;a href="http://www.JennaNorwood.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.JennaNorwood.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Thank you : )&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To your radiant health!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenna&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jenna Norwood&lt;br /&gt;America's Supercharged Living Expert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.JennaNorwood.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.JennaNorwood.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Media Contact            &lt;br /&gt;Speaker: Jenna Norwood                                               &lt;br /&gt;Email: Jenna(at)SuperchargeMe.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Posted by Martha Muehe (&lt;a href="http://www.essenic.com" target="_blank"&gt;www.essenic.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://img2.meetupstatic.com/04199747090604847485/img/logo_82.png" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>MaraMore.com</member_name><member_id>2656748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>6</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1299571661000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Raw Foodists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>RawBoston</urlname><id>733136</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Raw Food Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1259802649000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Jenna Norwood @ Harvard University</name><id>12004613</id><headcount>16</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1260309600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/RawBoston/events/12004613/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/5/d/9/global_12067497.jpeg</photo_url></item>