<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>106 Pennybrook Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01905</zip><lat>42.476158</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Lynn Woods Reservation</name><city>Lynn</city><id>710792</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.986000</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>We'll meet in the parking lot.  After the walk there will be a potluck at Ruthie's condo located near the park. The theme will be mexican potluck.  Indicate in your rsvp if you will be joining us for the potluck as well as the walk and what you will be bringing for your contribution.  Look forward to seeing you all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;LYNN WOODS RESERVATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Lynn Woods Reservation was founded in 1881, the second largest municipal park in the United States, is a 2,200 acre municipal forest park located in Lynn, Massachusetts. The Woods offers over 30 miles of scenic trails for hiking, running, horseback riding, mountain biking (not allowed during the winter), cross-country skiing, and nature walks. Three active reservoirs provide pretty pond-like scenery among natural forestland, as well as clean water for the City of Lynn. Dungeon Rock is a well-loved underground tunnel with a history of pirate lore and treasure seekers. The Rose Garden, Houghton Horticultural Garden, and Amphitheater areas provide more formal settings to explore. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The City of Lynn’s Department of Public Works, Park Commission, and Lynn Water and Sewer Commission share jurisdiction and management of the Reservation. The Park encompasses nearly one-fifth of the entire land area of the City and represents a significant natural, watershed, and public recreational resource in eastern Massachusetts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lynn Woods Ranger&lt;br /&gt;Dan Small Phone&lt;br /&gt;Fax&lt;br /&gt;Email 781-477-7123&lt;br /&gt;n/a&lt;br /&gt;LynnWoodsRanger@aol.com&lt;br /&gt;Rules and Regulations &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HOURS: Sunrise to Sunset. For your safety and the protection of the woods, the reservation is closed at night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BIKING: You must stay on officially marked trails only.  Official trails will have a colored paint blaze and are on this map.  Take the time to learn the layout of the trail system so that you will not accidentally ride on an illegal or closed trail.  If it  isn't on the map it isn't an official trail.  Biking is not allowed on the trails marked &amp;quot;foot traffic only&amp;quot;.  Responsible riding will help protect the forest and the future of biking in Lynn Woods.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HORSE-BACK RIDING: Riding is permitted on orange blazed fire roads only.  Please do not run horses or ride on the hiking trails.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DOG WALKING: City Ordinance for restraining dogs is in effect throughout the reservation.  Owners are responsible for removing waste from trails, roads and parking lots.  Pets are prohibited from entering in or upon reservoirs due to the potential for contaminating our drinking water supply.  Poop pollutes:  Waterborne diseases such as E.coli, Camphylobacter fetus and Crytosporidiosis are caused from fecal contamination.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SWIMMING: No swimming or boating is permitted in any of the reservoirs in the reservations as they are all used for Lynn's drinking water supply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FIRES: No fires are allowed, except by permit.  Fire has been a major threat to the forest in Lynn Woods.  In order to prevent future fires from destroying the woods, we cannot allow grills, stoves or fire to be lit without a permit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FISHING: Fishing is prohibited due to the impact on the water supply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROHIBITED: Camping, paintball, ATV and dirt bike riding are prohibited due to the safety and conservation concerns.  See kiosks at both entrances for a full list of rules and regulations plus other park information.&lt;br /&gt;Park Information&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Main Entrance (west): Take Walnut Street to Pennybrook Road.&lt;br /&gt;Directions to Eastern Entrance: Take Lynnfield Street (Route 129) to Great Woods Road.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To find out how to get involved in the protection and improvement of Lynn Woods, call Friends of Lynn Woods at 781-477-7123 or click here to visit our website: &lt;a href="http://www.flw.org" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.flw.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a detailed map of Lynn Woods visit our website. There are also maps available at City Hall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To get involved in advocating for responsible bicycle use in Lynn Woods, call New England Mountain Bike Association (NEMBA)  at (800) 57-NEMBA, email to 72773.2557@compuserve.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For water supply information, contact Lynn Water and Sewer Commission at (781) 596-2400. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Area Information:&lt;br /&gt;2,200 acres in Lynn, Lynnfield and Saugus - 2nd largest municipal park in the country&lt;br /&gt;Walden Pond=240 acres; Breed's Pond=208 acres; Birch Pond=82 acres&lt;br /&gt;Gannon Golf Course (18 hole)=180 acres;&lt;br /&gt;Gravel Fire Roads=10 miles;&lt;br /&gt;Official Trails=30 miles;&lt;br /&gt;Highest Elevation (Burril Hill/Stone Tower)=285 ft.;&lt;br /&gt;Longitude West 70 degrees-55'-30&amp;quot; to 71 degrees-00'-00&amp;quot;;&lt;br /&gt;Latitude North 42 degrees-27'-00&amp;quot; to 42 degrees-31'-00&amp;quot;;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sites and Attractions: (Park hours are from sunrise to sunset)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact the Park Ranger for natural and cultural history tours of the sites and trails.&lt;br /&gt;When planning a group outing, check with the ranger for seasonal updates/closures.&lt;br /&gt;Check bulletin boards in parking lots for seasonal programs, maps and regulations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dungeon Rock (Dungeon Rd): Open to the public 9:00-2:30 Tuesday - Saturday, subject to change. Please contact lynnwoodsranger@aol.com in advance for weekly schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rose Garden (Main Entrance): Open to the general public year round. Weddings, by request, by approval, by the Lynn Board of Park Commissioners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amphitheater (Main Entr&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kathryn</member_name><member_id>3302152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288542499000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Recreational Walkers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>walkers-255</urlname><id>415396</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>The Chestnut Hill Walking Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1286298093000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>LYNN WOODS LYNN MA and POTLUCK LUNCH</name><id>15009456</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288537200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/walkers-255/events/15009456/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/2/3/global_7785619.jpeg</photo_url></item>