<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Nashua Drive</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03064</zip><lat>42.764248</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Margaritas Mexican Restaurant</name><city>Nashua</city><id>2186301</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.463165</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Elaine, who runs the Dynamic Introductions - Merrimack Valley Region, NH &amp;amp; MA meetup group, is running this event, so you should address any additional questions about how this is run, including the cost for the speed dating portion, to her, but I will be in attendance as a further contact person for you at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The description, below, of the event is from her meetup listing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speed Dating, with expanded age ranges, and an "CUPID PARTY" to follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 Please register on line PRIOR to event to hold your spot for Speed Dating at www.8MinuteDating.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All speed dating participants attend the after party for FREE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speed Dating starts at 6 pm, after Party for ALL AGES at 8 pm following the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 $10 cover for CUPID PARTY includes free appetizers, door prizes, and a chance to meet someone special just before Valentines Day! Hosted by Dynamic Introductions &amp;amp; 8MinuteDating.com, profits to organizer goes to a great cause.....see www.MotivatingMiles.org for details of their wonderful cause to benefit terminally ill New Hampshire residents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need or would like further information, please call Elaine at 603-262-1560&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ask where the speed-dating event is being held.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>NeilL</member_name><member_id>3034835</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1360807264000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1359950510000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Speed Dating with CUPID Party after event</name><id>102889252</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1360796400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/102889252/</event_url></item>