<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;

ORAGNIZER: Paul Shoemaker
CONTACT: &lt;a href="http://photo.meetup.com/513/members/3108784/" class="linkified"&gt;http://photo.meetup.com/513/members/3108784/&lt;/a&gt;
WHO: All members.

What: Cutler Park Reservation photo shoot
When: Sunday, April 21, 2pm
Who: Anyone with a camera. A min of 10 people need to RSVP to hold this event.
Event Description: 

Ask and ye shall receive. The group discussion made it clear everyone was looking to get out and off the computer use their camera's. So let's check out some of the more photographable areas in New Engalnd.  This event is not confirmed until 10 "Yes" RSVP's are noted.

Advanced photographers please consider joining us and sharing you photographic knowledge on light and outdoor techniques.

Where:

Cutler Park Reservation (Parking on Kendrick Street)
Needham, Dedham
617-333-7404 

The seven hundred acres known as Cutler Park comprise the largest remaining fresh water marsh on the middle Charles. Located in Needham and Dedham, the marsh and small lake attract over 100 species of birds which make Cutler Park a prime spot for nature study. Other activities suitable to this wetland preserve are hiking, canoeing and fishing. Open year-round, dawn to dusk. 

Cutler park has a nice boardwalk through the marsh. Meet at 2pm in the parking lot. Afterwards we can go for late lunch or a coffee. If you need a ride, please say so in your RSVP. 

CUTLER PARK MAP
&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/maps/cutler.gif" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/maps/cutler.gif&lt;/a&gt;

DIRECTIONS TO PARKING ON KENDRICK STREET

Take Exit 19A off Route 95. At the first set of lights, make a right onto Second Ave. At the end of Second Ave., make a right onto Fourth Ave. At the end of Fourth Ave., make a right onto Kendrick St. Look for the reservation sign on the left side of the street, before the PTC office building. Park in the lot with the sign.

&lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/cutlerPark.htm" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/metroboston/cutlerPark.htm&lt;/a&gt; 

Fresh City 
241 Needham Street 
Newton, MA 02464 
Phone (617) 244-7071</description><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1177351397000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newenglandphotographynetwork</urlname><id>353886</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.8499984741</group_lon><name>New England Photography Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>22</yes_rsvp_count><created>1168377761000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cutler Park Reservation</name><id>5379403</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1177178400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newenglandphotographynetwork/events/5379403/</event_url></item>