<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Hartford CT</address_2><address_1>300 Columbus BLVD</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06106</zip><lat>41.765041</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mortenson Park </name><city>Hartford</city><id>550417</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.669594</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>1.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Saturday, July 12, 5:00 - 10:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring Picnic lunch Or purchase food there.&lt;br /&gt;Location: Mortensen Riverfront Plaza &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of our International Festival Series presented by Lincoln Financial Foundation, this festival brings you an evening of music featuring some of the best international Latin Jazz and Salsa artists. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On-site Marketing and Promotional Opportunities: &lt;br /&gt;Riverfront events attract large numbers of patrons from all over New England. Riverfront events may be an ideal environment to market or promote your product, business, or service. If you would like more information on marketing opportunities at Riverfront events, send your inquiry to vending@riverfront.org. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food Vending Opportunities: &lt;br /&gt;Riverfront Recapture programs a variety of concerts, festivals, and sporting events that include food vending. All food and beverage vendors are required to complete an application and receive approval from Riverfront Recapture. To receive an application, send your inquiry to vending@riverfront.org. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Merchandise Vending Opportunities: &lt;br /&gt;Riverfront Recapture programs a variety of concerts, festivals, and sporting events that include food and merchandise vending. Merchandise vendors are required to complete an application and receive approval from Riverfront Recapture. To receive an application, send your inquiry to vending@riverfront.org.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll give my Number a couple days before.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy AKA Jeanine</member_name><member_id>5547282</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1216069865000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Fun-Bunch</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH</urlname><id>648134</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.7600021362</group_lon><name>The West Hartford Over 40 Fun Bunch!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213242419000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ray Gonzlavez Salsa Festival</name><id>8127663</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215896400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/West-Hartford-FUN-BUNCH/events/8127663/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/e/b/global_3362283.jpeg</photo_url></item>