<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Runtime: ~2hrs likely | PG-13 - SF Action.

Director: Steven Spielberg

Starring Harrison Ford, Shia Lebouf, Cate Blanchette, etc.

Genre: Adventure

More info: &lt;a href="http://imdb.com/title/tt0367882/" class="linkified"&gt;http://imdb.com/title/tt0367882/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.indianajones.com/site/index.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://www.indianajones.com/site/index.html&lt;/a&gt;

Reviews: N/A

Trailer: 
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/v7Gqi2IeIL0&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;

or download the big files:
&lt;a href="http://movies.yahoo.com/feature/indianajones.html" class="linkified"&gt;http://movies.yahoo.com/feature/indianajones.html&lt;/a&gt;

Description: N/A

Notes: Please do not RSVP YES if you do not intend to come. Yes is not a MAYBE. If you can't figure out what your going to do in the future, please do not burden us with that. Please buy your tix AHEAD of time! I'm going to watch this regardless of people coming, but it will more fun with people.

If it's downstairs, I'll be right behind the corded rope after ticket stubs have been ripped in front of the popcorn counter. If it's upstairs, I'll try to grab one of the tables in front of the coffee house near the large monumental windows.

Due to the popularity of the film, we might not be able to gather and reserve seats for EVERY SINGLE one of us! But that's alright, because after the film ends, we will wait for you outside of the exits of the film [b]auditorium[/b] for bathroom breaks. I'm not talking about the CINEMA exits to the streets, i'm talking about the room that you just watched the film, go outside into the halls and we will ALL be there in a large group! Remember to LOOK FOR MY HAT after the movie finishes! THat's when I'll call to make reservations@Bennigans or Rock Bottom.

The movie begins@7:45PM, I'll be there @7PM. We will plan to go in about 7:30PM sharp to get seats if we can. Otherwise, it'll just be a mad rush towards the auditorium. REMEMBER TO MEET US afterwards if that is the case! Thanks! Cya there!</description><how_to_find_us>I"ll be wearing my trademark green hat+Meetup logo+my screename JediFonger in front as usual. If upstairs, metal tables. If downstairs, right in front of the popcorn stands. After the film ends, We'll be outside the movie exits. Pls wait for us.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214356074000</updated><rating><average>4.63999986649</average><count>11</count></rating><why>We won't bite. Love to have discussions about the films after movie ends. The group often goes out afterwards and socialize.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>36</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198727023000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull</name><id>6974350</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1211583600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6974350/</event_url></item>