<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>903 Boylston St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02115</zip><lat>42.348255</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 778-0089</phone><name>Lir Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>668965</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084130</lon></venue><fee><label>sliding scale </label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>-$10 per person</description><amount>5.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a progressive working on campus? Join Campus2Community for happy hour to meet other campus progressives! Tell your friends &amp;amp; colleagues to RSVP at &lt;a href="http://www.campus2community.net"&gt;www.Campus2Community.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fee: $5-$10 (sliding scale) cash at the door - newcomers welcomed! &lt;br /&gt;

 Complimentary appetizers - cash bar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Campus2Community is an inclusive multi-issue network of progressive faculty and staff in the Greater Boston area. Campus2Community is a project of Socializing for Justice, a grassroots group established in 2006 to build a cross-cultural, cross-issue progressive community, network and movement in Boston based on the philosophy of abundance. We're doing it by putting the social back in social justice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show up to get connected and collaborate (or commiserate) with like-minded progressives from other departments and other area campuses. Be inspired by all the great organizing, research and education being created in Boston area schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond meeting progressive faculty and staff - Campus2Community will help you get connected with local social justice organizations so you can better support the progressive students on your campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started - meet us for happy hour! While you're waiting for the next one on October 17 you can post job opportunities, internships, events or other resources on the C2C Message Board at &lt;a href="http://www.campus2community.net"&gt;www.Campus2Community.net&lt;/a&gt;. Click on "Discussions" at the top of the page, select the appropriate folder and then start a new conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Invite your friends - each person needs to RSVP for themselves - this event is open to any faculty, staff, or grad student working at or attending school in the Greater Boston area.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Robbie Samuels</member_name><member_id>3091753</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350525597000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SoJusters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>sojust-tm</urlname><id>299655</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Socializing for Justice</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347858189000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Happy Hour for Progressive Faculty, Staff &amp; Grad Students</name><id>82732092</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>7200000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350511200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/sojust-tm/events/82732092/</event_url></item>