<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was it a winter or a long spring?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Summer is not far behind&amp;hellip; Yay!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; No matter, come to the first wine tasting at Ralph&amp;rsquo;s house for 2012 in Cheshire.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We want to bid fare thee well to Denise Brown who has been a member and leader in at least these three groups.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; She has decided to pull up stakes in CT and move back to CA permanently to be with family and friends on the left coast.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Santa Barbara is calling her back.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; We want to send her off in a great wine tasting event.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Don&amp;rsquo;t know Denise, you may like wine!&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Enjoy the night as well with friends and soon to be friends.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; The event will be held this March 10th from 6-10pm.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Party Express, Wine and Dine New Haven and Dine out New Haven will all feel the loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For wine night, everyone will bring a bottle of wine from CA in honor of Denise (no boxed wine or Yellow Tail please) AND a pot luck dish, finger food, hors d'oeuvres or desert.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Please indicate what food item you want to bring when you sign up.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; This invitation will go out to 3 groups of 20 people ea.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; Please bring your own expendable glass in case it breaks or you forget it.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I have some, but not enough for all even though I now have some extra Benmarl wine glasses now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If&amp;nbsp;you are coming by yourself or don't want to go in with someone just bring a bottle of wine that is &lt;strong&gt;$15 or more&lt;/strong&gt;. Couples or groups can go in together on a bottle that is $25 or more in multiples of $15 depending on the quantity of people in the group, to ensure we have a good assortment of wines to taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get some different types of wine so we have a varied taste testing...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reds Malbec, Blends, cab, merlot, shiraz pinot noir,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;whites -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;sav blanc, chards, Riesling, pinot grigio, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please ensure you show up if you RSVP yes, since we may have a waiting list and you are taking up a person&amp;rsquo;s spot if you do not show up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Please note* The address will be sent a few days prior to the event if you don't have it already to all the "yes" RSVPs, due to this being a private residence.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; It should go without saying to Drink Responsibly.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; I will have water and coffee too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy, responsibly!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>knock on the door.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ralph</member_name><member_id>8774347</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331667006000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Party People</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Partyexpress</urlname><id>478650</id><group_lat>41.2900009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.8600006104</group_lon><name>PartyExpress !!  Let's Get Together and have Fun!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1329365195000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Wine night at Ralph's house</name><id>52548292</id><headcount>60</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1331420400000</time><rsvp_limit>21</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Partyexpress/events/52548292/</event_url></item>