<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>290 Harvard St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02446</zip><lat>42.342934</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617 734-2501</phone><name>Coolidge Corner Theater</name><city>Brookline</city><id>726945</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.122505</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;From an email to Nerd Fun from Coolidge Corner's Science on Screen program:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://by113w.bay113.mail.live.com/default.aspx?rru=inbox" target="_blank"&gt;http://by113w.bay113....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; &lt;i&gt;Gort, Klaatu barada nikto!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Robert Wise’s 1951 film, about Klaatu, a humanoid alien who travels 250 million miles to Washington, D.C. with his giant robot protector, Gort, to warn Earth’s leaders that human beings must stop their warring ways or face perilous consequences, is widely considered to be one of the greatest science-fiction movies of all time.  Filmed in stark black and white and shot in a realistic style, The &lt;b&gt;Day the Earth Stood Still&lt;/b&gt; perfectly captures the suspicions and fears of the Cold War political climate, creating a pervasive mood of uneasiness that is enhanced by Bernard Herrmann’s eerie, Theremin-driven score.  Decades after the film’s release, Klaatu’s ultimatum for disarmament, given just before he returns home, still has the power to chill:  '…But if you threaten to extend your violence, this Earth of yours will be reduced to a burned-out cinder. Your choice is simple: join us and live in peace, or pursue your present course and face obliteration.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The film features several strong performances, but perhaps the most memorable character is the one who remains silent and nearly motionless throughout: the iconic robot Gort.  Played by the 7’7” actor Lock Martin, the metallic, featureless Gort is an ominous presence, capable of vaporizing anything he targets by firing lethal laser beams from beneath his visor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Over the years, both celluloid and real-world robots have become increasingly sophisticated and complex. Before the film, &lt;b&gt;Dr. Dennis Hong&lt;/b&gt;, associate professor of Mechanical Engineering and director of the groundbreaking Robotics &amp;amp; Mechanisms Laboratory at Virginia Tech, will talk about some of the amazing advances in robotics, including humanoid robots of a less menacing variety than Gort.  Hong’s lab has invented a number of novel robots and mechanisms, including 'whole-skin locomotion' for mobile robots inspired by amoebae, a unique three-legged walking robot, STriDER, and CHARLI-L (Cognitive Humanoid Autonomous Robot with Learning Intelligence), a 5-foot-tall robot that requires no remote power source or computer, has arms and legs, and walks like a human.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;For his contributions to the field, Dr. Hong was given the National Science Foundation’s CAREER award, and in 2009 was named as one of Popular Science's Brilliant 10.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Tickets:  $9.75 general admission, $7.75 students and Museum of Science members, free for Coolidge Corner Theatre members.  Tickets available online at www.coolidge.org/science or at the Coolidge box office, 290 Harvard Street, Brookline&amp;quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Release Date&lt;/u&gt;: September 28, 1951 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Purchase tickets&lt;/b&gt;: $9.00 &lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/showtimes" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where to meet:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As usual, T.J. Maher will get there at 6:00 pm if anyone wants to hang out and socialize before. Rain shine, or bone-chilling winds, the Coolidge Corner forms a line starting at 6:15 pm in the alleyway outside the theater, a line which quickly wraps its way down the brick wall next to the theater and turns the corner. We can all get in line by 6:15 pm, giving us more time to say hello to each other. The doors open at 6:40 pm, and the theater fills up fast. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;T.J. Maher is 5 foot 7, with short brown hair, blue eyes, a &amp;quot;Hello My Name is T.J.&amp;quot; nametag, and a red MEETUP sign attached to his black messenger bag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;... If the runtime of the move is 92 minutes, and the Coolidge Corner lists the event as 2 hours, 22 minutes, the talk should be around fifty minutes long. We should be getting out of the Theater by 9:25 pm. Anybody up for the Jewish Deli, Zaftigs &lt;a href="http://www.zaftigs.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.zaftigs.co...&lt;/a&gt; ? When you exit the building, hook a right and head to the street. T.J. will be acting like a human landmark, big ole MEETUP sign in tow, and we can decide if we want to go somewhere after or not. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Dennis Hong, according to his TED Talks profile:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ted.com/speakers/dennis_hong.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ted.com/sp...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As director of a groundbreaking robotics lab, Dennis Hong guides his team of students through projects on robot locomotion and mechanism design, creating award-winning humanoid robots like DARwIn (Dynamic Anthropomorphic Robot with Intelligence). His team is known as RoMeLa (Robotics &amp;amp; Mechanisms Laboratory) and operates at Virginia Tech. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hong has also pioneered various innovations in soft-body robots, using a “whole-skin locomotion” as inspired by amoebae. Marrying robotics with biochemistry, he has been able to generate new types of motion with these ingenious forms. For his contributions to the field, Hong was selected as a NASA Summer Faculty Fellow in 2005, given the CAREER award by the National Science Foundation in 2007 and in 2009, named as one of Popular Science's Brilliant 10. He is also a gourmet chef and a magician, performing shows for charity and lecturing on the science of magic.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; ' &lt;i&gt;I still cannot forget the mind-blowing sensation when I first watched the movie Star Wars. I was fascinated by R2D2 and C-3PO. Since then, I decided to become a robot scientist and never changed my mind&lt;/i&gt;.'&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dennis Hong's Faculty page at VirginiaTech College of Engineering:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.me.vt.edu/people/faculty/hong.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.me.vt.edu/...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Virginia Tech engineering students build CHARLI, a full-sized humanoid robot&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vt.edu/spotlight/innovation/2010-04-26-charli/charli-robot.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vt.edu/spo...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;As CHARLI takes his first steps, anxious onlookers stand ready to catch him if he falls. His stride is short, but upright, as one foot is placed in front of the other in the basement of Virginia Tech’s Randolph Hall. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;But CHARLI is no toddler.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;He is a 5-foot tall humanoid robot built by graduate and undergraduate students with the Virginia Tech College of Engineering’s Robotics and Mechanisms Laboratory (RoMeLa).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;After a long moment, CHARLI comes to a rest. An audible 'Whew!' is heard from CHARLI’s main architect, doctoral student Jeakweon (“J.K.”) Han. Dennis Hong, associate professor of mechanical engineering and director of RoMeLa, can’t resist a joke. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'One small step for a robot, one giant leap for robotics,' he shouted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Hong isn’t entirely facetious, though. CHARLI (that’s for Cognitive Humanoid Autonomous Robot with Learning Intelligence) is historic. CHARLI is the first untethered, autonomous, full-sized, walking, humanoid robot with four moving limbs and a head, built in the United States. His two long legs and arms can move and gesture thanks to a combination of pulleys, springs, carbon fiber rods, and actuators. CHARLI soon will be able to talk as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Fans of robotics are taking note [...]&amp;quot;. [ &lt;b&gt;MORE:&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;a href="http://www.vt.edu/spotlight/innovation/2010-04-26-charli/charli-robot.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vt.edu/spo...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How David Comes up with Ideas, according to Science Nation:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nsf.gov/news/special_reports/science_nation/acrobaticrobots.jsp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nsf.gov/ne...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;[...] 'Yeah, many of these wacky robot concepts originate from my dreams,' [David] explains with a grin. &amp;quot;I go to bed at three or four in the morning and when I close my eyes, I see these weird circles and blocks and lines exploding in my head and some of these assemble and form these weird types of robotic mechanisms.'&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot; 'Next to my bed, I keep a notepad and a special pen that has an LED light on it because I don't want to wake up my wife by turning on the light. I just jot down and sketch everything and go back to bed. Every morning before my first cup of coffee, before I brush my teeth, I open my journal. Many times, it's empty. Many times, it's all scribbles. But from time to time, I see these really ingenious ideas hidden in my sketches and that's my eureka moment. I type all my ideas into a database on my computer. When we have calls for proposals in robotics, I look at my database of ideas and try to find a match,' he says&amp;quot; [...] [ &lt;b&gt;Video&lt;/b&gt;: Dennis Hong in his lab&lt;a href="http://www.nsf.gov/news/special_reports/science_nation/acrobaticrobots.jsp" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nsf.gov/ne...&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Robotics and Mechanisms Laboratory (RoMeLa):&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.romela.org/main/Robotics_and_Mechanisms_Laboratory" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.romela.org...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Robot Evolution by Intelligent Design:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Robotics &amp;amp; Mechanisms Laboratory at Virginia Tech is a facility for graduate and undergraduate robotics research and education with an emphasis on studying novel mobile robot locomotion strategies. Our research interests are in the area of Robot Locomotion and Manipulation, Kinematics and Mechanisms, and Autonomous Systems&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Science on Screen:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/science" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The Boston area is filled with academic superstars - so why not bring them to the movies? With Science On Screen, we present a feature film or documentary with a basis in science, along with exciting introductions by noted scientists in a related field&amp;quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.coolidge.org/map" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.coolidge.o...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;Parking&lt;/u&gt;: Nearby metered public parking is available behind the theatre (on Center St. one block from Harvard St.) and along Beacon Street. Meters are free after 6:00pm and on Sundays and holidays. Please note that the lots tend to fill up on weekends or during large events, so please plan a little extra time to find space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;u&gt;By train&lt;/u&gt;: take the Green Line (C branch to Cleveland Circle) trolley from downtown to Coolidge Corner via Beacon Street. The Coolidge Corner stop is at Harvard Street, 5-10 minutes from Kenmore Square&amp;quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>T.J. Maher</member_name><member_id>4996698</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>14</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1292455327000</updated><rating><average>4.71000003815</average><count>7</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1289588588000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Day the Earth Stood Still (1951)w/ roboticist Dennis Hong @ Coolidge Corner </name><id>15428161</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1292284800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/15428161/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/c/7/global_19570551.jpeg</photo_url></item>