<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>7 Wendell Depot Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01379</zip><lat>42.549891</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-544-3559</phone><name>Wendell Free Library</name><city>Wendell</city><id>1390616</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.397167</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Relying exclusively on government documents, statements from the best witnesses available, and the words from the mouths of the killers themselves, Dark Legacy produces a thoroughly substantiated criminal indictment of George Herbert Walker Bush, establishing beyond a reasonable doubt his guilt as a CIA supervisor in the conspiracy to assassinate John F. Kennedy. If we could present this evidence to a jury in Texas, he would pay with his life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;***********&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part one presents the overwhelming mountain of evidence that President Kennedy was hit by bullets from the front and rear. Every witness in the Dallas emergency room attests, on camera, to the fact that a bullet from the right front blew a fist-sized whole in the back of the President's head. The New York Times carried these statements on the day of the murder; and has covered them up ever since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part two presents the on-camera testimony of the witnesses who actually handled the President's body, the FBI report, and the photographic evidence all proving unequivocally that the President's body was stolen from the Secret Service and the wounds altered, before the body was delivered to Bethesda Naval hospital for the autopsy. Jackie Kennedy accompanied an empty casket on the plane flight home. Who had the power to do all this without attracting public attention? It's a short list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;************&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part three presents the Nazi-connections of the Bush family, which prompted the FBI to seize their assets during WW II, as Nazi assets. It presents the suppressed fact that Watergate burglar and CIA operative E. Howard Hunt was found by a jury to have been in Dallas and involved in the conspiracy to kill Kennedy. Hunt was a supervisor of the misguided CIA-led anti-Castro Cubans who broke into the Watergate. He is not only connected to Bush through Watergate; and through Bush's father, Prescott; but five days after the assassination, the head of the FBI, J. Edgar Hoover, wrote a memo, titled &amp;quot;Assassination of President John Fitzgerald Kennedy&amp;quot; in which he named &amp;quot;George Bush of the Central Intelligence Agency&amp;quot; as the supervisor of what Hoover himself called the &amp;quot;misguided anti-Castro Cuban&amp;quot; killers of the President. Bush has said he doesn't remember the events of that day, but FBI documents place him in Dallas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is difficult to assess the stature and significance of someone who has been dead as long as John Kennedy. His killers have also been his detractors, actively desecrating his memory, as they did his body. The movie begins with a short presentation of some of his most powerful and important speeches; including a stunning speech to the UN in which Kennedy calls for the complete abolition of the military industrial complex. These same men the military industrial complex, ripped him from us, and the darkest features of our history since that time are all directly the result of his murder. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discussion will follow the film. Please download flier from &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/files/"&gt;files&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. And get and show this film to honor this anniversary of a clear coup d'etat for the military industrial complex leading to such false flag operations as on September 11, 2001, Iran-Contra-Gate, USS Liberty attack, Gulf of Tonkin. To buy the film and watch the trailer, visit &lt;a href="http://thedarklegacy.com/"&gt;The&lt;b&gt;DarkLegacy&lt;/b&gt;.com (official film web site)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>jonathan mark</member_name><member_id>387101</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291242731000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>valley911truth</urlname><id>300645</id><group_lat>42.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6800003052</group_lon><name>Valley 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1285879674000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Dark Legacy: George Bush and the Murder of John Kennedy</name><id>14955002</id><headcount>20</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1290470400000</time><rsvp_limit>50</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/valley911truth/events/14955002/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/5/4/2/global_18371442.jpeg</photo_url></item>