<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;New Rally Point: Corner of Tremont and Park!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(That's where we usually meet our folks)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a repeat of our famous Boston's Homeless Assistance meetup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As usual, my intention is not only to provide clothes and food, but also treats. In addition to sandwiches and lunches, don't hesitate to bring your favorite treat (preferably in single size portions, we'd like to please as many people as possible). I don't think treats are on the menu very often, so let's bring some!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Requests:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to participate in a different way, we have started to take orders, in order to make a different kind of difference... If you'd like to procure any of the items below, please let me know and I can arrange pickup. This week's list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- John, a pair of sneakers size 12 wide&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Rob, a pair of sneakers size 13&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Tony, a pair of pants size 38&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Arthur, a pair of pants size 38&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Ali, you've asked for a pair of woman's pants, size 9/10 (not sure who it is for)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Angelo, a pair of sneakers size 11.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- James, a pair of sneakers 10.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Anne Mary, a pair of sneakers 9.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Sharon, sweat pants with stripes, medium, pink or black (with matching top if possible)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Tooth paste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;- Shoes size 10 thru 14&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;span&gt;- 2-t-shirts size large and 2xx for a special person who is going to surgery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Norma had a great idea, she brought some toiletries from hotels where she stayed and figured to put them to good use! It was a hit! She also mentioned that the dollar store can be a good supplier for some of the requested items. When I think about it, it makes sense, they still need all the basic stuff like anyone else! Great suggestion Norma!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking orders is something relatively new, and in the future we need to make sure that we tell anyone who asks for a special order that there is no guarantee. I'd rather not place their expectation too high... But if we can, I think that would be terrific.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Frederick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Across from the movie theater on the commons</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>frederick</member_name><member_id>25269862</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368292133000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Boston Volunteers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>BigEnoughtoDeliver</urlname><id>1343564</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Volunteers. Big enough 2 deliver, small enough 2 care</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1367183490000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clothes Drive and Lunch Treat</name><id>116643142</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>4500000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368287100000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/BigEnoughtoDeliver/events/116643142/</event_url></item>