<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>55 Constitution Rd</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02129</zip><lat>42.372042</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 242-5601</phone><name>Charlestown Navy Yard Visitor Center</name><city>Charlestown</city><id>975971</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.058883</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/1/6/8/event_158708552.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;"Don't fire until you see the whites of their eyes!"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Free guided tour of the Bunker Hill Battlefield with a National Park Service Ranger. Space is limited so if you sign up then you should go. This is not overbooked, it has a waitlist so don't screw your fellow nerds out by squandering a spot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Including a breathtaking climb of the Bunker Hill Monument. 294 steps is a lot more than you think it is but we can walk off the post event drinks in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bunker Hill Museum opened in 2007 and is available for free to tour as well after the battlefield tour or in place of the monument climb for those who don't want to climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the event, we can take the T-Water Shuttle ($3) from Charlestown to State Street for an afternoon drink at The Landing. It's the best "poor man's harbor cruise" in the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will post a separate event for the Landing in case anyone is just looking for afternoon drinks and the Patriots should be on as well. (if you're not into football, at least you'll know where they got their name from)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We should meet at the Charlestown Navy Yard at 10:45. There is a small tent set up near the Cassin Young (big gray ship with 793 on it)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Landing doesn't have food so have a good brunch before you go if you want drinks. or not. I don't care. just an FYI. does anyone read this far. probably not. someone is going to ask if we're taking the water shuttle and that's in the 5th paragraph. we all know who you are but you don't because you didn't read this far. and I'm sure we'll see comments posted by some of these people. if I respond to dumb questions, please know that I'm being sarcastic and only doing so for my own amusement.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Eric</member_name><member_id>8776856</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347918612000</updated><rating><average>4.82999992371</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1347635194000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Free Guided Walking Tour of the Bunker Hill Battle Site</name><id>82383172</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347806700000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/82383172/</event_url></item>