<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>18.0</amount><required>1</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for the first of several exciting meetup investigations this year. We will be investigating the haunted Wachusett Village Inn in Westminster, MA. We have conducted several investigations there in the past, and we have consistently had lots of activity and have captured good EVPs and other evidence. The oldest building in the inn is haunted by at leat three spirits: a woman, a little girl, and a man (Mr.Palmer). Mr. Palmer, especially, is comfortable with the presence of investigators and seems to like to chat. I look forward to meeting him again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event begins at 6pm with a 1-hour presentation on protection: how to protect your self from accidents -- and from spirits -- when conducting an investigation. Occasionally investigators do have to cope with a spirit who wants more than to just communicate. Investigators on our team can tell you that they have had to contend with all kinds of unwanted contact from negative spirits, and they'll vouch for how important it is to know at least the basics of how to protect yourself from the unseen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 7pm to 8pm we have dinner at the inn. The inn has come up with a specially priced pre fixe menu for us -- a choice of several different entrees and sides at only $18.00pp. &amp;nbsp;This is a good deal, and it's the only charge for the event. The inn is generous letting us investigate multiple haunted rooms in the old building for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From 8pm to 1am we investigate. Bring your equipment and have fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to spend the whole night at the inn, they are giving us a special room rate of $69.00, significantly lower than their book rate. You might like to rent one of the haunted rooms for the rest of the night, after the investigation ends. &amp;nbsp;To reserve a room, please contact the inn directly and explain that you are with Footsteps Paranormal and so entitled to the $69.00 room rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because to the size of the location, I need to restrict the size of the investigation to 20 people, so consider signing up soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy hunting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandy </member_name><member_id>7992934</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1331651199000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Paranormal Believers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>footsteps-paranormal-meetup</urlname><id>1305459</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-72.0</group_lon><name>Footsteps Paranormal Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1328565958000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Investigation of the Haunted Wachusett Village Inn, Westminster, MA</name><id>51298062</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1331503200000</time><rsvp_limit>19</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/footsteps-paranormal-meetup/events/51298062/</event_url></item>