<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>A &lt;b&gt;2-day&lt;/b&gt; and approximately 24 mile hike on the Appalachian Trail starting on Stratton-Arlington Rd, VT and heading northbound to Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) in Mad Tom Notch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet 9/26/09 at 9 AM at the starting point AT parking area on Stratton-Arlington Rd., 7 miles west of West Wardsboro, VT. The parking area is gravel and dirt. We'll hike with rest stops the roughly 12 miles to the shelter for the night. We will ascend 1,706 ft. to the peak of Stratton Mtn. (alt. 3936 ft.) at mile 3.8 and there will be a firetower at the top for views. We'll have a generally descending trend after Stratton Mtn. We'll stop at about mile 7 at the Straton Pond Shelter for lunch. I figure after going an additional 5 miles we'll reach the William B. Douglas Shelter (alt. 2220 ft.) within the Lye Brook Wildernes of the Green Mountains by about 7 PM at the latest. We'll have dinner and set up for the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll get up and ready somewhat early the second day given the approximate 12 miles we need to cover and wanting to do that at a slower pace. We should be hiking by 8:00 AM and reach the endpoint by about 6:30 PM at the latest. The second day has us decending, with a stop at Spruce Peak Shelter (alt. 2220 ft.) at mile 3.4 for water, to Rte 11 &amp;amp; 30 (alt. 1840 ft.) at mile 6.3. We'll eat lunch here in the or around the AT parking area. We then start ascending Bromley Mtn. and at mile 8.1 for the day stopping for water at Bromley Shelter (alt. 2500 ft.). At mile 9.5 for the day we reach the peak (alt. 3260 ft.) with an observation tower for views. Then we descend 2.5 miles into Mad Tom Notch (alt. 2446 ft.) and the endpoint on Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) where we will have a shuttle placed for the ride back to the beginning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll then shuttle back to the beginning to recover vehicles left there. After that we head home!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please note that terrain, conditions, and individual party members may affect the overall timing of the hike and may necessitate backup plans if any member of the party runs into significant issues or if there are weather related issues that spring up. I have been conservative with the estimated times and as long as all parties are reasonable fit, experienced, and equipped we could come in earlier than I estimated. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== ADVISED MUST-BRING GEAR/SUPPLIES ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;NOTE: Nights could be cool so watch the weather and pack accordingly!&lt;br /&gt;* Backpack -suitable to hold sleeping bag and all other gear and food, overall weight should be no more than about 40 lbs &lt;br /&gt;* Waterproofed hiking boots -Must be comfortable &amp;amp; broken in  &lt;br /&gt;* 2 pair wool socks &lt;br /&gt;* Hat -something good in the rain and/or sun &lt;br /&gt;* Layers of clothing -Cool mornings &amp;amp; possibly hot afternoons, avoid cotton as it stays wet. &lt;br /&gt;* Comfortable underwear -no chaffing! &lt;br /&gt;* Rain poncho/jacket -essential! -rain pants optional &lt;br /&gt;* Sleeping bag &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Bug spay -essential!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Sunscreen &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Headlamp -or flashlight, fresh batteries -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Emergency whistle &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;2 quart water min.&lt;/b&gt; -strongly suggest bringing a water filter to restock on water &lt;br /&gt;* Trail meals -2 lunches, 1 dinner, 1 breakfast. High energy meals should be planned. Only meal time to cook are dinner &amp;amp; breakfast. &lt;br /&gt;* Trail appropriate high energy snacks &amp;amp; electrolytes -e.g. at least G.O.R.P (Good Old Raisins and Peanuts), beef jerky, granola bars, GU energy gel, Gatoraide drink powder, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* &lt;b&gt;Toilet paper -in plastic bag to keep dry -essential!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Hand soap/hand sanitizer -in plastic bag &lt;br /&gt;* Personal backpack First Aid kit&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;== OPTIONAL GEAR ==&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;* Camera &amp;amp; extra batteries &lt;br /&gt;* Compass &lt;br /&gt;* Backpacking cookstove -if cooking &lt;br /&gt;* Matches -for cookstove &lt;br /&gt;* Something to sleep in -PJ's or shorts and T, etc. &lt;br /&gt;* Games or reading for night activity &lt;br /&gt;* Head net -keep bugs out &lt;br /&gt;* Tent &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the Meetup location&lt;/b&gt; on Stratton-Arlington Rd. 7 miles west of West Wardsboro, VT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps/1250+Stratton+Arlington+Rd+West+Wardsboro+VT/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Approximate location/directions to the endpoint&lt;/b&gt; AT parking area on Mad Tom Notch Rd. (USFS 21) near Peru, VT: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mapquest.com/maps?city=Peru&amp;amp;state=VT&amp;amp;address=2200+Mad+Tom+Notch+Rd" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mapquest.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;=== Legal Stuff ===&lt;/b&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;By clicking on &amp;quot;Yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Maybe&amp;quot; for this event you agree, warrant, and covenant as follows:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In consideration for accepting this entry, I, the registrant, intending to be legally bound, hereby, for myself, my heirs, my executors and administrators, do waive and release any and all rights for damages I may have against any parties or persons connected with the Hartford Area Hiking meetup group for and related to the above listed event. I attest and verify that I am physically fit to participate in any portion of this above listed event. I grant Hartford Area Hiking permission to use any photographs, film or videotapes of this event for any purpose.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Not sure what vehicle I'll have at the starting point. Look for 6'2" guy &amp; you have my picture on the hiking site.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1254263981000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1251508217000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike on the AT from Stratton-Arlington Rd VT to Mad Tom Notch Rd VT</name><id>11228736</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1253970000000</time><rsvp_limit>7</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/11228736/</event_url></item>