<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>38 Cilleyville Rd</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03216</zip><lat>43.434834</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Kearsarge Lodge Hall</name><city>Andover</city><id>12376242</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.857582</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;The Andover Constitutional Freedom Alliance invites all interested NH Citizens to attend our monthly meeting where the topic will be: “Agenda 21″ and or ” “Sustainable Communities”. This is planned to be an open discussion on the pros and cons of this initiative. We will have a real thought provoking dialogue on this issue, the perceived good and or bad will be discussed in an open, honest, and respectful way, granting us all the chance to understand what the “excitement” is all about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will be moderated by Hon. Jenn Coffey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests: Hon. Gregory Carson, Esq. – Carson serves as the Director of NH Office of the US Dept of Housing and Urban Development, as well as Secretary for the NH GOP. Previously Carson served as the Asst Majority Leader of the NH House of Representatives, as well as, Chairman of the Rockingham County Republican Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim Carter – Tim Carter is one of the organizers of the Lakes Region Teaparty and has done extensive research on the Granite State Future program — a new regional plan of governance for NH that comes from the top down and and is controlled by unelected people who serve private foundations and corporations. A former councilman from Amberley Village, Ohio, he served for 8 years on the Amberley Village Planning and Zoning Board. He is also the founder of www.AsktheBuilder.com with over two decades of experience as a custom home builder and custom remodeler, who was selected as one of the top 50 re-modelers in the USA by Remodeling Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Kearsarge Lodge Hall, 38 Cilleyville Rd. Andover, NH &lt;br /&gt;

Time 7:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>shemdogg</member_name><member_id>7638748</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1364955004000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1363886083000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>"Agenda 21" or "Sustainable Communities" Debate</name><id>110369302</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1364943600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/110369302/</event_url></item>