<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Union St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02043</zip><lat>42.212359</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>781 749-7160</phone><name>Wompatuck State Park</name><city>Hingham</city><id>726971</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.859782</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Hello &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather has not cooperated with me for last couple time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wompatuck State park provides nice trails for cycling. I am planning a ride  about 6 miles in circle starting at the parking lot near the main entrance at the north end of park along the Union St. (Near Union St crosses Charles St.) and ride toward the camp ground, then go toward Aaron River Reservoir.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trail map in below website. &lt;a href="http://www.mass.gov/dcr/parks/southeast/womp.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.mass.gov/d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am taking my Mt. Bile. Trails are paved but no cars worry about. Some area are bit bumpy not sure if the road bike can take it. (I am not familiar with road bike)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We can target 4 and half minutes/mile to keep the ride modest, and make it faster or slower depending on the ability of the group. Earlier in this planned trail will have some moderate climbing to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I myself will bike from Hingham Shipyard to the parking lot so that I can add additional total 8 miles (4 miles from/to the parking lot). I don't want to recommend this to group because that requires crossing/biking busy street. But, if you want to, you can join me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Masahiro&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I am on the silver Mt. Bike with Black helmet and Mt Bike Pants.</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272837789000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Fitness Lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssfmgfitness</urlname><id>280193</id><group_lat>42.1699981689</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9499969482</group_lon><name>The South Shore Fitness Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1271950743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Cycling at Wompatuck (moderate)</name><id>13258750</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272664800000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssfmgfitness/events/13258750/</event_url></item>