<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1741 S Willow St</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03103</zip><lat>42.953915</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>603-668-5557</phone><name>Barnes and Noble</name><city>Manchester</city><id>759357</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.436569</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>In September we continue to explore the intersection between Buddhism and modern psychology by discussing the recently published book “Emotional Awareness: Overcoming the Obstacles to Psychological Balance and Compassion” by the Dalai Lama and Paul Ekman&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two leading thinkers engage in a landmark conversation about human emotions and the pursuit of psychological fulfillment...At their first meeting, a remarkable bond was sparked between His Holiness the Fourteenth Dalai Lama, and the psychologist Paul Ekman, whose groundbreaking work helped to define the science of emotions. Now these two luminaries share their thinking about science and spirituality, the bonds between East and West, and the nature and quality of our emotional lives. In this unparalleled series of conversations, the Dalai Lama and Ekman prod and push toward answers to the central questions of emotional experience. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the sources of hate and compassion? Should a person extend her compassion to a torturer—and would that even be biologically possible? What does science reveal about the benefits of Buddhist meditation, and can Buddhism improve through engagement with the scientific method? As they come to grips with these issues, they invite us to join them in an unfiltered view of two great traditions and two great minds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Accompanied by commentaries on the findings of emotion research and the teachings of Buddhism, their interplay—amusing, challenging, eye-opening, and moving—guides us on a transformative journey in the understanding of emotions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Henry Holt &amp;amp; Company, Incorporated, 2008 – hardcover – list price $23.00 – available from Barnes and Noble.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for a small sign on a cafe table saying "Book Discussion"</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Aurore Eaton</member_name><member_id>3983123</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1255389393000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>People interested in Buddhism</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha</urlname><id>447070</id><group_lat>42.9900016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4700012207</group_lon><name>The Manchester Buddhism Sangha</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>12</yes_rsvp_count><created>1231687643000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Continued discussion of "Emotional Awareness" by the Dalai Lama and Paul Ekman</name><id>9497748</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252969200000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Buddhism-Sangha/events/9497748/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/5/global_1946069.jpeg</photo_url></item>