<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>101 North Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01756</zip><lat>42.122640</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-473-7539</phone><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary</name><city>Mendon</city><id>669262</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.566860</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Maple Farm Sanctuary is an animal sanctuary providing lifelong &lt;br /&gt;homes for abused, abandoned and unwanted farmed animals while &lt;br /&gt;promoting veganism and respect for all life through public &lt;br /&gt;information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What:       3rd Annual Open House  - Picnic, Music and Barn &lt;br /&gt;Tours.&lt;br /&gt;Where:    Maple Farm Sanctuary, 101 North Avenue, Mendon, MA &lt;br /&gt;01756&lt;br /&gt;When:      November 2, 2008 (Sunday)   1:00 – 5:00 pm   &lt;br /&gt;Cost:         $10.00 per person&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The family-friendly event will feature a presentation from &lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm Sanctuary co-founder Cheri Ezell-Vandersluis who &lt;br /&gt;will share the compelling story of how she and her husband, &lt;br /&gt;Jim, abruptly ended their profitable generations-long meat and &lt;br /&gt;dairy farming business to create a safe haven for animals.  We &lt;br /&gt;encourage event participants to get involved in protecting the &lt;br /&gt;rights of all animals by raising awareness about the cruelty &lt;br /&gt;that exists in the factory farming and fur industries.  &lt;br /&gt;Attendees will also be treated to live performances by vegan &lt;br /&gt;musical guests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tours of the beautiful Maple Farm Sanctuary grounds will be &lt;br /&gt;available throughout the event.  Tour participants will have &lt;br /&gt;the opportunity to learn the animals' stories and meet Cassie &lt;br /&gt;the cow, Piggie Wiggy the potbelly pig, Lucky the pony, &lt;br /&gt;Butterscotch the goat, along with llamas, chickens, horses, &lt;br /&gt;dogs and more.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sanctuary has taken in a fraction of the billions of farmed &lt;br /&gt;animals that are bought, sold, tormented and slaughtered by the &lt;br /&gt;meat, dairy and fur industries. They will live the remainder of &lt;br /&gt;their lives in peace, free to roam and meander the land.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are approximately 80 animals living at Maple Farm &lt;br /&gt;Sanctuary. This includes cows, horses, sheep, llamas, ducks, &lt;br /&gt;chickens, pigs, turkeys, dogs, goats, and a miniature pony.  &lt;br /&gt;Maple Farm is located on 121 acres of beautiful farm land in &lt;br /&gt;Mendon, Massachusetts.   &lt;br /&gt;See you there!!!&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1226169349000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1224365855000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Maple Farm Sanctuary 3rd Annual Open House  - Picnic, Music and Barn </name><id>8986756</id><headcount>10</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1225648800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/8986756/</event_url></item>