<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Sargent Hall, Rm 17O</address_2><address_1>12O Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02108</zip><lat>42.358734</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>4O1-316-6513</phone><name>Suffolk University Law School</name><city>Boston</city><id>387788</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.059920</lon></venue><fee><label>Pay AT: filmfinancing.org</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>HOSTED BY: EXEMPLAR LAW PARTNERS, LLC&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;THIS IS A PAID EVENT&lt;br /&gt;SIGN UP ONLINE AT: www.filmfinancing.org&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time&lt;br /&gt;6:00 pm ET - 10:00 pm ET&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location&lt;br /&gt;Suffolk University Law School&lt;br /&gt;120 Tremont Street&lt;br /&gt;Sargent Hall, Room 170&lt;br /&gt;Boston, MA 02108 Suffolk University Law School&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Institute for International Film Financing (IIFF) is an innovative, independent social-impact organization that endeavors to bridge the gap between the worlds of filmmaking and finance for the benefit of all stakeholders ? including the public at large. Founded in 2003, IIFF is incorporated in California as a not-for-profit, public benefit corporation. IIFF is headquartered in San Francisco and has chapters in the SF Bay Area, New York City, New England, Florida, Los Angeles, and Switzerland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Abstract: &lt;br /&gt;After successfully establishing chapters in the San Francisco Bay Area, New York City, New England and Los Angeles, the Institute for International Film Financing (IIFF) continues its monthly, multi-city gatherings at the junction of film and finance with a special event in downtown Boston, MA. This month's New England Townhall Meeting in Boston, MA, is graciously hosted by Exemplar Law Partners and Suffolk University Law School.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This &amp;quot;grassroots&amp;quot; community meeting is designed to introduce IIFF to Connecticut's filmmakers, entrepreneurs and financiers as well as the public at large. Our goal for this and future gatherings is not only to provide unbiased insight &amp;amp; education about the business of film ?and film financing in particular? but also to foster &amp;amp; inform productive relationships between attending professionals. The event features a powerful roster of highly topical speakers from the worlds of film and finance. We are delighted to welcome real-world financiers among our guests for the evening. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evening's presentations plus panel discussion will address key issues relevant to filmmakers, financiers, and anyone interested in the economics, business mechanics, and financial dynamics of film. They will be followed by Q&amp;amp;A time. Attendees will also have ample opportunity to interact &amp;amp; network with our distinguished presenters and panelists and amongst themselves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Program Details: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PROGRAM SCHEDULE&lt;br /&gt;6:00-6:30 pm ... Registration and introductions&lt;br /&gt;6:30-7:45 pm ... Three featured presentations with Q&amp;amp;A (4x20 min)&lt;br /&gt;7:45-8:00 pm ... Networking break (15 min)&lt;br /&gt;8:00-9:40 pm ... Four featured presentations with Q&amp;amp;A (3x20 min)&lt;br /&gt;9:40-10:00 pm ... Moderated panel discussion with Q&amp;amp;A (20 min)&lt;br /&gt;10:00+ pm ... Community time at area restaurant&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;MODERATOR&lt;br /&gt;The event will be moderated by Donald Bertrand, a veteran financial-sector corporate attorney turned private-practice lawyer who provides entertainment law services in Connecticut and New York. Don's law office in West Haven, CT (www.ctLawHaven.com) represents various clients on a host of screenwriter, composer, producer and filmmaker issues. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PRESENTERS&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Alternative capital structures for film financing&amp;quot; by Christopher Marston, a prominent member of the Boston financial and legal community, focused on financial structures for corporations and the entertainment and film industry.  As the Founding Partner of Exemplar Law Partners, Christopher works closely with Exemplar's emerging enterprise clients as a strategic partner by combining his advanced business expertise and education with his legal savvy to take clients to the next level.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;What Filmmakers and Financiers Need to Know About Digital Distribution&amp;quot; by Scott Kirsner, editor of the blog CinemaTech (&lt;a href="http://cinematech.blogspot.com)" target="_blank"&gt;http://cinematech.blo...&lt;/a&gt;, which covers the intersection of filmmaking and new technologies. He is also a weekly columnist for the Boston Globe, and a regular contributor to Variety and BusinessWeek. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;Strategically Funding Independent Films Using Tax Credits and How an Independent Film Recoups and Profits&amp;quot; by Vinca Liane Jarrett, who today with her newly founded legal practice in conjunction with FilmPro Finance LLC, has become a leading innovator and representative in the entertainment industry.  Attorney Jarrrett represents a variety of established and budding filmmakers from the organization of their film companies through finding distribution for their projects. She attends dozens of key film festivals, assisting clients negotiate deals and packaging clients music and film projects. Additionally, through her company FilmPro Finance, LLC Jarrett makes introductions to producer clients to potential sources of financing. In 2002 Jarrett formed the company FilmPro Finance LLC assisting primarily A-list producers establish funding for&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Christopher Marston</member_name><member_id>2731493</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1273542274000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>entrepreneur-674</urlname><id>232461</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Revolve Nation's Boston Entrepreneur Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1191209139000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Institute for Int'l Film Financing Townhall Meeting (Thursday, October 4, 2007)</name><id>6460215</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191535200000</time><rsvp_limit>55</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/entrepreneur-674/events/6460215/</event_url></item>