<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hello all,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join me for Ari Folman’s “wholly innovative, original, and vital history lesson, with pioneering animation, &lt;i&gt;Waltz with Bashir&lt;/i&gt;.”  As this film will be in its opening weekend, I suggest you buy your tickets ahead of time by visiting the Kendall’s &lt;a href="https://tickets.landmarktheatres.com/Landmark.aspx?TheatreID=231" target="_blank"&gt;site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One night at a bar, an old friend tells director Ari Folman about a recurring nightmare in which he is chased by 26 vicious dogs. Every night, the same number of beasts. The two men conclude that there's a connection to their Israeli Army mission in the first Lebanon War of the early eighties. Ari is surprised that he can't remember a thing anymore about that period of his life. Intrigued by this riddle, he decides to meet and interview old friends and comrades around the world. He needs to discover the truth about that time and about himself. As Ari delves deeper and deeper into the mystery, his memory begins to creep up in surreal images… Folman's animated documentary has been acclaimed worldwide and is winner of 6 Israeli Film Academy Awards, including Best Film, Director, Screenplay and Art Direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A. O. Scott says: “&lt;i&gt;Waltz With Bashir&lt;/i&gt; is a memoir, a history lesson, a combat picture, a piece of investigative journalism and an altogether amazing film.  &lt;i&gt;Waltz With Bashir&lt;/i&gt; will certainly enrich and complicate your understanding of its specific subject — the Lebanon War and, in particular, the massacre of Palestinians by Lebanese Phalangist fighters at the Sabra and Shatila refugee camps — but it may also change the way you think about how movies can confront history.”  Read the complete review &lt;a href="http://movies.nytimes.com/2008/12/26/movies/26bash.html?ref=movies" target="_blank"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As is our custom, Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film and then it’s off to a local restaurant to discuss. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope to see you there!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Nina will be holding a Meetup sign near the front row after the film.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Nina</member_name><member_id>4237709</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1291949575000</updated><rating><average>4.57999992371</average><count>12</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>307808</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston International/Arthouse Movie Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>26</yes_rsvp_count><created>1230846765000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Waltz with Bashir</name><id>9420582</id><headcount>25</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1232217000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Boston-International-Arthouse-Movie-Meetup-Group/events/9420582/</event_url></item>