<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>58 Main St</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01038</zip><lat>42.372700</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>The Dike</name><city>Hatfield </city><id>761794</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.594704</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;This walk is along the dike next to Connecticut River in Hatfield, Massachusetts. This walk will take place August 6th at 10:00 AM. It is people and dog friendly. All dogs must start on leash until we know everybody gets along. There is a wide path that provides plenty of space for several walkers with their doggy companions. The Town of Hatfield is a historic agricultural river town on the west bank of the Connecticut River. The Connecticut River forms the eastern and southern boundary of the town. It is also part of the Mill River Watershed. There are incredible views of the Connecticut River on the left side of the path. On the right side of the path, you will view the farmlands of Hatfield. There is a spot where our dogs can take a dip in the river if weather permits. While driving to this location, you will view the remarkable historic character of Hatfield made up of a dense concentration of well-preserved 18th and 19th century family homes. Plan to walk an hour out and turn around to walk the same path back. Bring your camera, too, the views are really pretty. And, bring bug repellent -- the mosquitos can be pretty fierce near the water. See Mapquest, Google or Yahoo for directions to 58 Main St., Hatfield. The building is a former school which has also been used as a library. It's two story, brick - parking is behind the building, and these is a ball field there also. The path along the dike is accessible from behind this building. Call me (Kristi) at 413-695-9848 if you get lost or need additional information.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I have a vanilla PT Cruiser and black lab with blue leash; also see my picture on my profile</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kristi</member_name><member_id>7010444</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1316880482000</updated><rating><average>4.17000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1308338379000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>A WALK ALONG THE CONNECTICUT RIVER - HATFIELD DIKE</name><id>22583071</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1312639200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/22583071/</event_url></item>