<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Gorham, NH</address_2><address_1>off Hwy 16, just  north of 19 mile trailhead</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03581</zip><lat>44.387840</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Mount Moriah  Stony Brook</name><city>Gorham</city><id>256302</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.173134</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;This is a member lead dayhike&lt;/b&gt;. All hikers will review the trail maps and itinerary and follow the hike safe guidelines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Stony Brook Trail leads from NH Route 16 near Gorham to the Carter-Moriah Trail between Mount Moriah and North Carter. It is mostly easy walking and probably the most popular day hike of Mount Moriah, although there is substantial elevation gain due to the low start.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Distance: From NH Route 16 to Carter-Moriah Trail, about 3.5 miles one-way&lt;br /&gt;From NH Route 16 to Mount Moriah, about 5.0 miles one-way&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Elevation gain: From NH Route 16 to Carter-Moriah Trail, about 2200 feet&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To Mount Moriah, about 3200 feet, nominal on return&lt;br /&gt;From the parking lot, the Stony Brook Trail immediately crosses a bridge over Stony Brook and continues up the far side, soon crossing a side stream on a bridge over a gorge. The trail follows an old woods road, then suddenly leaves it R to descend and recross Stony Brook, this time with no bridge. The trail climbs to reach another woods road at .8 miles and turns L on it. (This is the former route of the trail, bypassed when a housing subdivision was built across it. In an emergency, continuing down the old route and asking a homeowner to call 911 may be the fastest way to get help.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trail continues up this road which becomes steeper and fainter. At 2.3 miles, a brook is crossed on rocks and the trail ascends to the col between Mount Moriah and North Carter at 3.5 miles, where it ends at the Carter-Moriah Trail. The junction with the Moriah Brook Trail is just to the L. The summit of Mount Moriah is 1.5 miles to the L on the Carter-Moriah Trail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mountainsummits.com/pictures/newhampshire/moriah/moriah.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stony Brook Trailhead: NH Route 16 about 1.8 miles S of US Route 2 in Gorham, elevation about 934 feet&lt;br /&gt;44.3635°N, 71.1769°W (WGS84)&lt;br /&gt;WMNF fee site $3.00 or annual pass&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ALL CANCELLATIONS OR CHANGES TO RSVP'S SHOULD BE MADE BY 6 PM THE NIGHT BEFORE THE HIKE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3 YES RSVP'S ARE NEEDED TO CREATE A MEETUP.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bara</member_name><member_id>3491697</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>5</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1245676496000</updated><rating><average>3.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1243388325000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mt Moriah and North Carter: Stony Brook Trailhead</name><id>10500203</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1245502800000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/10500203/</event_url></item>