<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1098 Commonwealth Avenue</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02215</zip><lat>42.352027</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-383-6651</phone><name>Saray Turkish Restaurant</name><city>Boston</city><id>845519</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.124357</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Saray Restaurant - New Turkish Restaurant in Allston.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saray is a new Turkish restaurant in Packard's Corner, in the space on Commonwealth Ave. that use to be Beckett's Pub. They are across from Shaw's Market.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The menu is not quite as extensive as the Family Restaurant in Brookline Village, but offers soups, salads, a range of hot and cold appetizers, seafood dishes, a variety of kebabs and a number of other entrees. they do not serve liquor, but have a number of interesting beverages such as Turkish soft drinks and juices.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is a cozy little neighborhood restaurant.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A comfy room that people enjoy being in and to me that is very important.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The reservation will be under Jo-Ann.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will be inside waiting for everyone.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are running late or lost please call the restaurant.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since this event falls on a holiday the parking will be free.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By MBTA take the Green Line  and take the Boston College Trolley and get off at Packard's Corner.  Or from Kenmore Square or Watertown T Stop take the 57 Bus and still get off at Packard's Corner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By car go to www.mapquest  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our focus is on friendly and respectful gatherings while sharing a delicious meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please be considerate of your fellow diners time by arriving promptly for events. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please bring enough cash to pay for your expenses, which are mainly meal, drinks, tip, and tax. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All RSVP's are on a first come, first served basis. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may only RSVP YES or NO. Maybe isn't an option. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please RSVP YES only if you are certain you will attend an event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure you can attend because you have other unconfirmed plans or uncertain transportation, please RSVP NO with a comment requesting to be placed on wait list. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If an event is full and you wish to attend, please RSVP NO with a comment to be wait listed. If there is an overwhelming response, the reservation may be increased or another seating arranged. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your name appears on the event page as a YES after the event and you have not attended the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If an organizer changes you're RSVP to NO because you haven't replied to final update event confirmation email deadline, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any guests you've RSVPd for NO-SHOW it will count as if you've NO-SHOWED. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you change your RSVP from a YES to a NO within twenty-four hours of the event, it is counted as a NO-SHOW. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are a NO-SHOW for three events you are removed from the group. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;NO-SHOWS impact everyone; from you, who could or has been on the wait list to the organizer as well as the restaurant's who staff based on our reservation.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If it is less than twenty-fours from the meal and you are not able to attend or are running late, you must contact the organizer directly by phone. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An email from you explaining your absence is an expected courtesy. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are removed and there were extenuating circumstances, please email Tonya about rejoining. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your feedback is appreciated so, rate the event and venue by completing surveys afterwards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An organizer will arrive at least fifteen minutes before the event to confirm seating as well as welcome diners.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Allan</member_name><member_id>4472329</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1199405351000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Fellow Foodies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>brunchclub-107</urlname><id>273555</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, &amp; Dinner Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196864547000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>2008  - New Years Dinner......</name><id>6860409</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1199232000000</time><rsvp_limit>14</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/brunchclub-107/events/6860409/</event_url></item>