<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Bradley Airport</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06096</zip><lat>41.928687</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Sheraton Hotel</name><city>Windsor Locks</city><id>1089899</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.683873</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>25.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;b&gt;October 17, 2009&lt;br /&gt;8:00 a.m.-5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Sheraton Hotel, Bradley&lt;br /&gt;Airport, Windsor Locks, CT&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                      &lt;b&gt;Keynote Speaker - Congresswoman Michele Bachmann&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Updated per Judy Aaron. Thanks Judy.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;     Connecticut Liberty Forum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;     For the second year in a row, liberty comes to Connecticut.  The second annual Connecticut Liberty Forum will be held at the Sheraton Hotel, at the Bradley Airport, in Windsor Locks on October 17, 2009, from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     The Liberty Forum is not about politics.  It’s not about political parties.  The Liberty Forum is about the Constitution. It’s about educating the public about the meaning of the Constitution, and how its provisions are being implemented in terms of the issues facing Americans today.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;     The theme of this year’s Liberty Forum is: “The Economy and the Constitution:  How Do We Protect Our Economic Freedom in a Constitutional Manner?”  The Connecticut Liberty Forum will bring together people from all walks of life, from federal, state, and local government leaders, to authors, to taxpayers, to grassroots citizens.  Discussions will be held throughout the day on topics such as: the Constitutionality of federal bailouts; the role of the federal reserve; how to balance the budget and assist those in need during difficult economic downturns; what is a sound money system; and how can individuals protect and defend our economic and Constitutional freedom?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;      This year’s keynote speaker will be Congresswoman Michele Bachmann of Minnesota.  Congresswoman Bachmann has been cast as a somewhat controversial public figure for her recent stand in questioning federal treasury officials about whether their actions, indeed, are Constitutional.  Congresswoman Bachmann is expected to give the keynote speech addressing the recent actions of Congress and the executive branch in resolving the current economic crisis.  Congresswoman Bachmann’s speech will be presented at a brunch at 10:00 a.m. &lt;b&gt;(there is an additional $25 fee for this brunch - please see below).&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;    Others attending and topics of their talks include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Robert Schulz, founder, We the People Foundation for Constitutional Education, “Continental Congress 2009, the Next Step for A Free People”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Goshen First Selectman Robert Valentine, “What Effect Does the Recent Increase in Federal and State Tax and Spending Have On Local Government?”;&lt;br /&gt;James Perloff, Author, “The Shadows of Power”, “American Sovereignty and the Coming World Government”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Andrew Schiff, Investment Consultant, Euro Pacific Capital, “Constitutional Monetary Policy”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jim Azzola, Campaign for Liberty, “Is the Federal Reserve and Its Policies Constitutional?”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Walter Reddy, Committees of Safety, “What is Constitutionally Sound Money?”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan Kniep, President, Connecticut Federation of State Taxpayers Organizations, “What Effect Does the Recent Increase in Federal and State Tax and Spending Have on Taxpayers?”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Markley, former Connecticut State Senator, “What the Founders Meant to Preserve”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grassroots Advocacy Panel including Bob MacGuffie, Right Principles; Tanya Bachand, Connecticut Tea Party Coordinator; Estelle Stevenson, We the People Connecticut State Coordinator; Pamela Kurtz, Regional Coordinator for Independence Caucus, “How Ordinary Individuals Can Make a Difference”;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Stango, founder, Dora’s Hope, “Reforming Medicaid to Expand Home Care Choices”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Paul Maresca,  &amp;quot;Bringing the Power Back to the People.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attorney Michael Agranoff , &amp;quot; CT's Wasteful Spending - How Agencies Like DCF Squander Your Money&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website: &lt;a href="http://nheld.com/CTLibertyForum.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://nheld.com/CTLi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Online registration: &lt;a href="http://ctlibertyforum2009.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://ctlibertyforum...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Email: ctlibertyforum@nheld.com&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We hope you will join us for the informative event. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The cost is $25 admission advance purchase ($30 at the door). There is complimentary hotel parking.&lt;br /&gt;The Keynote brunch is $25 extra and must be bought in advance - no brunch tickets will be sold at the door.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pre-purchase your CT Liberty Forum admission now for only $25, because at the door it will be $30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you wish to attend the Brunch with Congresswoman Michele Bachmann (from 10:00am -11:00am) you must pre-purchase a ticket for that event by Oct 13 - either through the mail or online - Admission for the brunch is only $25. Tickets for the brunch can NOT be purchased at the door and it is separate from the CT Liberty Forum admission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Purchase online or by mail&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://nheld.com/CTLibertyForum.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://nheld.com/CTLi...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please remind your friends and associates not to miss our wonderful lineup of speakers who have come to discuss how we can protect our economic freedom in a Constitutional manner during these troubling times. While we’ve had a couple of changes to the speaker’s lineup, ( &lt;a href="http://nheld.com/CTLFBios2009.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://nheld.com/CTLF...&lt;/a&gt; ) we can’t wait to hear from those who are scheduled. (&lt;a href="http://nheld.com/CTLF09EventSchedule.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://nheld.com/CTLF...&lt;/a&gt;)  There is complimentary hotel parking.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s make this a terrific showing of support for all of those who are out in the forefront fighting for our liberty.&lt;br /&gt;Please help us to make this a success.  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For further information, please contact:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Attorney Deborah G. Stevenson&lt;br /&gt; Executive Director, National Home Education Legal Defense, LLC&lt;br /&gt; Founder, Connecticut Liberty Forum&lt;br /&gt; (860) 354-3590&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Judy Aron&lt;br /&gt; Research Director, National Home Education Legal Defense, LLC.&lt;br /&gt; (860) 523-7257&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>barbara g.</member_name><member_id>7156348</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1256080070000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-1358</urlname><id>841263</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>Connecticut Ron Paul for President 2012</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1255191409000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>CT Liberty Forum</name><id>11595537</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1255780800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-1358/events/11595537/</event_url></item>