<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Intersection of MA State Routes 9 and 16</address_2><address_1>Two North Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01770</zip><lat>42.242802</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-650-3659</phone><name>The Peace Abbey</name><city>Sherborn</city><id>87395</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.370201</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;1 PM VEGAN MEAL &lt;br /&gt;

Share delicious vegan cuisine. This has traditionally been a potluck, but we are exploring another option for this year -- check back for details. &lt;br /&gt;

Special treat: The Like No Udder vegan soft serve ice cream truck will be with us, serving up softies, milkshakes, and more! &lt;br /&gt;

3 PM SPEAKER PRESENTATION - GARY KOWALSKI &lt;br /&gt;

We are very pleased to present Gary Kowalski, author of bestselling books on animals, nature, history and spirituality. A graduate of Harvard College and the Harvard Divinity School, his work has been translated into German, French, Spanish, Japanese, Chinese and Czech. Gary's work centers on the connection of spirit and nature. &lt;br /&gt;

Among his celebrated titles: &lt;br /&gt;

The Souls of Animals &lt;br /&gt;

Goodbye, Friend: Healing Wisdom for Anyone Who Has Ever Lost a Pet &lt;br /&gt;

Earth Day: An Alphabet Book (for children) &lt;br /&gt;

The Bible According To Noah: Theology As If Animals Mattered &lt;br /&gt;

Blessings of the Animals: Celebrating Our Kinship With All Creation (Fall 2012) &lt;br /&gt;

We'll use the church next to the Peace Abbey for the speaker program. It seats 350, so we'll have plenty of seats!&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338812851000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Vegetarian/Vegan Enthusiast</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood</urlname><id>1312890</id><group_lat>41.8199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Rhode Island Vegetarian and Vegan Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1336582378000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>BVS' annual event at the PEACE ABBEY</name><id>64091232</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338742800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Vegan-Vegetarian-Organic-RawFood/events/64091232/</event_url></item>