<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>24 Schoosett St (Route 139)</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02359</zip><lat>42.069830</lat><repinned>True</repinned><phone>(781) 826-4811</phone><name>The Omelette Factory</name><city>Pembroke</city><id>443557</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.800100</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>2.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>Ok, you'll have to excuse Mike again - He long ago gave up on being a frustrated novelist and decided to become a frustrated ad copywriter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The slogan above is not found in any advertising for The Omelette Factory in Pembroke, but Mike is sure that this is simply because they haven't thought of it yet. Fortunately, even in the absence of Mike's assistance, the Omelette Factory has prospered to the point of being one of the few South Shore restaurants specializing in breakfast and lunch (more recently they have also begin serving dinner) that, in terms of seating capacity, can comfortably accomodate a group like SSDOMG.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please join us there on Saturday, December 15, at 10:30 AM for what promises to be a morning filled with with fun, great conversation and cholesterol! We are told that the interior of the restaurant has been redone, giving it a newer look, while the food remains tasty and the prices competitive. In addition to omelettes, all the usual breakfast favorites, such as pancakes, French toast and Eggs Benedict can be found here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SPECIAL NOTE: One thing that we need to emphasize at the management's request is TIMELINESS! They will be accomodating us during one of their peak times - once the group is seated, if we have too many empty chairs they may not be able to hold them for long. This is a popular and busy restaurant!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions: The Omelette Factory is at 24 Schoosett St (Route 139) in Pembroke &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=Omelette+Factory&amp;amp;near=Pembroke,+MA&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;cid=42104124,-70801490,10758360735968662419&amp;amp;li=lmd&amp;amp;z=14&amp;amp;om=1" target="_blank"&gt;(Map)&lt;/a&gt;. This is just before Route 139 intersects with Route 53 if you're heading West on Route 139.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 3: Take Exit 12 (Route 139) and head West toward Hanover and Route 53. Exiting Route 3, you will find yourself in a commercial district that includes many retail businesses - many of you are probably familiar with this area from visiting The Christmas Tree Shop. Once you're past the cluster of shops, the road takes on a more rural appearance, with undeveloped land alternating with a few businesses and residences. The intersection with Route 53 is about 1 to 1.5 miles from the off-ramp. As you near Route 53, you should see a sign on your right indicating that the intersection is ahead. Once you see this, watch on your right for a sign reading &amp;quot;McGee Pre-Owned Superstore&amp;quot;. The Omelette Factory is THE NEXT DRIVE ON YOUR RIGHT and shares its parking lot with DJ's Goldmine Fine Jewelry.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you find yourself passing Itza Party on your right, you have just passed The Omelette Factory and will need to turn around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Price Range: Between $5.00 - $10.00 for most breakfast entrees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HANDICAPPED ACCESS: Yes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ORGANIZER: Mike&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When and Where:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, December 15 at 10:30 AM&lt;br /&gt;The Omelette Factory&lt;br /&gt;24 Schoosett St (Route 139)&lt;br /&gt;Pembroke, MA 02359&lt;br /&gt;(781) 826-4811&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Angela</member_name><member_id>341074</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1198367491000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>6</count></rating><group><who>South Shore Diners</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>ssdomg</urlname><id>313308</id><group_lat>42.2099990845</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0</group_lon><name>The South Shore Dining Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>11</yes_rsvp_count><created>1196528648000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Breakfast Made On Site to Your Specs!</name><id>6836658</id><headcount>9</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1197732600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ssdomg/events/6836658/</event_url></item>