<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>44.0197903, -71.5067434</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03585</zip><lat>44.218056</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Greeley ponds Trailhead parking</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>9927622</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.912766</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Is anyone interested in hiking Osceolas in the White Mountains?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty:&lt;/strong&gt; Moderate &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Length:&lt;/strong&gt; 7.5 miles &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; Half day &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;strong&gt;Overview:&lt;/strong&gt; A short but steep climb to get to the tallest peak in the Sandwich Range and it's sister peak East Osceola. Although both summits are wooded there are ledges on the way up East and a viewpoint towards the east from Mt. Osceola. To get there, we will take the Greely Pond Trail from the Kancamangus Highway to the Mt. Osceola trail, which turns off to the west just before the ponds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; To hike both mountains via Greeley Pond Parking area, &lt;br /&gt;

 Begin on the Greeley Pond Trail via the Kancamagus Highway (Route 112) in Lincoln, New Hampshire and hike for 1.3 miles until you come to a fork in the trail with Mount Osceola Trail, where you will bear right to switch trails. Follow this trail up for 1.5 miles to the summit of East Osceola Mountain. From there, continue over the summit on the Mount Osceola Trail for 1.0 miles where you will find yourself on the summit of Mount Osceola. To get back to the parking lot, retrace your steps the same way you came up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driving Directions:&lt;/strong&gt; Take I-93 N to Exit 32. Take a left off the light at the exit ramp and stay on the Kancamgas Highway (Route 112) for 9.7 miles East. Drive through the tourist town of Lincoln and past the Loon Ski Resort; continue past the trailhead to the East Pond Trail and until you begin up a switchback on the Kancamagus Highway right after Big Rock Campground. The Greenley Ponds Trailhead will be on your right. There is a $3 fee to park here for the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather Forecast:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Osceola"&gt;http://www.mountain-forecast.com/peaks/Mount-Osceola&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1351436750000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>New England Hikers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-England-Hiking-Meetup</urlname><id>462914</id><group_lat>43.6399993896</group_lat><group_lon>-72.25</group_lon><name>The New England Hiking Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1350794955000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Hike Mt. Osceola (4320 ft) and Mt. Osceola East (4156 ft)</name><id>87883732</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1351344600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-England-Hiking-Meetup/events/87883732/</event_url></item>