<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><fee><label>Parking fee</label><accepts>paypal</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per car (CT resident)</description><amount>7.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>This is a roughly 3 mile one-way hike in Peoples State Forest. Some portions will be somewhat steep downhill at the beginning. I've structured this hike to be friendly for near beginner hikers and still see what sights there are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet by 4 PM at the state forest main parking area on the west side of East River Rd. This paved parking area is roughly across the street from the main entrance (see the map, the gray block near the entrance and to left, west). Please park and meet near the attendant's booth at the entrance of the parking area. We'll start the hike by taking my van (seats 6 besides myself) on Greenwoods Rd. to the far northern starting point of the hike (the &amp;quot;Big Spring&amp;quot; point marked on the map) by 4:15 PM. Kevin will park there with everyone to start the hike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll start the hike on the blue w/yellow dot Jesse Gerard Trail and head generally south. There will be some modest overlooks near the beginning of the hike and some portions of the hike will be somewhat steep downhill through the forest. We'll then eventually intersect with the Robert Ross Trail and continue to head south with a much more modest downhill grade. We'll then reach the Nature Center where we'll take a short section of trail out to the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hike should last about 1.5 hrs. and be over by about 5:45 PM. Kevin will need a lift to his van.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The leader on this one is Kevin S (&lt;a href="http://hiking.meetup.com/151/members/2499916/"&gt;http://hiking.meetup....&lt;/a&gt;) so please direct questions on this event to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Do not pay fee by PayPal, pay your share at the state forest. Parking fee is $10 for non-CT residents.***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*** Water is a must on the hike -1 Qt. Bug spray strongly advised. ***&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pets on a leash are permitted on hiking trails. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A map can be found at:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dep.state.ct.us/STATEPARKS/maps/peoples.pdf"&gt;http://www.dep.state....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directions from Hartford (about 45 min.):&lt;br /&gt;* Take Route 44 west&lt;br /&gt;* Take right onto Route 181, RIVER RD., about 1 mile&lt;br /&gt;* Go across the steel bridge&lt;br /&gt;* Take an immediate left onto East River Road&lt;br /&gt;* The parking area is approximately 1 mile up on the left.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information, see &lt;a href="http://www.dep.state.ct.us/STATEPARKS/forests/amerlegion.htm"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.dep.state.ct.us/STATEPARKS/forests/amerlegion.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dep.state....&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1159526497000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Hiking Enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Hartford-Area-Hiking</urlname><id>209210</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>The Hartford Area Hiking™ Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1155659374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Kevin S's Hike at Peoples SF in Barkhamsted CT</name><id>5078735</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1156622400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Hartford-Area-Hiking/events/5078735/</event_url></item>