<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>430 Gorham Road</address_1><state>ME</state><zip>04106</zip><lat>43.636547</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borders</name><city>South Portland</city><id>863730</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.332540</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Likeness, Tana French&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.borders.com/ProductImages/products/00/58/49/a/58494278_a.jpg" border="0" alt='' /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt; The haunting follow up to the Edgar Award-winning debut In the Woods Tana French astonished critics and readers alike with her mesmerizing debut novel, In the Woods. Now both French and Detective Cassie Maddox return to unravel a case even more sinister and enigmatic than the first. Six months after the events of In the Woods, an urgent telephone call beckons Cassie to a grisly crime scene. The victim looks exactly like Cassie and carries ID identifying herself as Alexandra Madison, an alias Cassie once used. Suddenly, Cassie must discover not only who killed this girl, but, more importantly, who is this girl? A disturbing tale of shifting identities, The Likeness firmly establishes Tana French as an important voice in suspense fiction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please bring your a book or 2 or 3 to swap! Thanks!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anna Karenina by Leo Tolstoy&lt;/b&gt; was our original choice for this month. Due to the length of the book, not everyone was going to have time to read it. Will we still discuss this book at the end of the meetup for those of you who read it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt; Considered by some to be the greatest novel ever written, Anna Karenina is Tolstoy's classic tale of love and adultery set against the backdrop of high society in Moscow and Saint Petersburg. A rich and complex masterpiece, the novel charts the disastrous course of a love affair between Anna, a beautiful married woman, and Count Vronsky, a wealthy army officer. Tolstoy seamlessly weaves together the lives of dozens of characters, and in doing so captures a breathtaking tapestry of late-nineteenth-century Russian society. As Matthew Arnold wrote in his celebrated essay on Tolstoy, &amp;quot;We are not to take Anna Karenina as a work of art; we are to take it as a piece of life.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please bring your a book or 2 or 3 to swap! Thanks!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be at the table closest to the cafe door. I'll leave the book on the table.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rebecca</member_name><member_id>8243578</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1272892419000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Out &amp; Abouters</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>Portland-Out-and-About-Group</urlname><id>1365436</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Out and About Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1256827371000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>April Book Club &amp; Book Swap - The Likeness</name><id>11741316</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1272495600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Portland-Out-and-About-Group/events/11741316/</event_url></item>