<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Your friendly neighborhood organizer here with an update on the time. 7:00 was a bad guess for the movie time, it's actually showing at 8:20. I'll be at the theater in my red cap at 7:50. If the movie is showing upstairs I'll be waiting in the upstairs lobby by the cafe tables next to the window, and if it's showing downstairs I'll be waiting just beyond where tickets are taken, across from the popcorn/candy/soda place.

And now back to our previous description...

Well, this is directed by Uwe Boll, whose video game adapations have ranged from the fun and watchable in [i]Bloodrayne[/i], to the so bad it made even Christian Slater seem uncool in [i]Alone in the Dark[/i]. But, this latest effort is his biggest budget and widest release to date and stars Jason Statham, Ray Liotta, Ron Perlman, and Burt Reynolds (I don't care what anyone says, that dude can act.) and I am a huge sucker for sword and sorcery, so... meetup!

7:00 is my guess, (It's actually at 8:20, see above.) I will update this event when AMC posts the exact time. I'll be in the theater lobby 30 minutes before showtime, and we'll head into the theater 10 minutes before showtime. If it's downstairs, I'll be right behind the corded rope after ticket stubs have been ripped in front of the popcorn counter. If it's upstairs, I'll try to grab one of the tables in front of the coffee house near the large windows.

Synopsis: A simple family man is forced to take up arms after an evil sorcerer unleashes an army of bloodthirsty beasts that destroy his small village and capture his beautiful wife. As the marauding forces overrun the land in an effort to overthrow the king and his loyal magus, the once peace-loving peasant and his two companions venture into perilous, uncharted terrain on a daring rescue mission. In this breathtaking fantasy adventure, director Uwe Boll conjures up a medieval world filled with royal treachery, dark magic and spectacular battles.

Official website: &lt;a href="http://inthenameoftheking.com/" class="linkified"&gt;http://inthenameoftheking.com/&lt;/a&gt;

Trailer:
&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/2cGhxixal5A&amp;rel=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a red baseball cap with the meetup logo.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1206381660000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>6</yes_rsvp_count><created>1198719459000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>In the Name of the King: A Dungeon Siege Tale</name><id>6973550</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1200186900000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/6973550/</event_url></item>