<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>171 Milk Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.358387</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 451- 7415</phone><name>Coogans</name><city>Boston</city><id>533322</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.053375</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Happy hourers will hang once again at Coogan's in the Faneuil Hall area to imbibe social lubricants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get there when you can. I'll arrive at 5:30 and hang until about 9.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll buy the first new member who finds me, a drink.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free Baileys, Kahlua, &amp;amp; Malibu treats for everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trivia contest begins at 7. Join the winning teams!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy complimentary appetizers paid from our winnings. Get there before they're gone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.irishconnection.com/index.php?id=45" target="_blank"&gt;Coogan's Web Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you come hungry here's &lt;a href="http://www.irishconnection.com/pdf/coogansmenu.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Coogan's Menu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Great burgers. steak tips, pizza and a $10 lobster special.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;PLEASE MAINTAIN YOUR OWN TAB OR PAY AS YOU ORDER - THANK YOU&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trivia rules:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Up to six players on each team to be eligible for the first place prize. Be aware if a team with less than  six players has one of the top three scores, that team would win first or second place. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Use the Stump! sheet, to keep your team score, which the trivia jockey (TJ) provides . Write the categories as the TJ reads them, and keep track of the points you've wagered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) When the TJ asks a question, you have one song to write your team name, your answer, and your wager on an answer ticket and hand it in. You can wager 1, 3, 5, or 7 points in the first two quarters, and 2, 4, 6, or 8 points in the last two quarters. You can only use each value ONCE per quarter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) There are three bonus rounds where you can earn lots of extra points! Your TJ will explain how they work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5) No shouting out any answers, and absolutely no using cellphones/other devices to look up answers! Teams that break this rule may be disqualified.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will be seated at the end of the bar furthest from the entrance and should be the only one wearing a Happy New Year tiara.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tonya</member_name><member_id>3389565</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>13</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1219527109000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>Drinking Buddies</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nightlife-421</urlname><id>505098</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Boston Happy Hour</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>15</yes_rsvp_count><created>1218290656000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>It's Thirsty Thursday, So It's Time For Coogan's Again</name><id>8508963</id><headcount>17</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1219354200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nightlife-421/events/8508963/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/6/d/d/global_3479853.jpeg</photo_url></item>