<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1 Under Price Way</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01760</zip><lat>42.295244</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(508) 424-0088</phone><name>Jordans Furntiture IMAX</name><city>Natick</city><id>799763</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.398907</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;New Info:&amp;nbsp; The 6:15 p.m. show on Sunday 7/17 is now sold out so this meetup won't have any new "Yes" entries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows - Part 2: An IMAX 3D Experience
 &lt;br /&gt;Sunday, July 17 at 6:15 p.m.
 &lt;br /&gt;IMAX Theatre at Jordan's Furniture
 &lt;br /&gt;1 Underprice Way (off Rt. 9), Natick, MA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, so few people answered my poll regarding where to see the final Harry Potter film that I had no clear direction on how to organize the meetup. So, figuring that this would be the last/only time we could see a Harry Potter film in IMAX 3D, I'm organizing this for that venue.&amp;nbsp;Hopefully the really devoted Harry Potter fans will enjoy that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IMAX showings on Friday and Saturday, July 15 and 16 have already sold out.&amp;nbsp; So the meetup is scheduled for Sunday evening, July 17, at 6:15 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to participate, YOU WILL NEED TO BUY YOUR TICKETS ONLINE IN ADVANCE, and then respond as a "Yes" to the meetup so we can gather as a group.&amp;nbsp; The web site is here:&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.jordans.com/Imax.aspx"&gt;http://www.jordans.com/Imax.aspx&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;
 &lt;br /&gt;Tickets include the glasses and cost $14.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;=&amp;gt; I am sure this screening of the IMAX will sell out very soon, so if you would like to participate you will need to do this right away!!! Please do not respond "Yes" to the meetup and then expect to get your tickets when you arrive at the IMAX, as they will be sold out. It's best to print your ticket at home rather than pick it up at the concession, as it will be really crowded there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you buy tickets and respond "Yes," I'll coordinate with you separately as to when and where to meet in the building. We will need to get there really early so we don't end up sitting in the front row -- probably before 5:30.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Movie Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows - Part 2: An IMAX 3D Experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the epic finale, the battle between the good and evil forces of the wizarding world escalates into an all-out war. The stakes have never been higher and no one is safe. But it is Harry Potter who may be called upon to make the ultimate sacrifice as he draws closer to the climactic showdown with Lord Voldemort. It all ends here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cast: Daniel Radcliffe, Rupert Grint, Emma Watson, Ralph Fiennes, Alan Rickman, Helena Bonham Carter
 &lt;br /&gt;Genres: Action/Adventure, Science Fiction/Fantasy, Adaptation and&amp;nbsp; Sequel
 &lt;br /&gt;MPAA Rating: PG-13 for some sequences of intense action violence and frightening images.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will coordinate separately with those who purchase tickets in advance.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Sandi</member_name><member_id>6039490</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1311007621000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>FraminghamMovieMeetup</urlname><id>1133762</id><group_lat>42.2700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4199981689</group_lon><name>The Framingham Movie Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1310225673000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Framingham Movie Meetup: Harry Potter 7, July 17, 6:15 p.m.</name><id>25128861</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1310940900000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/FraminghamMovieMeetup/events/25128861/</event_url></item>