<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1> 175 Tremont Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02111</zip><lat>42.353249</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(617) 423-5801</phone><name>AMC Loews Boston Common 19</name><city>Boston</city><id>450116</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.064293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>[b]Update[/b]

The movie is at 6:30. I will be at the movie theater at 6:00. I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie's upstairs, I'll be at the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand. We'll head in to the theater 10 minutes before showtime.

After the movie, we gather just outside the theater doors (the theater wear the movie is showing that is, not outside) and talk about where we're going for food and drinks. Sometimes I lose people at that point - and I'm not sure if it's because I just lost someone or they didn't want to come to dinner. So, if you are coming to dinner, please find me after the show. I will be wearing that red hat. 'Cause that's my job - to wear the hat!

[b]Synopsis[/b]

In "The Forbidden Kingdom," American teenager Jason (Michael Angarano), who is obsessed with Hong Kong cinema and kungfu classics, finds an antique Chinese staff in a pawn shop: the legendary stick weapon of the Chinese sage and warrior, the Monkey King (Jet Li). With the lost relic in hand, Jason unexpectedly finds himself transported back to ancient China.

There, he meets the drunken kungfu master, Lu Yan (Jackie Chan); an enigmatic and skillful Silent Monk (Jet Li); and a vengeance-bent kungfu beauty, Golden Sparrow (Crystal Liu Yi Fei), who lead him on his quest to return the staff to its rightful owner, the Monkey King - imprisoned in stone by the evil Jade Warlord (Collin Chou) for five hundred years. Along the way, while attempting to outmaneuver scores of Jade Warriors, Cult Killers and the deadly White Hair Demoness, Ni Chang (Li Bing Bing), Jason learns about honor, loyalty and friendship, and the true meaning of kungfu, and thus frees himself.

[b]Trailer[/b]

&lt;xobject width="425" height="355"&gt;&lt;xembed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/hE7ny2bfXF0&amp;hl=en" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="425" height="355" style="margin : 5px ; max-width : 700px ; max-height : 700px"&gt;&lt;/xembed&gt;&lt;/xobject&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing my red hat with the meetup logo. If the movie's upstairs, I'll be at the tables near the window. If downstairs, I'll be behind the rope where tickets are torn across from the popcorn stand.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Frederick Hill</member_name><member_id>4478749</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>8</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1212077775000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Kung fu movie fans, we have Jet Li and Jackie Chan, together! While the movie has the potential to be not-so-good, and I wish Chan was directing, I have to see it. From the trailer it looks like they spent some money, though.</why><group><who>Movie Fans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>movies-280</urlname><id>225256</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Boston Movie Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1207335027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Forbidden Kingdom</name><id>7673937</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1209247200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/movies-280/events/7673937/</event_url></item>