<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Suite Number: 4000, North Entrance</address_2><address_1>1000 Winter Street, Bay Colony Corporate Center</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02451</zip><lat>42.394714</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Emerging Enterprise Center at Foley Hoag</name><city>Waltham</city><id>597058</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.251785</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>20.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Clean Technology for Healthy Businesses and Growing Profits&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.entretechforum.org"&gt;www.entretechforum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://etfmar12.eventbrite.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/registerpng.png" width="119" height="25" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an economy where companies are straining to grow revenues and reduce costs, leaders are learning they can leverage Clean Technology and Sustainable Technology innovation as their &amp;ldquo;new frontier&amp;rdquo;, creating competitive advantage resulting in an expanding, thriving business. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Please join our March, 20th EntreTech Forum to hear from &amp;ldquo;green-technology entrepreneurs&amp;rdquo; on how they raised their capital and scaled their businesses. Also featured are leading experts in how leveraging &amp;ldquo;sustainable technology&amp;rdquo; provides both competitive and profit advantage. Our panel will review this new technology and the growing markets for it along with the opportunities it creates for entrepreneurs. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a startup in the field or looking for ideas to improve your revenues and profits, please join us for this informative and interactive discussion. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

Forbes Magazine reported that MIT Sloan Management Review and Boston Consulting Group surveyed 2,874 executives in 113 countries on Sustainable Technology. The survey found that two-thirds of companies see sustainability as a &amp;ldquo;competitive necessity&amp;rdquo;. Also, 31 percent of responding companies reported that sustainability is boosting their profits. In an economy where companies are straining to grow profits and reduce costs, clean and sustainable technology may hold the new frontier for your business. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Panel:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2012Mtg/Slaughter.jpg" width="100" height="151" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;E. Sarah Slaughter, President and Executive Director, Built Environment Coalition&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sarah Slaughter is President and founder of the Built Environment Coalition. She was most recently the Associate Director for Buildings and Infrastructure in the MIT Energy Initiative, coordinating research across MIT focused on improving the built environment, and led the development of a program to improve the built environment and economic development across New England that involved over 120 companies, nonprofit organizations, and local and state government agencies. Before her work with MITEI, she was co-founder and head of the Sustainability Initiative in the MIT Sloan School of Management, focusing on strategies for sustainable organizations and communities. Previously, Dr. Slaughter was founder and CEO of MOCA Systems, Inc., a construction program management company based on the construction simulation software system from her MIT research. At MIT, she was a professor in the Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering, focusing on innovations for the built environment. Earlier, she was a professor of Civil and Environmental Engineering at Lehigh University and conducted research in the NSF Center for Advanced Technology for Large Structural Systems (ATLSS).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her current research focuses on innovations for sustainable and disaster-resilient infrastructure and the built environment. Dr. Slaughter is currently a member of the National Academies National Research Council (NRC) Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment, the National Academies DOD Standing Committee on Materials, Manufacturing, and Infrastructure, the NRC Committee on Federal High Performance Green Buildings, and is a National Academy Associate. She also serves on the Massachusetts Sustainable Water Management Advisory Board, the Sustainability Committee in the International Facilities Management Association (IFMA), and several national advisory committees and editorial boards of professional publications. She currently serves on the Board of Directors for Retroficiency, Inc., ERG, Inc., and the Charles River Watershed Association. Dr. Slaughter has published over 50 articles and books, and is a recognized expert in the field of sustainable facility assets, and in innovations in the built environment. She received her S.B., S.M., and PhD from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. &lt;br /&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2012Mtg/Lucci.jpg" width="100" height="107" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Patrick Lucci, Managing Director, Lynnfield Green Technologies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patrick has been a marketing executive in the technology and biotech industries for more than twenty years. He has developed and implemented marketing programs for hardware, software and therapeutics primarily in the areas of biotechnology, PC graphics, audio, video and multimedia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His background is unique in that he is one of the few individuals in the industry who has been on the corporate side as a senior executive with public and private technology companies such as Number Nine Visual Technologies, Integrated Circuit Systems and Hercules Computer Technologies. On the agency side, he was Director of Broadcast Services at Gray Strayton International and was a partner at Lucci &amp;amp; Stringer. At these two consulting firms, specializing in technology and biotech companies his clients were notable industry leaders such as Xerox, Security Dynamics, Cadre Technologies, Computervision, Biogen and Analog Devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His experience also includes technology journalism; first as a science and technology reporter at WEEI NewsRadio in Boston and as a contributing editor at CNET, The Computer Network. He also hosted Techbeat, a call in program at The Talk Station, WRKO in Boston. Additionally, he guest lectures on marketing technology products and companies at Babson College. He also holds a U.S. Patent for a digital audio amplifier developed at Jam Technologies in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perspectives from these venues have provided him with the experience and leadership skills to create programs that have literally transformed companies such as Number Nine, Hercules and Jazz Multimedia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These skills have not gone unnoticed. His ability to conceive products and promote them through targeted, strategic marketing campaigns has won more than 15 industry awards including The Award for Technical Excellence from PC Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/Mar2012Mtg/DHooghe.jpg" width="100" height="100" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Alexander D&amp;rsquo;Hooghe, Associate Professor in Architectural Urbanism at MIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander conducts a research group called &amp;lsquo;Platform for a Permanent Modernity&amp;rsquo;, and a design office called &amp;lsquo;Office for Permanent Modernity&amp;rsquo;, located in Boston and Brussels. He develops architectures of the territory: durable formal orders handling complexity within a simplified frame. The formalization of infrastructures is key. The group won several large-scale buildings and competitions overseas, currently in various stages of permitting; and published internationally, most recently with &amp;lsquo;the Liberal Monument&amp;rsquo; (Princeton, Fall 2010),. D&amp;rsquo;Hooghe obtained his Ph.D. at the Berlage Institute in 2007 i.c.w. T.U.Delft, after achieving a Masters in Urban Design at the GSD in 2001.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="http://entretechforum.org/images/Bruce%20head%20shot%20with%20hardhat.jpg" width="100" height="99" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Bruce Dike Hiles, President, New England Solar Hot Water Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Bruce is president and founder of New England Solar Hot Water. Bruce's early career was davoted to the design and installation of large simulation and visualization systems involving holograpgic imagery. This work included several high profile instalations at the Smithsonian institutuion (hologlobe I), Chabot Observatory (Hologlobe II) andand at Den Den in Osaka, Japan. This background in large electro optic installations and a passive for renewable energy leb Bruce to study sun tracking systems and thermal coatings for solar thermal collectors. Bruce developed and subsequently sold patents in the are of polarizer aand MEM's based optics with sun tracking applications (US patents (7,242,524 6,262,841). In 2007 Bruce put aside research and devopment to pursue implementing solar thermal technology with the establishment of NESHW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Cost: &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/strong&gt;$25 public, $10 students &lt;br /&gt;

and active military;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="http://entretechforum.org/specregs.htm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promotional Registrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Larry Grumer</member_name><member_id>12792562</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1332288954000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Technology Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>EntreTechForum</urlname><id>1133540</id><group_lat>42.3400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0899963379</group_lon><name>The EntreTech Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314976310000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Clean Technology for Healthy Businesses and Growing Profits</name><id>qnlkbcyqfbbc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1332282600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/EntreTechForum/events/32004572/</event_url></item>