<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Let's get out on Friday night and have some fun listening to some great music!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of New England's preeminent Blues Masters, Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell has been entertaining audiences for decades. His astounding technique and encyclopedic repertoire enables him to entertain ALL NIGHT LONG!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ricky is a singer, songwriter, guitar slinger that plays and sings with passion and finesse, quickly drawing his audience into a Blues experience like none other.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you like your Blues with a traditional foundation and a touch of modern flair served up high energy style, The Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell Band will deliver the goods!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss this great Blues band!&lt;br /&gt;Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell has shared the stage with Blues luminaries John Lee Hooker, Eddie Clearwater, Mighty Sam McClain, Ronnie Earl, Jerry Portnoy, Duke Robillard, Kim Wilson, Tommy Shannon and Chris Layton (Double Trouble), Susan Tedeschi, Toni Lynn Washington, Roomful of Blues and many others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Performing with The Mike Crandall Band, Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell was a finalist at the 2008 International Blues Competition in Memphis, Tennessee! To view a video of their performance, click here:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.e-webvid.com/MikeCrandall_Broadband_JDW.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.e-webvid.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drummer Daniel Banks has covered a lot of ground in his still evolving career. At age eleven, he made an appearance on the David Letterman show and performed with Paul Shaffer and The CBS Orchestra. This was in 2005 and his career has been picking up momentum ever since.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The young drummer keeps a busy schedule performing regularly with some of New England's top bands. Daniel has shared the stage with Blues Music Award winners and nominees including Janiva Magness, Duke Robillard and David Maxwell, as well as New England icons James Montgomery, Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell, Toni Lynn Washington and a roster of other notables too extensive to list here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, Daniel has recently opened up new performing&lt;br /&gt;opportunities by expanding his endeavors to include lead vocals and bass guitar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're sure that whatever musical path Daniel decides to follow, he will meet with great success. He is truly New England's Phenom Drummer. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell&lt;br /&gt;featuring Daniel Banks&lt;br /&gt;Mari's Place&lt;br /&gt;35 Washington Street&lt;br /&gt;Quincy, MA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/marisplaceinquincy" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.myspace.co...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell serves up burning Blues and more!&lt;br /&gt;The Kingpin of the Blues!&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell and sample some of his music,&lt;br /&gt;please visit:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.barrelhouseblues.com/ricky_russell.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.barrelhous...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To learn more about Daniel Banks, and sample some of his music,&lt;br /&gt;please visit:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://barrelhouseblues.com/daniel_banks_2.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://barrelhouseblu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BarrelhouseBlues.com endorses and promotes Ricky &amp;quot;King&amp;quot; Russell and Daniel Banks.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>See my picture....will send cell to those who rsvp yes</how_to_find_us><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1239062699000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Friends</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>beantownandbeyond</urlname><id>553596</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Beantown and Beyond 25-40 Something Singles</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1238353594000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Ricky "King" Russell featuring Daniel Banks @ Mari's Place in Quincy </name><id>10063436</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1238805000000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/beantownandbeyond/events/10063436/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/1/a/f/global_4486527.jpeg</photo_url></item>