<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>523 Taugwonk Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06378</zip><lat>41.406924</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>860-535-1222</phone><name>Stonington Vineyards</name><city>Stonington</city><id>766716</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.901157</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Join me at &lt;a href="http://stoningtonvineyards.com/about_news.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Stonington Vineyards'&lt;/a&gt; Harvest Wine &amp;amp; Food Festival September 29th, from 11a-5p.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 2-5pm there will be a 14-piece, all-female Swing band...so bring your dancing shoes (and a partner!) The entire days' event is free, although local gourmet restaurants will be on hand to provide lunches for purchase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winery tours are at 12p, 2p, and 3p, and wine tasting is an all-day affair!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the event ends at 5pm, and the beaches aren't too far away, this event could continue on at the beach, local restaurants/shops, or even Mystic Aquarium. Also, the early event-ending time will keep your Saturday night free. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Carpooling is encouraged, drunk-driving is not. I can fit 3 people in my car. If you can drive, please note that in your RSVP to help facilitate carpools. Plan on leaving New Haven at 10a Saturday, so we can make it to the festival early; over 2400 people are expected to attend the festival! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some info about the winery: &lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.stoningtonvineyards.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stonington Vineyards&lt;/a&gt; was established by Nick and Happy Smith in 1987, when purchasing 58 acres in the Stonington Uplands on which winegrapes had been planted earlier in the decade. The winery was constructed in 1988/89 incorporating the latest in winemaking technology and the traditional methods of barrel fermentation. From the start, Mike McAndrew has been the Winemaker, garnering the reputation for producing quality, European-style table wines that have won numerous awards over the years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stonington is best known for its barrel fermented Chardonnays and its proprietory blends Seaport White and Triad Rose. We also produce, as varietals, Vidal Blanc and Cabernet Franc.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Come support a Connecticut Winery, drink and be merry! Of course, the idea isn't getting drunk, it's appreciating the wines, purchasing bottles, and enjoying a light festival atmosphere.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eric is your contact for this event. 86-0214-9361&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Devorah, AJ, &amp; Jason</member_name><member_id>3217243</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1191247292000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1185472624000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Harvest Wine &amp; Food Festival Sept 29, 11-5pm Stonington, CT</name><id>6080968</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1191074400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/6080968/</event_url></item>