<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;br /&gt;UPDATE:  we can still start to meet at about 5:45/6:00pm&lt;br /&gt;I will have my nutritous MackDonalds meal there while i unpack all my stuff&lt;br /&gt;but lets start the trip about 7 like all the other events..&lt;br /&gt;or if we feel everyone comming is there and no need to waite..&lt;br /&gt;We still have to move the cars to the boat ramp and that takes time anyway..someone has to stand guard with the yaks and equipment..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This river has a lot of interesting features,&lt;br /&gt;I hope to put in in one place and retrieve from the Weslean boat launch making it a one way trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will need some time to do the car switching thing..so we wont take off on the water right away. Someone will be there gaurding the yaks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GETTING THERE, from the north, &lt;br /&gt;Look at your map first.. I really try to add all the turns and stuff but once in a while i have left out something.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;get onto Rte 9 south, (to and in Cromwell/Middletown) go to exit 19 &lt;br /&gt;Turn (right) off the exit, =west toward Kmart and Stop and Shop &lt;br /&gt;At the first light you see (intersection of rte 372 and rte 3) take the left (south toward stop n shop) onto rte 3= shunpike rd &lt;br /&gt;There is a KFC, MackDonalds, and a Drunkin Doonuts while heading to the next traffic light. Use Drunkin Donuts (driveway) there is an empty lot which is coned off sometimes but since there is construction going on , park down in the far back of the Drunken Donuts lot. &lt;br /&gt;There is a water trail sign showing the most dangerous animals and what not to feed the animals...including the banjo boys... &lt;br /&gt;I will have  spare kayaks with me for anyone that wants to use them. BUT YOU MUST KNOW WHICH ONE...since most of em are ocean types and not very stable for beginners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;oNE KAYAK i found EMPTY after the last person became dinner for some wild animal.. &lt;br /&gt;No sinGing &amp;quot; Har... Paddling in a dead mans kayak, looking over my back, in case the gohst wants it back..&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The trip usually takes 2 hours or so but if we do some exploring ..then its over when its over provided you have not been eaten by wild creatures....&lt;br /&gt; iF YOU SURVIVED..WE CAN EAT AT THE LITTLE CANOPY BY THE WESLEAN BOAT RAMP after loading up and stuff like that..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rain Back up Plan: Go to Betsy's concert suggestion listed in the Un-Married but not Despirate Meetup group listing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Kevin S</member_name><member_id>2499916</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1183067712000</updated><rating><average>4.59999990463</average><count>5</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>10</yes_rsvp_count><created>1182449634000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Sunset Kayak Trip on the Mettabassett River Cromwell/Middletown CT</name><id>5918375</id><headcount>11</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1182894300000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/5918375/</event_url></item>