<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Ste: 102</address_2><address_1>20 Locust Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01923</zip><lat>42.569004</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-836-6501</phone><name>Ideal Business Center</name><city>Danvers</city><id>597231</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.938170</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for a better way? Are you sick and tired of your job,would you rather have more Time Freedom to spend more time with family, have fun, more vacation time and time for the things you love to do.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;Imagine waking up (when ever you want) going to the mail box and there is a check for you 300-3600 every MONDAY. Well this is Anthony J. Pasquale and I am telling you right now, this is a LIFE CHANGER. Join us July 26th 7: 
&lt;span&gt;...&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;00pm Tuesday Night.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Look you have been working very hard, the question is: Are you any better then when you were 1year, 3year, 5years ago, do you have a plan to retire, do you hate you J-O-B (Just Over Broke). How would you like to Create Wealth and live the Life you have always wanted, surrounded by great people who want to see you Succeed!
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; The secret to success is finding a proven business system to PLUG into. A System that is a proven business plan with clear vision, strength and support, enabling Independences to earn residual, ongoing 24/7 income part time, which can lead toward financial security. This powerful system offers unparalleled benefits and support with no territorial restrictions, automated internet marketing &amp;mdash; allowing the opportunity for Distributors to build their business as fast or as slow as they desire.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; To get started building an UnFranchise business online and earning residual, ongoing 24/7 income, Independent Distributors follow a detailed systemized plan and are provided a custom Web Portal and management tools to run their business. Market America provides the products and services, creates the marketing materials, and handles the shipping and distribution. Most of the administrative and operational duties of an UnFranchise Business are handled by Market America, allowing Distributors to focus on serving their customers&amp;rsquo; needs, and creating a lucrative business and financial security for themselves.
 &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt; Anthony J. Pasquale
 &lt;br /&gt; 978-836-6501&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;span&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;
    &lt;a&gt;See More&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Ready to Create Wealth!!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anthony Pasquale</member_name><member_id>6925152</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1314749754000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>New to Network Marketings</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1342126</id><group_lat>42.5699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.9400024414</group_lon><name>Network Marketing Support Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1311704862000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>New Way of Networking with Wealth!</name><id>27111931</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1314745200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Network-Marketing-Support-Meetup-Group/events/27111931/</event_url></item>