<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Newington</address_2><address_1>719 N Mountain Rd</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06111</zip><lat>41.721981</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Hartford Saengerbund</name><city>Newington</city><id>434458</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.716141</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Please note: This is for the 21 and over crowd!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Viele von euch haben oft gefragt "Wo konnen wir zusammen ein Bier trinken"?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Endlich besuchen wir wieder The Hartford Saengerbund Society, a private German-American club. &lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;BITTE RSVP&lt;/span&gt; so we will know how many seats to save.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is their opening Friday for the season, so there should be many people there. Ich hoffe dass ein ganze Menge von euch kommen werden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to carpool or get lost, Dianne's cellphone is 860.233.3079&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please, when you get there identify yourself as part of "Dianne's Kaffeeklatsch" and&amp;nbsp;a club member&amp;nbsp;will come to sign you in.&amp;nbsp; (This is a formality required by the State of Ct.)&amp;nbsp; They are having a dinner on this evening which you can purchase or just buy &amp;agrave; la carte or just ein Glas Bier, bitte. The choir will be practicing downstairs, and we might get to hear a German song or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don't know where it is (and many people don't) you can call Dianne.&amp;nbsp; She is willing to carpool from West Hartford.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use GPS of course, but here are simple directions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From West Hartford, get on New Britain Ave heading toward Hartford.&amp;nbsp; Pass under the only&amp;nbsp;railroad bridge. Turn right at the first traffic light.&amp;nbsp; This is South St which changes its name to Main St in Newington. Drive until the next big intersection with traffic light.&amp;nbsp; Turn LEFT.&amp;nbsp; This is "Hartford Ave" and Route 176 although it doesn't look like a State highway.&amp;nbsp;Turn left at the next traffic light.&amp;nbsp; This is North Mountain Rd which curves around like a "U".You will see DataMail and some other businesses and&amp;nbsp;international clubs.&amp;nbsp;About half-way around you will see the sign for the Saengerbund.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See, it's really not so difficult!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>In the dining room on the right</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dianne</member_name><member_id>3815102</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1315661011000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Deutsch speakers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>german-425</urlname><id>438488</id><group_lat>41.7599983215</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6900024414</group_lon><name>The West Hartford German Kaffeeklatsch</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>9</yes_rsvp_count><created>1314154374000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Stammtisch</name><id>30666621</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1315605600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/german-425/events/30666621/</event_url></item>