<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>45 Mount Auburn Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.380001</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-401-8047</phone><name>The Democracy Center</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>221452</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.129997</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Conspiracy Cafe at 45 Mt. Auburn St. in Harvard Sq. is now open &lt;b&gt;EVERY&lt;/b&gt; Sunday from noon to 8:00 pm. It offers a unique setting for 9/11 Truth activists and those curious to learn more about current events through books, DVDs, film screenings and informal discussions, in a casual cafe environment. The Conspiracy Cafe offers a wide selection of books, cds, &amp;amp; other media.  So whether your desires are social, intellectual or oriented toward activism, the Conspiracy Cafe has something for everyone. Hope to see you at the next Conspiracy Cafe!  So what are you waiting for?  Bring a friend, bring yourself, bring an open mind!  Come check out what Conspiracy Cafe is all about!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FILM LINEUP FOR THIS WEEK'S EDITION:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:00 Noon - 1:40  Pretext For The North American Union&lt;br /&gt;This presentation is an important, detailed and timely look at forming of the North America Union (NAU). This is information is most helpful to those who knows little about the NAU or the CFR. This complete presentation is broken into three segments&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.livevideo.com/video/911Revolution/6613771DC9224FD9B1C3960DA1573A5B/pretext-for-a-north-american-union.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kill the Messenger 1:40 - 2:35&lt;br /&gt;A 2005 French documentary about Sibel Edmonds. The documentary focuses on both Ms. Edmonds's personal struggle to expose the criminality that she uncovered while at the FBI, and also the 'secret' itself - the network of nuclear black-market, narcotics and illegal arms trafficking activities. Interviewees include David Rose, Philip Giraldi, Daniel Ellsberg, Coleen Rowley and Russell Tice. Edmonds was fired from her position as a language specialist at the FBI's Washington Field Office in March, 2002, after she accused a colleague of covering up illicit activity involving foreign nationals, alleging serious acts of security breaches, cover-ups, and intentional blocking of intelligence which, she contended, presented a danger to the United States' security. Since that time, court proceedings on her whistleblower claims have been blocked by the assertion of State Secrets Privilege.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=10Jn4vTGb_8" target="_blank"&gt;trailer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2:35 - 3:35   9/11: Dust &amp;amp; Deceit&lt;br /&gt;This disturbing film by Penny Little ?911: Dust and Deceit at the WTC?  exposes the environmental disaster of 9/11 through interviews with scientists, waste management specialists, government workers, volunteers, the heros and victims of the dust which permeated the air after 911.&lt;br /&gt;No online preview of the film is available.  Visit the website for the film here to learn more info about it.  &lt;a href="http://www.911dust.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Dust &amp;amp; Deceit website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3:35 - 4:20   Secrets of the CIA&lt;br /&gt;Five former CIA agents describe how their initial pride and enthusiasm at serving their nation turned to anguish and remorse, as they realized that they were actually subverting democracy and killing innocent civilians all in the name &amp;quot;national security&amp;quot; and promoting foreign policy agendas. &lt;a href="http://www.wanttoknow.info/051130ciasecrets" target="_blank"&gt;For more info click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4:20 - 5:40 Taxi to the Dark Side&lt;br /&gt;A gripping investigation into the reckless abuse of power by the Bush Administration.  By probing the homicide of an innocent taxi driver at the Bagram Air Force Base in Afghanistan, the film exposes a worldwide policy of detention and interrogation that condones torture and the abrogation of human rights. This disturbing and often brutal film is the most incisive examination to date of the Bush Administrations willingness, in its prosecution of the 'war on terror' to undermine the essence of the rule of law.  This film asks and answers a key question: what happens when a few men expand the wartime powers of the executive to undermine the very principles on which the United States was founded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.taxitothedarkside.com/" target="_blank"&gt;click here for official website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5:40 - 8:00  Police State 3: Total Enslavement&lt;br /&gt;The United States government, at all levels has fallen under the control of the desperately wicked New World Order clan The events of Sept 11th mark the initiation of the final sick push of the illuminati to consolidate their one world order and transform earth into a prison planet. In over two and a half hours, Alex Jones chronicles in stunning detail the true character of the globalists. Learn the master plan of the blood-thirsty elite to financially, physically and spiritually imprison not only America but the world. Total Enslavement is the third installment in the critically-acclaimed Police State series and is a must-see for all who love freedom. This film documents the nightmare rise of the Homeland Security dictatorship, Patriot Acts 1 and 2, the Total Information Awareness Network, government-run white slavery rings, the new prison surveillance economy and much more. The very future of humanity depends on exposing government-sponsored terrorism and how the globalists pose as our saviors whem in fact, they are the terrorists.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be manning the front table &amp; entrance room &amp; putting the dvds on!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>user 4883658</member_name><member_id>4883658</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1204650189000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><why>We'll be hitting the streets &amp; having a street action as well! People should not be going through Harvard Square without knowing the truth about 9/11! So if you want to come &amp; participate in street actions &amp; see hard hitting films THIS is your spot!</why><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1204055263000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Conspiracy Cafe!</name><id>7412820</id><headcount>6</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1204477200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/7412820/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/f/7/global_3289271.jpeg</photo_url></item>