<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>250 North Great Rd.</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01773</zip><lat>42.453022</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>(978) 369-6993</phone><name>Minute Man National Park</name><city>Lincoln</city><id>1001515</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.305901</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>I went to Minuteman National Park on July 4 and it was great but I didn't get to see everything. I highly recommend seeing The Road to Revolution, the free 25-minute film playing every half hour in the visitor's center. I just saw it, but I want to check out these things:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) &lt;b&gt;Market Fair and Militia Muster&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Date:  July 24, 2010&lt;br /&gt;Time:  9:30 AM to 5:30 PM&lt;br /&gt;Location:  Hartwell Tavern - Rt. 2A, Lincoln&lt;br /&gt;FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Details:&lt;br /&gt;In colonial New England, militia training days often doubled as social events. Visit Hartwell Tavern and experience an important aspect of life in a colonial town. Volunteer re-enactors will stage military drill and musket firing demonstrations, an 18th century market fair, period competitions and more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) I would also like to visit this historic home there:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Home of Captain William Smith: Open House&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open Thursday - Monday&lt;br /&gt;June 26 - September 6, 2010&lt;br /&gt;12:30 - 4:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Open Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday&lt;br /&gt;October 2 - 31, 2010&lt;br /&gt;12:30 - 4:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the home of Captain William Smith, commander of the Lincoln minute company. The house, dating from the late 1600's, has been restored by the National Park Service. Not only was this the home of a minute man, but also a &amp;quot;witness house,&amp;quot; meaning that it lay on the road the British soldiers used marching to Concord, and retreating back to Boston under fire. A wounded British soldier left behind was cared for by Catherine Smith, William's wife. Enjoy the unique architectrual features of the house. The closest parking is the Hartwell Tavern parking lot on Rt. 2A. Lincoln. FREE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) It looks like this would require additional driving, but I want to see this too:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Wayside: Home of Authors,&lt;/b&gt; where 19th-century authors kept the spirit of the Revolution alive by contributing to the creation of a American literary identity. 40-minute tours are 10 am, 11 am, 1 pm, 2 pm, 3 pm, and 4:30 pm. $5.00&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the Revolutionary era, The Wayside was the home of Samuel Whitney, muster master of the Concord Minute Men. During the literary renaissance of the 19th century, it was home to three families of authors. The young Louisa May Alcott wrote her first published work here. Extensive renovations to the house were made by Nathaniel Hawthorne, including the vaulted tower study. Harriett Lothrop, using the pen name “Margaret Sidney” wrote the “Five Little Peppers” stories at this “Home of Authors.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To continue to The Wayside from Hartwell Tavern, continue west on Route 2A for ¾ mile. At the blinking light, bear right and follow the signs towards Concord Center. You will be on Lexington Road. You will pass the Meriam’s Corner parking area on your right. Approximately 1/3 mile from Meriam’s Corner, you will see The Wayside, a large yellow house on your right with a parking area across the street. Turn left onto Hawthorne Lane to access the parking lot.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Let's meet at the Visitor's Center at 10 am.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Directions:&lt;/u&gt; 250 North Great Rd., Lincoln. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From I-95: Take exit 30B. You will be on Route 2A west. The park is 1-mile west off ramp.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From MassPike: Take I-95 Exit (exit 14) and follow above directions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From Route 2: Follow Route 2 to I-95 North. Proceed north one exit to 30B. Follow directions above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll wear my Meetup button and will be hanging out in the Visitor's Center at 10 am</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Anna</member_name><member_id>404606</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>4</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1280092225000</updated><rating><average>4.25</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>people</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>NerdFunBoston</urlname><id>661701</id><group_lat>42.3499984741</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0699996948</group_lon><name>Nerd Fun - Boston</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278958701000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Minuteman Park Market Fair and Militia Muster</name><id>14079001</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1279980000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/NerdFunBoston/events/14079001/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/8/3/global_16383971.jpeg</photo_url></item>