<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>2nd Annual Family Camp sponsored by Camp Constitution (campconstitution.us) runs from Saturday afternoon July 10 to Friday morning July 16.  This camp will feature classes given by folks like Pastor Garrett Lear, N.H. State Rep Dan Itse and featured instructor Rev. Steven Craft.  Classes and workshops will include several on the U.S. Constitution, God and Guns, what is wrong with government education,, an expose on the United Nations, an expose on the environmental movement, Economics 101, the Federal Reserve Bank,  how to influence elected officials and opinion molders, how to become an opinion molder and a trip into the surrounding towns to engage in activism. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   In addition to the classes and workshops, field trips to historic Concord, MA, and a hike up Mt. Monadanock is also planned.  Recreational activities include swimming, boating, volleyball, basketball, softball, ping-pong, fuseball, indoor rock climbing wall, and chess tournaments.  We have campfire every night were we sing songs, tell corny jokes and skits, recite poetry, etc.  A daily camp newspaper is printed giving opportunities for attendees to work on their wriiting and communication skills. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   This camp is opened to entire families (children under three are free-accompanied by an adult),  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   The cost of for a full week for campers ages 12 and up is $295.  Adults who serve as staffers $200.  Discounts for children under 12.  And special rates for those who bring tents or trailers.  We also offer day rates which includes three meals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  For more information, please call me at (857) 498-1309 or visit the web site campconstitution.us &lt;br /&gt;    &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>harold shurtleff</member_name><member_id>3658665</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1278793360000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Ron Paul 2012 Supporters</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>ronpaul-6</urlname><id>455674</id><group_lat>43.2400016785</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5100021362</group_lon><name>New Hampshire Ron Paul 2012 Headquarters</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1265293125000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Camp Constitution Family Camp</name><id>12517102</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278788400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/ronpaul-6/events/12517102/</event_url></item>