<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>1256 Massachusetts Ave</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.372696</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-661-1515</phone><name>Harvard Book Store</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669098</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.116380</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steven Pinker, Lois Lowry, Wendy Kaminer, and Steve Kleinedler&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;discuss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The American Heritage Dictionary of the English Language (Fifth Edition)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thursday, December 8, 2011, 7:00 PM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : center"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size : medium"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:: :: ::&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Harvard Book Store is thrilled to welcome STEVEN PINKER, LOIS LOWRY, WENDY KAMINER, and STEVE KLEINEDLER to discuss The American Heritage Dictionary of the English Language, Fifth Edition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;The much-anticipated Fifth Edition of The American Heritage Dictionary of the English Language is the premier resource about words for people who seek to know more and find fresh perspectives. Exhaustively researched and thoroughly revised, the Fifth Edition contains 10,000 new words and senses, over 4,000 dazzling new full-color images, and authoritative, up-to-date guidance on usage from the celebrated American Heritage Usage Panel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In keeping with the American Heritage tradition of cutting-edge research, the Fifth Edition represents the work of a dedicated team of experts, scholars, and contributors. Thousands of definitions have been revised in rapidly changing fields such as astronomy and biology, geographical entries and maps have been completely updated, and the dictionary&amp;rsquo;s signature feature notes on word history, synonymy, and language variation have been enhanced and improved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trustworthy advice on controversies and conundrums in English usage is provided by the American Heritage Usage Panel, a group of 200 prominent users of the language. Under the leadership of Steven Pinker, preeminent researcher on language and the mind, the Panel passes judgment on both new and longstanding usage problems. No other dictionary offers such discerning and helpful guidance on issues of usage, grammar, and style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1323393759000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1322087303000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Pinker (et al.) on Words</name><id>42216712</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1323388800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/42216712/</event_url></item>