<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Storrow Dr</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01970</zip><lat>42.352674</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Boston Esplanade</name><city>Boston</city><id>696064</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.085946</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;i&gt;While I do not want to divert from our plan on the Esplanade, perhaps a couple truther's would like to go down and greet Cheney in the morning and then return to the 4th event on the Esplanade later. The peace and impeachment groups will be sending folks down. If you go try to bring some 9/11 Truth Now signs with you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Meet at the Charleston Naval Yards, 10:30, Pier 1, where the Constitution docks.&lt;br /&gt;(You can see it easily on the maps below.) We should get as close&lt;br /&gt;to the Constitution as they allow us.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/bost/planyourvisit/upload/BOSTmap.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/bo...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nps.gov/bost/planyourvisit/upload/Chas%20NY.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nps.gov/bo...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;directions to Pier 1:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ussconstitution.navy.mil/Directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ussconstit...&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People that want to meet Cheney to yell at him will meet up at the Esplanade at the site where we will be handing out fliers and DVD's. we will take off in order to be in time to greet cheney. Consider that Cheney will be in charlestown so if you have a bicycle/ roller blades/ skateboard/ hover board/ scooter/ teleportation device that will be the most efficient way to get to the navy yard to greet him. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;anyone with ideas for our own &amp;quot;21 gun salute&amp;quot; in honor of truth and impeachment etc. should do some brain storming quickly because i and others in charlestown would think it would be neat to hold our own impromptu ceremony... what do you think?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;anyone know of the noise ordinances in regards to using a bullhorn? or holding signs/ banners. please find out the specifics so we can inform people wanting to infringe on our rights.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bostonherald.com/news/regional/general/view.bg?articleid=1104453&amp;amp;srvc=rss" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.bostonhera...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WASHINGTON - Vice President Dick Cheney will be in Boston on July Fourth to attend a ceremony aboard the USS Constitution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cheney spokeswoman Megan Mitchell said today that Cheney will attend Friday?s military reenlistment ceremony on the historic warship, known as &amp;quot;Old Ironsides.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Constitution was commissioned in 1797 and is docked at Boston?s historic Charlestown Naval Yard, a national park. The ship never lost a battle, from fighting pirates in the Caribbean to British in the War of 1812.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;© Copyright 2008 Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten, or redistributed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ussconstitution.navy.mil/EventCalendar.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.ussconstit...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;July Events &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fri., July 4, 2008: Turnaround Cruise&lt;br /&gt;11:30am: USS Constitution will leave Charlestown Navy Yard's Pier 1. The ship will perform a short turnaround, but unlike previous years, no visitors will be allowed aboard. Due to maintenance conditions, &amp;quot;Old Ironsides&amp;quot; will not make her normal tour of Boston Harbor. Visitors can view the ship's short cruise from the Navy yard or any pier in the immediate area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;12:30pm: 21-gun salute to the nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Susan C. Serpa   &lt;br /&gt;www.neimpeach.org&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>mark WeAreChangeBoston.org</member_name><member_id>4641561</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1215355027000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Concerned Citizens</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>WeAreChangeBoston</urlname><id>388713</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0199966431</group_lon><name>We Are Change Boston / Boston 9/11 Truth</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1215054926000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Come and greet Dick Cheney in Charlestown</name><id>8268378</id><headcount>2</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1215181800000</time><rsvp_limit>846</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WeAreChangeBoston/events/8268378/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/f/3/6/global_981894.jpeg</photo_url></item>