<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>40 Brattle Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02138</zip><lat>42.373675</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>617-876-6837</phone><name>Brattle Theatre</name><city>Cambridge</city><id>669117</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.121272</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;MIKA BRZEZINSKI&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;discusses&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;All Things at Once&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;with&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Joe Scarborough&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;$5 tickets will go on sale starting Wed., Dec. 16&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Harvard Book Store is pleased to welcome journalist and co-host of MSNBC's Morning Joe, MIKA BRZEZINSKI, to talk about her new book All Things at Once, with fellow journalist JOE SCARBOROUGH.&lt;br /&gt;The daughter of former National Security Advisor Zbigniew Brzezinski and artist Emilie Brzezinski, Mika Brzezinski grew up with a unique perspective on the balance between an ambitious work life and a fulfilling family life. Her new book, All Things at Once, is part memoir and part rallying cry for women to pursue the vocation, be it work or family or both, that best fulfills them. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;In this straightforward, frank account of her career trajectory, Brzezinski, the daughter of President Carter's national security adviser Zbigniew Brzezinski, does not bother to disguise her hard-fought ambition to secure a top news anchor position or hide the fact that she is not satisfied (nor very good at) being a stay-at-home mom of two daughters. From the beginning of her TV career, working her way up at local affiliates in Hartford, to her big break, getting hired in 1997 for an overnight CBS network anchor program in New York, Up to the Minute, the author resolved to make the frantic pace work, despite the increasing toll the late hours and absences from her family were taking. Distracted, pressured to return too early to work after the birth of her second child and exhausted, she took a bad fall down the stairs of her Yonkers home while holding her infant. The trauma scared her into slowing down, but not for long. Opportunity has seasoned Brzezinski but not hardened her, and having found her venue and voice with Morning Joe, she shares a refreshingly pragmatic approach for the professional woman.&amp;quot; —Publishers Weekly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;$5 tickets will go on sale STARTING WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 16, and will be available for purchase online &lt;a href="http://www.harvard.com/events/press_release.php?id=2433" target="_blank"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;, at Harvard Book Store, and over the phone with a credit card (617.661.1515).&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mika Brzezinski is an MSNBC anchor and co-host of MSNBC's Morning Joe. A graduate of Williams College, she began her journalism career as a local reporter and anchor in Hartford, Connecticut. In 1997 she joined CBS, where she was their official &amp;quot;Ground Zero&amp;quot; reporter after the September 11, 2001 attacks, anchored CBS Evening News Weekend Edition, and was a frequent contributor to CBS Sunday Morning and 60 Minutes. In 2007 she moved to MSNBC, where in addition to co-hosting Morning Joe she reports for NBC Nightly News and serves as an alternating anchor for Weekend Today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joe Scarborough is a journalist on MSNBC. From 1995 to 2001 he served as a member of the U.S. House of Representatives from Florida, and he also served as publisher and editor for The Florida Sun. In 2003 he joined MSNBC as the host of Scarborough Country, and he currently hosts the weekday morning show Morning Joe, which features interviews with top newsmakers and politicians, along with analysis of the news of the day.&lt;/center&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>No organizer will be present. See message board below.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Steve Gluck</member_name><member_id>2864884</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1296256287000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Citizens of the World</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Cambridge-Moveable-Feast</urlname><id>370532</id><group_lat>42.3899993896</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>The Cambridge Moveable Feast</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>3</yes_rsvp_count><created>1260168198000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Mika Brzezinski</name><id>12034413</id><headcount>3</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1262991600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Cambridge-Moveable-Feast/events/12034413/</event_url></item>