<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>524 Main Street</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02670</zip><lat>41.666611</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Borsari Gallery Cape Cod</name><city>Dennis</city><id>11845842</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.162544</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Read the book Gone Girl with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marriage can be a real killer. &lt;br /&gt;

One of the most critically acclaimed suspense writers of our time, &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; bestseller Gillian Flynn takes that statement to its darkest place in this unputdownable masterpiece about a marriage gone terribly, terribly wrong. The &lt;em&gt;Chicago Tribune&lt;/em&gt; proclaimed that her work “draws you in and keeps you reading with the force of a pure but nasty addiction.” &lt;em&gt;Gone Girl&lt;/em&gt;’s toxic mix of sharp-edged wit and deliciously chilling prose creates a nerve-fraying thriller that confounds you at every turn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We'll meet at the to discuss the book and have a lovely lunch. The tea menu is prefixed at $21.00 and includes tea, a choice of lunches and dessert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Village Tea Room at Borsari Gallery combines both Art &amp;amp; Tea in a setting that is both a culinary and visual experience unlike any other. Located in the Village of Dennis, on Historic Route 6A, this beautiful barn dating back to the 1800’s, has been lovingly restored and provides a truly amazing setting for Afternoon Tea with friends old and new.&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Barbara will be wearing her Girls Just Wanna Have Fun Pin!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Barbara </member_name><member_id>7313867</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1363912006000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>women</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>1305818</id><group_lat>41.6500015259</group_lat><group_lon>-70.3000030518</group_lon><name>"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun!"  Women Social Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1361393872000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club---Gone Girl</name><id>105561802</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1362931200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Girl-s-Just-Wanna-Have-Fun-Social-Meetup-Group/events/105561802/</event_url></item>