<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Dear Westborough Spirituality Meetup member,  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How are you?  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We had a wonderful discussion. Thanks for all of sharing of your experience and input. It was a great meeup last time. We also enjoyed the movie and ice cream.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last time we discuss about how to create the peace in the world though ourself first. As an old saying: A thousand miles begins with one step. Everyday we face a lot of people, with all of the relationships are the resource for us to create good energy. If we start sending out the peaceful energy to the world, this world will become much better.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for all of your's sharing that we can do a lot of things from a little friendly smile to helping others. If we can transform our mindset, than everything around us could be very different. I am the one starting the peaceful energy and I am also the one stopping the vicious cycle. Even it is a tinny thing, but it may makes a huge different. It likes a butterfly effect.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month, we are going to share and discuss more about creating a peaceful energy from calming down my monkey mind and also have a deep understanding of causation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you would like to meet more friends with the same interest about seeking a spiritual life, please come and share your thoughts and experiences about how to practice spirituality in daily life.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the day and let’s create positive energy to the whole world. Hope see you all in our meetup.  &lt;br /&gt;If weather is nice, we may can take a little walk after. Let's have some fun! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/about/"&gt;About this Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>This will be the second building on your right when you come into condos or 617-223-7166 when have trouble to find</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan</member_name><member_id>4981726</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>2</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1285597903000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Spiritual People</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>spirituality-149</urlname><id>670379</id><group_lat>42.2799987793</group_lat><group_lon>-71.5999984741</group_lon><name>The Westborough Spirituality Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1283316000000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Westborough Spiritual September  Meetup</name><id>14614815</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1285524000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/spirituality-149/events/14614815/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/d/7/6/global_2055446.jpeg</photo_url></item>