<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Where: North Cemetery, Portsmouth&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;What do John Langdon, William Whipple, and Capt. Thomas Thompson all have in common? All three were great Americans, patriots, and Portsmouth residents...and all, along with many other notable individuals, share as their final resting place the North Cemetery on Maplewood Avenue in Portsmouth, New Hampshire. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, this hallowed ground is in great need of some TLC. Join us for a walk through this small, historic graveyard to pick up trash and show our respect for some of the great men and women who helped shape the colony and later the State of New Hampshire, and the infant United States of America.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The cemetery is about 1 mile from the McPherson house, so feel free to park there and walk over, or you can park by the cemetery if you prefer. All who participate should return to the McPherson house afterwards for refreshments and socializing. Please bring the beverage and snack of your choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trash bags and plastic gloves will be provided.  Furthermore, not that please feel free to carry openly.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tom</member_name><member_id>4294423</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>1</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214936008000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>8</yes_rsvp_count><created>1213906271000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Patriotic Graveyard Clean-Up</name><id>8174609</id><headcount>8</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214762400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/8174609/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/3/2/6/global_4426902.jpeg</photo_url></item>