<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>163 Pawtucket Boulevard</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01854</zip><lat>42.643787</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>978-459-0802</phone><name>Heritage Farm Ice Cream &amp; Restuarant</name><city>Lowell</city><id>1314481</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.340266</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos4.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/3/2/c/0/event_167952992.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;This has been a great place to gather to meet new friends, enjoy some good times, and NOW get some exercise! &lt;br /&gt;

 For all you new folks that joined us Monday; thanks for coming. We know you had a good walk and you’ll be back again for another fun time! &lt;br /&gt;

 For anyone that would like to walk with us, just come on by and you’ll be introduced to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an easy walk, but consistency and stamina development is the key. So each week we’ll continue to walk, but increase our distance and/or activities a bit more. Last time (Oct 8th) we had a little longer walk than the week before of about 3 miles. So this week we’ll increase to 4+ miles (about 1 1/2 hour). &lt;br /&gt;

 We had a great time walking and talking along the river with the foliage continuing to get more beautiful in colorful. In addition, a blue herring, a Carp, Canadian Geese, Ducks, Squirrels, Chipmunks, were all there with us as we admired them in their natural habitats. There’s always something new to see. So let’s continue to enjoy this wonderful fall location, have fun, and get some easy exercise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we finish our walk we can visit The Heritage Restaurant, just across the street, for a snack and hot beverage. Last week 8 of us enjoyed each others company over burgers. wraps, and salads. We had a lot of fun as we became new friends. We even had the unexpected pleasure of a poetry reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll meet between 5:30 - 5:45pm at the concert park benches just across the street from Heritage Ice Cream &amp;amp; Restaurant. For those that don’t know me, I’ll have a MEETUP pin on the back of my cap. If you come later, we’ll be walking, so just look for a group and ask everyone if they’re the MEETUP group. My cell #; (603) 204-1657&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is also a DOG FRIENDLY WALK, so bring them along if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Dana Ordway</member_name><member_id>4903547</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1350353884000</updated><rating><average>4.75</average><count>4</count></rating><group><who>Night Life &amp; Outdoor enthusiasts</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>PortsmouthAndBeyond</urlname><id>496430</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The Portsmouth "and beyond" Nite Out Meetup Group</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1349927638000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Walk &amp; Talk Along the River!</name><id>86485252</id><headcount>12</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1350336600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/PortsmouthAndBeyond/events/86485252/</event_url></item>