<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>50 Chapman Pl</address_1><state>CT</state><zip>06108</zip><lat>41.773003</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>East Hartford Community Cultural Center</name><city>East Hartford</city><id>774507</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.644718</lon></venue><fee><label>Event fee</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>45.0</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>CHARTER OAK PHOTOGRAPHIC SOCIETY, INC.   PRESENTS A PHOTOGRAPHIC SEMINAR:  ? IMAGE DESIGN IN NATURE AND BEYOND? (The Digital Transition)  BY:  TONY SWEET  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, November 3, 2007 (9:00 am to 4:30 pm)  East Hartford Community Cultural Center    After 20 years as a professional jazz artist, Tony changed careers and directed his creative juices towards nature photography.  The improvisational, spontaneous, and abstract nature of jazz are also integral elements of nature photography.  Today, Tony?s work is published worldwide.  His images are represented by the Getty Picture Agency.  His photographic prints  are exhibited at the Nikon Corporate office in NYC, Mercy Medical Center, John Hopkins Breast Center, and in the Smithsonian in Washington, D.C.  Tony conducts ?Visual Artistry? photography workshops throughout the continental United  States and Canada.  Tony?s articles and photography are featured in Shutterbug and Rangefinder magazines, and as contributor to Nikonnet.com.  He is a staff writer for Nikon World magazine.  He has authored three books in the art of photography.  Fine Art Nature Photography, Fine Art Flower Photography, and Fine Art Photography:  Water, Ice, and Fog.    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This seminar is sponsored in part by Nik Software, Inc. and Hunt?s Photo &amp;amp; Video.  Hunt?s will be on site to  sell their photographic products and equipment.  (If you have any special requests for Hunt?s, please contact  Gary Farber at 1-800-221-1830 ext 2332 or by email at DigitalGuyGary@wbhunt.com).  Door prizes are being   provided by Hunt?s Photo &amp;amp; Video and Lowe Pro.      &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fee    Before 10/20/07   Charter Oak Photographic Society Members  $40.00   $45.00   &lt;br /&gt;At the Door 11/3/07   Charter Oak Photographic Society Members  $40.00   $45.00   Non Members*      $45.00   $50.00    Special Student Fee               At The Door Only    $ 25.00    *A $5.00 credit will be allowed toward a Charter Oak membership, if application is made on or before the Seminar Day.  ?    Introduction and Overview  ?    Visual Rhythm?Compositional Techniques I  ?    Nik Filter Show Illustrating Creative Use of Niks Color Efex Pro Filters  ?    Lensbaby Presentation  ?    Depth of Field, etc.  Advanced Compositional Techniques II  ?    The Art of Interpretation  ?    Special Effects:  Digital Sandwiching, Multiple Exposures and Recent Work and Q&amp;amp;A &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                                    REGISTRATION FORM  Please complete and send to Ms. Gretchen Hein, 44 Broadview Street, Bristol, CT 06010-5106 along with  your check for the full amount made payable to Charter Oak Photographic Society, Inc.  Deadline for   advanced registration is 10/20/07.    No. _____  Charter Oak Member(s) at $40.00 per person      $ _______   No. _____ Non member(s) at $45.00 per person    $ _______        Total amount of check enclosed  $ _______  Name(s) and Address(es) of Seminar attendees:  ______________________________________________________________________________________  _____________________________________________________________________________________&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1194267712000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193175545000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Photo Seminar by Tony Sweet</name><id>6604655</id><headcount>120</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1194094800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/6604655/</event_url></item>