<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="color : #000000"&gt;Organizer: Alex Nedzel @ (617) 461-7823&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the entire description before you RSVP and answer all questions that are part of the RSVP. Failure to answer them will result in your removal from this event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;If you RSVP from a mobile device the questions may not show up - be sure to use a computer to update your RSVP so you can answer them (go back to the event page, click change "RSVP", click "YES", then answer them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSVPs for this event will close at 3pm on Saturday.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #ff0000"&gt;Your safety, and the safety of the group, is the most important thing. If you underestimate the demands of this event; overestimate your experience, knowledge, skills or abilities; or come unprepared you put yourself or others at risk – consider this before you decide to participate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we're doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The plan is to climb one of the 4,000 footers in NH - Carrigain (#13 @ 4,700'). It is one of the highest peaks along the southeastern ridge bordering the Pemigewasset Wilderness Area. An observation tower on the summit provides hikers with a stunning view of the surrounding White Mountains. We will be using Signal Ridge Trail to reach the summit and then retrace our steps to return to the trailhead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;It could be cold and windy, it could snow, or it could be warm with blue skies. Be sure to look at the gear information listed below - you will need warm layers, wind protection, snowshoes and crampons, among other things. I will update everyone if weather conditions more than what is described below. If you don't know what to wear and/or bring with you or have any questions contact me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Do not rely on others to have extra items to share with you at the meeting spot or on the trail. You should know how to use all of your equipment - test and adjust it prior to this trip.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://hbbostonamc.org/docs/Gear_lists/Winter_Dayhike_equip.pdf"&gt;Click for a &lt;strong&gt;list of items needed for a winter day hike&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests are not permitted,&lt;/strong&gt; other than the host's guests (these are folks who have registered from the AMC side).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dogs are permitted&lt;/strong&gt; on this hike provided they are experienced "hikers", well-behaved, you bring a leash in case you need to use it, and you have a copy of their most recent rabies vaccination. Be sure to indicate in your RSVP if you will be bringing a dog.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trip Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We start as a group, hike as a group, and finish as a group.&lt;/span&gt; Our pace will be that of the slowest hiker. This trip isn't for you if you are faster than the group and don't want to stay with us, if you want to head off on your own, or if you are slower than the group and expect us to constantly wait for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;On this &lt;strong&gt;moderate pace (1.5-2.0 MPH)&lt;/strong&gt; out-and-back trip we will &lt;strong&gt;hike 14 miles&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;climb about 4000 feet&lt;/strong&gt;. It should take an average hiker &lt;strong&gt;about 9 hours to complete this trip&lt;/strong&gt;, not including time for rest/food breaks and challenging winter conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This event is considered to be &lt;strong&gt;INTERMEDIATE-ADVANCED&lt;/strong&gt; because of the pace, distance, elevation gain, and likley winter conditions.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;We could alter our plans because of fatigue, weather, and/or other conditions and there is no guarantee that we will complete the entire event as described here (i.e. we might not reach the summit).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I did my research using the Appalachian Mountain Club's "White Mountain Guide", a trail map, and the Internet. You need to become self-reliant by becoming familiar with the route, terrain, and potential hazards since you are ultimately responsible for your own safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.trailsnh.com"&gt;current trail conditions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(trailsnh.com), and enter "Carrigain" into the "Where 'ya headed?" box.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Mountain weather is subject to rapid changes and extreme conditions. Dangerous weather conditions will cancel - I will post an update and/or send an email to all confirmed participants a day or two ahead of time. We will assess travel and weather conditions during the hike and make changes to our planned trip as necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Click for the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://forecast.weather.gov/MapClick.php?lat=44.08413251541452&amp;amp;lon=-71.4609146118164"&gt;current weather forecast&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(weather.gov)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;We will meet in the parking area on the south side of Sawyer River Road, roughly 2 miles in from Route 302 west of Bartlett, NH.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;According to Goo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color : #222222"&gt;gle Maps this spot is about 174 miles from Boston and it should take about 3 hours 5 minutes to drive there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/Rx3MyV"&gt;Click for &lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://mapq.st/Rx3MyV"&gt;customizable driving directions&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Mapquest)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While carpooling is encouraged you are responsible for coordinating your own rides. Use the comments section below to communicate with others who may also be looking to share a ride. If you do share a ride be sure to share the expenses - suggested donations per person are $20 from Boston MA, $15 from Salem/Nashua NH, and $10 from Concord NH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMC Trip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;I am running this is an official AMC trip.  Once you add yourself here on Random, I'll be in touch to finalize your sign-up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;The AMC's participant waiver/release is pretty similar in spirit to Random's, except that you sign a hardcopy at the trailhead. You can preview it &lt;a href="http://www.outdoors.org/pdf/upload/volrelease.pdf"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Any questions, don't hesitate to be in touch via e-mail, or via phone at my number above.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Random Group of Hikers Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a condition of your voluntary participation in this activity you acknowledge and agree to the following: this activity involves inherent risks that can cause property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death to participants and/or others; you assume all risk associated with this activity; you are responsible for having the necessary knowledge, skills, abilities, clothing, and equipment to safely participate in this activity; you know and will follow the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikesafe.com/"&gt;Hiker Responsibility Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;; the organizer(s) of this activity are volunteers; and you release, hold harmless, and indemnify the organizer(s) and all members of this group from any and all claims for property damage, injury, illness, disability, and/or death - including those caused by negligence and/or other reasons.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Silver Toyota Yaris 4-door with MA Plates.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Alex N</member_name><member_id>13486965</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1357597730000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1357334816000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>NH4K - Mt. Carrigain on the Spur of the Moment</name><id>97934552</id><headcount>5</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1357473600000</time><rsvp_limit>12</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/97934552/</event_url></item>