<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>125 Canal St Providence R</address_1><state>RI</state><zip>02903</zip><lat>41.827427</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>401-351-3434</phone><name>Fat Belly's Pub</name><city>Providence </city><id>1448674</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.409843</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As of this writing there are 3 days, 21 hours, 53 mins and 10 seconds to go according to the official Super Bowl countdown clock. (Yes, I actually went to nfl.com for the SECOND time ever, the first was last year - lol!) Whether you're rooting for the Steelers or the Packers (or don't care at all) come down to Fat Belly's, cheer your heart out, hang out with friends, and enjoy some pretty good food, watch the game and socialize! Afterall, really, isn't that what its all about!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know we've been going to Fat Belly's a lot lately, but it really is one of the better places to watch a game (TV's galore!). If there is great opposition, I'm open to suggestions, but for now the plan is to get a table upstairs or downstairs at 5:30PM or before and see what happens. Of course, I'm open to standing as well - the choice is yours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game time is 6:30pm and the hype will begin before, so come at 5:30 or come at 6:30, come early, come late, but come on down for some fun, friends and good cheer! Please RSVP! If we get a large group, I'd like to give Fat Belly's a head's up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there! bring a friend!&lt;/p&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be wearing a silver scarf, but you can't miss us!</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>R. Elsbeth</member_name><member_id>4049064</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1297215946000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><why>Come down to Fat Belly's to watch the Pittsburgh Steelers and Green Bay Packers battle it out for the Super Bowl title of the new decade plus one (2011)!</why><group><who>P-Collective Members</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>newintown-995</urlname><id>1302228</id><group_lat>41.8400001526</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4000015259</group_lon><name>The Providence Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>13</yes_rsvp_count><created>1296695801000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Super Bowl XLV at Fat Belly's!</name><id>16420781</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1297031400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/newintown-995/events/16420781/</event_url></item>