<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>3 Battery Wharf</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02109</zip><lat>42.366689</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Fairmont Battery Wharf</name><city>Boston</city><id>1441888</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.051118</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flash Forward Boston kicks off June 7-10, 2012 at the Fairmont Battery Wharf.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new installment of the Festival had our Programming Committee [Erin Elder, Clare Jordan, Robyn McCallum, Andy Adams and MaryAnn Camilleri] exploring the topics that interest and influence our industry. The committee, made up of professionals working in the commercial, fine art and social media aspects of the photography world, found loads of common ground and know that they've come up with timely and informative topics for lectures, panel discussions and seminars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After all, who doesn't want to learn how to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make more money as a freelancer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a social media campaign [or even start one, for that matter]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise essential funds for projects or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn how Art Directors find work?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Along with bringing you some top-notch &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;exhibitions&lt;/a&gt;, the Flash Forward Festival is all about 'How to Succeed in Business', and we are thrilled to share this noteworthy line up of guests and talks with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special guests this year include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ch&lt;/span&gt;ris Dixon&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vanity Fair&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Natalie Cusson&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;enRoute&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; will talk about their roles as Design and Art Directors of leading magazines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Knight&lt;/strong&gt;, co-founder and editor of iPad-exclusive &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once Magazine&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; will talk about his experience &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;creating an app&lt;/a&gt; that uses this dynamic platform that challenges traditional economic models of publishing and re-imagines what a photo story can be.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tina Ahrens&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;strong&gt;Emphas.is&lt;/strong&gt; will inform photojournalists and photographers about the ins and outs of &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;HOW TO FUND THEIR PROJECTS&lt;/a&gt;! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian photographer &lt;strong&gt;Tony Fouhse&lt;/strong&gt; will talk about the &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;twists and turns of working on a project&lt;/a&gt;, what happens to influence that process, and how to adapt to change along the way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also have some incredible events and exhibitions organized for you: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, The &lt;strong&gt;Griffin Museum of Photography&lt;/strong&gt; will host their annual &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Focus Awards&lt;/a&gt; on June 6 at Fairmont Battery Wharf. The awards will kick off the Festival, honouring educators, photo editors, historians, writers, and others who have significantly elevated the photographic medium. We are thrilled to host the Focus Awards at the &lt;strong&gt;Fairmont Battery Wharf&lt;/strong&gt; and excited to attend what will be an enjoyable evening. Join us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other exceptional attractions at this year's Festival include an exhibition curated by &lt;strong&gt;The Humble Arts Foundation&lt;/strong&gt;; a &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Mini Book Fair&lt;/a&gt; in conjunction with &lt;strong&gt;Printed Matter&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;Indie Photobook Library&lt;/strong&gt;; a PRE-FESTIVAL exhibition curated by &lt;strong&gt;Jason Landy/Panopticon Gallery&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;strong&gt;Eunice Hurd/ Robert Klein Gallery&lt;/strong&gt;; an &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;AIB student show&lt;/a&gt; curated by &lt;strong&gt;James Hull&lt;/strong&gt; at &lt;strong&gt;Laconia Gallery&lt;/strong&gt;; and an &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;outdoor exhibition&lt;/a&gt; on the &lt;strong&gt;Rose Kennedy Greenway Conservancy&lt;/strong&gt;. This year the indoor and outdoor component will cover more ground and engage more areas of Boston. There will be nothing like walking along the Harborwalk and exploring everything the festival has to offer. Full details on many of these events are already posted on the &lt;a target="_blank" style="color : #de0079 ; text-decoration : underline"&gt;Flash Forward Festival website&lt;/a&gt;, and the rest will be coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mean, we could go on, but this is already a lot of info to wet your whistle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the coming weeks, the Festival website will be updated with MORE guests and surprises. With the success of last year's Festival and the awesome response it received, we look forward to hosting another great event in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flash Forward Boston kicks off June 7-10, 2012 at the Fairmont Battery Wharf.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make your travel arrangements now, and remember: &lt;strong&gt;the FLASH FORWARD FESTIVAL IS FREE!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With our sincere thanks and gratitude to all our amazing sponsors TD, Fairmont Battery Wharf, Fairmont Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, enRoute, BBW, Griffin Museum of Photography, Photo Shelter, Flak Photo, Printed Matter and Media Sponsors: The Boston Globe, The Boston Phoenix, Art New England and Panorama Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Scott Erb</member_name><member_id>762115</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>Donna Dufault</member_name><member_id>1714904</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1339083034000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Photographers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>photo-22</urlname><id>120247</id><group_lat>42.25</group_lat><group_lon>-71.7699966431</group_lon><name>Worcester Alliance of Photographers - AKA: WAP</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>14</yes_rsvp_count><created>1330992257000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Flash Forward Boston: Photo Festival: Free!!</name><id>55126032</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1339070400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/photo-22/events/55126032/</event_url></item>