<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>524 Allen Ave</address_1><state>Ma</state><zip>04103</zip><lat>43.704441</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>Allen Avenue Unitarian Universalist Church</name><city>Portland</city><id>5060042</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.282913</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the May 2013 Transition Challenge, Transition Start ups in Portland is hosting a series of Thursday evening events! &lt;span&gt;This night we a having a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;potluck and storytelling event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stories bring strategies to life. They inspire us to take action and connect us to shared purpose. Hosting a conversation to share stories looks like a anecdote circle. We'll break bread together and we sit in a circle to share our stories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event is an opportunity to develop clear agreement about leadership for our initiative, so the stories that we will share will be about leadership in community, the good and the bad ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The evening of stories will be harvested for points of resonance and connection, for patterns we can identify, and eventually, we will pick a story that is the most significant one for developing our Transition culture. This will guide our leadership group going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event will be facilitated by the Resilience Hubs own Rachel Lyn Rumson. &lt;span style="text-align : justify"&gt;With more than ten years of  facilitation and process consulting experience, Rachel Lyn has been working professionally as a trainer and educator for over five years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/6/8/event_234184712.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : right"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;span&gt;She has been called an animator due to the “life” that she brings to groups, actively engaging them in the work. Her masters thesis on regenerative systems combined with her study of Permaculture Design form a keystone of her practice.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;As systems thinker, Rachel Lyn embraces the complexity of each project and works to maximize the goals of her clients in business and in activism. She values learning processes and dialogue as vital components of each project and seeks to develop communities that intentionally create together.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align : left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please join us for a story filled evening. Bring a dish to share and a potluck kits with utensils.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Rachel Lyn</member_name><member_id>4529129</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1368754299000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Permies</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>portlandpermaculture</urlname><id>215138</id><group_lat>43.6599998474</group_lat><group_lon>-70.2600021362</group_lon><name>Portland Maine Permaculture &amp; The Resilience Hub</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1368039266000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Taking the Transition Challenge: Potluck and Storytelling</name><id>118408662</id><duration>10800000</duration><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1368743400000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/portlandpermaculture/events/118408662/</event_url></item>