<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>I am a small business owner and entrepreneur.  I would like to form a group of independent business owners who are looking to share information to grow and improve our businesses and exchange ideas.  I would like to limit the group to 10-12 people to make meetings manageable and to ensure that we are in a position to help each other.  Members are assured that they will have no competitors in the group.  Each member must be able to bring a unique perspective and to provide a sounding board for ideas to help other members.&lt;br /&gt;     Active participation is a requirement.  If you cannot commit to meetings, please do not sign up or you will be dropped from the membership.  Membership will be limited to serious participants only who are business owners.  Start-ups and non-profits are welcome.  Going Concerns and for-profits are preferred.  Any kind of business that is not conflict with existing members' business will be considered.&lt;br /&gt;     Membership is first-come, first-served.  I will interview potential members to ensure that the group is appropriate for the member.&lt;br /&gt;     Thank you for your interest.  I look forward to a long and mutually beneficial exchange.&lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Peter Melencio</member_name><member_id>2726681</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1196709403000</updated><rating><average>4.67000007629</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Small Business Owners</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>smallbiz-595</urlname><id>541347</id><group_lat>42.3199996948</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4300003052</group_lon><name>The MetroWest Small Business Forum</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1193270883000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Framingham Small Business November Meetup</name><id>6612035</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-18000000</utc_offset><time>1196294400000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/smallbiz-595/events/6612035/</event_url></item>