<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;a href="http://wiki.nhruby.org/index.php/Upcoming_meetings" target="_blank"&gt;http://wiki.nhruby.or...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're suffering withdrawl from the lack of a NHRuby.org meeting last month, don't worry - we're back for a great meeting this month! Join us at our usual location, RMC Research in Portsmouth, NH for a trio of interesting talks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Brian Turnbull will be giving an presentation on HTTP, the protocol that powers the world wide web. Every web page requested and displayed in a web browser is delivered via HTTP. But HTTP can facilitate all sorts of client/server communication. In this talk, Brian will discuss and present the major aspects of the protocol for application to your own projects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Scott Garman will be giving a talk on how to quickly set up a Virtual Private Server (VPS) as a Rails deployment environment. This talk is specifically geared toward this process as preparation for the Rails Rumble programming contest, coming up in mid October. Rumble participants will be given a Linode VPS to use during the contest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;* Continuing on the Rails Rumble preview theme, Nick Plante will give an overview of the git source code management system, as well as the elegant and powerful GitHub hosted web service for managing git repositories. Rumble participants will be expected to use git and GitHub during the contest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rumor has it that Nick will have some signed copies of his newly released book, Practical Rails Plugins that will be given away as door prizes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WHEN: Tuesday, September 16, 2008. 7-9 PM.&lt;br /&gt;WHERE: RMC Research Offices, 1000 Market Street, Portsmouth, NH.&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I'll be there?</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Tim</member_name><member_id>4013131</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1224628970000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>3</count></rating><group><who>Ruby programmers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhruby</urlname><id>885450</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>The NH Ruby and Rails Meetup</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>7</yes_rsvp_count><created>1219190874000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Seacoast NH Ruby and Rails September Meetup</name><id>8579870</id><headcount>7</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1221606000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhruby/events/8579870/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/c/7/f/global_4005199.jpeg</photo_url></item>