<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Hi Everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This event was moved to SUNDAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is no after-party either but I am going to the Fireworks in East Hartford since that too was moved to SUNDAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now that summer is here, we are starting to head out to  more shore areas and a bit more challenging conditions until the fall season when we return to some new and old local rivers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you haven't done any self rescue classes or practiced lately, you don't want to be surprised out in the deep.&lt;br /&gt;This is not a formal class but more for practice and for some first timers who will get a chance to try it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather: &lt;a href="http://www.usairnet.com/cgi-bin/launch/code.cgi?Submit=Go&amp;amp;sta=KHFD&amp;amp;state=CT" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.usairnet.c...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Weather is looking very good for SUNDAY.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So instead of a long distance event i would like to keep things close to home and have to option to &lt;br /&gt;hit the fireworks close to home also for a only a few of you that may be interested in going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was thinking this is a good day to practice self rescues  to keep in rescue shape for the upcomming more challenging open water treks to the destinations planned. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am more worried about recreational kayaks on the ocean as we travel further out and much further than we have in the local rivers to get to our destinations. Recreational yaks don't really belong out in the ocean but with care and thought along with staying close to us, you can go and enjoy a great day with us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BUT One small wave and those recreational boats with the big opening is full of water and they have no flotation internals so plan accordingly. Self rescue is usually not very possible with these boats but assisted rescues work pretty good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of us including my self have not fallen in a lot lately and we get so used to our paddling skills untill we do fall in and find because we haven't practiced..its harder than we think... im usually good for 3 attempts then i am worn out..(and just think i have practiced in the past and should know and be better, but that is a reality).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;a biginner for the first time..well..you better hope there is someone to help you if you are out on the open water..(thus the reason for a whistle on your Life Jacket and are wearing the life jacket properly so it wont float up to your neck/head..) You cant put on a life jacket very well when in the water watching the wind and waves take away your boat - paddle- and the boats contents of fresh water and things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue"&gt;SO IF YOU PLAN TO JOIN US ON THE OCEAN (ACTUALLY ANY TIME ON THE WATER),&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE LOOK AT THE VIDEO LINKS ON THE GROUPS MAIN PAGE OR DO YOUR OWN SEARCH TO HAVE AN IDEA WHAT TO DO PRIOR TO THIS EVENT.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IF YOU HAVE A PADDLE FLOAT AND PUMP BRING IT. IF YOU DON'T HAVE ONE AND YOU HAVE A YAK..YOU MAYBE SHOULD BUY THEM ESPECIALLY IF YOU EVER GO OUT ALONE... 99% OF THE TIME I HAVE MINE LOADED AND  READY TO GO..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The whole idea of this event is not to make you an expert but for you to learn at least one technique (the paddle float self rescue) so you on your own can get in on a deeper water situation.... (Or help a biginner or seasoned person in their time of need).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remember the paddle float re-entry is not the best technique compared to others (IE the Eskimo roll), (its also not a preferred method in rough waters either) but learning the other ones requires the basic knowledge of how a boat behaves in re entry and how we really need some effort to get in using the paddle float at first and even at other times in our experiences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have to start somewhere and this is the best kind of technique to start with.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now in the past 3 or more years we had this at BOLTON Lake, I have been given a few suggestions for other more private places and may choose them also, i have already inspected 3-4 and found them not viable for us, and will take into consideration a few more..before i make a decision. But i plan to have it at a generally local area to Hartford so there is that limitation but will see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After this self rescue event- i know most want to go home and shower..eat etc...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You don't need to reserve any of my boats for this event, i will bring what i feel is ONE good starter boat ( The Eddyline Wind Dancer) &amp;amp; one a bit more challenging. I will work with a few of you at a time that will be with us in the ocean trips.  Others will help each other too so everyone will get a chance im sure..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring your own boat if you have one to learn your own physical and the boats  limitations along with discovering what you can do to make it more seaworthy..IE FLOAT BAGS for and aft) Some of you will im sure not look at your safe and stable feeling boat the same, because they may not be..LOL&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Oh i forgot : this kind of event is a good excuse to sort of swim in an area we are not supposed to and get away with it legally up to a point.&lt;br /&gt;--------------------------------&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Getting to the Bolton Lake Boat Launch area:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take  Rte I - 384 heading East to Bolton Notch.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continue on Rte 44 E (Take the left part of fork) ...rte 6 is to the right&lt;br /&gt;There is a traffic light with a post office and a small shopping area to the right, continue to the next light.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At The next light has the boat launch to the LEFT and a church to the right. (South street intersection)&lt;br /&gt;Enter the boat launch area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;PLEASE LEAVE THE LAUNCHING CIRCLE OPEN after unloading AND PARK ON THE DESIGNATED SIDE AREAS, the DEP cops show up all the time it seems. They are looking to make some money and kayakers are the rich ones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you need help unloading we will always help you but don't know if you need help all the time so ask anyone to help you, we do this at all events anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pleas as always inventory your equipment at arrival and when leaving especially when people are trying to help, things seem to be forgotten and left behind..etc.. I don't mind the help but it usually costs me some gear every time because of distraction or items placed in the car and me taking it for granted its all there..&lt;br /&gt;i assume the same goes for others too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you all soon..&lt;br /&gt;al-r&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>I will wear my Bright Orange Hunting Hat and will be near the boat ramp.</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>AL-r</member_name><member_id>2711041</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>11</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1279650119000</updated><rating><average>4.80000019073</average><count>10</count></rating><group><who>River and Shore Kayak-r's of CT</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>HCR-SK</urlname><id>238228</id><group_lat>41.7000007629</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6699981689</group_lon><name>~~~~HARTFORD COUNTY RIVERS &amp; CT SHORE KAYAK GROUP~~~~ HCR-SK</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>19</yes_rsvp_count><created>1278589457000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>---SUNDAY---KAYAK Self Rescue Practice @ Bolton Lk </name><id>14038493</id><headcount>15</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1278867600000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/HCR-SK/events/14038493/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/2/e/a/global_13060842.jpeg</photo_url></item>