<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>302 n main st</address_1><state>NH</state><zip>03867</zip><lat>43.312897</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>pizza hut</name><city>rochester</city><id>6300712</id><country>us</country><lon>-70.994293</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Come hang out with other liberty-lovers in the northern Seacoast region. The location has changed. New location&amp;nbsp;- Pizza Hut Italian Bistro, 302 N Main St, Rochester, conveniently located between Spaulding Turnpike exits 14, Ten Rod Rd,&amp;nbsp;and 15, N Main St / Rte 11 (to Farmington). On the east side of Main St, directly across from the tiny Main St mall where the Planet Fitness gym is located, the restaurant shares a driveway with the Dunkin' Donuts. I haven't told the restaurant we're coming but they generally seem to have plenty of room, just tell the person seating you you're with a small group, Seacoast Liberty (at this point I would tell them we might get 5 people, though I hope to make this event larger over time). There are two rooms so I have no idea which one they'll put us in. This place is a lot more comfortable and conversation-friendly than the old location, where we had to raise our voices to be heard over the music. This will be a monthly event, repeating every month, on the second Saturday of the month at 6 pm. It is to this point the only weekend meetup for Seacoast Liberty, so I would like to encourage people from other areas to attend. I made it only once a month because it is a bit out of the way for many people, I would also love to have friends come over from the Lakes region, and from Maine, it is only about 30 minutes from Sanford to Rochester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want this event to become something where we discuss our plans and ideas for activism and not just hang out, though that can be fun as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Bryce Nielsen</member_name><member_id>24332732</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1334519758000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>SeaLs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>nhseacoastliberty</urlname><id>950500</id><group_lat>43.0699996948</group_lat><group_lon>-70.7799987793</group_lon><name>NH Seacoast Liberty</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1332031445000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Meetup in Rochester, at Pizza Hut Bistro</name><id>qgkgqcyqgbsb</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1334440800000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/nhseacoastliberty/events/56773842/</event_url></item>