<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;Explore East Rock Park during this end-of-summer hike which will take us along the Mill River, through College Woods park where we'll stop for a quick geology lesson about the formation of East Rock and some stretching, then across the iron foot bridge, and up and over Whitney peak to descend to Lake Whitney's Dam where we can view a huge waterfall from rocky ledges in the woods while having a snack or lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hike will take approximately 2.5 hours including lunch so we should be back by 12 noon. The trails are easy to moderate in difficulty level but have a few rocky sections here and there. We'll be hiking at a moderate pace so you should be relatively healthy and physically fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see a map of East Rock, please visit... &lt;a href="http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/media/2008EastRockMap.pdf"&gt;http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/media/2008EastRockMap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or take an interactive tour... &lt;a href="http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/eastrockTour.asp#_self"&gt;http://www.cityofnewhaven.com/Parks/ParksInformation/eastrockTour.asp#_self&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting location will be near Orange Street. &lt;strong&gt;The exact Meeting location will be sent to Yes RSVP's on the night prior to the event.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Please note that RSVP's will close on Saturday Sept 8 at 6 pm.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please bring your own water and snack. Post-hike activity could also include kayaking or canoeing on the Mill River. You would need to transport and secure your own boat until after the hike. Questions? To contact me, please email me on my profile page.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>christine</member_name><member_id>6235505</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1347236113000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><group><who>NHC'ers</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>New-Haven-Collective</urlname><id>211163</id><group_lat>41.3300018311</group_lat><group_lon>-72.9400024414</group_lon><name>The New Haven Collective</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>18</yes_rsvp_count><created>1346538743000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>East Rock Hike - Lake Whitney Waterfall</name><id>80428852</id><headcount>0</headcount><duration>9000000</duration><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1347197400000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/New-Haven-Collective/events/80428852/</event_url></item>