<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>So you have your new scooter and you know you can go fast enough to ride on the highway, but the thought is scary or the one time you did it felt almost too intense.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Riding on the highway is like like anything else the more you do it the more you get better at it, however learning while on a long ride or learning on your own is not the way to learn. .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I thought before the Scooter Show and Tell when the roads are quiet we can do some short rides on the pike, from West Newton to Newton Corner and back a couple of times and then on to the Marriott hotel (non-highway) There are no tolls on this stretch of the Pike and the road is smooth and clean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even if you are a seasoned rider, your input and tips will he helpful to those new at the slab, not to mention fun&lt;br /&gt;Experienced riders will be covering your front and back door, and we will take at 50-60 mph steady as she goes!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Riders should be wearing safety gear.. for safety :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We will meet at the Dunkin Donuts on Washington street in West Newton Square at 9AM and start promptly, arrive earlier if you want time to have a coffee.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you will come!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>Look for Scooters</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Paul Shoemaker</member_name><member_id>3108784</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1214313006000</updated><rating><average>4.0</average><count>1</count></rating><why>Chaperoned Scooter practice will help you feel more comfortable on the highway, dealing with wind, learning to relax and let the bike do the work in a safer environment that doing it alone.</why><group><who>Twisted Tourists</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>Scooters</urlname><id>379328</id><group_lat>42.3800010681</group_lat><group_lon>-71.1299972534</group_lon><name>Twisted Touring</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1212205027000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Highway Practice</name><id>8046827</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1214139600000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/Scooters/events/8046827/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/2/d/2/global_4080722.jpeg</photo_url></item>