<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>S.E. 10th Avenue</address_1><state>FL</state><zip>33301</zip><lat>26.107679</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>800-419-5179/7418 </phone><name>Port Everglades</name><city>Fort Lauderdale </city><id>987204</id><country>us</country><lon>-80.132919</lon></venue><fee><label>Price</label><accepts>cash</accepts><currency>USD</currency><description>per person</description><amount>688.010009766</amount><required>0</required></fee><status>past</status><description>THE IRA’S SINGLES EVENTS PROUDLY PRESENTS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         THE SECOND ANNUAL CARIBBEAN SINGLES CRUISE !!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one Big Party and one Big Way of Relaxing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         As of today, 8/10/2010, Updates Below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Over 230 Singles from around the country are coming, and this number is expected to grow. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Roommate Matching Service available until this Friday, 8/13/2010&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. The longer you wait, PRICES will go up for the cruise and air portion of the trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                     DETAILS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; FABULOUS SINGLES CARIBBEAN CRUISE ON THE MAGNIFICIENT                                  CROWN PRINCESS DEPARTS ON OCTOBER 30 2010/SATURDAY FROM FORT LAUDERDALE WITH &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                THE IRA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; AS YOUR GRACIOUS HOST!!!!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         LOVE BOAT INFO BELOW &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7 GLOURIOUS DAYS and NIGHTS OF FUN, TERRIFIC FOOD (No Cooking for 7 Days) 24/7 NON-STOP ENTERTAINMENT, ISLAND ADVENTURES, AND WHO KNOWS- YOU MAY MEET THAT SPECIAL PERSON OF YOU LIFE!!!!!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; COST: Under $100.00 a day!!!  From:$688.01Person. Rooms are filling up very quickly; a small deposit will hold your space. The sooner the better that you sign up, as rooms go very quickly. To request a cabin, you may make a deposit of $250 now and pay the balance 70 days prior to the sail date, or you can pay in full today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For  Complete Details, and of course the Fine Print, please see the web site below:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                  &lt;a href="http://www.vacationstogo.com/singles_c26.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.vacationst...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                                 DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SHIP:                              The Crown Princess&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hosting Information: I have traveled with Vacations to Go on their Single Cruises many times. They do an awesome job, generally getting a few hundred singles from around the county. In addition to their scheduled activities, I will host and organize smaller parties for “our group”, and if you are on the shyer side, or first time cruiser, I will be sure you are well introduced into the group. If you see someone of “interest”, where the “spark” is, yet “shy” or “apprehensive” of introducing your self to, I will be happy to do a “ classy” introduction. This will be my 24th cruise, so if you need any assistance with questions, I can help. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                                RESERVATION INFORMATION. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.  Please DO NOT BOOK  on line, as Cory  and I need to know who is from  “our group”. See Below for Reservation Information. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Contact:  For Reservations and Information, Please contact:  Corey, callen@vacationstogo.com, 800-338-4962extension 7292 , from Monday to Friday, 10am to 7pm, CST . &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. When making the reservation, Please let him know you are part of The Ira Singles Group.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4.     Send me an email at mistrchrming@aol.com,  or a phone call- 860-604-5792, with any questions, and or if you have booked this awesome cruise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5.     My anticipated air fare from South West will be aprox. 260.00 Round Trip. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6.     Anticipated number of singles should be in the range of 300 Plus from around the country………………&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Oct 30th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sail from beautiful Fort Lauderdale at 5pm (boarding is from 1pm to 4pm). Join us poolside for the sail away festivities and meet lots of other fun-loving singles! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sunday, Oct 31st&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A day at sea. Join in all the exciting singles activities with your Vacations To Go host. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday, Nov 1sth&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 7am to 4pm visit charming Grand Cayman Island. Explore the colorful marine life by submarine, swim with stingrays, relax in the sun on Seven Mile Beach, or visit the famous turtle farm. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tuesday, Nov 2nd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 10am to 5pm, visit Roatan, Honduras. Floating 30 miles off the Caribbean coastline of Honduras, in the Bay Islands, Roatan is 29 miles long and two miles wide. Reefs surrounding the islands are teeming with marine life and offer some fantastic scuba-diving and snorkeling opportunities. Idyllic beaches also lure visitors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday, Nov 3rd&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 7am to 5pm, visit Cozumel, Mexico and snorkel on famous Palancar Reef, dive at Paraiso Reef or go inland and visit the great pyramids and temples of the Maya. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thursday, Nov 4th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another day at sea. Take part in exclusive singles activities and mingle with friends. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Friday, Nov 5th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From 9am to 4pm, enjoy Princess Cays, Bahamas, Princess Cruise Line's private destination on the southern tip of the island of Eleuthera in the outer Bahamas is full of activities promising a great island adventure! With a beautiful beach with barbeque and bar facilities, and a basketball court and water sports pier, everyone will enjoy the day on their own private tropical island! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Saturday, Nov 6th&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At 7am, the Crown Princess returns to Fort Lauderdale. Be sure to gather those phone numbers to keep in touch with your new lifelong friends, and don't forget to plan ahead for your next cruise with Vacations To Go! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Organized singles activities with our singles host,  The Ira and VTG Staff &lt;br /&gt;Private singles cocktail parties/mixers (with complimentary cocktails) &lt;br /&gt;Single-mingle dining &lt;br /&gt;All meals and non-alcoholic, non-carbonated beverages &lt;br /&gt;Lavish buffets and complimentary room service &lt;br /&gt;Nightly Vegas-style shows and comedy routines &lt;br /&gt;Dancing nightly &lt;br /&gt;Live music nightly on deck and in clubs and lounges &lt;br /&gt;Lotus Spa featuring fitness, beauty &amp;amp; spa facilities &lt;br /&gt;Port charges and taxes &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;If you share your cabin with a friend or use our Match Program to find a roommate, the per-person prices are:&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Inside cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $688.01 &lt;br /&gt; per person&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Oceanview cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $788.01 &lt;br /&gt; per person *&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Balcony cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $1,048.01 &lt;br /&gt; per person&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you prefer to have a cabin to yourself, the prices are:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Inside cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $997.01&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Oceanview cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $1,147.01&lt;br /&gt;  *&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Balcony cabin:&lt;br /&gt; $1,947.01&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;       &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>A beautiful Large Cruise Ship in the Water Crown Princess</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Ira Wettenstein</member_name><member_id>5032313</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>3</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288462687000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Cool Singles</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>www-theirassinglesevents-com</urlname><id>1411725</id><group_lat>41.9300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6399993896</group_lon><name>The Ira's Singles Events, LLC.</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>102</yes_rsvp_count><created>1263304106000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Ira- One Terrific Singles Cruise. October 30. Time is Running Out!!!!</name><id>12297283</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288458000000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/www-theirassinglesevents-com/events/12297283/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/8/1/0/global_12626064.jpeg</photo_url></item>