<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>43 Butler Road</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01057</zip><lat>42.049046</lat><repinned>True</repinned><name>Peaked Mountain Tract</name><city>Monson</city><id>7356262</id><country>us</country><lon>-72.352036</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://photos2.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/4/a/d/a/event_122479162.jpeg" style="max-height : 700px ; max-width : 700px ; margin : 5px ; float : left"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;Peaked Mountain (pronounced pea-kid mountain) is part of a land trust maintained by a group called "The Trustees Of Reservations". Below is the website www.thetrustees.org and the specific page for this place. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/pioneer-valley/peaked-mountain.html"&gt;http://www.thetrustees.org/places-to-visit/pioneer-valley/peaked-mountain.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find out more details about this place including trail maps. &lt;br /&gt;

A brief excerpt from the page states, "Explore woods roads through a former working forest and trek to a summit that rewards with panoramic views from Mount Wachusett to Vermont’s Green Mountains."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have never been but I have heard very good reviews from people who have gone there. Information about this place states that dogs are allowed either under voice control or on leash. I just called today and verified this information is current. We will be parking at the lot on Butler Road and hiking on the fire roads as the trail map shows. We can do a loop to the summit via an easier walk on Rosalyn's Turnpike to Bernie Ave to Ruth's Mountain Road. I was informed Valley View is a more strenuous hike and not recommended for older dogs per the suggestion of one of the trustees I spoke with today. According to the trail map we can then return back via Ruth's Mountain Road to Skid Row or Orchard Trail. The names of these fire roads were given by people who built these roads from Peaked Mountain Coop following a fire in 1984.  I will post the trail map in the Files section under the MORE tab on our group's website. &lt;br /&gt;

Directions are from the website. Take Route 32 South and continue all the way to Monson. Just before the soldier statue in Monson turn right onto High St. Take immediate left onto Ely Rd. Proceed 1 mi., then go straight at stop sign onto Lower Hampden Rd for 2 mi. Turn left onto &lt;br /&gt;

Butler Rd. Pass a small parking lot on the right, which is for the Miller Forest Tract entrance, and go 1.2 mi. to main entrance and parking (20 cars) is on the left.&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michelle </member_name><member_id>34071322</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1338757014000</updated><rating><average>5.0</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Dog lovers</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>WesternMassDogs</urlname><id>1085798</id><group_lat>42.5400009155</group_lat><group_lon>-72.5299987793</group_lon><name>Western Mass Dogs - Walks and more!</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>5</yes_rsvp_count><created>1337819413000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Let's Check Out Peaked Mountain</name><id>66086102</id><headcount>4</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1338732000000</time><rsvp_limit>20</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/WesternMassDogs/events/66086102/</event_url></item>