<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_2>Building E51, Room 315</address_2><address_1>70 Memorial Drive</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>02142</zip><lat>42.360600</lat><repinned>False</repinned><name>MIT Sloan School of Management</name><city>Cambridge </city><id>1010762</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.084600</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>The Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance is proud to organize this event in partnership with &lt;a href="http://web.mit.edu/misti/mit-israel/" target="_blank"&gt;MISTI MIT-Israel&lt;/a&gt; and the MIT Sloan &lt;a href="http://stuff.mit.edu/afs/athena/activity/s/sloan-ibc/home/home.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli Business Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Itai Karelic, head of the U.S. office of &lt;a href="http://www.greenlettechnologies.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Greenlet Technologies&lt;/a&gt;, will discuss his company's smart grid technology.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;11:30am-12:00pm Networking &amp;amp; Intros &lt;br /&gt;12:00-1:00pm Presentation and Q&amp;amp;A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An MIT campus map is available online at &lt;a href="http://whereis.mit.edu/?go=E51" target="_blank"&gt;http://whereis.mit.ed...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Information about parking at MIT is available online at &lt;a href="http://www.talentforum.org/directions.htm" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.talentforu...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Greenlet Technlogies&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenlet Technologies offers electric utilities with fully automated system that provides verifiable demand response without the need for professional installation at customer site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greenlet offers electric utilities with a B2B solution for power reduction, a model called “Virtual Plant”. Using our highly integrated software-hardware system utilities can reduce power during peak, avoid power outages and high generation costs and avoid building new power plants. The solution enables utilities to send pluggable units (greenletTM) to customers for self deployment. The central management system automatically connects to the greenletsTM via Internet and remotely controls a very large number of loads. The solution minimizes customers’ efforts – all that is required of them is to plug in our units, and connect the gateway to their internet router.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Itai Karelic&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Itai heads the US office of Greenlet Technologies and is responsible for the company’s sales, business development and strategic alliances. He helped form Greenlet’s strategic direction prior to the company securing seed funding and joined the company at its inception in September 2008 once such funding was awarded.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prior to joining Greenlet Technologies Itai specialized in large scale privatizations, in the US, Europe and the Middle East.  As part of his commitment to facilitate not only environmental change but also social change Itai is a Director at the Nicholson Foundation and serves on a per need basis as an executive on loan to the administration of Newark’s Mayor Cory Booker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Itai holds an MBA from Warwick Business School. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Jonathan Shapira</member_name><member_id>6110717</member_id></event_hosts_item><event_hosts_item><member_name>David Dolev</member_name><member_id>8049486</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1288880330000</updated><rating><average>4.5</average><count>2</count></rating><group><who>Entrepreneurs</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>boston-israel</urlname><id>1175193</id><group_lat>42.3699989319</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0500030518</group_lon><name>Boston Israel Cleantech Alliance</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>17</yes_rsvp_count><created>1288292016000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Greenlet Technologies: An Israeli Perspective on Smart Grid</name><id>15261320</id><headcount>30</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1288798200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/boston-israel/events/15261320/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/e/1/global_19140225.jpeg</photo_url></item>