<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>Movie night! The theme for September is food from a movie.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am in a bit of an esoteric mood, plus when it comes to film knowledge Bill should be the one writing this month's theme - but he isn't... So I decide to share a bit of movie history trivia about the first nationally famous film critic - Pogo the Monkey. Pogo the Monkey became what we all recognize a the sock monkey toy, has a reference in Grand Theft Auto the video game, and a very funny fake commercial &lt;a href="http://crazymotion.net/pogo-the-monkey/wwrLZ44x3lGwjAy.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://crazymotion.ne...&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following is from &amp;quot;The Trendliest&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;The earliest form of film criticism came courtesy of Pogo The Monkey when he attended a screening of Eisenstein’s Battleship Potemkin back in 1925. After watching the film journalists asked Pogo what he thought of the film and Pogo raised three out of his ten fingers and then proceeded to fling his feces in the director’s general direction. Everyone took this to mean Pogo was none too impressed by Eisenstein’s pioneering use of montage. The monkey confirmed his feelings about the film by stating “my cousin Zippy could do a better job directing a snuff flick.” Pogo’s caustic sensationalism was quickly rewarded by the Chicago Daily Courier, who rewarded the chimp with his very own film and entertainment column. His ten finger rating system quickly became the norm for all film criticism and often his quotes were taken out of context and used on film posters. The most famous of these incidents was on the poster for The Wizard of Oz which read, “The Wizard of Oz Is A Landmark Piece…” when the actual line from the monkey’s review said “The Wizard of Oz Is A Landmark Piece of Crap.” As a critic Pogo became so famous that a comic book called “The Critic” was written about him. That comic book was later turned into an animated TV show starring Jon Lovitz, which was widely panned and had an abbreviated run on FOX.&amp;quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your job is to pick a movie and make your recipe something from that movie. Plan to cook onsite unless you dish takes more than 60 minutes to prepare.   &lt;br /&gt;If you will need the bar-b-q let me know and we'll get it fired up so it is ready when you get here.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you at the movies!&lt;br /&gt;</description><how_to_find_us>my home so you will notice me and the dogs, will send address a few days before</how_to_find_us><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>caryl</member_name><member_id>5833728</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1257974572000</updated><rating><average>4.88000011444</average><count>8</count></rating><group><who>Cooks</who><join_mode>closed</join_mode><urlname>The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group</urlname><id>874344</id><group_lat>41.7700004578</group_lat><group_lon>-72.6999969482</group_lon><name>Fabulous Foodies</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>20</yes_rsvp_count><created>1250294807000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>The Hartford Cooking And Recipes September Meetup</name><id>11115057</id><headcount>19</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1252710000000</time><rsvp_limit>26</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/The-Hartford-Cooking-And-Recipes-Meetup-Group/events/11115057/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/1/0/2/8/global_10198136.jpeg</photo_url></item>