<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><venue><address_1>Please call 508-361-7978 for directions</address_1><state>MA</state><zip>01754</zip><lat>42.433427</lat><repinned>False</repinned><phone>508-361-7978</phone><name>Robin's House</name><city>Maynard</city><id>1165405</id><country>us</country><lon>-71.449507</lon></venue><status>past</status><description>Omnivore’s Dilemma is not a book with a particular vegan view.  However, this book is eye opening on all food sources (and surprising uses!) including organic veggies.  Without trying to give too much away, here is a “vegan” review of the book I found on line &lt;a href="http://www.satyamag.com/sept06/iyer.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.satyamag.c...&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;About the book:&lt;br /&gt;In this groundbreaking book, one of America’s most fascinating, original, and elegant writers turns his own omnivorous mind to the seemingly straightforward question of what we should have for dinner. To find out, Pollan follows each of the food chains that sustain us—industrial food, organic or alternative food, and food we forage ourselves—from the source to a final meal, and in the process develops a definitive account of the American way of eating. His absorbing narrative takes us from Iowa cornfields to food-science laboratories, from feedlots and fast-food restaurants to organic farms and hunting grounds, always emphasizing our dynamic coevolutionary relationship with the handful of plant and animal species we depend on. Each time Pollan sits down to a meal, he deploys his unique blend of personal and investigative journalism to trace the origins of everything consumed, revealing what we unwittingly ingest and explaining how our taste for particular foods and flavors reflects our evolutionary inheritance. &lt;br /&gt;The surprising answers Pollan offers to the simple question posed by this book have profound political, economic, psychological, and even moral implications for all of us. Beautifully written and thrillingly argued, The Omnivore’s Dilemma promises to change the way we think about the politics and pleasure of eating. For anyone who reads it, dinner will never again look, or taste, quite the same. &lt;br /&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Victoria Mangus</member_name><member_id>8074795</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1282508125000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>Vegans</who><join_mode>open</join_mode><urlname>vegan-516</urlname><id>1286801</id><group_lat>42.4300003052</group_lat><group_lon>-71.4499969482</group_lon><name>Vegan Metro West Network</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>4</yes_rsvp_count><created>1279493130000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>Book Club: Omnivore's Dilemma by Michael Pollan</name><id>14140137</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1282503600000</time><rsvp_limit>10</rsvp_limit><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/vegan-516/events/14140137/</event_url><photo_url>http://photos1.meetupstatic.com/photos/event/9/e/1/global_7118529.jpeg</photo_url></item>