<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>	<item><status>past</status><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are interested in participating in this workshop you need to act now - some of classes will fill fast!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Annual Excursions Spring School&amp;nbsp;...&amp;nbsp;Instruction in safe mountain travel for hikers of all levels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Spring is coming! Dust off your backpack and refine your skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;This workshop offers instruction in safe mountain travel to hikers of all levels. Between the seven available classes, most every aspect of 3-season backcountry travel is covered. The weekend is filled with instruction, field exercises, lectures, and discussions. And when you&amp;rsquo;re not learning, there is plenty of great food to fuel you back up!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While I have not done anything with the New Hampshire Chapter I spoke&amp;nbsp;with Rick Silverberg, Director of the AMC New Hampshire Chapter's&amp;nbsp;annual workshops and Alex Nedzel, an organizer with the Random Hikers and both the AMC Boston &amp;amp; AMC NH Chapters. After talking with them I think they have put together an excellent program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;While you can use our event page to communicate with others from our group you will need to register directly with the AMC's NH Chapter. Before you register be sure to read about the workshop offerings described below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;=====&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Your time will be divided between your individual class and activities for the entire workshop. Each class runs for the duration of the workshop, so you may participate in only one class per workshop. All groups will spend extensive time outside.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Choose one of the following available classes. Once you find the class for you, go to the "How to Register" section below and follow the instructions. If you are not sure which class is right for you, just ask one of the Workshop Directors listed below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;#1 - Basics of Outdoor Safety: Beginner &amp;amp; Intermediate Classes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instruction in general mountain safety, equipment, route finding, map &amp;amp; compass, off trail navigation, weather, trip planning, nutrition, emergencies in the mountain environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;#2 - Map and Compass: Everything you wanted or needed to know:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;This session will be a small group of 8 participants and two instructors who will spend the weekend together reviewing and learning the details of map and compass culminating in field exercises and off-trail navigating with the compass on a bushwhack route.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;#3 - How to stay out for the night with just your daypack and day hiking equipment in an emergency:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;This section will be a group of up to 8 participants and two instructors who will be in the lodge Friday night. The day on Saturday will be filled with instruction on how to: make do, adapt, stay safe and survive the night in an emergency with your day hike equipment only. This group will spend the night out on Saturday in a simulation of an emergency stay without tent or sleeping bag.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;#4 - Backpacking: Beginner &amp;amp; Intermediate Classes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instruction in backpacking equipment, camp site selection, route finding, map &amp;amp; compass, weather, trip planning, cooking, and emergencies. For those who want take their skills beyond day hiking. Plan to spend Friday &amp;amp; Saturday night outdoors and provide for your own backpacking equipment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;#6 - Leadership and Mountain Skills:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;For those who have good 3-season hiking skills and wish to enhance them to run trips of their own. Exercises in planning, organizing, and conducting trips with emphasis on leadership techniques and group dynamics. Plus the basics of accident scene management, medical considerations, and off-trail navigation. This course is also for those with potential and desire to become Trip Leaders for the NH Chapter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;=====&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On-line Application:&lt;/strong&gt; Please apply via our on-line application to ensure the accuracy and priority of your application. You may access the on-line detailed information and application by clicking &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://amc_registration.ccntr.org/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. If this is your first time using the online registration form, you must first create an account. Otherwise, login with your password. Then after you have completed the registration form, please send your payment to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rich Desmaris &lt;br /&gt;

17 Longwood Avenue &lt;br /&gt;

Londonderry, NH 03053&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Written Application:&lt;/strong&gt; For those unable or unwilling to do the on-line application you may download the application by clicking &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://amc-nh.org/committee/excursions/SpringSchool_12reg.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (PDF).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;--OR--&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Send a large (No. 10, 4.12"X 9.5") self addressed envelope with first class postage with your telephone number to the Registrar:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="padding-left : 30px"&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Rich Desmaris&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;17 Longwood Avenue&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Londonderry, NH 03053&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;Please send a separate envelope and postage for each applicant. Please indicate which workshop you want to attend.&amp;#8232;&amp;#8232;Once you have your application, fill it out and send it with your payment to the registrar. You must be 18 years or older to attend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Workshop Director:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color : #000000"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If unsure of attending and need more info please contact Director Rick Silverberg at (603) 225-5921 from 7:00 PM - 10:30 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><event_hosts><event_hosts_item><member_name>Michael Blair</member_name><member_id>3942422</member_id></event_hosts_item></event_hosts><maybe_rsvp_count>0</maybe_rsvp_count><waitlist_count>0</waitlist_count><updated>1335053635000</updated><rating><average>0.0</average><count>0</count></rating><group><who>randomites</who><join_mode>approval</join_mode><urlname>random-hikers</urlname><id>492954</id><group_lat>42.3600006104</group_lat><group_lon>-71.0599975586</group_lon><name>Random Group of Hikers</name></group><yes_rsvp_count>2</yes_rsvp_count><created>1334455906000</created><visibility>public</visibility><name>AMC NH Chapter's Annual Spring Hiking Workshop (April 20-22)</name><id>djdzrcyqgbcc</id><headcount>0</headcount><utc_offset>-14400000</utc_offset><time>1335049200000</time><event_url>http://www.meetup.com/random-hikers/events/60612822/</event_url></item>